Mind if I have another look
at the key we retrieved, Narancia?
Huh?
Here.
Wait! Don't throw it!
You son of a bitch!
Man, you're such a drama queen!
Shouldn't you be glad
that you even can feel pain?
I just had my hand reattached
a half hour ago, and it still hurts!
Jesus...
"My sincerest thanks for
protecting my daughter, Buccellati.
Go to the water fountain with a tortoise
on the sixth platform at Naples Station and use this key.
Then, take my daughter to Venice by train.
P.S. You will no longer receive orders
for this mission once you arrive in Venice."
What's there at
this fountain in the station?
The boss mentioned a way for us to travel
without being discovered by the enemy.
The station is dangerous,
but we'll have to trust him and go there.
D-Do you think the boss is in Venice?
Since he mentioned it in the note...
That isn't important.
We just need to follow orders.
There's an express train bound for Florence
leaving in ten minutes. We'll take that.
Mista, anyone following us?
So far, so good.
The station's gonna be dicey, though.
Anyone paid off by the enemy
will rat us out at the drop of a hat.
The boss's daughter, Trish...
Her life is at risk because of a father she's never met.
I wonder how she feels...
I'm thinkin' the same thing, Fugo...
I can't stop thinking about her like that, either.
Huh?
Th-Th-That's...
Please forgive Fugo!
He didn't mean anything by it!
He wasn't trying to take advantage of the sudden stop
to peek at your tits or reach up your skirt or anything!
It was just an accident!
Hey, cut it out!
I really did just lose my balance,
and you're making it worse!
Please don't tell the boss!
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 14  The Express Train Bound for Florence
Florence bound departs at 16:35 from Platform 6
He's actually here. It's Buccellati.
I can't believe he came to the station
and made this so easy for us!
I'm gonna fucking get him!
Either he's been pushed to the limit and lost his damn mind,
or he's sure he has a way of escaping our pursuit.
Either way, I'm gonna fucking get him!
I'm gonna fucking get him,
and avenge Formaggio and Illuso!
Hey, wiseguy...
Quit the "I'm gonna fucking get him!" shit already.
That phrase doesn't exist in our world.
Those are words uttered by the weak.
By the time phrases like that
enter the minds of people like us...
...we've already killed the target,
and and our work is done!
I've never once uttered those words.
Pesci, neither will you, right?
If you really are one of us.
You get what I'm saying here?
Yeah... I got it, Bro!
What you can say is "I got him!"
Prosciutto...
I'm gonna head toward him via the platform.
Pesci, you board the train
and head towards the front.
Got it!
We'll flank him.
We need the boss's daughter alive, after all.
Buccellati, the train is about to depart.
Is something wrong?
There isn't another water fountain
on this platform, is there?
The key won't fit into this keyhole.
Besides, it doesn't even need a key...
It's been unlocked this entire time.
This is just a stopcock.
Buccellati, what about the lock on the fire hydrant?
The shape of the keyhole is completely different!
If there's a lock or door that takes this key...
...it isn't around here!
Should we pass on this train?
Next one for Rome
departs in fifteen minutes, but...
No!
Some of our enemies were tipped off
and are about to arrive at the station.
We need to leave as soon as possible!
The sixth platform...
The water fountain with the tortoise...
This has to be the place!
Dammit! What's...
The tortoise...
Hey, Pesci, why am I running into you?
I-I was wonderin' the same thing!
Where'd Buccellati go?
Buccellati hopped onto the train
right in front of me.
It makes no sense that you didn't
bump into him in the hallway.
Well? You get what I'm saying?
N-Nobody got past me!
Buccellati, his crew, the new guy,
and the boss's daughter for sure aren't here!
Something's weird here.
Bro, the train's about to leave!
They gotta be hiding somewhere in the station!
They'll watch us trying to find 'em
and get away on another train.
Let's just get some hobo
to search the station or something!
Something was left behind
at that water fountain.
And now it's gone.
He made off with it...
Some sort of dark object!
Hop on, Pesci!
Why?!
I have a hunch...
I don't know how, but I get the feeling
Buccellati and the others are somewhere on this train.
You sure about that?
A feeling?!
I'm sure the boss is helping them out somehow.
I get the feeling that if we don't check this train,
we'll lose them for good!
A feeling?
Shut up and hop on, Pesci!
It takes approximately three and a half hours
to travel from Naples to Florence by train.
One and a half of those hours
is a non-stop ride to Rome.
Aww, we got on...
Quit complaining.
Hey, there's a gap
between the floor and the door.
What's on the other side?
Isn't that the driver's compartment?
There's no way seven people're
all crammed up in there.
You never know.
Use your Beach Boy to attack the inside.
Do it.
Beach Boy!
I knew there wasn't seven guys in there...
There's two!
Got 'em!
Shit. It really is cramped in here.
Looks like it's just the driver in here.
But they're definitely
somewhere else on the train.
Huh? Hey, wait a sec...
There's only one?
Pretty sure I felt
two living things in there...
I could've sworn there was one more...
Hey, Pesci!
We've gotta be real thorough here.
We'll search this train front to back!
We'll drag Buccellati and his crew out
no matter where they're hiding!
But you stay here.
Huh?
If they figure out we're here,
they may try to stop the train.
Gotcha, Bro!
They have the girl with them.
It won't be easy for them to
move around or jump off the train.
That's our big advantage here.
We'll massacre them and take the girl
long before the train reaches Rome!
The key wasn't meant for a keyhole.
It was meant to be placed in this tortoise's shell.
Somehow, that activated its ability...
...and turned the key itself into
an entrance to this place where we can hide.
Th-The tortoise is a Stand user?
O-Ouch!
Wh-Where am I?
I'm under the seat?
Ouch!
B-But seriously, this is sweet!
The tortoise is like
some kind of spaceship!
But this room isn't an illusion
or anything like that...
It's a real, physical place.
Even the sofa and
other furniture are real.
The fridge has even got chilled drinks.
I suppose the boss was considerate
and left them there for us.
Tortoises are quiet and like being in the shade,
and they don't move around very much.
It should help us reach Venice
by train without worry.
Guess it doesn't make sense
for someone to be in the locker...
I really don't got my bro's instincts...
B-Bro!
D-Don't tell me he...
The Grateful Dead!
A-Are you really gonna do it?!
You're gonna doom all the passengers?!
We don't even know
if they're on this train!
I told you we had to be thorough here!
They're definitely here.
What's the big deal, anyway?
Train accidents happen
every year all over the world.
This will be less brutal.
Coco Jamboo
Mr. President
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
It's probably just 'cause
the room's inside of a tortoise,
but it feels kinda muggy in here.
Narancia, you want a drink, too?
It's all cold drinks, but we have cola,
mineral water, sparkling water, regular water,
apple juice, orange juice, pineapple juice...
Hey, you getting all this?
Huh? What was that?!
I asked if you wanted something to drink!
Why don't you get a nap in
while you're at it?
You look beat.
I'll keep an eye on the ceiling.
Oh, okay!
My shoulders feel stiff all of a sudden,
and my back hurts.
There we go...
I'd really like something warm...
Something easy on the stomach.
I told you, all we got is cold drinks!
Do you ever listen
to what people tell you?
I'll just have a banana, then.
Man, gardens like these take my breath away.
They're so calming...
So beautiful...
I'd love nothing more than to reminisce about
laying under the sun in the garden while I was a kid...
Hey, cut that out!
Licking your fingers before you
turn the page is nasty!
Huh? Did I do that?
Me? As if!
Hey, you got something
dangling out of your mouth.
Now that's nasty.
What the hell is that?
Hey!
A tooth?
For some reason,
I can't eat the banana...
It's all dried up...
And really hard...
Oh, come on...
You're just pulling my leg, right?
Man, you really got me...
Thought that was a tooth for a second.
Wasn't very funny though,
and I'm still kinda grossed out...
What's really hanging from your mouth?
Huh? You ask me something again, Mista?
You'll have to speak up, now...
I didn't quite catch that...
Like I said, this banana is falling apart...
I-I can't eat it...
I-It's all dried up...
A-All the fruit...
Wh-What the hell happened to you?!
Didn't you hear me? Okay, then...
There's something wrong with your face!
N-Narancia, you...!
I'll speak louder for you this time!
You paying attention now?!
I can't eat this banana!
Look! It just crumbles...
It's old and rotten...
Buccellati!
I know!
It's a Stand attack!
Th-There must be an enemy on the train!
Huh? What?
What's this white stuff?
It came from my head...
What the hell is this?!
What's wrong?
Did something... happen?
Th-They've all aged!
Mama... Wake up... Wake up...
Mama... Mama...
Wake up...
Wh-Who the hell... i-is this?
What? Impossible... It can't be!
It's me?!
What the fuck is going on?!
A-A Stand that makes people age?
Did they figure out we're inside the tortoise?!
Calm down, Mista.
If they knew we were inside the tortoise,
they would have attacked us directly.
And seeing as that's not the case,
they have no idea.
The enemy probably only knows
we're somewhere on the train.
In order to find Trish,
they're attacking everyone on board indiscriminately!
D-Does that mean everyone on board
is being affected by this?
Most likely.
They're desperate.
I'm sure they'll try anything...
...without even a second thought.
This leaves us two choices.
One: Take Trish and
get off the train, somehow.
Or two: We find the enemy, even though
we don't know their range, and eliminate them.
We're doing the second one, of course.
If we wanna take her and run,
we'd have to stop the train.
It's too risky.
Assassination is one option we know will stop them...
Assassinating them with my Sex Pistols!
You're absolutely right.
But we don't have any time.
We're aging at a rapid rate.
B-Buccellati...
M-My hands...
Th-They're crumbling!
They're falling apart!
You're right, Buccellati.
We really don't have any time!
Wait a minute, Mista...
You can't go... just yet...
What are you saying, Giorno?
I'm warning you... you can't go just yet.
We don't have time to mess around!
Wait.
Hear him out.
What are you trying to say, Giorno?
Why are we all aging at a
different rate than Buccellati?
Mista's and my symptoms are comparatively light...
Trish's even more so!
But why?
We're just aging at different rates is all!
I'm going!
No... If they're attacking
everyone indiscriminately with age...
They could end up killing her as well,
even though she's their target.
There must be a condition
determining the rate at which we're aging.
I have a hypothesis...
I believe the enemy is differentiating between men and women
by the difference in their body temperature.
I once read that women have more fat in their bodies,
making them less susceptible to fluctuations in temperature.
Supposedly women also age better
and live longer than men.
Don't you think it's a bit warm?
The enemy is differentiating the rate at which we're aging
based on slight differences in body temperature.
All that matters is that
the men age faster than the women.
That makes a lot of sense,
but then why are you and I not aging the same?
You callin' me a girl?!
Difference in body temperature...
Come to think of it,
our bodies were slightly cooler...
...since we all drank cold drinks.
Narancia had nothing to drink.
Th-That's it!
Giorno, it's exactly like you said!
We're aging slower because
our bodies are slightly cooler!
We gotta cool everyone down!
Cool 'em using ice!
Wait, Mista!
You'll have to take that ice with you!
I-Is this all we got?
None of this changes the fact that
we need to eliminate the enemy.
Mista, you're going to
take that ice and defeat them...
Before the ice melts
and you lose your Stand power!
Just the driver...
Doesn't look like anyone else is in here...
It's so muggy...
This Stand really is attacking
anyone and everyone.
I wonder if the tortoise is aging, too...
Although I've heard tortoises can
pretty much live forever.
Guess it'll outlive us...
Aww, man...
What's Bro thinking?
This is really dangerous...
What's he gonna do if I get old, too? Jeez...
The air conditioner?
If I cool down the driver's compartment, it should
cool the inside of the tortoise too and slow down their aging!
Got something!
A little fishy took the bait!
Wh-What the hell is this hook-like thing?!
A d-different Stand than the one that's aging us?
There's another one?
Two of them?
There's two bad guys?!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
The Grateful Dead Part 1