Guess I gotta say it...
The name's Formaggio.
How do you like that?
And that?! And that?! And that?!
He's probably planning to
follow me back there...
But...
I just have to get back without being followed!
I'm gonna follow my orders!
Did anyone else just hear a loud bang?
I wonder what it was...
Come back for now, Aerosmith!
That asshole's still around here somewhere,
but I gotta find a way out.
Attacking with my Stand with
all these people around is asking for trouble!
Huh? I stopped bleeding...
Felt like he got me good, too.
Huh?
Where'd this knife come from?
This isn't mine...
Mine's not this big.
Where'd my knife go?
This isn't my shoe, either!
It's way too big!
Where the hell is my shoe?
Something feels off about this seat...
A-And the steering wheel...
I-I can't reach it!
My foot can't reach the pedals...
and the seat is huge!
I can't see the windshield!
What the hell?
This can't be my car!
Where is it?
Where's my car?!
I can't get back without it! Shit!
Is he seriously this stupid?
Get a fucking clue!
You're shrinking!
The effects from cutting your cheek
are finally starting to show!
W-Wait, these are my knife and shoe!
So that means...
Finally up to speed, dipshit?
Too little, too late!
You won't be doing any more driving like that!
S-So this is that stalker guy's Stand ability?
I'm gonna make you cough up
the location of the boss's daughter!
This fight is just getting started.
No turning back now!
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 10  Hitman Team
Hey, how long do I have to wait for my mineral water?
I'm parched.
At this rate, I'm going to die of thirst.
Yeah... I'd like to have lunch
some time this century.
Well, I'm good, but these little rascals gotta eat.
Feed us!
Narancia is pretty late...
This is why I was worried about him going!
Drop it, Fugo. How many times-
I'm not dropping it! After I-
I-I'm sorry...
Anything my Little Feat cuts
will start to shrink.
Takes a little while for the ability
to take effect, though.
Your bandanna and clothes
will keep shrinking with you.
Your knife and shoe stopped shrinking
since they were separated from your body.
So basically, the more you shrink,
the less you'll be able to use!
O-Oh, yeah!
I gotta call Buccellati and the others!
Ouch!
What's wrong with this automatic door?!
Am I still shrinking?
This door...
I'm so light that it won't open!
Got that right, dumbass.
Still...
I gotta hurry to that phone
and call for help!
Got it open, bitch!
There's no use struggling!
Guess you haven't realized it yet,
but your clothes and wallet are shrinking with you!
You need a telephone card or coins
to use the pay phone!
Gotta have money that's the right size!
Narancia's Height: 62.5cm
Maybe this guy's not as stupid as I thought...
This is bad...
I'm fucked if his friends learn about my ability!
Plus, if Buccellati hears about this,
he'll move the boss's daughter somewhere else!
I definitely can't let that happen!
That's enough!
H-He's here!
The fucker's gotta be around here somewhere!
Where are you?
Under the phone?!
Show yourself!
This is perfect.
You over here?
In another two or three minutes,
he'll have shrunken down to the size of a cockroach.
Where the hell are you, motherfucker?!
Narancia's Height: 58.0cm
His Stand's size and strength are gonna
shrink until he's powerless...
...and then I'll get to torture
the shit out of him!
Then I win!
Guess I don't got a choice...
He shouldn't be able to find me
as long as I wait here...
I finally figured it out, you bastard!
You're in my right ass pocket!
Gotcha now!
So you can shrink, huh?
Were you in my pocket this whole time?
Shit. You sure are tiny, though!
Hey!
How did he figure out I was in his pocket?!
Light him up, Aerosmith!
T-Turn back!
Wha-
A-A ballpoint pen?!
Narancia's Height: 53.0cm
Goddammit!
Where did you go?
What the hell did you do?!
You fucking stalker!
Where are you?!
That was close...
If Little Feat shrinks anything other than me,
it takes more time since it uses a lot of energy.
But when it changes something back to normal size,
it happens instantly, like that ballpoint pen.
It created enough momentum
to send me flying all the way over here.
But how did he figure out
I was in his pocket?
Did I move around too much
and tickle his ass?
N-No way!
But I hid right away!
How did it find me?!
There you are!
You're not getting away, you creepy fuck!
It's gunning for me!
Th-This is bad!
Little Feat!
Wh-Where'd that motherfucker go?!
That was way too close for comfort...
If I hadn't been sent flying from the
air pressure in the tire, I'd be dead!
But I'm sure there's no way it's gonna...
Y-You gotta be kidding me! Damn!
His Stand can do more than
just shoot things up!
Somehow it's figuring out
where I am and pursuing me!
And it's not like it can see me moving
or hear me making any noise...
That wouldn't explain how it figured out
I was in his pocket, or where the tire sent me flying!
Found you!
You're down the drain!
I-It can even find me underwater?!
Little Feat!
F-Fuck!
Think, think, think, think! Fucking think!
I can't go out like this!
The Hitman Team is
composed of nine members.
Formaggio is one of them.
2 years ago / Naples
I intend to address the waste issue
at next week's assembly.
That isn't a problem?
Not at all. I simply intend to tell the
Minister of Tourism the right way to move forward.
Business as usual.
I'm worried you're
pushing yourself too hard.
Dear, don't you think you've had
enough to drink tonight?
What the hell, Pesci?
You drinking milk again?
W-Well, my tummy hurts
when I drink espresso...
Pesci, this is why you're
such a complete mammone!
You drinking milk makes the rest of us
look worse by association.
Do you even know why we let you
tag along to these business meetings?
You need to work on your conduct.
O-Okay...
So, Formaggio, have you made any progress?
Pesci, I got a little something for you.
A present.
Guess it went well.
Yeah, this gig's pretty much wrapped up.
We just gotta sit back and watch.
Let's finish up and
go watch soccer or something.
Narancia Ghirga
Aerosmith
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
The food was delicious.
Thank you very much.
We await your return.
All right, time to finish this.
What a wonderful evening.
I'm glad I ordered the white wi-
What's wrong, dear?
Are you in pain?
Hey!
Why the hell are you parked here?!
Outta the way!
W-Wait, what's that coming out
from underneath the car?
I-I-It's blood!
All right, let's get out of here.
What's the matter, Pesci?
Your knees give out?
We're back!
How did it go?
Perfect!
The guy got blown to bits.
The cunt with him died too, though.
I guess it was the perfect gig
for your useless ability!
Whatever.
Do it yourself if you don't like my methods.
Melone, how much was it for this gig?
Twenty million lire.
Fucking chump change!
Calm down, Ghiaccio.
We'll deal with the money later.
More importantly...
Where are Sorbet and Gelato?
They playin' hooky?
Maybe off gettin' frisky somewhere?
They're together, aren't they?
And you call me useless?
No, something's wrong here.
Gelato is one thing,
but Sorbet would never miss a chance to hit it big.
He always shows up to stake his claim.
Once an organization is established
and starts to mature as a group...
...there will always be those
within the group who choose to rebel.
By smuggling cheap drugs from Central Asia
to various countries in Europe and America...
...the organization makes back
tens to hundreds of times what they invested.
For this reason, it's not so strange...
...that some within the organization would
go after the boss's territory, even at the risk of their own lives.
Find them?
No. No sign of them.
Th-They musta got done in since they were
snoopin' around tryin' to figure out who the boss is!
Could be.
Those two are crazy motherfuckers.
Polpo controls all the gambling...
...and those fucks selling drugs
are making a fortune, too!
And all we, the Hitman Team,
get is lousy pay from the boss!
It's not fair!
We're the best motherfuckers
in this goddamn organization!
We deserve better than
this fucking dog shit!
He suffocated?
Yeah... Just Gelato, though.
Sorbet's corpse isn't here.
"Punishment"
A few days later, dozens of packages
with no sender were delivered to the team.
Seriously?
This fucking shit again?
Who's the asshole sending these?!
Frames?
These aren't paintings, though.
Is this like modern art or some shit?
They all got weird shit in them.
Hey!
Th-That's the same color nail polish
Sorbet always wears!
I-I've seen it before...
He and Gelato use the same shade!
Get the frames out and line them up.
There were thirty-six of
these pieces of art in total.
Oh, hell no...
You can't be serious! This is...
I don't wanna see no more!
Shut up!
That's...
They were pieces of Sorbet's body,
chopped up and preserved in formalin.
His face was found
contorted in fear when put together.
He had likely been kept alive and cut into pieces
from his toes up with a very sharp object.
It was a rather brutal form of murder.
The Hitman Team came to a
second realization at this time, as well.
D-Do you think that Sorbet...
...was sliced up right in front of Gelato?
Yeah. He must have been so overcome
with fear and despair...
...that he swallowed his own gag
and choked on it!
This was a silent message from the boss.
Everyone...
Forget about Sorbet and Gelato.
From then on,
they were shunned by the organization.
They never attempted to uncover
the boss's identity ever again.
At least, not until...
...they discovered the boss had a daughter.
Shit!
I'm not gonna die in a place like this!
We're gonna kill the boss and
take control of his drug routes!
I'm gonna climb my way out of this hellhole!
It's filled with holes?
He shot that rat dead? Why?
I-Is it possible...?
It went the other way...
It's still looking for me...
Breathing?! That's it!
Narancia's Stand,
Aerosmith, tracks breath!
Apparently mosquitoes find animals to suck blood from
by sensing the carbon dioxide they exhale.
That's what's happening here!
Now I know how he found me in his pocket!
Come to think of it, when all those people
showed up in the alleyway, he stopped looking for me.
He was worried he was
gonna shoot one of them!
It's been sensing my breathing!
There you are!
He shot again!
Looks like it doesn't know
the difference between me and the rats!
In that case...
Look at these creepy little fuckers...
Th-These numbers...
And this movement pattern...
There must be a ton of rats breathing!
They're going the same speed!
And in the same direction, too!
A threat... It was only a threat
when I didn't know how it worked!
Just how did he find me?
Now that I figured it out,
it's nothing more than a harmless mosquito...
...Narancia!
I win, Narancia!
I'm getting the hell outta here
and waiting for you to shrink into nothing!
H-How?
The same movement pattern...
They're all moving the same way...
...but one of them is breathing
way harder than the rest.
You tired?
Feeling out of breath?
You got something heavy on top of you
making it hard to breathe?
Maybe I should shoot the shit out of
this fatty and see what happens!
Dammit!
Yes! A clean shot!
Th-That was close...
He would have got me if I
hadn't returned to normal size!
If your Stand wasn't
basically harmless by now...
Narancia's Height: 13.2cm
...I would have been killed!
I-I didn't get him!
Did Aerosmith's power
shrink along with me?
My attacks aren't doing shit anymore!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Narancia's Aerosmith