Leone Abbacchio became a police officer
after graduating from high school.
His motivation for joining the force
stemmed purely from his innate sense of justice.
But not long after becoming a police officer
as he had always dreamed...
...Abbacchio became aware of
the incongruous nature of the job.
While the police willingly
risked their lives to protect others...
...these very people who
they were sworn to serve...
...deceived them, committed theft,
injured others in hit-and-runs...
Hold it!
...and threw stones
through police car windows.
Ma'am!
Are you all right?
Hey, you!
You're a cop, aren't you?!
The masses were ungrateful, demanding, insulting,
and disparaged the police, questioning their competency.
Even when the police risked their lives
to arrest the lowest of the low...
Serial Thief Isacco Finally Arrested!
An Entire Group Wiped Out
...the law was lenient towards those with money,
resulting in many being set free.
Isacco Released
on 70 Million Lire
Victims Furious
Quit causing us so much trouble!
Sorry!
Well, what's done is done.
We just gotta find us some suckers to scam.
Eventually, Abbacchio began to
take this incongruity to heart.
Come on, Officer...
Cut us a break.
This young lady's dad is up to his neck in debt,
and she needs the dough.
We ain't bothering no one!
Hey, what's the hold up?
I have another client waiting.
Christ, I know!
Even if I arrested them,
they'd just post bail and be released.
The only difference is whether they pay
the court and their lawyers, or me.
You're a swell guy, mister...
Real swell for a cop...
One night, a report was received
about an armed robbery at a shop.
Abbacchio! You take the back!
Freeze! You're under arrest!
H-Hey, you again...
I really fucked up this time...
You're...
He was shot in the head...
Hey, can't you just tell 'em
you didn't see nothin'?
Come on, lemme go!
I swear I'll be good!
No! You're under arrest!
Come on, think about it...
If you arrest me,
word'll spread that you took a bribe!
That gun's real scary...
Could ya not point it at me?
Abbacchio!
He's got a gun!
Oww! That hurt! Fucking shit!
I'm dead!
I'm dead...!
I'm dead...
I'm so dead...
At that moment,
Abbacchio's future ended.
In addition to the corruption charges,
his actions had inadvertently led to the death of his partner...
...and for that, he would bear a cross
he could never put down again.
It was at this point that his
body and soul were consumed by darkness.
Whether anyone else died,
or he lost all his limbs...
...his heart would forever
remain unswayed.
Abbacchio, isn't it?
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting Gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting Gold
Episodio 06  Moody Blues Strikes Back
You can solve the mystery, right?
I'm counting on you!
Giorno!
What the hell are you doing?!
G-Giorno!
Giorno is in danger!
Giorno Giovanna...
You're one crazy son of a bitch!
All this just to prove yourself...
What the hell is wrong with you?
Y-You...
Th-This Stand...
Defend yourself with Gold Experience!
I-Impossible!
Giorno... Where are you?
Stay off that part of the deck, Buccellati.
Seriously, stay way back.
I still don't see Giorno Giovanna as one of us...
...but he seemed damned sure
you wouldn't abandon him.
He's done some pretty crazy shit.
Giorno Giovanna...
What was your plan
if that stunt had killed you?
I'll say it again, Buccellati:
Stay off that part of the deck.
Th-The fly...
Narancia's shoe...
Giorno's power is still active.
Could this mean he's alive?
They're here, Buccellati!
Narancia and the enemy
are below deck!
Sticky Fingers!
Narancia, Fugo, Mista,
and Giorno aren't here!
They're somewhere below the fly, you think?
It's just like Giorno said...
The enemy isn't just staying hidden and
attacking us from inside a locker or behind an object...
Hey! The fly's coming back around.
Weird...
Where is it going?
Where is the enemy hiding,
and how are they doing it?
As for how the enemy's ability works...
I hate to admit it,
but it looks like Giorno was on to something.
I'll use my Stand to solve the mystery!
But... This spot is dangerous, Buccellati!
Moody Blues!
Will Narancia from
five minutes ago work?
Yeah. Should be fine.
Is the fly all right?
It's headed toward the bow.
Now's our chance. Act fast.
On it.
What's that noise?
Headphones.
Five minutes ago,
Narancia was listening to music on his boombox.
Huh? What's wrong with this thing?
It just died on me!
Why'd the music stop?
Not here.
I just bought it!
Narancia was attacked a bit after this.
Dammit!
He's got balls to sell me this piece of shit!
I'll fast forward.
That geezer from the electronics store
is gonna pay for this!
His ten billion belongs to us now!
With that kind of money,
the position of capo will be ours for the taking!
A-Awesome!
Where is it?
I can hear myself.
Where in Capri did you
hide all that treasure, Buccellati?
Narancia was attacked
right after this conversation!
I can't say just yet.
Hopefully we'll get a good view
of how he was attacked, Abbacchio.
My Stand's replay captures events perfectly.
We'll know everything from
how much Narancia was sweating, down to his pulse.
It will follow him wherever he went!
It's about to start...
Let's get behind him.
Here comes the attack.
L-Look! It's just like Giorno's wound!
There it is!
H-He's...
He's deflating like a punctured balloon!
Mario Zucchero
Soft Machine
Power: A
Speed: C
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
He's deflating from
the air leaking out of his wound.
At least we have
the enemy's ability figured out.
He's being sucked in!
Pause it, Abbacchio!
So that's it.
He's inside the pipe.
Here's the answer to our mystery.
His nails, flesh, and bones
feel like a floppy condom.
His shoe and belt buckle, too.
At least he still has a pulse.
Just like Giorno said, he's alive.
I finally get it...
The enemy used his ability on himself,
allowing him to hide somewhere in the pipes or floor...
...as well as drag Mista,
Fugo, and Giorno along for the ride.
That explains why Giorno's fly
can detect the general area they're in...
...but can't pinpoint their exact location.
Glad we got his ability nailed down.
Now we just gotta make pursuit...
...find and save Narancia and the others...
...then beat this asshole up.
I'm gonna resume Moody Blues' replay!
Pursuit?
Wait a second, Abbacchio!
You can't fight back or defend yourself
while replaying something!
Entering the pipe is too risky!
I know right where Moody Blues is going.
When this asshole gets close,
unzip the floor and get him.
We can't beat him
unless we pursue, Buccellati!
It went left.
That's where he got Mista.
Moody Blues just went
beneath the life preserver.
It's headed toward the cabin
where Fugo and Giorno were taken.
So the enemy is moving around
with Narancia and the others?
It's starting to slow down...
That's where the asshole was hiding earlier.
Inside that bollard!
The enemy is right there below deck!
He's coming after us!
I'm not sure if he realized
we figured out his ability, but...
This one's got balls!
The pipe!
Unzip it and pull them out!
Sticky Fingers!
Th-They're not here!
Where's the enemy, Abbacchio?
Where's your Moody Blues?
Right there...
It's my Stand.
I can tell where it is...
It's right around there...
Right around where?
It's right where you just unzipped!
I know my Moody Blues is there!
Where are they?
Impossible... I know for sure it's there.
Is there still some mystery
we haven't solved?
This is bad!
End the replay
and recall your Stand!
I already did!
Something's wrong...
What is this wall?
Where the hell is this?
Did you hear that, Buccellati?
That's the sound of a pipe wall.
We can't see it,
but Moody Blues is definitely right below us...
Trapped inside the pipe...
What are you doing?
The enemy is right here!
The pipe is wide open,
but somehow it's trapped inside...
It's getting closer...
Does that mean it's right here?
We need to run!
Run?
That smartass, Giorno Giovanna,
asked me to solve this mystery.
He's a snot-nosed brat...
...but I'm going to solve this!
Abbacchio...
It's coming!
There's one more mystery
surrounding this enemy.
It's starting to come together.
I'll solve it and kill this asshole!
That sense of unease
I felt when I saw the mast...
Earlier today...
It's right there!
Recall your Stand!
I just solved the second mystery!
Abbacchio...
Kill him... Buccellati!
The mystery behind it...
The place where he's hiding...
It's dragging you in!
Grab my hand!
Dammit!
H-He's gone...
Where did he go?
What?
You son of a bitch...
Where did you take Abbacchio?
He's not in the cabin
or the drainage pipe...
Where are you hiding
Abbacchio and the others?
So seein' as there's seagulls flyin' around...
...we gotta be gettin' close to shore.
I finally got you all to myself, Buccellati.
You son of a-
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I'm the one doin' the talkin' here.
Keep that fuckin' yap shut
'til I order you to answer me!
Good.
I could eliminate you whenever I like,
plus I'm keepin' your buddies alive in limbo.
Can I get a thank you?
I coulda killed 'em and threw 'em overboard...
Chopped up nice and fine
for the fishies to gobble up.
If you work with me,
maybe I'll put 'em right again.
All you gotta do is tell me
where Polpo's got his hidden fortune!
Are you from Passione?
You really...
...don't know nothin'.
I'll fuckin' kill you, motherfucker!
Listen here!
All you can say is where the money's at!
Just try bullshittin' me
with your asshole of a mouth!
I'll kill one of your buddies for every word!
Say, "What?" and I'll kill 'em!
Say nothin' and I'll kill 'em!
Lie to me and I find out,
and I'll kill 'em again!
Got it?
Watch what you say real close-like.
So lemme ask again...
Where's the money?
Black-tailed gulls.
Huh, where?
Those aren't seagulls.
They're black-tailed gulls.
"How can you tell the difference?", you ask?
Black-tailed gulls sound like meowing cats.
You called them seagulls,
but they're actually black-tailed gulls.
I'm killin' one!
Just try it!
See if you don't go down with the boat!
Wh-What the fuck did you do?!
I didn't punch the deck
to figure out where Abbacchio went.
I was putting a hole
in the bottom of the boat.
A-A hole?
Abbacchio solved the mystery
of where you're hiding.
Then he went out of his way to prove it.
Now I know right where you are
and how to expose you.
It was Abbacchio's blood.
He intentionally cut his hands open
and left a trail of blood.
A trail of blood which didn't go below deck!
The trail ends right here on the main deck!
So what did that tell me about
where you dragged him off to?
I rented the yacht on the far left.
Abbacchio realized it
when he looked up at the sky.
I know right where you are,
so if you don't want to drown...
...you better show yourself.
There were two boats!
Motherfucker...
You hid by thinly covering
this yacht with another one.
And you attacked us by traveling
through the thin gap between them.
No wonder we couldn't figure it out.
I'm actually kind of impressed.
Stay back, Buccellati!
I'll kill your buddies!
You should know better than anyone that no self-respecting gangster would flinch at a weak threat like that.
Give up and I'll let you go.
But the instant you stab Abbacchio...
...you're finished.
It's just like Giorno said.
The fact that you had to attack
while hidden is your weakness.
You're way too slow.
Abbacchio!
Good work...
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Abbacchio...
The end result isn't what matters.
It's how you reach it.
Join my team.
Don't die chained to the past.
Enter the Sex Pistols Part 1