yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 02  Buccellati is Coming
Giorno Giovanna.
His father's name is Dio Brando.
Dio only ever saw women as tools
to be used or food to be consumed...
...so no one is sure how Giorno's mother
managed to give birth to him without being killed.
Giorno's mother was a beautiful woman,
but far from a model parent.
She and Giorno lived in Japan
after he was born.
Yet more often than not, she was away from him
until early morning, leaving young Giorno alone at home.
You sure it's okay
to leave your kid home alone?
Isn't he only two or something?
Oh, it's nothing to worry about.
I'm not about to sacrifice my freedom
just because I had a kid.
Shiobana
He often awoke in the dead of night
while his mother was gone.
The experience proved horribly traumatic
for a child no older than one or two.
Seeing no point in crying,
Giorno sat alone, trembling in bed.
Shortly after Giorno turned four,
his mother was wed.
Because she married an Italian,
she and Giorno became Italian citizens.
Umm, excuse me...
What are you doing over here?
Come on, Haruno...
Come take some photos
with your stepdad.
Your mother is waiting.
But whenever Giorno's mother was away,
his stepdad would inevitably...
You're always trying to read my expressions...
Are you trying to piss me off?!
But the opposite was true.
What's your problem?
Oh, the bread.
Here.
Christ, what a gloomy kid.
In actuality, the person who got him in the habit
of reading people's expressions...
...was his stepdad.
This made Giorno a prime target for
the local children to take their anger out on.
Hey, what's wrong with you, Giorno?
Why'd you trip over nothing?
Hey, kids, hurry up on home.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Go back where you came from,
you stupid Jap.
He never fights back, does he?
He creeps me out.
He began to believe that
he was the lowest of the low...
...and that it was only a matter of time before he would grow up
to be like the rest of the twisted people who lived in this city.
But a certain incident spared
Giorno from succumbing to this fate.
Shit, where did he go?
Don't let him get away!
He couldn't have gone far with those wounds!
Son of a...
You don't think he's hiding in someone's house, do you?
Keep your eyes on the ground!
His blood will lead us right to him!
You go on ahead. We'll go this way.
Hey, kid...
You seen an injured guy around here?
He's tall and has black hair.
He went that way.
Heh, over there?
He's goin' nowhere fast
with those wounds!
We got him for sure!
He felt no fear.
He only felt compassion for the seemingly lonely,
isolated man lying there on the ground.
Hey!
Coming!
Fortunately, the man's body was obscured by
the suddenly taller surrounding grass.
This was due to the power of
Giorno's Gold Experience.
Though, because he was not yet aware he possessed this ability,
he had done it subconsciously.
About two months later...
I'll never forget what you did for me.
Not long after...
...Giorno's stepdad stopped hitting him.
Shit!
What's Giorno to him?
Come sit over here, Giorno!
His bullies immediately changed their tone.
Come on, don't be shy!
It's not the best seat, but...
The man was a gangster.
Here, enjoy!
This is... too much...
This must be a mistake...
The scoop of chocolate is on me!
Thank you...
Don't sweat it!
Your friend has always taken good care of me.
The man was content
to quietly look out for him.
Despite Giorno's habit of reading people's expressions,
the man treated him with respect like any other person.
Giorno learned how to trust others, a trait his parents should have instilled in him, from silent interactions with a stranger.
What was that?
A gunshot?
Talk about unlucky...
Let's stay out of it...
U-Umm...
What is it?
The man took on a somewhat cruel attitude towards Giorno,
determined not to drag him into the world of gangsters.
Hey, wait up!
Stop!
You're the guy who killed my dad, right?
What the hell, brat?!
Dammit!
Your father was scum.
He broke the rules
by selling drugs on my turf.
Even had the nerve to sell them
to women and children.
That's why I killed him.
How? Why?!
Why is the gun jammed?
You're...
You're scum, too!
Giorno didn't think the man was scum at all.
Bizarrely, a gangster who regularly broke the law and
committed crimes, was responsible for molding Giorno's heart.
In a city run by corrupt politicians and
a police force who ignored the cries of the weak...
...Giorno Giovanna found a reason to live.
Rather than looking up to a Serie A Star football player,
he strove to be a Gang-Star!
This taste... is the taste of a liar!
My name is Bruno Buccellati.
Now answer me.
This interrogation has already
turned into a torture session.
Does your head feel like
it's about to wobble off?
Regardless, I doubt you have a clue what I've done to you.
My body has a zipper?!
Giorno Giovanna...
If I wanted, I could roll your head around like a ball
while questioning you about who had it out for "Leaky-eye" Luca.
I don't think I can take
another one of his attacks...
He'll rip me to shreds!
I realized I had this ability a few months ago...
...but I've never used Gold Experience
to attack another person...
When Gold Experience strikes
an inanimate object, it can imbue it with life.
It can change any object
into any living creature.
But...
...I don't know what will happen
if it attacks a human being!
Answer me, Giorno Giovanna!
I have no choice!
Muda!
TN: Muda is a taunt/battle cry used to express futility.
What?!
Y-You're...
...a Stand user!
So you could see my ability!
A what user?
So you're the one who
had it out for Luca!
Didn't Gold Experience land a direct hit?
I expected to break a bone or two
at the very least...
Damn you...
Wh-What?
What did you do to me?!
What the...?
I was just trying to stand up...
I'm overflowing with energy!
I can feel it welling up inside of me!
It's as if my body's been filled with
life-giving gasoline!
What's this?
It's moving so slowly!
Am I feeling this way because
you used your ability on me?
If so, you're a fool to fight with
a Stand that powers up your enemy!
Take this, Giorno Giovanna!
What? I can see myself...
What am I doing back there?
The handle isn't bent!
Do I somehow have this all wrong?
I thought I was moving with incredible energy...
...but since my body is over there...
...did my consciousness
somehow escape and come over here?
Dammit! I have to dodge it!
I-It's so painful!
Sharp pain is spreading through my face!
Giorno didn't slow down...
My consciousness just went berserk!
Muda!
It seems when Gold Experience imbues a human being with life,
they go berserk... Or rather, their consciousness does.
I'm not sure why I have this ability...
...but I intend to make full use of it.
Bruno Buccellati
H-Hey!
What are you two doing?
Don't make me call the police!
I apologize for the disturbance.
Rest assured,
we won't let any civilians become involved.
So this is Giorno Giovanna's Stand?
No... It doesn't seem like he even
understands the concept of Stands...
But this ability...
It appears that both of our abilities
only extend a few meters.
And here I thought you were some random
fifteen-year-old punk without any affiliations.
Giorno Giovanna!
You're the one who had it out
for "Leaky-eye" Luca, aren't you?
The boss is eager to discover your motive!
Would you believe me if I said
it was an accident?
I assume you would just have me eliminated.
That's what you came here
prepared to do, isn't it?
When deciding to eliminate someone...
...you accept the risk that you yourself may be
the one eliminated, correct?
He's going to kill me... He's serious!
This punk really wants to finish me off!
The conviction in the way he holds himself
tells me he'll make good on those words!
Sticky Fingers!
So that's his Stand?
I'm sure of it, now.
My Sticky Fingers is much stronger.
I wasn't instructed to
bring the perpetrator back alive.
Though I'd like to finish this here...
...I've had enough of your strange,
dangerous ability...
...so I'll be taking my leave.
Once I've put some distance between us...
...I'll have you eliminated.
He can even pass through solid walls
by putting a zipper on them?!
This is bad!
I shouldn't have let him
leave the cable car!
If I lose track of him now,
having Gold Experience won't matter!
If he pursues me with that ability,
my life will be in a state of constant danger!
He'll kill me!
I can't let him escape!
If he tells his friends about me,
this will get out of control!
I have to stop him here and now!
For the sake of my future!
O-Oww!
Watch where you're going, dammit!
He disappeared!
Where could he have gone in an instant?
No!
Can he go inside people with his zipper?
What else could explain it?
That must be how he put that eyeball
and those fingers inside me!
Buccellati hid himself inside
one of these people like a costume...
...and plans on using them
to get back inside the city!
Better grab my broom.
They're all heading in different directions!
I don't see any zippers...
Which one is it?
Who is he hiding in?
What's with you, you stupid fly?!
A tooth?
I imbued the tooth I knocked out of your mouth
with life and had it be reborn as a fly.
I knew the fly would return to you
and give away your location...
...but this is no good.
Earlier I promised we
wouldn't involve any civilians...
...but we did. I was wrong.
At the very least,
he was only hit by the power of his own punch...
...so I suppose it could have been worse.
Hang in there.
Giorno Giovanna, I can see your ability
is not one to be trifled with.
You leave me no choice...
It will be dangerous,
but I have to eliminate you right here, right now.
I can't let you escape.
The situation is too desperate.
"Let me escape"?
Don't concern yourself.
The only thing you should be worrying about...
...is what you'll do when I
zip you apart across the ground.
This battle will be won by
whoever lands the first blow.
What's wrong?
Come at me, Giorno Giovanna!
Muda!
Now your consciousness will go berserk.
"My blow landed first, so how...?!"
I can't blame you for thinking that.
This isn't my arm.
My Sticky Fingers' ability allows me to
connect two objects together with a zipper.
This arm belongs to that kid.
I switched his out for mine.
It's only natural that I would take precautions
to minimize the risk of being hit by your ability.
That's why your Gold Experience didn't work.
What are you trying to do, Giorno Giovanna?
It's time I eliminated you!
Unbelievable... He ripped his own arm off
just to extend his range and attack a moment faster!
Gold Experience!
I-It's happening again!
My consciousness is going berserk!
H-He's going to kill me!
The destructive power of Giorno Giovanna's
Stand ability isn't very strong...
...but in this case,
that makes it even worse!
If I have to experience that agonizing pain
not just once, but multiple times...
...I'll probably die of shock from the pain!
Don't!
He went out of range?
What are you doing, Giorno Giovanna?
Why did you stop attacking me?
Why didn't you finish me off?!
Because you're a good person.
You're a gangster,
but also a good person.
You hesitated for a moment before attacking me,
so I decided not to attack you, either.
When you saw the state of that boy's arm you took,
you were momentarily shocked and didn't attack me.
You were shocked that he
had been shooting up drugs.
How old is he?
Thirteen...
If you were the kind of gangster
not to be fazed by something like that...
...I'd likely be rolling on the ground
in pieces right now.
But you're different.
That's why I stopped.
There are people in this city who
have no qualms selling drugs to children.
They're unforgivable.
I can tell that's what you feel.
But the person selling the drugs is your boss.
It makes you feel conflicted.
That's why your heart ached
when you saw his arm.
So what's your point?
This has nothing to do with me eliminating you.
I was ordered to eliminate
the person who had it out for Luca!
You not attacking me doesn't change
the fact that I'm going to kill you!
No...
You won't try to kill me.
What?
You won't kill me.
I'm sure of it.
Why is that?
Because we're going to be
on the same side.
I plan on defeating your boss
and taking over this city.
What?!
In order to rid this city of gangs who sell drugs to children,
I need to become a gangster myself.
Are you telling me...
...you're going to join our organization?!
Are you serious?
Do you have any idea what you're getting into?
What a nice view...
Yeah!
If I'm going to take over this city...
...I'll have to join the organization that rules it
and work my way up.
Buccellati...
I'm going to become a Gang-Star!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Meet the Gangster Behind Bars