O-Oww!
My fucking head...
Hey, Fugo...
Could you take a look at my head for me?
Ah, you got a bump all right.
Looks swollen.
Oww! That hurts!
Knock it off!
Quit touching it!
Damn you, motherfucker!
You're gonna pay for this, asshole!
You gave me a friggin' bump!
Here comes the pain!
Take this! And that!
Seriously!
Who do you think you are?!
Fucking loser!
Oh, he dropped something.
Let's see...
Mario Zucchero.
From Rome.
So he's a thug from Rome...
That a piece of garbage stuck to your face?
Or is it just seaweed?
Sure looks like seaweed,
but it could be plastic, too.
Would break my heart if it was garbage.
That'd mean this beautiful ocean's polluted.
Mind if I take a closer look?
Hey, buddy...
I asked if it was okay to take a closer look.
Least you could do is
answer a simple question, asshole!
Capri...
When the ancient Greeks colonized
various lands throughout the Mediterranean Sea...
...they sought out the most
beautiful places in the world.
Among those colonized lands was Capri.
The blue sea, the sparkling sky...
In stark contrast to the beautiful scenery, the shoreline is
made up of sheer white cliffs, giving it a fortress-like appearance.
While the Roman Empire reigned, an emperor vacationed there,
only returning to Rome after ten years.
Bruno Buccellati and his team are about to reach the island
in order to lay claim to Polpo's hidden fortune of ten billion lire.
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 07  Enter the Sex Pistols Part 1
Buccellati, we should set course for land soon.
I've been on the lookout for some time,
and there doesn't seem to be any boats following us.
No one should be aware that
this boat is headed to Capri.
Yeah, there aren't any boats around, but...
I'm worried about how he
learned of Polpo's hidden fortune.
I just can't accept that he chose
to follow us on his own.
I noticed you eyeing these earlier,
but they're not mine.
They were inside the boat.
Which one do you want?
The glasses or the fishing line?
We need answers.
We're gonna be in deep shit
if you don't start talking.
You working with someone, Mr. Zucchero?
Probably a Stand user too, huh?
That's why I'm using these.
You sure you don't got a preference?
If you're not gonna choose...
...I'll just have to use both!
Well? Feel like talking now?
Ma-ri-o Zuc-che-ro.
Heaven, Hell, or the Ninth Circle of Hell?
Heaven, Hell, or...
The Ninth Circle of Hell?
His name reading says he's going
straight to the Ninth Circle of Hell!
If you're not gonna tell us
your partner's name or what their Stand does...
...then I'd start worrying about
that other eye of yours, Mr. Zucchero!
Quit fucking around!
Jesus. Get over here and look at this.
He was using the boat radio.
I presume you found something
with Moody Blues' replay?
Let's have a look.
The boat was flat at the time, but now that it's back to normal,
we should be able to see this in three dimensions.
Giorno!
You're still not allowed to see my Stand.
Turn around.
I'll do you a favor and let you listen in.
While I was watching the replay,
he started using the radio in the cabin below us.
He contacted someone.
I already took four of 'em as hostages.
Only Buccellati and another guy are left.
I'll be done here in no time.
They were goin'...
...to Capri!
Didn't hear 'em say where the money's at, though.
Hey, what are we gonna do?
He told someone where we're headed!
Once I eliminate his friends,
I'm gonna make Buccellati cough up the location. Over.
Was their yacht the Lagoon?
Whereabouts are you?
About two hours from Capri.
Buccellati's afraid of bein' tailed,
so he's takin' the long way.
Got it.
I'll take a speedboat and wait for you at Capri.
Dock at Marina Grande.
Over and out.
The conversation ends there.
The radio cut out.
How could this happen?
This is awful! He could go from Naples
to Capri in thirty minutes with a speedboat!
He's already on the island for sure!
Who was that?
Who was he talking to?
I won't stop 'til this guy
coughs up his buddy's name!
No, he's a hardcore gangster.
Odds are it will take too long
to get any good info out of him.
I doubt we would get anywhere today.
Besides, he may not even know
what his partner's Stand is like.
There's a good chance he chose to
keep it a secret even from him.
So what can we do?
We'll never make it to port
without getting spotted!
If he figures out we're the ones
driving the boat and not Zucchero...
Not to mention if it doesn't arrive
at Marina Grande in about an hour...
...the man on the radio will
realize something happened to Zucchero!
Will we still be able to get
the money if that happens?
Worse yet...
...we may not even make it back
to Naples alive!
What's the plan, Buccellati?
We can't wait on this.
Our best bet is to catch him off guard.
We have to beat him there somehow...
Before the boat reaches port...
...one of us needs to head
to the island and eliminate him.
You hearing yourself right now?
You sure you're not retarded?
Get to the island before the boat?
You planning to swim there or something?
Yes.
Huh?
I can imbue this lifesaver
with the life of a fish.
If it pulls me along,
I'll reach the island faster than the yacht.
And naturally, since it's my Stand,
I'll be the one going.
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream...
I want to obtain that ten billion lire.
We need that money to ensure
Buccellati becomes a capo...
...so that we can move up in the ranks.
Giorno...
You wanna go? Good.
Not a bad idea, kid.
Too bad you don't have a clue
who this guy is or what he looks like.
Capri is flooded with tourists.
How the hell do you think you'll find him?
I gotta side with Giorno on this one.
Even though I have no idea who this guy is...
If he's waiting for Zucchero
to get there in this boat...
...I think we have
a good shot at striking first...
...before he can strike at us.
So how many people can
that fish of yours pull, Giorno?
My Stand, Sex Pistols,
specializes in assassinations.
It's perfect for the job.
Let's go get him!
Guido Mista
Sex Pistols
Power: E
Speed: C
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: B
I didn't expect it would take this long
to reach the island from the yacht.
We have twenty minutes before Zucchero
said he would meet with the man on Capri.
We can't take much longer than that.
Giorno, how's the marina look?
Not good.
Like Abbacchio said, it's full of tourists.
Several seem to be waiting for someone.
They're probably just waiting
for sightseeing vessels, but...
Mista, you have a plan for finding the mystery man
in the next twenty minutes, right?
What are you doing?
We're way overdue for lunch.
I'd prefer to eat at one of the restaurants over there,
but having lunch on the marina is probably a bad idea.
I don't know that guy's face,
but he probably knows mine since I'm on Buccellati's team.
Yours too.
I have no idea what you're talking about...
...but listen, Mista.
I know I said we had twenty minutes,
but it could be closer to ten if he's the nervous type.
Possibly not even five.
He may fear something
happened to Zucchero...
...and become suspicious if
the Lagoon doesn't arrive at port on time.
We'll never find him if that happens.
We need to make our move right-
Like I said, it's time for lunch!
You eat lunch when it's lunchtime!
Even boutiques and bookstores honor lunchtime.
Nobody works unless
they've had their lunch.
I mean, not saying I work that way...
...but unfortunately these little rascals
like to keep the custom.
Lunchtime!
I'm starvin'  here!
Here you go, fellas!
Lunch is served!
Tuscan salami is delicious!
Yummy!
So good!
Gimme that!
Not this again, Number 3!
Stop making Number 5 cry!
And quit fighting.
There's enough for all of you.
They all think they do the most work,
so naturally they also think they deserve more than the others.
I try really hard not to play favorites.
Number 5!
For crying out loud, quit crying!
What are they?
How many of those things do you have?
Hey, they aren't "things"!
They get testy if
you treat 'em like pets.
There's six in total.
No Number 4 since it's bad luck.
Each of them clings to a chambered bullet.
Clings to it?
My buddy over here is rushing us...
You guys mind holding off on the nap
'til after we're done working?
Fat chance!
Hey, Number 3!
I told you to stop hitting the others!
Mista!
I'll get 'em ready to go.
Giorno...
Go grab the radio out of
the plastic bag we brought.
We get to pig out once the gig's out!
Up and at 'em, fellas!
Here's the plan: I'm gonna sneak up to
the watchhouse and stick to the shadows.
Is there anyone waiting for
a yacht called the Lagoon?
We received a transmission from
a Mr. Zucchero on the Lagoon!
Please come to the boat watchhouse!
Is there anyone waiting for
a yacht called the Lagoon?
We received a transmission from
a Mr. Zucchero on the Lagoon!
He might decide to play it safe
and not answer the radio call...
Please come to the boat watchhouse!
Or maybe he'll get excited and expose himself,
thinking he found the hiding place of the ten billion lire.
It's a gamble, but whoever comes to the boat watchhouse
to answer the radio call is our guy.
Giorno, if anyone comes
close to the watchhouse, give me the signal.
I'll shoot whoever takes the call!
But since Buccellati told me not to kill him,
I'll avoid his vitals.
Or try to, at least.
Nobody's moved yet...
No one's headed toward the watchhouse...
Is no one going to answer?
Is nobody waiting for the Lagoon?
There's a transmission
from Mr. Zucchero!
No, nobody is making a move!
But he must be somewhere on the island!
Is he just too cautious to answer the call?
Did something happen, Zucchero?
Calling me out like that...
Is there a problem? Over.
What's going on?
No one approached the watchhouse!
He's there! How?
This is bad!
Does the watchhouse have a back entrance?
He's already inside!
It's too dark to see his face...
Mista hasn't realized he's in there!
At this rate, he'll realize it's a setup
and make a run for it!
I have to tell Mista!
What?
The guy is coming to answer the call?
Who is it?
Which one of them is coming?
N-No!
He's not headed there!
He's already inside!
Don't expose yourself!
He's by the window!
Isn't that guy...
...part of Buccellati's team?!
Didn't Zucchero take care of him on the yacht?
Mista! Behind you!
He's on the radio! Mista!
Damn!
He can't hear me!
This is better than him not noticing!
He's already there!
Mista! He's already on the radio!
Come on! Pass, pass, pass!
Go, Sex Pistols!
Let's do this!
Shoot!
Yay!
Nailed it!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
D-Did he get him?
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Wh-What was that noise?
Gunshots.
Did it bother you?
I doubt it was as loud
as it is in the movies.
Anyway, if it did bother you...
I'm kinda busy right now.
I'll hear your complaints later.
Guess Giorno just can't wait.
So there was a rear entrance...
He must have entered through this door
and got on the radio.
Either he was extra cautious, or he entered the back door
out of habit since he knew he probably wouldn't be spotted.
Still...
Good job, Pistols!
Yay!
Leg!
Leg! Hey, hey!
Got him right in the leg!
We shot through his right leg!
Yeah, you sure did!
He won't get away now!
There's a bunch of people out here...
And this side is basically a cliff...
No way he climbed that.
He must be crawling around somewhere.
If he was hiding anywhere...
...it would probably be in that truck.
If he's a Stand user, he probably has
a close-range type that's extremely powerful.
If it could be controlled remotely,
he would have attacked me by now.
Since that's the case,
the guy who I shot in the leg...
...is probably hiding behind the truck
so he can lure me in as close as possible to attack.
Well, not like he'll get me
even if I do get closer to him.
He's probably just ahead.
But since I have no idea what his Stand is,
getting close to him is too risky.
I should wait for Giorno and-
Well, guess that option's out!
He's in the driver's seat!
He must've hotwired the engine!
Shit's gonna get ugly
if I let this truck get away!
Damn, this is bad!
I still don't know what he looks like!
I doubt Giorno does, either!
Dunno what kind of Stand he has,
but I don't got a choice!
This is for the ten billion and Buccellati!
Eat lead!
Mista...
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Enter the Sex Pistols Part 2