Because we're going to be
on the same side.
I plan on defeating your boss
and taking over this city.
What?!
In order to rid this city of gangs who sell drugs to children,
I need to become a gangster myself.
Are you telling me...
...you're going to join our organization?!
Are you serious?
Do you have any idea what you're getting into?
What a nice view...
Yeah!
If I'm going to take over this city...
...I'll have to join the organization that rules it
and work my way up.
Buccellati...
I'm going to become a Gang-Star!
Pass! Pass!
Thanks!
Fine.
I'll report back that I couldn't
locate Luca's assailant...
...then introduce you as a
prospective member of the organization.
However, if at any point it becomes known
that you're planning to overthrow the boss...
...I won't help you.
Known traitors are beyond help.
You alone will have to atone
for your transgression.
That aside, I'm willing to gamble
on your golden dream...
...and the noble resolve you showed me
by ripping your own arm off, Giorno Giovanna.
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting Gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting Gold
Episodio 03  Meet the Gangster Behind Bars
Our organization oversees every industry in Naples.
Passione... That's what we call ourselves.
The name Passione comes from
the word "passion", not the boss's name.
No one knows the boss's name,
or even what he looks like.
We receive orders from
a number of his capos.
Giorno, the capo who will decide whether you
join the organization or not is a man named Polpo.
He's in this building.
But this is a...
It's a prison.
Correct. Polpo was convicted of an undisclosed crime
and won't be released for fifteen years.
However, he still gives out orders from within these walls,
exercising his power within the organization.
He could leave this place any time,
but he chooses to stay.
He feels no need to leave.
Why?
You'll see for yourself.
Giorno Giovanna,
you'll have to pass an interview with him.
Think of it like any other job interview.
What the interview will entail
entirely depends on his mood.
But whatever you do,
do not let him discover your true intentions.
Understood.
Oh, yeah. Your Stand ability...
That's what you called it, right?
I was going to ask how you got your ability,
but instead could you tell me if there are others like you?
That, too, is something
you'll see for yourself.
If you pass, that is.
Before entering, please place your watch,
valuables, and the contents of your pockets in the tray...
...then proceed to the
next room for a pat down.
Stand here, hands raised above your head.
Once past the gate,
please continue straight down the hall.
Polpo is in cell N-28.
The room is divided by a pane of tempered glass,
but you may speak with him.
Touching the glass or exchanging items with him
are both strictly forbidden, however.
You have fifteen minutes.
Once you pass through,
the gate will close.
Yell for us if anything happens.
I'm going to meet him
directly in his cell?
Not in a visiting room?
Do you not know who he is?
That left arm of yours...
Is it injured?
That's not a bed...
I see the fingers on your right hand are slightly reddened,
as if you've been holding something.
A bag, judging from the lines.
That tells me you've only been using your
right hand to hold the bag until now.
Why is that?
Well, uh... You're correct.
I was holding a bag in my right hand since,
as you pointed out, I injured my left arm.
I envy your freedom to be
so reckless with your body.
Care for some wine?
I have some exquisite Chianti Classico.
It pairs perfectly with Scamorza cheese
and caviar spread over crackers.
I was told we weren't
allowed to exchange items.
They're all talk.
The things people say
and the things people do...
...are at constant odds.
It's both the best and
worst aspect of humanity.
The only downside to
remaining in this cell is, well...
Polpo...
...the fact that I can no longer admire
the great work of Michelangelo in the Sistine Chapel.
It's not that he feels no need to leave prison...
It's that nothing would change
whether he left or not.
With a body like that,
he may even be safer in a cell.
The more important question is
how he even managed to get through the door...
Buccellati spoke with me about you.
So you'd like to join our organization, huh?
Hmm... Giorno Giovanna, was it?
Anyway, why don't we get
this interview underway?
What was that?
Were my eyes deceiving me?
For a second, it looked like Polpo took
a bite out of his fingers with the cracker...
No... Perhaps Polpo is just
a Stand user like Buccellati.
Either way, I have to make sure
he doesn't find out that I'm one, too.
What do you believe is the most important quality
that a potential candidate could possess, Giorno Giovanna?
Perhaps how capable they are?
Oh? So just how capable are you?
During my pat down,
I borrowed these from that woman.
I thought they may prove
useful for your test.
I'll return them to her
when I leave, of course.
What else can you do?
Besides that, the only other unique skill I have
is being able to stuff my ear inside my ear canal.
Now that's an amusing skill!
But, you see...
The most important quality one can possess
is something else entirely.
It's trustworthiness,
Giorno Giovanna, my friend.
The most important quality a candidate
can possess is trustworthiness.
Being clever or talented are worth as much as
the piece of cracker stuck between my teeth in comparison.
This test will evaluate your trustworthiness...
...through the flame of this lighter!
Take it with you and ensure
the flame is never extinguished.
Careful!
Take extra precautions to ensure
the flame isn't disturbed.
A 17th-century theologian
by the name of Fuller once said...
"He's my friend that speaks
well of me behind my back."
In order to join our organization, you'll have to demonstrate
your trustworthiness even when you aren't being watched.
Your task is to keep this lighter for twenty-four hours
without letting the flame go out.
Manage that, and you may enter our ranks.
Simple, isn't it?
The lighter has plenty of fluid in it.
All you have to do is sit quietly in your room
and watch over the flame until 3:00 PM tomorrow.
If you're a diligent man and act carefully,
the flame should never go out.
Ergo, we'll be able to trust you.
However, if you're a man
who would take me lightly...
...and end up falling asleep, sneezing, knocking over the lighter,
or letting a gust of wind blow out the flame...
...that would mean you're untrustworthy,
and therefore unworthy to join our organization.
Now, take the lighter.
This is your entrance exam.
You have twenty-four hours.
I look forward to seeing you again
at 3:00 PM tomorrow.
Twenty-four hours...
All visitors are to be subjected to another pat down
upon passing through the gate.
Once you've received permission
to leave the facility...
...continue to the next room
to reclaim your belongings.
Wait!
Polpo didn't explain anything to you?
Huh?
Get in position
for your pat down!
You were warned that accepting
anything from him was strictly forbidden!
This is bad! I had the impression that Polpo was
bribing these people to allow me to leave with the lighter!
Visitor, raise your hands
and proceed forward!
So Polpo's test has already begun...
But I...
...can't fail here!
I need to pass this test
and become a member of Passione!
Hirose Koichi
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Echoes Act 3
Step forward, visitor!
Just like I hid her ID in my hand
where no one could see it...
Raise your hands and proceed forward!
Prepare for your pat down!
...I'll hide this flame!
You're free to go.
Nothing seems to be amiss.
You may leave the facility.
However...
Please open your hands
and display your palms.
I'll remind you again that
accepting anything from him is strictly forbidden.
Open your hands, visitor!
I'm checking them now.
A flower?
A real flower?
Fine. I see no reason not to allow this.
You may now leave the facility.
I turned the lighter into a flower
and hid the flame within its petals.
That was too close...
But could this flame be
Polpo's Stand ability?
This wind could ruin everything!
Hey, Giorno! Perfect timing!
Could you push the shutter
button on the camera for us?
No.
Sorry to bother you,
but could you help me carry this?
No.
I finally made it back to my dorm...
Th-That was close...
This should stop the lighter from falling over,
and these objects will protect it from any air currents.
I just need to keep a close eye on it for the next
twenty-three hours until I see Polpo at 3:00 PM tomorrow.
I know...
I'll make sure my
window is locked, just in case...
I don't want it opening
and letting any gusts of wind in.
What?
Who could be opening my door
without knocking first?
Th-That's...!
Looks like he's out...
Now's my chance!
It's that Japanese guy again!
If I'm not mistaken,
his name is Koichi Hirose!
How did he know where I live?
Guess my suitcase and
belongings are gone by now.
But maybe my passport
is lying around here somewhere...
I bet selling someone's ID
would be really tough...
I kinda feel like a burglar
sneaking into his room like this, but...
No! He's the thief here!
What's so wrong with taking my stuff back?
His passport? No!
It's in the file box on top of my desk!
I was planning on returning it to him!
Soon Koichi will notice the lighter's flame!
If he does, he'll probably put it out!
He won't want to risk starting a fire!
What should I do? What should I do?
I need to get the lighter back
as soon as possible!
Gold Experience!
I used Gold Experience to imbue
the lamp's cord with the life of a snake.
That bread is quite tasty, after all.
It went for it!
Now to pull it up with the cord...
What happened?
It can't be!
Unbelievable...
He found the lighter!
This won't end well!
I need to make sure
he won't put out the flame!
This symbol!
It's the official seal of Japan!
I found it! My passport!
I-It's burning!
Thank goodness...
Huh?
That's strange...
I swear I saw a lit lighter...
What a close call...
He nearly extinguished the flame.
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream!
In order to take my first step toward achieving that dream,
I must protect this flame at all costs!
Whoops, almost got ya!
Real sorry about that!
I was cleaning the stairs.
Oh, you were just splashed a bit.
I'm happy you weren't soaked.
Perhaps we're being rewarded
for our good deeds.
Doing good deeds is very important.
If you had been acting unkind, I probably
would have gotten you with the whole bucket of water.
No way...
This can't be happening...
The flame...
If I ask, will Polpo let me try again?
No...
If he were that forgiving,
he wouldn't have given me a test like this.
Flame?
Is your lighter not working anymore?
Is it ruined?
Was that my fault?
No, it wasn't you...
I just need to figure out
what I'm going to do about it...
Far as I can see,
it doesn't look damaged.
It's still letting out gas.
What did you just say?
Yeah, gas is still coming out!
Is this the flint?
Did you try pushing it?
That's impossible...
It shouldn't be possible to reignite it...
Just look at this fine craftsmanship!
This entire test was predicated on
whether or not the flame stayed lit.
Such an impressive lighter!
If I were able to reignite it,
this test would be pointless!
It was shockingly bright for a second there,
but it seems to be working.
See?
By the way, you wouldn't happen to be using that lighter
to light cigarettes, would you?
This isn't right...
It actually lit up again...
Something is wrong here!
Is that a...?
Could that really be a Sta-
You reignited the lighter, didn't you?
You shall be given one chance.
Two paths lie before you.
Th-That's...!
The first path leads to the life of a chosen one.
The other leads to your demise.
A Stand!
That must be Polpo's Stand!
I'm sure of it!
You reignited the lighter!
Accept your fate!
It can't be! You villain!
What are you doing?!
This soul...
...was not one worthy of being chosen.
"Worthy of being chosen"?
H-Hey, are you...?
He's dead...
Uninjured, but dead...
Is it because it attacked his soul?
Does his Stand drag out people's souls
and kill them with an arrow?
Could that be it?
But what does "worthy of being chosen" mean?
Someone who can join the gang?
You, too, reignited the lighter, did you not?
You shall be given one chance.
Two paths lie before you.
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Joining the Gang