Passione is a major organization
comprised of gangsters.
At the lowest rank are groups
containing six to ten members, such as my team.
Capos like Polpo command those teams.
They take control of specific areas,
making them their turf.
There are also certain specialized teams,
such as the assassination team and drug team.
Even though we're part of the same organization,
I prefer not to associate with those teams or their capos.
The boss towers above the rest.
The only person he trusts enough to
contact directly is his right hand man.
We have no way of finding out
who he is or where he's hiding.
Gangsters in this country hate standing out,
since it makes them a target for assassination.
So even capos dress normally to blend into crowds,
and some even have cover jobs.
This is especially true of the boss.
He won't reveal his identity to anyone.
Snoop around, and you're dead in no time.
I've known several operatives caught doing this.
So, Giorno, in order for you and I
to get close to our mysterious boss...
...we need to earn recognition.
If we can't earn the trust of someone close to the boss
and achieve recognition, we'll never defeat him.
So to start with,
we'll need to gain better standing...
...so that one of us can be promoted to capo.
We can't do this alone, of course.
A team we can trust...
We'll need one in order to
take down the boss.
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting Gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting Gold
Episodio 05  Find Polpo's Fortune!
The news of the incarcerated Polpo's death
spread among the other capos in Passione.
Intelligence team is saying it was suicide.
That ain't his style.
Polpo was locked up in a special cell.
No way he was murdered.
You think he defied the boss?
Ya don't get many capos
as trustworthy as him.
That's even harder to believe.
More importantly...
Yeah... The problem is who's replacing him.
How do I look?
Rome 10:05 a.m.
I just got word that all the capos are freaking the hell out.
Seems like Polpo offed himself.
Hey, watch where you're going!
I'm good!
Suicide? That fatass?
Watch where you're going, for fuck's sake!
I dunno if that Polpo guy was
depressed because he was so fat...
...or if rotting in prison made him melancholic,
but either way, he was a complete pussy.
He deep-throated a gun
and blew his brains out.
You sure it was suicide
and not murder or something?
Gotta be suicide.
They did some autopsy thing on him.
Specialists who do that can tell the
difference between suicide and murder.
Hey, the light.
So anyway, you hear the
rumors about Polpo's fortune?
Rumors?
Never heard about those rumors, just like
I ain't never heard about where the edge of the universe is.
Rumor has it he exchanged a chunk of his fortune for gold and jewels...
...and hid them somewhere
before he went to prison.
A big, fat, hidden fortune.
It's black money he couldn't keep in the bank
that even the organization didn't know about.
No one was dumb enough to
go after it while Polpo was alive...
...but now that he's dead,
his money's up for grabs.
Literally free money.
They say it's worth about five billion lire.
Five billion?
I'd be flying to Monaco or Japan with a girl on both arms
if I had that kind of money!
Not me. I'd work my way up.
If that money made me a capo,
I'd get to taste even sweeter honey.
But who knows where it's hidden...
Nobody knows?
Yeah. And I'm just spitballing here...
...but it's hard to imagine such a major fatass like Polpo
even walking by himself.
You really think he could hide
five billion by himself?
He had someone do it for him.
Someone tight-lipped.
Not sure if someone
that tight-lipped even exists...
...but Polpo sure liked Buccellati.
Buccellati?
He's one of the thugs outta Naples, ain't he?
Yeah.
If he'd have anyone hide it, it'd be him.
Now that Polpo's dead,
Buccellati will probably go for the five billion lire.
Even Buccellati can't resist
that kind of money.
Hey, Zucchero!
Zucchero actually fucking ditched me!
Did he swallow all that bullshit?
If you're gonna follow Buccellati, watch yourself.
Apparently he and his underlings are Stand users, too.
Naples 11:26 a.m.
Hey, Fugo...
It's pretty nice outside...
Would it hurt to skip studying for a day?
I'm just not feeling it today...
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your strawberry cake.
Listen, Narancia...
Set it there.
Yes, sir.
You're a talented guy.
Not just anyone would seek help after
failing to get a proper grade school education.
You already learned
your multiplication tables!
You'll get it if you do like I said.
I know you can do this.
Ready?
What's six times five?
Six times five... Six and five...
Thirty?
Correct!
I knew you had it in you!
You basically have it half-solved!
So that's it!
Six times five is thirty! Sweet!
Hey, what the hell's going on here?
What do you mean?
It's just strawberry ca-
No shit it's strawberry cake!
It sure as hell ain't
chocolate cake or cheesecake!
But that's not what I mean!
There's four slices of cake!
They trying to kill me?!
This again, Mista?
Screw you!
Choosing from four things is bad luck!
Choosing from five things is cool...
Choosing from three things is cool...
But choosing from four things
means bad shit's about to go down!
When I was a kid, another kid adopted a kitten from
a litter of four that was born in our neighborhood...
...and he lost an eye
after the thing scratched it out!
He beat it to death right after, of course.
Like I said, that's just an old wives' tale.
Logically speaking, someone has to pick from four slices
if they're all taken one-by-one.
That's the thing!
The restaurant should've thought of that
and brought out three slices instead!
Talk about bad service!
Jeez... Don't eat it, then.
But I want strawberry cake!
I did it!
I did it, Fugo! Well?
You're finished? Let's see...
What is this?
Did I get it?
You fucking dipshit!
Are you fucking kidding me?
How many times do I have to pound
this shit into your thick fucking skull?
You braindead motherfucker!
Damn... He's totally snapped.
You just told me six times five is fucking thirty!
How the fuck could the answer be less than that?!
Hey, Abbacchio...
You gonna eat that piece of cake?
What's that?
You just call me a
braindead motherfucker?
I wouldn't look down on people if I was you!
You're dead...
I'm gonna kill you, Fugo...
You piece of shit...
What the hell are you guys doing?
I heard you yelling from the entrance!
You're bothering the other customers!
I brought the new member
we talked about yesterday.
Let me introduce you.
His name is Giorno Giovanna.
I'm Giorno Giovanna.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
I'm sorry, Fugo...
No, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, Narancia.
I'll try harder next time,
so teach me again!
Hey, you guys!
I made the call to bring him here,
so show some respect!
Mr. Buccellati...
What is it?
Phone call for you.
Ah, of course.
I expect you all to give Giorno
a proper welcome. Understand?
I'll be back in a minute, Giorno.
I'd like you all to get
acquainted while I'm gone.
Understood.
Giorno, was it?
Why don't you take a seat?
Let's talk over tea.
Mr. Buccellati.
Thanks.
Buccellati here.
Understood...
Is something wrong?
No.
Buccellati!
Buccellati, do you have a moment?
Oh, if it isn't Mrs. Menini!
Is everything okay?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Could we speak outside?
Of course.
Here, drink up.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Fifteen?
Jeez, you're two years younger than me!
Thank you for the drink.
What's up?
You just finished thanking me for
so generously pouring that cup of tea.
Would be pretty rude
to not drink something you said thanks for.
Or is it too lukewarm for your tastes?
Maybe he won't since he's
not serious about joining us!
What are you guys doing?
Oh, it's nothing to worry about.
They graciously poured me a cup of tea.
No freakin' way!
What did you guys do?
Sick! He actually drank it!
D-Dude, you're insane!
Did you seriously drink it?
There's no way he actually did!
So how did you do it?
Where is the tea?
Just tell me at the very least! Please?
Who's to say?
You're all keeping your
abilities secret too, aren't you?
He's a Stand user?
As to where the liquid in my cup went...
I changed one of my teeth into a jellyfish
composed of 98% liquid, then had it suck it up.
Can your ability
move things or something?
Open your mouth!
You don't got a hole in there, do you?
Did you seriously drink it for real?
I don't know why...
Is it your favorite drink or something?
...but Giorno Giovanna seems to
have a knack for winning people over.
If you tell me what your abilities are,
I may tell you mine.
You're a cautious guy.
I can respect that.
Does Buccellati know?
More or less.
They aren't quite ready to work as a team,
but we have no time to lose.
This has to happen now.
Enough screwing around!
We're heading out.
Huh? Where?
Follow me and you'll find out.
Now let's go.
Buccellati!
How are you doing?
Oh, Mr. Buccellati!
Hey, Buccellati!
Stop by my store sometime!
Will do!
So what are we doing about the car?
We got a loaner.
As I suspected, the people here
completely trust him.
Too bad a certain someone ruined the last one...
Hey, I already told you I didn't do it on purpose!
Buccellati, this is a dear friend of mine...
She's being abused by her son
and doesn't know what to do.
Isn't that right?
I see. That's horrible.
I'll give him a stern talking-to.
What's your son's name?
Thank you so much...
He's usually such a sweet boy!
But he recently got into drugs...
Buccellati, I've lived in this
neighborhood for fifty years...
But for some time now,
I've felt uneasy...
Who keeps selling these awful drugs?
I'm so scared...
Please. Will you protect us, Buccellati?
You're going to stand up for us, aren't you?
Yeah... I'll make things right.
I'll sort it out, somehow...
When you said we were heading out,
you meant going on a cruise?!
That's tight!
Since when do we own a yacht?
We're renting one.
Huh?
Just a rental, huh...
Hey, Buccellati...
Whatever you do,
please don't rent one with the number four on it.
It'll sink for sure...
This again...
It wouldn't be floating right now if that were true.
Shut up!
How about you take it for a ride?
We'd like to rent a yacht.
Sure thing!
Pick whichever one you like.
Anything but four!
Fine.
We'll take the one on the far left, sir.
Of course. I'll give you the key.
Right now, I'm thinking we'll need it for three days.
How much is that?
Oh, no, I could never
take your money, Mr. Buccellati!
Take her out as long as you like.
Much appreciated.
Pops, ring me up!
This feels amazing!
Hey, Narancia... Hey!
Huh?
So, uh, I just...
You bought some drinks, didn'tcha?
Wanna sell me one?
Huh?
Every time you say that, you always stiff me!
Give me a break!
Gimme one! C'mon, hurry!
You're hopeless...
Cola or Spalite?
Cola...
A-Actually, I'll take Spalite since it's colorless...
Here.
Thanks, man!
Mind holding my magazine for a sec?
Thank you... and a-thank you...
Huh? What's wrong with this thing?
It just died on me!
Why'd the music stop?
I just bought it!
Dammit!
He's got balls to sell me this piece of shit!
That geezer from the electronics store
is gonna pay for this!
Hey!
Buccellati, come on already!
Tell us where this boat is going!
Fine. We should be far enough
away from shore by now.
We're headed to Capri.
Capri?
I suppose we're not
going there for sightseeing?
Correct.
Then what are we doing there?
This morning,
the capo Polpo committed suicide.
What? Suicide?!
Polpo did?
Get outta here!
Why?
It doesn't matter why he died.
Polpo did plenty of stuff
that could get him killed.
But what does that have to do
with going to Capri?
While he was alive,
Polpo possessed a secret fortune.
It's worth...
...ten billion lire!
T-Ten billion?
I'm the only person who knows its location.
I was the one who hid it for him.
His ten billion belongs to us now!
With that kind of money,
the position of capo will be ours for the taking!
A-Awesome!
He's definitely the kind of guy
who goes for broke!
He's gonna become a capo,
just like I hoped!
He earned this chance by working hard
and getting recognition from a capo.
I'd expect nothing less.
Seriously? This just took a
sudden turn for the awesome!
Where is it?
Where in Capri did you
hide all that treasure, Buccellati?
I can't say just yet.
Rumors of his hidden fortune are
already circulating within the organization.
We can't let anyone know
until we've secured it.
B-Buccellati...!
Hey! Something's going on!
What's going on, Narancia?
Narancia!
What the hell are you playing at?
H-Hey, come look at this!
Only his shoe is left...
Hand it over, Giorno!
I don't understand what's going on...
Where did Narancia go?
You guys didn't see it?
It looked like Narancia
was pulled into the box.
What?
That's not even possible!
He couldn't have tripped and fallen
into the ocean, right?
Narancia, where'd you go?
Hey, Narancia!
If you're just screwing around and hiding from us...
...then tell us where you are already!
Narancia, where are you?
Narancia! Please answer!
Mista?
What are you doing, Mista?
Where did you go, Mista?
He couldn't have...
Come on, Mista!
Why are you messing around at a time like...
Fugo?
Hey, Fugo!
What?
Did he...?
Abbacchio, Giorno,
we need to stay close together!
We're under attack!
Someone is hiding on the boat!
This is a Stand attack!
But why now?
The money...
My knowledge of the fortune's location must have gotten out,
and now someone is trying to beat us to it.
They're probably from the organization.
You think they've been following us
in hiding since we set out?
Seems like it.
They probably got fed up with waiting for me
to reveal the location of the money.
They plan to eliminate you guys,
then make me cough up the location.
They can take their time, too,
since we're stranded out in the ocean.
You mean Narancia and
the others are dead?
I didn't say that.
But ten billion lire is at stake...
They would gladly kill another
member of the organization for that.
No, Narancia and the others are alive.
They're somewhere on this boat.
I don't know if our attacker
plans to use them as hostages...
...but they're alive.
Giorno Giovanna,
what the hell makes you so sure of that?
I used my Stand to
turn Narancia's shoe into a fly.
It's attempting to return to its owner, Narancia.
If Narancia were truly dead, it wouldn't
be buzzing around in search of him.
Can you find him?
He's alive...
He's alive, but...
The fly isn't going down into
the cabin or inside the locker.
It just keeps moving.
It's buzzing around that area
in search of Narancia.
What the hell is his ability, anyway?
Be quiet and listen.
Narancia is somewhere
near the cabin's entrance.
That much is certain.
Yet for some reason,
the fly is lost and can't find him.
I believe it's safe to assume
we'll find the enemy wherever Narancia is.
Likewise, I can confidently say that
the enemy isn't merely hiding behind an object.
I see.
So if we don't first solve
the mystery of the enemy's ability...
...we'll be killed if we get close to it?
Yes.
But the fact that their ability requires them
to attack while hidden is a disadvantage.
It means that once we've solved the mystery,
we can defeat them.
If you use your Stand, Abbacchio...
...you may be able to
defeat someone like that.
Defeat?
Can your ability
solve the mystery for us?
Hard to say...
Hey, Abbacchio!
Don't get hung up on petty
bullshit at a time like this!
Petty bullshit?
No.
My safety's at risk here.
I'm not just gonna reveal my Stand ability
to a stranger I don't trust.
Buccellati...
I don't know what
made you trust this guy...
...but I don't consider him one of us.
If we can't solve the mystery of this enemy,
we'll all be killed!
That's just a baseless theory
from an untrustworthy brat.
It's just his panicked imagination.
He didn't see anything.
Abbacchio!
The enemy is just hiding
somewhere in the cabin.
I'll find them and take them out.
If we get close without solving the mystery,
we'll be killed for sure.
Shut the fuck up!
You goddamned brat...
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream.
What are you on about?
You can solve the mystery, right?
I'm counting on you!
Giorno!
What the hell are you doing?!
G-Giorno!
The enemy is over there!
Damn!
Giorno is in danger!
Abbacchio...
Giorno Giovanna...
You're one crazy son of a bitch!
All this just to prove yourself...
What the hell is wrong with you?
Moody Blues Strikes Back