Mind if I have another look
at the key we retrieved?
Go to the water fountain with a tortoise
and use this key.
D-Don't tell me he...
The Grateful Dead!
Just the driver...
Doesn't look like anyone else is in here...
Got something!
A little fishy took the bait!
Wh-What the hell is this hook-like thing?!
A d-different Stand than the one that's aging us?
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Bro, where'd you go?!
Episodio 15  The Grateful Dead Part 1
Why aren't you here?!
Buccellati and his crew
are on the train!
But which one of 'em did I hook?
It's not Trish, that's for sure.
Only a man could be
putting up this much of a fight.
The hook got stuck in his left hand.
Weight is 68 kilograms!
I'm gonna reel ya right in!
Hey, you're kidding me...
Th-The hook's sinking in deeper!
It's so fast!
It's racing up my arm like it's nothing!
Th-This line...
I must have Mista!
He tried snapping the line with a bullet!
Guido Mista uses a gun!
Can't nobody snap my Beach Boy's line!
I wonder where the shock from
him shooting the line is gonna go!
Time to reel ya in!
I'm screwed if I can't get this line out!
Sh-Shit!
It's making its way up to my brain!
S-Son of a bitch!
Sex Pistols!
Grab hold of the hook and stop it!
N-No good!
It's pulling us in!
We're not strong enough for this!
Sh-Shit... I've gotta find it...
I've gotta find it before it's too late!
Find it!
Gotta find it!
We gotta find it no matter what!
Find it!
What was that?
Was that Mista's pistol?
Just who were you aiming for?
What if you had hit one of the passengers?
Or did you seriously think you could
find me by firing off your gun?
Not gonna happen!
My hook's about to reach deep into your ear!
We gotta aim lower
or the ice isn't gonna spill out!
Lower! Aim a bit lower!
Over here!
Blast it to bits!
Found the ice!
Smash it up, fellas!
What're you doing?!
I knew the asshole had to be cooling himself...
This'll totally freak him out!
D-Dammit...
How could you?!
My ice...!
He's screamin' and looks white as a sheet!
My ice!
Could this guy be...?
It's him!
He's the dude with the line and hook!
That fishing-rod-looking thing is his Stand!
I-I gotta scram!
Ice!
If I don't find more ice,
I'm gonna die of old age, too!
H-Help me...
Outta the way, ya old fossil!
Get your stinkin' zombie hands off of-
My body feels so heavy,
I don't want to move...
I ordered a real fatty cut of steak...
...but I don't feel like eating it anymore...
Get offa me!
Yahoo! Got his hand!
Get Mista over here!
C'mon over here, Mista!
Mista! Over here!
We got the enemy user!
Sex Pistols!
All of you, back in the chamber!
It won't make a difference
whether you answer me or not...
...but I'm going to ask you one
very, very simple question.
If you don't answer within
two seconds of me asking...
...I'm putting a bullet in
each of your eye sockets...
Uno, due...
That's all the time you got, capisce?
So here goes...
Where the hell is your friend hiding?
Uno...
L-Like I know!
I dunno where he is!
Due... Then die!
Hey... Please help me...
I've always loved fatty cuts of steak...
...but I don't feel like eating it anymore...
Hey! Out of my way!
You'll get your appetite back real soon, okay?
No, it just doesn't sound good anymore...
Especially not for you, Mista.
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Grateful Dead...
Huh? Wh-What?
W-Wait! Are you...!
You crafty...
It works even faster through direct contact.
My power is at its strongest...
...while Grateful Dead touches you.
P-Pistols...
I-It's too fast... No...
I-Is that you, Bro?
Are you really Bro?!
I-I had no idea!
Y-You were here the whole time?
I-I can't believe you aged yourself
to blend in with the other passengers...
Bro! Prosciutto!
You're the coolest!
S-Stop that!
Why are you so mad, Bro?!
You fucking idiot!
What the hell were you doing?! Huh?!
I didn't think he'd shoot the ice!
What could I have done?!
You still don't get it?
Pesci, you fucking mammone!
Please quit hitting me, Bro!
Listen up!
I'm only pissed off because you lack resolve, Pesci!
I don't blame you for being shocked
after those things got rid of all your ice...
I'm being aged too, so I know how it feels...
But if it had been
any other person on our team...
...they wouldn't have called their Stand back
when they were that close to finishing off the enemy!
Even if it meant losing an arm or leg!
You're a complete mammone, Pesci.
You lost your cool.
You're such a baby.
It wasn't because of the ice.
There's fear lurking deep within your heart.
It's time to grow up, Pesci.
If you don't, we'll never make it big.
We'll never defeat Buccellati and his crew.
And just so we're clear...
We're not some bunch of losers that hang around
pickup artist alleys or social clubs...
...patting each other on the back
and boasting how we're "gonna get 'em" someday.
Once our mind's made up
to get someone...
...the deed's already been done!
Let's go, Pesci.
Here, have some ice.
You mentioned sensing another presence in
the driver's compartment earlier, didn't you?
I don't know how they're all hiding in there...
...but the girl's in the driver's compartment!
Prosciutto
The Grateful Dead
Power: B
Speed: E
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Don't worry about Narancia!
Save that ice for yourself!
You need to keep
your own body chilled.
Fanning him with air or cooling him
with a wet towel won't have any effect.
The only thing that can help him is ice.
He'll be the first to die at this rate.
Narancia and the rest of us are prepared to
follow the boss's orders, no matter the cost.
Your biggest concern
should be your own safety.
Your safety is our job.
It's not as if you chose to be here.
As for the enemy who's causing us all to age...
Mista will take care of him.
I'm sure... he'll figure something out...
Mista...
I think I finally have a good idea...
...where, and how, they're hiding.
I need to think outside of the box
in order to find them.
Buccellati received some kind of
dark object from the boss at the station.
That's it. That's what I need to look for
in the driver's compartment!
Hey, Pesci...
What do you think the
other presence you felt in here was?
Do you still feel it?
A-About that... Bro...
I wouldn't put too much faith in me...
I ain't so smart...
Pesci, Pesci, Pesci, Pesci...
I believe in you.
If you're still upset
that I yelled at you earlier...
...you just need to be confident.
If you really put your mind to it,
your Beach Boy's ability would be unbeatable!
Don't you think?
That presence you felt earlier
is extremely suspicious.
It's do or die time, Pesci.
There's nothing wrong with
being confident in your ability.
R-Really?
Yes, really!
Try to remember.
It doesn't matter how unimportant it seemed.
Did you see anything strange?
Maybe some dark-looking thing?
Huh?
Some... dark-looking thing?
That's it, Bro!
I was gonna look under
the driver's seat earlier!
I noticed something super weird!
S-Sorry...
Guess I was just imagining it...
I knew it...
You shouldn't have counted on my instincts, after all...
No, it looks like you were right.
Come again?
Excellent work, Pesci.
This mystery is solved!
I finally get it thanks to you!
B-Bro?
Wh-What are you...?
Why is there animal shit
near the driver's seat all of a sudden?
It's not mouse shit, either.
If it were just some rodent,
it would've dropped dead by now.
The shit's not old, either.
Looks like it was just freshly deposited.
So what does that tell you, huh?
Humans aren't the only beings
who can possess Stand abilities.
This can only mean...
...the animal is moving through the shadows!
Grateful Dead!
Wh-What the heck is that?!
I-It's a tortoise? A tortoise?!
Found her! It's Trish!
I can see the others, too!
Just like I thought,
everyone except Trish is dying of old age!
That settles it!
I'll concentrate my aging ability
right into the tortoise!
Grateful Dead!
Wait a sec, Bro!
Isn't... one of them missing?
One of them isn't there anymore!
Mista! Please get up!
This is all the ice I got left,
but please feel better!
I dunno if it's thanks to my attentive nature...
...or if I just barely lucked out...
But since I put one of the ice cubes
I picked up earlier inside my hat...
Number Five... It looks like you were
the only one who had the effects of the aging reversed.
You did good stopping those bullets for me...
All three of 'em.
Number Five...
I have one more request...
If you wanted me to go to Buccellati,
I already revived Number Six and sent him over there!
He took the ice in your pocket and went to tell them
two enemies were headed for the tortoise!
That's good... I don't need the ice anymore...
...after all...
Mista!
It's Buccellati, Bro!
Buccellati's the missing one!
It doesn't matter if Buccellati's in there or not!
All that matters is that we take Trish alive!
Grateful Dead!
What the heck?!
Sharp instincts.
And you're fast, too.
I just have to defeat him, right?
The one in black!
You got it, Buccellati!
Everyone's aging'll be reversed if you beat him!
What the fuck is Mista's Stand doing here?
I pulled the trigger myself and put three bullets
through his head, point-blank... didn't I?
So what is that thing
doing here with an ice cube?!
Don't let it touch ya!
You'll age super-duper fast if it does!
Get him!
H-He's fast...
Bro!
Don't worry about me!
Deal with everyone in the tortoise!
Make it fast!
Kill the rest of his crew!
Wasn't that a bit careless of you, Buccellati?
After Mista went through
all that trouble to warn you...
Defeating me, even if it costs
the lives of your crew, to protect the girl...
Isn't that your mission?
You're a failure of a capo!
Take this!
What?!
I will complete this mission...
...and I'll protect my crew, too.
That shouldn't be difficult
if I'm only facing the likes of you.
It's fast...
It's really fast...
Your... Sticky Fingers, was it?
It definitely seems faster than my Stand...
But you don't seem to fully understand
the implications of going fast, Buccellati!
I may be out of breath...
...but so are you, Buccellati.
Since we both used our Stands at full speed,
we burned a lot of energy.
You didn't get that and attacked me
as fast as you could...
...and now you're aging again
even though you're standing in place!
The more horsepower a car has,
the warmer it gets!
You're burning calories like crazy!
You're a smart guy,
so I'm sure you can figure out...
...what will happen if your body
keeps getting warmer!
B-Buccellati!
Th-The ice isn't working anymore!
So what are you going to do now, huh?
The zipper you put on me is starting to close.
The one on my chin is already gone.
What's wrong?
Exhausted from your stiff shoulders?
Sticky Fingers!
I see what you're doing!
You're too slow, Buccellati!
Got you! You're all done for!
We'll be taking the boss's daughter!
I was prepared for what would happen
if my body warmed up.
I was also prepared to get caught.
I will complete this mission.
I'll protect my crew, too.
The hardest part about being a capo
is that I've sworn to do both.
Are you prepared?
Because I am.
Wha-
Y-You can't mean...!
You son of a bitch!
You're kidding me!
Doing both is a simple matter.
If I can get you off this train...
As long as I can reverse the aging, my five subordinates will be back, and they'll be able to protect Trish!
You asshole!
Y-You're fucking insane! Let go of me!
We're moving at 150 kilometers an hour!
Oh, come on.
You're the one who grabbed me.
You got a fucking death wish, motherfucker?!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
The Grateful Dead Part 2