Maybe I should shoot the shit out of
this fatty and see what happens!
Yes!
Th-That was close...
He would have got me if I
hadn't returned to normal size!
If your Stand wasn't
basically harmless by now...
...I would have been killed!
I-I didn't get him!
D-Dammit.
Is Aerosmith's power shrinking
as I get smaller and smaller?
He's on the move again!
Come back, Aerosmith!
Th-This is really pissing me off,
but I gotta find a hiding place.
The motherfucker's getting desperate, too.
If he finds me, he'll do anything
to get me to cough up where the boss's daughter is.
I-It's so far away!
This sidewalk is way too big!
Move it!
You're in my way!
Sh-Shit...
Got you now.
Guess you're screwed.
Really put me through the wringer, though!
Ain't no one running from me
if I get them with Little Feat.
Now talk...
Where are Buccellati and your friends
hiding the boss's daughter?
K-Kill me!
Dammit, just kill me already!
You really think I'm desperate enough
to give up where my friends are hiding?!
Narancia Ghirga was born in 1984
under the sign of Leo.
When he was ten years old...
N-Narancia...
I'm right here, Mom.
Mom...
Hey, Dad...
About Mom's eye disease...
I hate you...
Thus Narancia started down the path
that would bring him to the present day.
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 11  Narancia's Aerosmith
Can you help me with this?
How many minutes do you think
it'll take to walk here?
Narancia rebelled against his father.
Minutes? That'll take hours.
He got through each day by stealing food
and sleeping over at the houses of his delinquent friends.
It went great!
It's all because you told us
about that shop, Bro!
You sure you don't need to be at school?
You got an actual
decent home to go back to.
Like I give a shit...
The most important thing
in the world is friendship!
Yeah!
You should dye your hair blond like mine.
Chicks won't be able
to keep their hands off you.
Yeah?
What? Seriously?
Pretty cool, huh?
You look stupid as hell!
Hey, where's Bro?
Who knows?
Haven't seen him in days.
Huh...
But the next day...
You assholes!
Spread 'em! Up against the wall!
You little punk!
You're going to juvie!
What the hell are you talking about?!
I wouldn't steal!
I'm not a-
Don't lie!
We got a witness!
Wha-
That's him!
This blond brat is the culprit!
N-No I'm not!
I'm sure of it!
He beat me and took off with my money!
Quit lying, you crusty old bitch!
I didn't do anything!
Just admit you're guilty,
you fucking punk!
Hey!
You're going too far!
You saw it too, right, lawyer?
He was trying to have another go at her!
A robbery...
A blond brat...
Don't tell me...
No, that's impossible!
Quit thinking up shit like that, dammit!
A year later, when Narancia was released from juvenile hall,
his eye was in bad shape.
The wound from the officer's punch
had become infected and seemingly wouldn't heal.
When he returned to town,
strange rumors began circulating among his friends.
Look at him...
I heard his mom died
from an eye disease, too.
How do they know that?
I only ever told Bro...
Wow, they already let you out?
Don't infect me.
You better stay the fuck back.
It can't be... But Bro...
He felt trapped,
so he used me as a scapegoat...
The one most afraid of these rumors
concerning his disease...
...was Narancia himself.
This is fate...
Soon... just like Mom...
...I'm gonna die from this disease!
He truly believed it.
He had nowhere left to turn.
He was all alone.
Narancia had given up on life
at the young age of fifteen.
How terrible... He's just a kid.
I feel sorry for him,
but we shouldn't get involved.
The young man brought Narancia into a restaurant,
then told the waiter and his friend waiting at the table...
I'd like to buy him a plate of spaghetti!
Would that be acceptable?
His friend at the table
didn't ask any questions...
...nor did he give him a look of disgust.
He simply set the plate of spaghetti he had ordered for himself
right in front of the filthy child.
He then helped the child
receive the treatment he required.
Three weeks later...
Why'd you do all this for me?
No reason.
If you like, you can stay at my place.
But children like you
should still live with their parents.
Also, go back to school. Understand?
U-Umm, are you a gangster?
I don't wanna go home...
Please let me work for you!
Don't be so naïve, you little punk!
Say more stupid shit like that
and I'll punch you in the face!
As instructed, Narancia returned home
and began going back to school.
However, he never trusted his father again.
Why was he so tough on me?
I'm nothing special.
But...
It's not like he was mad because he hated me,
and I don't think he was trying to insult me...
It felt nothing like when my dad
or the cops get mad at me.
The way he treated me
makes me feel encouraged!
Real men...
...should work for guys like him!
Six months later, Narancia went to see one of the capos
of the organization, Polpo, without telling Buccellati...
...and passed his test.
Narancia, if you're gonna cough up
where his daughter is...
...now would be the time.
The girl you're trying to kidnap
isn't a gangster or a criminal!
She's just a normal girl!
Buccellati fucking hates anyone who'd kidnap an innocent,
and it's got nothing to do with orders!
Good people don't do that shit!
We swore we'd protect her...
...and we'll keep that promise no matter what!
Could you stop it with the bullshit?
Guess you just don't get it...
All this shit about your friends
and protecting this bitch...
That's not what we're talking about.
What I'm telling you is that if we can off the boss, his drug operation worth hundreds of billions is ours for the taking.
Y-You motherfucker!
Hundreds of billions!
That much money's
gotta be worth a few lives!
That shit's ours!
No backing out now!
If that girl has the boss's blood flowing through her veins,
she's gotta have a Stand ability!
The boss doesn't want
anyone finding out!
We'll definitely figure out who the boss is
through his daughter's ability!
The boss's daughter is the only hint
we got to figure out who he really is!
What? She's a Stand user?
Hey, did you know?
There's a spider in South America
called the southern black widow.
Apparently, its venom can even kill humans.
The spider I have here isn't harmful to humans...
I actually caught it in the sewers earlier.
It's completely harmless.
But...
Even normal spiders bite,
and this one is still venomous!
Venomous enough to paralyze
and eat puny little insects!
Y-You aren't gonna...
Aerosmith!
Watch it!
I already told you,
your Stand is fucking worthless!
This bottle is gonna be your arena, Narancia!
Y-You motherfucker! Hey!
It's looking at you!
Check it out!
It's watching you with all eight of its eyes!
Open up!
Open the bottle!
Shit!
Listen up!
Even if it bites you, you won't die right away.
First it'll stop you from moving
by paralyzing your muscles.
But once you're trapped and can't move,
you'll be in for some real shit!
It'll start injecting you with
even more venom and digestive juices!
Your insides will be melted like a vanilla milkshake,
and then it'll suck you right up!
And best of all,
you'll be conscious the whole time!
If you ever feel like talking,
you can do that while it's eating you.
But I'd recommend talking
while you still have the chance...
...and tell me where the boss's daughter is.
I really don't wanna see someone
get turned to mush and eaten by a spider!
I-It's so fast!
You asshole!
A glass shard?!
He's had that with him this whole time?!
W-Webbing?
When did it...?
It bit him!
You can't move now that
your muscles are freaking out, right?
Just hurry up and tell me.
This is your last chance
if you don't wanna die.
Fuck... Like hell I'll tell you!
Dammit!
Looks like it's injecting its
digestive juices into you now.
You're gonna melt...
What's that?
Lookie here... This must've fallen out of your pocket
when you took out that glass shard...
Y'know... maybe I don't need you after all!
It's a map of the city...
A road map, at that.
And best of all...
It's been marked up with a pencil!
Just so you wouldn't get lost!
Are you fucking stupid?
I can find out where you came from
if I follow the directions in reverse!
A vineyard!
You came from a vineyard about
twenty kilometers southeast!
Grazie, Narancia!
Now that thing can just eat you and
lay its eggs inside you or whatever...
...dipshit!
Formaggio
Little Feat
Power: D
Speed: B
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: C
Twenty kilometers southeast!
The boss's daughter Trish
is somewhere in that area!
I did it!
I don't need shit from you anymore!
My Aerosmith has the ability to
track carbon dioxide...
...but carbon dioxide doesn't just
come from living creatures...
It also comes from burning things...
I remembered something...
When I was tracking you with Aerosmith...
...I also shot at a car.
I think I hit the gas tank...
...but I can't really tell
where the holes are from here...
Still...
I figured since the bullet holes are still technically burning,
Aerosmith could find them using the carbon dioxide.
So I shot at them...
I wasn't trying to shoot the spider earlier...
I was starting to freak out since it took a while
to make a big enough fire with my tiny-ass bullets!
What?!
Fuck!
All the shit I bought is toast!
Narancia's Height: 5.5cm -> 170.5cm (His normal height)
But man, it feels great to be big enough
that a little spider bite won't hurt me.
How dare you?
I'm gonna fucking kill all your friends!
Hideout...
Vineyard...
Just fucking wait, Narancia!
Little Feat!
Wh-What?!
He stopped the fire by
spraying blood out of his wrists?!
Dammit! This sucks!
This is gonna get ugly if he gets away!
I have to find him using Aerosmith's ability!
Sh-Shit!
Th-The radar...
These flames...
Y-You motherfucker! Where are you?
Is this good luck or bad luck?
Narancia, now that you've set the car on fire...
...you can't track me because of
all the carbon dioxide coming from the flames!
If there's gotta be a winner and a loser,
then I'm the winner!
You're not getting away!
I know where the boss's daughter is!
Now I just need to get out of here and tell the team!
We'll kill you all!
Assassination is what we do!
Assassination?
I'll have my revenge soon enough!
You'll never find me!
I win!
If I can't track your breathing...
If the flames are too big...
...then I'll just make them bigger!
If I set the whole fucking street on fire...
...you'll burn up and die since you're so tiny!
You're not getting away, Formaggio!
Are you insane, motherfucker?
You seriously set the whole street on fire!
Are you out of your mind?
Huh?!
Well, you just saved me the trouble
of setting the whole city on fire.
The reason I asked if
you were out of your mind...
...is because you're practically begging me
to kill you as soon as possible.
Thanks to the flames,
I'm up close and personal with you now.
Did you forget?
At this distance, my Stand is faster than yours!
Maybe.
Bring it, Narancia...
Little Feat!
Guess you win...
But your little shopping trip
wasn't as easy as you thought it'd be, huh?
Eh, Narancia?
Shit's about to get real difficult
for you motherfuckers!
"Go shopping," they told me...
Mission... failed.
My money and all the stuff I bought...
...went up in flames...
Narancia, repeat that to me one more time!
I told you, the shopping-
Not that!
You just said the enemy
found out where we're hiding!
But I took care of him right af-
That's not the issue here!
Buccellati, we need to ditch this place, pronto.
After I warned you so many times...
You fool!
It seems to me that Narancia did a great job
of foiling the enemy's plans.
He did what was necessary,
given the situation.
And now that the Hitman Team
knows our location, any wise boss...
...would surely instruct us
how to make our escape.
It would be unwise to leave
until we receive word from the boss.
Well, aren't you clever?
Are you our advisor now?
And just how do you know the boss
is gonna make contact with us?
We don't give a fuck
about your little hunches!
Buccellati!
I think we just got
a message from the boss!
Message for Buccellati
The boss always sends his orders
to the capos this way.
This is the first time
Buccellati's received one!
Let's see what it says.
"Head to the Archaeological Park of Pompeii.
I've hidden a key near the dog mosaic."
Look into this immediately!
"This key is for a vehicle which will
safely deliver my daughter to me."
Vehicle?
What does he mean by a safe vehicle?
A helicopter!
It's gotta be a helicopter key!
We can go wherever we want in a helicopter
without anyone following us!
It's a bit less than fifteen kilometers
from here to Pompeii.
An hour should be plenty of time
to go there and retrieve the key.
Fugo! Abbacchio! Giorno!
You three head to Pompeii
and retrieve that key!
Mista, Narancia, and I will stay here
and protect Trish from the Hitman Team.
Retrieve the key,
then contact me once it's safe.
Then we'll take Trish
and head over to the vehicle.
I'm counting on you.
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Second Order from the Boss