"Head to the Archaeological Park of Pompeii.
I've hidden a key near the dog mosaic."
"This key is for a vehicle which will
safely deliver my daughter to me."
Fugo! Abbacchio! Giorno!
You three head to Pompeii
and retrieve that key!
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 12  Second Order from the Boss
The city of Pompeii was considered a peaceful,
prosperous health resort by the Romans.
It was destroyed in an instant by ash and lava from
the sudden eruption of Mt. Vesuvius on August 24th, 79 AD.
Archaeologists later discovered that
all the houses, streets, bottles of wine...
...and even tracks left by carriages had been perfectly preserved
as they were when the volcano erupted 1,800 years ago.
The dog mosaic we're looking for is located near
the entrance of the House of the Tragic Poet in Pompeii.
Oh, Fugo...
You were supposed to turn right
at that intersection, not left.
You should have spoken up sooner, Giorno.
What use is it telling me to turn right
after I already went the wrong way?
You're absolutely correct.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful in the future.
You're missing my point, dammit!
Hey, Fugo...
We're in a hurry, so keep it together.
I'm well aware!
For fuck's sake...
Well, I expected nothing less of Fugo.
My real concern is the new guy,
Giorno Giovanna.
I'll treat him like the others
since that's what Buccellati told me to do...
...but something about him
rubs me the wrong way.
He's gonna fuck things up sooner or later...
Probably get us all killed.
Pompeii, huh?
I took a field trip here as a kid.
Haven't been back since.
Abbacchio, Giorno, let's move.
The place we're looking for
is a hundred meters ahead.
It should take us about thirty minutes
to find what we need and regroup with the others.
Abbacchio, Giorno, stay sharp.
To think we'd be found so soon...
How many we got?
One. For now.
He's peeking around the stone pillar behind us.
Pillar? Which one do you mean?
Open your eyes, Giorno...
There's only one pillar.
Can't you see it from that angle?
Fugo, it's true there's only one pillar...
...but I don't see anyone, either.
Quit messing around!
He's headed right for us!
Fugo?
There!
That guy walking toward us!
H-He was right there...
A man came out from behind the pillar!
I saw him in the mirror!
Wh-What?!
There! He's right there!
He's coming out!
H-He's inside the mirror?
He revealed his Stand!
Who's fighting him?
Hold on, Fugo!
I still don't know what you're talking about.
Is something wrong with the mirror?
This is bad!
He's about to attack!
Get away from the mirror!
What?
Giorno! Abbacchio!
Wh-Where did you go?
Giorno? Abbacchio?
Where did you go?!
The man in the mirror is gone, too...
What did he do?
A mirror hanging in a place like this
was bizarre to begin with!
What even is this ability?
I don't...
I don't know what it is...
...but something about the scenery feels off...
I'm right here.
What?!
Pannacotta Fugo...
Possesses an IQ of 152 which earned him
admission into university at the age of thirteen.
During his time there, he lost his temper with a professor,
assaulting him with a four-kilogram encyclopedia.
This sent him into an
unending downward spiral.
He is accompanied by
ex-police officer Leone Abbacchio, and...
Nothing on the other guy.
Must be new.
I believe I heard the name Giorno.
What did you do to them?
Y-You scumbag...
Where are you hiding them?
The watch numbers are backwards?
And now it's on my
right wrist instead of my left?
I-Impossible!
This is...!
Your ability is-
As I predicted, you figured it out quickly.
I'll take you all out one by one, Fugo...
It doesn't matter who goes first...
...but I'll start with you,
since you looked in the mirror first.
Abbacchio and Giorno weren't
the ones who disappeared...
I-I'm inside the mirror!
It was me!
I'm the one who was dragged in!
Fugo!
Where are you, Fugo?
Hey, Giorno!
Did you see something or not?
I'm not sure.
It looked to me as though
he suddenly disappeared, as well.
Fugo! Where are you?
Before he disappeared,
Fugo yelled at us to get away from the mirror.
He also asked us whether we could see
a man coming out from behind a pillar.
This mirror...
Is there something going on...
with this mirror?
The question is...
...where are you hiding the boss's daughter?
Well, that's the most
important question, anyway...
I should also probably figure out what the three of you
are doing here in Pompeii, the city of the dead.
I suppose you're here
looking for something.
If that's the case,
you came here to get something you need to protect the girl.
Am I right?
If you turn left up ahead,
you'll arrive at the famous dog mosaic.
Is there something there?
Well?
Whatever it is, it's mine!
Tell me what you're looking for, Fugo!
I refuse!
Then die!
No...
You're the one who's going to die
after witnessing my ability!
Purple Haze!
My Stand isn't appearing...
I see...
So your Stand is named Purple Haze.
Something's wrong.
I definitely called out my Stand...
I can feel it... so why?
Hey, Giorno...
Slowly walk toward me.
Slowly what?
Just get the fuck over here, idiot!
Fuck going slow! Move it!
What?! Th-That's...!
Giorno! Ignore that thing!
That's not our enemy!
That's Fugo's Stand!
Now hurry and get the fuck away!
Don't get any closer!
Fugo's-
Get the hell away from Purple Haze!
Move it!
You're currently inside the mirror.
I'm sure you can figure out why
I dragged you in here alone.
If I had brought anyone else in who could fight me,
I'd be in deep shit!
I control what's inside the mirror...
That's my ability.
Everything in here is a lifeless object.
You and I are the only living inhabitants.
I intentionally haven't let anyone else in.
I only allowed your physical body inside.
In other words...
Your Stand ability was left outside!
This is my Man in the Mirror!
Purple Haze materialized
outside of the mirror...
With that in mind,
there must be a way I can fight this!
Man in the Mirror
Illuso
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: B
Durability: D
Precision: C
Growth Potential: E
Pannacotta Fugo was born into a wealthy family
who owned a large estate in the suburbs of Naples.
In addition to being born into a life of luxury,
he was gifted with great intelligence, possessing an IQ of 152.
He appeared to have
a perfect life on the surface.
However, the weight of the expectations his parents
and others placed on him slowly began to crush his young heart.
At times, Fugo would experience fits of rage
that even he himself couldn't understand...
...but he did everything in his power
to control them and get by.
Later on, after entering university at the age of thirteen,
his rage manifested in the worst way possible.
Fugo, lad...
Professor.
What are you doing here so late?
I'm working on the assignment due next week.
I can't find any good former cases...
Oh, come now...
I already told you to come to me
if there was anything you didn't understand.
No, I wouldn't want to be
constantly bothering you...
It's my job to educate and lead
young people like you in the right direction.
How about it?
Why don't you come by
my house again for dinner, and...
Please excuse me.
Now, wait just a moment.
If you like, I suppose I could tell you
what will be on the next test...
It will be fine. Just relax.
Stop it... Stop it...
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it!
I'll be nice and gentle.
I told you to stop, asshole!
I always looked up to you!
You fucking piece of shit!
Did you hear?
Apparently Fugo got real friendly
with one of the professors.
You sure he wasn't the one leading him on?
Probably "charmed" his way
through the entrance exam, too.
Fugo's parents used their wealth
to ensure he wasn't found guilty...
...but they treated him
like filth and disowned him.
With nowhere to turn,
Fugo began shoplifting and pickpocketing to survive.
Ironically, this lifestyle encouraged him
to use his intellect to its fullest potential.
You little shit!
You trying to dine and dash on me?
I'm gonna throw your ass in jail!
No, I won't be going to jail.
Are you familiar with
De Sica v. Argento from 1982?
Since precedent will be taken into account,
the court will likely rule that I was acting out of necessity.
Mr. Buccellati!
Please say something to this brat!
How interesting.
This was around the time when Buccellati
was thinking about forming his own team.
So that's my life story, more or less.
Please don't take pity on me.
I don't see my situation as unfortunate.
Of course.
But, hmm... I feel our meeting here is fate.
Would you like to join my team,
Pannacotta Fugo?
I want your knowledge and intellect.
Mr. Buccellati, was it?
Joining a gang doesn't sound so bad,
but I've already made up my mind.
I'm going to live on my own, and keep to myself.
Oh? Why is that?
I already told you.
When I lose my temper, I do horrible things.
If I were to join your team,
I could end up killing you.
Well then, let's see if that comes to pass.
Come with me, Fugo.
I'll bring out the best in you.
Your fierce, impulsive rage and all.
These words moved Fugo's heart.
After that, Fugo took Polpo's test
and gained Purple Haze.
So this is Fugo's Stand...
Fugo isn't here,
yet for some reason his Stand appeared.
Fugo's probably doing all right for now
since this thing is here, but...
Dammit!
Where the hell did he go?
How is he protecting himself?
Stay back, Giorno!
Even more than that!
Fugo doesn't let this thing out very often.
It only happens when he's in deep shit.
This has gotta mean
Fugo's trying to fight somewhere!
You're still too close, Giorno!
He seems more worried about
that Stand than where Fugo is.
He feels threatened.
What's going on?
It started attacking out of nowhere!
This is really bad!
We need to get out of here!
We're leaving! Come on!
What are you talking about?
There's something in that mirror!
We need to find Fugo!
That's the most important thing right-
Don't talk back to me, you little shit!
I don't give a fuck what happens to you...
...but I'm telling you since you clearly have
no idea what the fuck is going on!
It punched it!
Run, Giorno!
I see.
So you activated your Stand
outside the mirror.
But... it won't mean shit!
It doesn't matter how
your Stand uses its ability.
It will never be able to hit me.
But I can beat you to death
whenever I feel like it!
A crow?
Why did a crow suddenly just fall?
A crow just fell out of nowhere...
Stand back.
Whoever's in Purple Haze's way
better move when it starts swinging.
What the hell is with these corpses?
It's a killer virus.
That's Fugo's Stand, Purple Haze's ability.
A virus?
Look at its hand.
After its fist connects with something,
one of the capsules breaks open...
...and the virus comes spilling out!
The virus goes airborne
and enters the body through inhalation or skin contact.
Then it rapidly multiplies.
It infects its host within thirty seconds,
then instantly kills them.
And once the virus spreads,
it doesn't matter who's nearby, be it friend or foe.
Just like those crows,
all of your bodily functions will shut down...
...and you'll die as you rot from the inside out.
That includes your Stand, too.
What's its range?
Five meters.
Right now, Fugo should be controlling his Stand
within five meters of his opponent.
That's obviously important,
but what's the range of the virus?
How close do you have to be to get infected?
We should be safe from here.
The virus inside its capsules dies within
a few dozen seconds of being exposed to normal indoor light.
The crows' corpses should be
sterilized by the sunlight soon.
It's vicious!
It strikes like an explosion,
then scatters like a storm.
It's a Stand which personifies Fugo's violent nature.
What is it doing?
I think it's trying to wipe off
the drool that dripped on its leg.
It always looks pissed off,
but it's really compulsive and cares about cleanliness.
You could say it's a Stand of habit.
His Stand doesn't seem to possess
much intelligence, if any...
That's because it's a reflection
of his angry side.
It also proves that Fugo
can't see Purple Haze right now.
He doesn't have it under control at all.
He'd never let it act like this if he did.
This corpse...
This crow...
Was it sick?
Was it infected by some virus or bacteria?
I knew it...
Fugo doesn't have it under control!
It attacked another random spot.
Wait, was that actually random?
There must be something in the mirror!
So now you attacked the mirror from the outside...
But that was pointless, Fugo.
That was a normal mirror
like you could find anywhere else.
No matter what your Stand
does on the outside...
No matter what kind of ability it has...
Not even viruses can enter
the world of Man in the Mirror!
Abbacchio, Giorno, please get my message...
Please don't let yourselves
be dragged into the mirror!
We need to hurry, Giorno!
Hey, Giorno!
Don't just stand there! Let's go!
Let me ask you this...
Where are we going?
To retrieve the key?
You're willing to abandon Fugo
while he's in danger?
Watch your mouth, motherfucker.
Listen here. We were ordered to retrieve the key
and safely bring the girl to the boss!
I want to save Fugo
just as much as you right now...
...but retrieving the key is our top priority!
Even if I were the one being
attacked right now and not Fugo...
...I'd want you guys to abandon me.
I don't mean to be rude...
...but I disagree!
Fugo may be in grave danger,
but it isn't like he's dead!
We should risk our lives to save him!
Besides, making another move before we know the enemy's ability puts us at risk, as well.
No! The worst thing we could possibly do
is risk all three of us being taken out!
I'll say it again!
We're moving on! Let's go!
I respectfully refuse!
We will solve this mystery,
rescue Fugo, then defeat the enemy!
That's the only way to ensure our safety!
I have seniority here,
so we're doing things my way!
You sure you still refuse?
You're gonna have hell to pay!
If somehow you survive, at least!
I'll ask you once more, Fugo...
What are you looking for here?
I've no intention of telling you!
I see.
Very well.
There's always the other two.
I just need the last one standing to tell me.
You're finished! Take this!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Man in the Mirror and Purple Haze