yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 20  Final Order from the Boss
How long until we arrive?
We're almost at the Rialto Bridge.
It will be another five minutes or so.
Good. Keep going.
Buccellati, can you remind me
what the boss's orders entailed?
I'll go over the boss's message again.
Are you all safe?
From the bottom of my heart, I thank you
for protecting my daughter.
Listen closely.
"The information contained on this disc was transferred to it
the moment you all boarded the train in Naples.
As such, I must inform you that I do not know
if you are currently being pursued...
...nor how many of you have presently fallen.
The information on this disc will assist you in safely
reuniting me with my daughter, which is my final order.
But I warn you; should you deviate from the instructions
contained on this disc even slightly, you will be shown no mercy.
If any of you do anything I have not instructed,
whether accidentally or intentionally...
...I will interpret it as an act of hostility.
Now, here is my final order.
Those of you remaining will depart...
...for the island of San Giorgio Maggiore.
You will accompany my daughter to the top
of the great bell tower at the local church.
Once my daughter has been safely escorted there,
your mission will be completed.
Order one: There are no stairs leading to the top of the tower.
Currently, the only means of reaching
the top floor is through a single elevator.
Only Trish and one designated bodyguard
are permitted to use the elevator.
Order two: The bodyguard is prohibited from carrying any knives, guns, cell phones, or similar items.
Order three: You must reach the island
within fifteen minutes of successfully retrieving this disc.
Furthermore, the disc has been outfitted with a tracking device,
so I will know when you are on the move.
Order four: The rest of you will remain on the boat.
You are not allowed to step foot on the island."
That's everything.
Buccellati, we've arrived.
So the boss is at the top of that tower right now...
He must be incredibly cautious
considering how detailed his orders were.
Though I suppose if he weren't,
he wouldn't be the boss of an organization.
Anyway, our mission is just about done now.
None of us died on the way,
so I guess it went well in the end.
Yeah, just barely, though.
We should have some fun in Venice
for a bit before we head home.
I hear they got great eats.
The food's good here, huh?
I forgot how hungry I was!
What do they got?
Squid ink pasta, horsehair crab salad...
...and I hear Hotel Cipriani serves great carpaccio.
Hey, knock it off!
Don't let your guard down!
This mission isn't over yet!
Narancia, keep an eye on the radar.
G-Got it...
Buccellati...
...I volunteer to be her bodyguard.
I'll escort her to the top of the bell tower.
Who the hell do you think you are?
It's Buccellati's obligation as capo to escort her, idiot!
The boss didn't specify since
he didn't know who would still be alive!
Of course. I'll go.
All right, Trish.
The two of us will enter the island as instructed.
I know...
This is our chance to unmask the boss.
I'll do whatever I can.
Oh yeah, Giorno. Could you give me that brooch of yours
as a good luck charm on this final mission?
Ladybugs are considered insects of the sun.
They're symbols of life, right?
They make good luck charms, don't they?
Oh, of course.
Yes. Ladybugs bring very good luck.
This brooch imbued with life by
Gold Experience's ability will act as a tracking device.
Buccellati...
What is it, Fugo?
I would like to take this opportunity to say something.
Why so formal? What is it?
I believed you would become capo someday,
and I believe you'll be able to complete this mission.
Of course he can.
Let's aim for an even higher position in the organization!
Yeah... We will.
Let's go, Trish.
If I can somehow get this onto the boss's body...
...Giorno will be able to track him down.
For now, I need to figure out who he is...
...at any cost.
The elevator is open.
It only has buttons for the first floor and roof.
It goes directly to either.
There are no other floors to stop on.
What's...
...What's going to happen to me?
I was suddenly kidnapped by gangsters like you guys,
was threatened with my life...
...and now, I'm about to be taken
to a father I've never loved or even met.
What will happen to me after this?
The boss is just concerned for your safety.
As for what will happen to you after this,
I have a good idea.
First, you'll be given a different name.
You may even need plastic surgery.
You'll be given new ID and a new family registry...
...and be sent to some faraway country
where you'll live a happy life.
Your father has the power to make that happen.
Here. Let me give you a hand.
It's not as if...
...I-I'm nervous or anything...
I wonder...
...if I'll come to like my father.
No family ever worries about that.
Yeah...
You're right.
To even worry about it is odd...
We're almost at the top.
Trish? Tri-
Wh-What?!
Trish... No... What's...?
Trish and I should be the only ones here...
No one other than the members of my team know I'm...
No... It couldn't be!
Could the boss...
...in order to ensure he remains hidden...
Did he give us this escort mission...
...so that he could personally eliminate his own daughter?!
Bruno Buccellati was born the son of
a fisherman in a suburb of Naples.
His father was never much of a people person...
...but he was an earnest and honest fisherman
who tried to protect his family from the cruelties of the world.
Bruno.
Dad.
You need me to fix the net?
Got it.
His mother was a kind woman,
and Buccellati loved the conversations he had with her.
He eagerly looked forward to the
bedtime stories she read him before he slept.
All right, it's time to sleep.
But...
Something happened when Buccellati was seven years old.
So what are you going to do about it?
Well... I'm looking for change,
so I want to leave this town.
After ten years of marriage,
his parents divorced.
As for why, only his parents could tell you that.
What are we going to do about Bruno?
After talking it out among themselves,
Buccellati's parents decided to let him decide.
Bruno, your father and I both love you very much...
...but we're going to be living apart from now on.
Who would you like to live with?
Me or your father?
We'd like you to decide.
You want to leave this place
and go to the city with me, right?
You're a smart boy.
You'd like to go to a good school, wouldn't you?
You'll meet so many more children your age there!
So you'll come live with me, right?
Won't you?
I...
...want to live with Dad.
What?!
Bruno, you should really think about this!
You like me better, don't you?
I'm staying here with Dad.
No...
Mom is strong...
She should be able to make it anywhere.
But...
All right, I'm leaving.
I'll come back once a month to visit.
Okay.
As Buccellati's gut feeling at the time warned him,
his mother remarried to a man from Milan two years after leaving.
From then on,
he only ever saw his mother at Christmas time.
His father, determined after his wife left him for the city,
did his best to send Buccellati to a good school.
Dad, I think we'll get some customers soon.
Oh, I guess it's about that time...
I'll reapply the nets.
All right. I'll let you handle it.
Though he had been nothing more than a fisherman until this point,
in order to earn money for his son's tuition...
...he began taking tourists and other fishermen on his boat whenever he had time to spare.
And the wheel of fate continued to turn.
Sirs, that island isn't good for fishing.
There are better-
Whatever!
That's where we wanna go fishing.
So just shut up and take us.
We clear?
R-Right...
That evening, Buccellati's father was rescued by the Coast Guard,
his body riddled with bullet holes.
He's sustained seven bullet wounds to his arms,
shoulders, chest, and torso.
We need an operating room open!
Dad! Dad!
Not all of the bullets passed through.
Dad!
For now, please just wait until his surgery is over.
Be strong.
Do you have contact information for anyone else in your family?
Dad...
Forensics is dropping by later,
so give them this as evidence.
Yes, sir.
Thanks.
Right.
H-How did this happen?
Evening, son.
Is he your father?
We found this at the scene.
Apparently, your father witnessed a drug deal going down.
They shot him up so he wouldn't speak.
Your father is an important witness in this case.
We'd rather he not die, either.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Dad was shot because of something like that?
Luckily, Buccellati's father survived.
Despite being shot seven times,
none of the wounds were fatal...
...and the boat that found and rescued him
happened to have supplies to treat his wounds...
...which allowed him to survive
until he reached the hospital.
He was graced by good luck all around.
But in terms of Buccellati's life,
it may have been better if he had died.
There are certain difficult situations
where an opportunity to follow the right path isn't presented.
Fishermen are way too damn tough, shit!
I'll keep watch!
Just hurry and finish him!
You got a lot of nerve
making us come out here at night...
Now go to hell!
Wh-Who the fuck are you?
A k-kid? H-Hey!
What were you doing under the bed?
It's just a fucking kid!
Grab the knife!
Th-That knife's dangerous!
Put it down!
Wh-What are you-
I'll protect you, Dad.
Don't worry.
Take your time getting better.
At the age of twelve, Bruno Buccellati committed murder
and entered a world no one should ever set foot in.
I can't turn back now.
They'll keep trying to get revenge and shut us up.
I can't trust the police, either.
The only protection afforded to him and his father was
an organization that controlled the city from the shadows.
Buccellati knocked on the doors of that organization.
And in return for his service and undying loyalty...
...they guaranteed his family's safety.
Believing the organization to be the true form of justice, he worked hard there.
He made a name for himself within the organization,
before the capo Polpo eventually took a liking to him.
Five years later, Buccellati's father died
due to complications from his wounds.
Buccellati loathed the white powder of greed
that had dragged him and his father into this situation...
...and swore that he would never forgive it.
But...
I-I'm sorry!
I won't bother them again!
I'll forget about that family!
Good.
Not like you'll be able to regret it once you're dead.
If you're also a gangster-
Those are...!
Hey!
What the hell is that?!
He learned that the organization's boss, a man whom he thought
embodied justice, was involved in dealing the drugs he despised.
In this city?
I thought they were forbidden!
And now...
Now the boss is...
The most heinous form of evil...
...is to knowingly exploit the innocent for personal gain!
A father did this to his innocent daughter...
...all to cover his own ass?!
Unforgivable!
Twice now you've betrayed my heart!
There!
Trish is still alive.
All right. It held.
But damn, I can't see his face.
Boss, my original plan was just to uncover your identity,
but things have changed.
I'm going to eliminate you here and now!
I don't have time...
...but the boss won't be
expecting me to betray him so suddenly.
This will be...
...an assassination.
I'll get ahead of the boss on
his escape route and finish him there.
This...
This hole...
I see.
It's the stairway to the charnel house
like you'd find in the basement of any church.
Once he's eliminated Trish down there
and thinks he's in the clear...
...he'll make his escape
through the other side of the building.
I managed to get here first.
Here he comes.
He came down the stairs!
Now!
You would be wise to leave this place...
...Bruno Buccellati.
If you step out from behind that pillar...
...you will die.
Sticky Fingers!
I-It's going to break off!
So he knew I was after him...
But since he hid himself again...
...I can only assume he isn't very powerful.
I'd like to know your motive here.
What is the meaning of this?
I've had the utmost respect
for your work on this mission thus far.
Did the joy of becoming a capo
not satiate your greed?
Or has your hubris fooled you into believing you could get the better of me?
When Trish wakes up...
...I'm going to tell her
that she never had a father.
Trish?
What about Trish?
My daughter has nothing to do with you.
You'll never understand
what I feel within my heart!
Giorno?
Buccellati!
Yes, I know he's on the move.
I know exactly where the brooch
you put on the boss's body is.
Right now, he's at the bottom of the stairs
leading to the charnel house.
He's right near the pillar that's
about two meters away from the stairs.
But wait, Buccellati!
Something tells me... you're in trouble!
There you are!
Take this!
Sticky Fingers!
The one who was in the pillar's shadow...
...was me!
Wh-What...
What's going o-
I've shown you this... as a parting gift.
Since this is the end,
I'll enlighten you.
What you just saw and felt
was yourself from the future.
You from several seconds in the past
just witnessed your future self.
That is my King Crimson's ability.
It erased time, then leapt past it.
No matter who dares try...
...I will not allow my
enduring dominance to be disrupted.
I must ensure that you disappear without a trace.
Buccellati, your mission to escort Trish...
...has come to an end.
The Mystery of King Crimson