What are you looking for here?
I've no intention of telling you!
I see.
Very well.
There's always the other two.
I just need the last one standing to tell me.
You're finished! Take this!
I hear footsteps...
Someone is running outside the mirror.
Could it be that your friends abandoned you,
prioritizing finding whatever it is you came here for?
They're headed for the dog mosaic.
I'm sure of it.
Well, Fugo, seeing as how
you're pretty much dead...
...I'm gonna go take
whatever's over there first!
W-Wait, dammit!
Abbacchio... Giorno...
Where is it? Where's the key?
There! That's it!
A mirror?
Was that here this whole time?
What's that? A key?
What?
I see.
I guess I'll just have to take it from you.
That's... It couldn't be...
Now that you've seen me...
...it's curtains for you, too!
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 13  Man in the Mirror and Purple Haze
Sh-Shit!
Fuck...
I think I'm starting to understand the enemy's ability.
So he's inside the mirror...
If that's even possible, then...
...Fugo must have disappeared by
being dragged into the mirror.
That somehow separated him from his Stand.
Anyway, right now I need to get the key!
Shattering the mirror actually
worked in my favor, Abbacchio.
Any reflective object becomes
an entrance to this world.
Now that it's in shards,
I have even more entrances to grab you from!
So I'll give you, and only you,
permission to come inside the mirror!
There! You're in.
The key is mine!
Wh-What?!
O-Only a Stand can grab
another Stand's neck.
You're the only one I dragged in here,
and you couldn't possibly have grabbed Man in the Mirror...
Shattering the mirror
didn't work in your favor at all!
All it meant is that you had
a worse view of the outside world!
You didn't get a good look at
what you dragged in here, did you?
You only gave permission...
...for me to enter?
Th-That's...!
Grazie!
I'm glad you dragged me in!
Moody Blues!
Dammit! That's a Stand!
Inside the mirror...
So it's a world where everything's flipped.
We never could have known.
It wasn't until you attacked us
that we had any chance of understanding your ability.
Fugo must be in here, too.
So, how do we get out of here?
If I have to kill you to get out of here, that's fine.
That's why I sent Moody Blues inside!
The ability to mimic how people look...
Well, shit. You got me.
Looks like your Stand itself isn't very strong.
Is it only good at
beating on normal people?
Well, what's the hold up?
Get up! Bring it on!
Listen here...
Like I said from the beginning, you're as good as dead.
I'll admit, dragging your Stand in
caught me off guard...
...but this changes nothing!
I'm not crouching here because I want to.
I'm doing it because I have to!
Yeah, no shit.
You're crouching so I can kick you easier.
I was crouching so I could pick up this mirror shard!
Hey, why do you look so surprised?
Is it the arm?
I'm sure you know exactly whose arm this is!
Like I said, any reflective object
becomes an entrance!
If I catch your reflection
with another shard...
...it becomes another entrance!
Get it now?
This is your arm I dragged inside!
Just to make sure you stop moving,
I'm only allowing half your body inside.
And as for your Stand,
I'll only let half of it out!
Now your Stand won't be able to move, either!
The key is mine!
Shit. He's gonna take the key!
We're not only gonna fail to
carry out our orders...
...but Giorno is gonna be right!
I respectfully refuse!
We will solve this mystery,
rescue Fugo, then defeat the enemy!
That's the only way to ensure our safety!
Shit!
My pride can't take a hit like that!
I can't let him have that key!
I swear on my pride and dignity that I,
Leone Abbacchio, will protect this key at any cost!
Yes, Man in the Mirror has to focus all its energy
when dragging someone into the mirror...
...so its destructive power is weak.
That much is true!
But if I do this,
I won't need any strength to kill you in an instant!
Even a four-year-old would be
strong enough to end you. It's too easy!
I win!
Thanks for telling me where the key i-
What's wrong?
Finish me off, already!
What the hell are you playing at, Abbacchio?
Trying to hide it like
some kind of smartass!
Even if you could move with your fucked up body,
you wouldn't get anywhere!
I'll figure out where you hid it!
Got that?
Hide?
What are you talking about?
What exactly did I hide, and where?
What the hell are you doing?
Show me your hand!
Seriously, what the hell are you doing?!
Lose something?
Did you find what you were looking for? Huh?
Why did he do that to his own hand?
Wait... If he chopped off his own hand...
...that means his Stand's hand
outside the mirror...
That's impossible...
Its hand is gone!
Don't tell me...
I-It has the key!
And it's going back!
If I recall, the new guy, Giorno,
is right around the corner!
He severed his hand
to bring his friend the key?
You should have slit my throat
when you had the chance.
At least that way my Stand's hand
would have stopped moving.
Whoops, almost had it.
Now you're too late.
That was the sound of the key
falling to the ground.
It's gonna get picked up!
That's some bullshit
you managed to pull off!
But I won't let that Giorno brat get away!
I'll drag him in here, too!
Do you get it now,
Giorno, you fucking idiot?
All that matters now
is that one of us returns safely.
If you can return safely with the key...
Carrying out our orders is
more important than anything.
Hey, Abbacchio...
Wanna take a guess
what's going on over here?
Your friend here's a real nice guy.
After you worked so hard
to get the key to him...
Care to guess what he's doing right now?
Not a damn thing!
The brat's not moving a muscle!
He has no idea what's going on, does he?
Giorno!
Get the hell out of here!
Take the key and run!
He can't hear you screaming
from inside the mirror!
F-Fuck...
At this point, there are two ways I can go about this.
I could dispose of Giorno
after I get the key from him...
...or I can slit his throat and
safely take it from him.
Let me think...
Guess I'm gonna slit his throat first!
He noticed me!
I'll allow only Giorno's body to enter!
I dragged him in!
Slit his throat, Man in the Mirror!
Wh-Wh-What?!
H-He... That's impossible!
It's the virus!
Th-That means Giorno...
...was infected by Fugo's Purple Haze!
I'll never give you the key!
And Fugo and Abbacchio
will safely return to the others!
Pannacotta Fugo
Purple Haze
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: E
Precision: E
Growth Potential: B
Giorno Giovanna...
That brat is fucking clueless!
Purple Haze's virus will kill him for sure!
My heart died with my partner
all those years ago.
I don't feel anything anymore.
Even after losing my hand,
I still don't feel a damn thing...
The only time I ever feel at ease...
...is when I'm following orders
for a greater cause.
I can play the soldier and
follow them without thinking.
Which is why...
...we have to retrieve the key
and protect the boss's daughter.
Following those orders is more important
than anything right now.
And yet Giorno...
That fucking brat...
He chose to put himself in danger to save Fugo and I
instead of safely bringing back the key!
Fuck you, you goddamn brat!
Why would you come in here infected?
Are you insane?!
Now I'm infected, too, goddammit!
Ah, yes.
We appear to be experiencing the same symptoms.
Apparently Purple Haze's virus infects
the entire body within thirty seconds.
It's over now.
This ended the moment you dragged me in.
Those mirror shards Purple Haze shattered...
Did Giorno put them back together?
When the enemy went after Abbacchio,
he took some shards with him.
Giorno must have realized that!
He used that information to
deduce the enemy's ability...
...infected himself with the virus...
...then let himself be
dragged inside the mirror!
That was the only way he could beat him!
Shit! Of all the dirty...
But you shouldn't have underestimated me...
It's not too late...
I'll have to resolve myself,
but it's still not too late!
Man in the Mirror!
Allow only me to leave!
But don't allow the virus!
The part of me that's infected
isn't allowed to leave!
This is bad!
If he makes it outside,
he'll be separated from the virus!
Abbacchio cut off
his own hand to get that key...
...so I, Illuso, c-can do the same thing!
This is nothing!
Giorno! Restrain him!
He escaped...
Giorno... After you...
...risked your own life coming here...
So... he left the mirror.
Th-That was a close one, but I did it!
My... My resolve won out in the end!
This is nothing!
I suspected he would go outside.
It's for the best.
He would have been defeated one way or another.
The fact that he went outside means
there's a chance I'll live!
Fugo! Now that he's outside,
Purple Haze can follow him!
Finish him off!
I can't, Giorno...
I can't tell where he is from in here...
I have no way to attack him!
I know where he is.
Gold Experience is still outside.
It turned that brick into a snake.
That's why it's moving.
Snakes can pinpoint where humans are
via their body temperature.
Got him!
What?!
A-After I built up the resolve to
sacrifice my own arm and come out here...
This... This can't...!
S-Stop it! Stop! Shit!
I'm going to get infected!
I-If that virus capsule bursts...
L-Luck hasn't completely abandoned me!
If Man in the Mirror can stop
this thing's punch for just a moment...
If I can block it just once...
Give him hell, Purple Haze!
Man in the Mirror!
Give it everything you've got!
I...
I did it...
I stopped it!
Now I just need to take its arm...
...into the mirror!
Huh?
What?!
B-But I blocked its punch...
After I built up the resolve...
and came out of the mirror!
W-We did it!
We're outside the mirror!
We defeated him and negated his ability!
B-But Giorno...
Purple Haze's virus is already spreading through your body.
Now that you're infected, I can't help you.
Yes, Fugo. But it all worked out.
I mean...
I'm glad he left the mirror.
The moment he dragged
the virus and I into the mirror...
...his fate was sealed.
The fact that he refused to accept defeat
and came outside was a pure stroke of luck.
Since the mirror world
was negated before I died...
...I was able to meet this snake.
Th-That snake...
Even though it's surrounded by
Purple Haze's virus, it's still alive!
This snake was born from a brick
near where one of Purple Haze's capsules broke.
Since it was born in an environment
teeming with the virus, it can't be infected.
Do you understand what this means?
The snake has natural immunity!
And if we take blood or cells
from something with immunity...
...we can formulate a serum
that will halt the spread of the virus!
Gold Experience!
Extract the serum from the snake
and inject me with it!
Giorno Giovanna...
I saw him as nothing more than
a new guy I couldn't quite pin...
...but he comes up with insane ideas
and manages to pull them off...
Something about it
gives me confidence in him.
It's not something I can put into words...
He's someone I can truly trust!
Just like Buccellati way back then!
Giorno!
I commend you for putting your life at risk!
No, Fugo...
I'm not the one who risked my life here.
I just made a prediction
and followed through...
The one who truly risked their life here...
was Abbacchio.
His hand is in grave condition right now.
He, more than either of us,
was determined to protect the key at the cost of his own life...
And if he hadn't brought the key
all the way over here...
...we couldn't have defeated the enemy.
Don't worry about me...
Go tend to his wounds...
Giorno!
Giorno, are you okay?
Jesus, Giorno...
I was planning...
to beat the shit out of you...
Guess I can't now with my hand like this...
I'll have to do it later...
They retrieved the key as ordered!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
The Express Train
Bound for Florence