I should be able to meet up with
Melone in about an hour.
Ghiaccio, I'll leave the situation to you and Melone.
You can never be too careful.
I'll stay back and try to figure out
where they're headed based on their journey so far.
Got it, Risotto.
How much longer are you going to make me wait?
Hurry up.
Restoring this should be trivial for you.
Risotto...
Do you really think you can
get away with betraying Passione?
We're running short on time.
Your left eye is next.
You only need a single hand and eye to work.
Y-You should know better than anyone!
All traitors, without exception,
will be erased by the boss...
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 18  Onward to Venice!
Wh-What?!
The hand I severed became
a living creature and invaded your body!
As you can see, it became a piranha!
It has a large hole in its torso
going up to its neck...
...yet it can still move?
Wh-What's wrong, Babyface?
Answer me! Hey!
This is tortoise shit...
This is actual shit left behind by the tortoise!
Why am I the one
who has to deal with this?
Dammit!
This pain in my heart...
You'll pay for this...
...by dying in disgrace!
I'll make sure of it!
If Buccellati and Trish won't
return to normal unless I defeat you...
...then that's what I'll do!
You can't escape!
I'm going for your head this time!
Just try me...
...you son of a bitch!
Dickhead
I'll kill you...
Go ahead and try it...
This is bad...
The downside to its automatic tracking
is that it doesn't always listen to me.
Asshole!
You've already gouged out
three pieces of my body...
I know the range of your attack!
Did its range...
...just extend itself?!
He grew taller?
His anger must have caused him to grow!
Di molto!
I knew that woman was
the right person to be his mother!
Simple is best.
I'm gonna kill this asshole my way!
Bring it back, Gold Experience!
Die!
Muda!
A direct hit.
Take a good look.
You didn't hit my head!
I win! It's over!
I told you, it's pointless.
Wh-What the hell?!
Look again.
The object that returned to
Gold Experience wasn't its own hand.
It was the motorcycle.
I imbued the motorcycle with life
and had it return as a hand.
You just assimilated the
motorcycle into your body...
...as a part of you.
This is nothing...
I'll just split apart and get away aga-
Think about it...
Motorcycles contain gasoline.
I'm fairly certain I can create a large enough explosion
to prevent you from escaping by splitting yourself apart.
What?!
Sizzling... Burning...
It seems as though doing things
your way was pointless... in the end.
Burn burn burn burn ...ing...!
I-It disappeared?
My contact with it disappeared?!
Damn! This is absurd!
That new guy!
He did it...
It should be somewhere around here...
My car's gone!
Where's my car? Who stole it?!
That's Melone's motorcycle...
I was told to ask around,
dig up whatever dirt will help me find them...
The digging part I get.
It makes perfect sense.
It's like digging for stuff hidden in the ground.
But why the flying fuck
would you dig up dirt?!
Dirt is fucking everywhere!
Jesus fuck!
What fucking bullshit is that?!
Who the fuck digs up dirt looking for dirt?!
Do I look fucking retarded?!
Goddammit!
Hey, Melone!
I can't find shit on Buccellati and his crew!
You getting this? Hello?!
I can hear you.
But I'm not giving up just yet!
I still have Buccellati's blood!
I can produce as many Juniors as we need!
I'll send one in pursuit right away!
You'd better, Melone.
We need to take the new guy more seriously.
He should be the first one we eliminate.
I'll find an even better mother...
...and create a powered-up, completely invincible...
...Junior who will track them down.
What was that?
It looked like a snake...
What? What's wrong?
What is a snake doing at a station in Rome?
I-It's burning!
This is... the new guy's ability...
He must have used the Junior's corpse to-
Hello?
Hey, Melone!
What the fuck?! Hey!
The venomous snake I sent to Roma Termini Station
just turned back into part of the enemy.
The user is eliminated.
That makes five.
If our intel is correct,
only two members of the Hitman Team remain.
We still gotta be careful.
Now let's get to Venice already!
Now Melone, too?
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Hello?!
It's me.
I managed to finish the analysis.
I'm sending you the data as we speak.
We just received a new order from the boss.
Abbacchio, could you come over here next to the chair?
Me?
Here's the order.
"Have Abbacchio use his Moody Blues
near the dining chair and rewind to just over 14 hours ago."
Someone else was inside the tortoise before us.
I believe that's what he's getting at.
Got it.
I'll start looking from about fifteen hours ago.
It transformed.
Hey, that old dude looks familiar!
That's the capo, Mr. Pericolo!
So he was the one who placed the tortoise near the water fountain at Naples Station.
And approximately fourteen hours ago,
he entered this tortoise.
I'm continuing the replay.
Buccellati and team,
I will now give you your final order.
Final order?
I'm using this method to give you the message
in order to prevent it from falling into the wrong hands.
What I'm about to tell you is of utmost importance and must remain between us.
I'm going to tell you how to
hand Trish off to the boss.
How we're going...
...to hand her over?
Listen closely, now.
Once you've safely arrived in Venice...
...go to this sculpture and retrieve
the OA-DISC that's inside.
It contains data that will instruct you on how to hand her over.
Hey! He burned it!
Abbacchio, pause it!
Right.
I'm pretty sure this is
the entrance to Venice...
Right in front of Santa Lucia Station.
The lion statue is there.
That is all.
Obtain the OA-DISC at all costs.
My identity has been compromised.
Nothing is more important right now
than bringing Trish to her father, the boss.
No evidence can be left behind.
Thanks to the boss, I've been able to live a wealthy, blessed, and fulfilling life.
My mission is over.
From the bottom of my heart,
I pray for your success.
What the hell?!
Mr. Pericolo...
They should have received the order by now.
Obtaining the disc, let alone reaching me,
will prove difficult for them.
The most important thing is
what awaits at the end...
Bring my daughter Trish here...
...to Venice.
The fortress city of the sea,
floating amidst the morning haze: Venice.
There is only one way to get there
by car from the mainland.
It is a bridge which stretches for 3.5 kilometers
over the sea known as the Ponte della Libertà.
The station lies just beyond it.
The lion statue where the target disc is hidden
can be found in a square there.
Giorno, so far I haven't seen anyone tailing us.
Yes. No one in front of us, either.
The city is still asleep.
We're the only car on the road.
Why do the windows keep fogging up so quickly?
What the hell?!
My apologies.
The tires just slipped a bit.
On a straight bridge like this?
Try to be more careful!
Do you even have a license?
No. I'm only fifteen.
What's that thing stuck on the window?
It's on the inside.
I didn't notice it when
I was looking outside earlier...
No, wait a second...
That shape...
It's... a finger!
Let's open the windows a bit.
The windows are fogging up from the
temperature difference inside and out of the car.
Wh-What?!
What's with this wind pressure?!
At first, we were frozen with fear... But...
With the help of a computer, it wasn't too hard to recreate the ashes that were lying next to Pericolo in the photo.
You guys fucking clueless!
You'll never get away from the Hitman Team!
It's an enemy!
They got on the roof of the car without us realizing it!
Mista, what are you doing?
Shoot the enemy through the roof!
The car is being chilled crazy fast right now...
It's so fast that my finger froze to the window and snapped off before I even felt the cold.
If I don't peel my face off the window,
my brain will freeze up.
Not sure I'm ready to sacrifice my face, though.
Where's the tortoise?
I don't see the tortoise in the car.
You two aren't with Trish and Buccellati?
If you went through the trouble of splitting up...
I got it!
You must be on a mission
to get something really important!
The location in the picture...
It has to be at the station in Venice!
Blood finally spurted from my hand!
Yeehaw!
I-Ice!
He covered himself in ice and
froze himself to the roof of the car!
The bullets can't get through to him!
What the...?!
N-No!
We're starting to freeze, too!
Save me!
Number Two!
Don't go!
Number Three!
What?!
A-All I did was blink,
and now my eyelashes are stuck together!
He must have positioned himself
on the roof on purpose!
The car is currently going
eighty kilometers per hour.
Which means...
It's similar to being stuck in
twenty meter per second wind.
The effective temperature drops by 1° Celsius
for every meter of wind velocity...
...so the air around us has chilled to -20° Celsius!
Then stop the damn car!
Why the hell are you still flooring it?!
Yes. I'm trying to...
But the brake pedal is frozen and won't go down!
I'm losing the steering wheel, too!
The engine is still running and seemingly won't stop!
The surface of the car has to have
reached -100° Celsius by now!
And at incredible speed!
So this is... the enemy's ability!
Th-The blood that was spurting out of my hand froze...
And the moisture from my breathing
caused my nostrils to freeze together...
And now my lips...
Shit! I can't breathe!
S-Stop the car, Giorno!
Can't you can turn the car
into a frog or something?!
Use your ability somehow!
I've already tried that...
But there are no organisms
that can be born at -100° Celsius!
You know about Paris, France?
In English, they pronounce it "Paris"...
But everyone else pronounces it
without the "s" sound, like the French do.
But with Venezia, everyone pronounces
it the English way, "Venice".
As in, The Merchant of Venice
and Death in Venice...
Why isn't the title Death in Venezia?!
Are they fucking mocking me?!
Use the Italian word
since it takes place here, fuckheads!
This shit pisses me off!
Are they seriously fucking mocking me?!
Fucking morons!
Looks like they're starting
to have trouble driving...
Mista...
My Gold Experience needs heat.
So unfortunately, the most I can do for you...
...is pick up these bullets...
You won't be able to fill the car
with any more holes!
I'll just freeze you to an even lower temp-
Bullets create heat from being fired, don't they?
So by firing the bullets Giorno picked up for me...
...I'm making heat!
I guess I'll go ahead and
do the honors for Giorno while I'm at it...
Gold Experience!
We did it!
Plant roots have the energy to prop up
asphalt in roads and even shatter rocks!
Keep hold of the steering wheel, Giorno!
We're gonna make a break for it!
So that must be the new guy's ability Melone mentioned.
But you're not getting away!
Seriously? What an asshole!
He's still coming after us!
I, Ghiaccio, will be taking
whatever's at the station, no matter what.
You're wasting your bullets.
My ability, White Album, freezes the moisture in the air
to an extremely low temperature, letting me wear it like armor!
Not only does it allow me to skate,
it also gives me enough power to shrug off your pathetic bullets!
Step on it, Giorno!
I can't go any faster!
The tires are still slipping!
But worst of all, they know our plan!
They don't know where the tortoise and Trish are...
...so if you look on the bright side,
we're not totally fucked.
Optimistic as usual, aren't you?
You're a strange man.
He's coming!
Floor it! Faster!
I told you, I can't!
If we slip, we'll lose even more sp-
Just do it, dammit!
Floor it!
I told you, you're wasting your time!
Number Three and Number Two
up on the roof, come back!
Here's hoping you share a long kiss...
...with Madame Concrete.
All the speed you've built up should make it extra passionate!
Yeah!
Good. We lost him!
Now get us into the city
and head straight for the station!
Before he can catch up to us,
we'll get our hands on the disc and hide!
Giorno!
You're not getting away!
There's no way you fucks are
making it to the station!
He's freezing the moisture from the car's exhaust!
What kind of temperature do you
have to freeze it at to do that shit?
Asshole!
Have another taste of lead!
He opened the trunk!
That means...
Sh-Shit! He got into the trunk!
Stop the car, Giorno!
He's gonna freeze up the brake pedal
so we can't stop again!
There's no need for that...
...Gunslinger Mista.
This was my plan all along
if I didn't find Trish here.
Shatter into-
G-Giorno!
It only cracked?
Is he invincible?
How can I destroy this armor?
Giorno!
Get away from him!
No! Not yet!
We made it to Venice!
I'm diving into the canal!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
White Album