This isn't right...
It actually lit up again...
Something is wrong here!
You reignited the lighter, didn't you?
It can't be! You villain!
What are you doing?!
This soul...
...was not one worthy of being chosen.
"Worthy of being chosen"?
H-Hey, are you...?
He's dead...
Uninjured, but dead...
You, too, reignited the lighter, did you not?
You shall be given one chance.
Two paths lie before you.
So anyone who witnesses the lighter
being reignited is indiscriminately attacked?
I-It's...!
Did it just tear my soul out
through my shadow?
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
You shall be given one chance.
Two paths lie before you.
Episodio 04  Joining the Gang
The first path leads to the life of a chosen one.
It's no use...
This thing is stronger than Gold Experience...
That old man died after
his soul was pierced by the arrow.
So what will happen to me...
...if it attacks my Stand?
The other leads to your demise.
Th-This arrow...
If it stabs me with the arrow, I won't survive!
I have no choice!
Though Polpo may be one of the capos,
if he thinks he can stand between me and my dream...
...and kill innocent people like that old man
as if they were nothing more than waste...
...then I must defeat him!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Gold Experience...
Your senses alone will go berserk,
and all movements will appear slow to you.
It's gone! Impossible!
It should still be out of control.
Even if it were able to move,
it would be incredibly slow.
It couldn't have disappeared!
It must be here somewhere...
It has to be!
I need to find it before it
breaks free from its slowed perception of time...
...or it will strike again...
What?!
I-In the shadows?! N-No!
It's moving slower,
but it hasn't lost its strength!
I can't move a muscle!
The shadows!
It really is in the shadows!
It can move through the shadows
at incredible speed!
It doesn't seem capable of
following me into the sunlight.
But the sun is going to set
on the other side of the school soon...
When that happens,
I'll have nowhere to run.
What will happen if I force it into the sunlight?
It's worth a try.
But how can I drag it out?
What should I do?
It's standing right there...
...waiting for the sun to set...
...with no incentive to rush.
You!
What are you up to, Giorno Giovanna?!
Koichi!
Why is there someone collapsed
at the bottom of the stairs?!
What did you do to him?!
Hey, you have it wrong!
That wasn't me!
The Stand right here atta-
I have it wrong?
I saw you talking to him earlier!
I was watching from the window!
You were... watching?
Then... did you see him ignite the lighter, too?
Huh?
Don't step into the shadow
of the handrail, Koichi!
Stay away from the shadows!
I-It's too late!
You witnessed the lighter being relit, did you not?
Two paths lie before you.
The first path leads to the life of a chosen one.
Wh-What's going on...?
The other leads to your demise.
This arrow!
Gold Experience!
The pain is unbearable...
It hurts a lot, but thanks to it...
...I found a way to drag it into the sunlight.
I turned the handrail into morning glories
and made them droop downward...
...which forced it out from the shadows!
Almost got it!
It managed to escape in a nearby shadow.
But if I can find a way to
drag it out of the shadows completely...
...I should be able to beat it.
Wh-What was...
What was with that Stand?!
If it wasn't obvious, we're under attack.
The old man who
reignited the lighter was killed.
Because you and I witnessed it...
...we've become the targets
of that thing's attack.
That's not what I meant.
That arrow...
It's from the Bow and Arrow!
I can't believe there's one in Italy, too...
What are you doing, Giorno Giovanna?!
Are you the reason another Stand
with the arrow appeared?!
I don't have time to explain...
But I swear I know nothing about it.
Do you know anything about this Stand?
Or about the arrow?
Why did you save me?
Please just answer me about the arrow!
The sun is about to set!
Why did you save me?!
I don't owe anything to a thief like you!
My actions were what led to
the lighter being reignited.
There was nothing I could do
to help that old man.
I'm truly crestfallen...
In my heart I know I'm doing the right thing,
but I feel disgusted with myself.
Yet in spite of that...
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a righteous dream!
Two years ago, I was struck by an arrow like that one
and gained my Stand ability.
If you're struck by the arrow
and an ability doesn't awaken within you, you die.
Awaken within you?
That's it!
That's what it meant when it said
"worthy of being chosen"!
One whose Stand has awakened!
That must be the motive behind Polpo's test!
I don't know the origin of the arrow...
...but I've encountered this same
type of Stand once before.
It's a long-range, remote controlled Stand!
Long-range and remote controlled?
It can only do predetermined,
simple actions, but...
...it won't stop attacking until
it's done what it was instructed.
Our best bet is to find its user
and take them down.
Unfortunately, that's impossible.
Its user is imprisoned.
There's simply no way.
Anyway...
It can't leave the shadow
of the school building right now...
...so let's circle around to
the other side while we still can.
Once we're there, before the sun completely sets...
...we'll lure it into the shadow of a moving object...
...then quickly get rid of it.
That will force it into direct sunlight.
Got it!
I-It's gone!
I have you!
Wh-What?!
You witnessed the lighter being relit, did you not?
The crows!
It left the shadow of the school building
by hiding in the shadows of those flying crows!
Th-That's...
Pointless!
N-No!
It really is faster and stronger
in the shadows!
Act 3! 3 Freeze!
My Echoes Act 3 has the ability to
make Stands and other things heavier!
I have made its hands heavier...
...so that it will be unable to lift
even a finger from the ground.
Its fingers should give out at any second!
I made both of its hands heavier!
It shouldn't be able to
bend its fingers anymore!
I-It's so strong...
It's determined to hold onto me
no matter what!
Two paths lie before you.
I-It's no use!
Any damage inflicted on a Stand
goes right back to its user!
If this keeps up,
Giorno's legs are gonna shatter!
Act 3! Undo 3 Freeze...
No.
Don't do that, Koichi.
Your ability to make things heavier...
Don't you dare undo it.
This is what I needed.
This ability you've brought with you
is just what I needed!
But your leg's gonna break!
Wh-What?
That tree...
Gold Experience has the ability to
continuously imbue objects with life...
...so it made the tree live
a full life until it withered.
Ability?
But that tree is at least
ten meters away...
Did you dig a hole to
touch the tree's roots?
Y-You did it!
The shadow is gone!
You dragged it out into the sunlight!
You said two paths lay before me...
...but for you, there's only one.
Excuse me Koichi,
but could you move a bit to the right?
Huh? Like this?
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Bask in the sunlight!
That was your only way forward!
Your one and only path.
I wonder if I'll be
allowed in the gang after all this...
What to do...
Power: E
Speed: A
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Polpo
Black Sabbath
That arrow...
The fact that there's an arrow in Italy
means there will be even more victims!
I need to tell Mr. Jotaro!
Wh-What are you doing?
Did you just say there will be more?
Polpo's Stand had the arrow,
and we defeated it.
You saw it yourself.
Defeated?
You couldn't be more wrong!
I'll admit we were able to
escape its attacks thanks to you...
...but the only reason it stopped was
because it was forced into the sunlight.
The user wasn't hurt at all!
They're fine!
So Polpo is still alive?
Not only is he still alive, but we probably didn't even
hurt him since he has a long-ranged, remote controlled Stand.
I doubt he even knows
there was a battle here.
What?!
So he really doesn't know what happened?
He doesn't know I'm a Stand user?
Enough questions!
If anything, he only would have
noticed his hands getting heavier...
...but there's no way he could have figured out
that you and I are already Stand users.
So excuse me,
but can you please move your finger?
I'm sorry,
but I can't allow you to make that call.
I'm begging you...
This isn't about a single enemy.
He's part of an organization.
If you tell someone,
the organization may find out.
Enemy?
Organization?
You're the only person
I'll speak of this to, Koichi.
The Next Day
Someone delivered me a special-order pizza.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Let's see, your name was...
Giorno... Giorno, uh...
Giorno Giovanna.
Ah, yes. My apologies.
Eating tends to make me lightheaded.
I think all the blood in my body
rushes to my stomach.
This may seem like an odd question,
but are you a man of faith, Giorno?
Well... I wouldn't say I'm particularly devout.
What I'm about to tell you
may go against God's word...
...but I would appreciate it
if you heeded my words.
If the most important thing
in the world is trustworthiness...
...then the most despicable thing
one can do is abuse that trust.
Hear me well.
To abuse one's trust...
...not only harms your reputation,
but causes you to adopt a lifestyle...
...that will push you into a corner
from which you will never escape.
We never fight others and
risk our lives over money, power...
...or even something as simple as
having your seat taken at the theater or on a bus.
Fighting is a foolish game
good only for preoccupying idiots.
However...
I would risk my life
if my trust were abused.
I believe that in such cases,
God forgives even murder.
Never forget that.
Congratulations!
I'm permitting you to join our organization!
Since you brought back the ignited lighter
as I trusted you would...
...you pass.
This is the badge of our organization, Passione.
A token proving you passed.
For now, you're to operate
under Buccellati's orders.
How about it?
Why don't we celebrate your...
Did that kid really protect the flame
for twenty-four hours?
Or did he reignite it
and become a Stand user?
I suppose it doesn't matter either way.
Clueless young boys like him
are easy to manipulate.
Regardless of the outcome,
we can use him as we please.
Oh?
I could have sworn I closed that...
The blood really does flow to my stomach
after I've eaten...
You encountered him again?
I'm sorry, Mr. Jotaro...
But I can't help but feel that Giorno Giovanna
isn't as dangerous as you think he is.
Why do you say that?
Well...
Well, I'll tell you in person.
Is that okay?
All right.
If that's what you prefer, it's fine.
I'll be waiting.
Thank you.
I'll talk to you later.
Mr. Jotaro, for a while I really wondered...
Could this Giorno kid
really have such aspirations?
Is he sane?
But I can feel it...
I can tell he has a noble heart.
I feel this way...
...because of what I saw in the three men who carried
the Joestar family blood in their veins back in Morioh.
Those three whose righteous hearts
could practically be called their energy.
I saw it in his eyes.
Without a doubt, the blood that flows through his veins
carries the will of the Joestars.
So for now, to respect his wishes,
I'm going to shut away what he told me inside my heart...
That golden dream of Giorno Giovanna's...
Anyway, it's time I go do some sightseeing!
The Next Day
Come with me, Giorno Giovanna.
What was that noise?
Ah, whatever.
When someone abuses your trust,
even murder is forgivable?
I see. You taught me an important lesson.
You abused that innocent old man's life...
...so I changed one of your guns
into a banana.
I hope you savor your last meal.
So... Where are we going?
To meet my team.
They're all Stand users.
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Find Polpo's Fortune!