Hey, mister!
I got one hell of a deal for ya!
I've heard that one before.
I'll even give ya a tour of the city,
free of charge!
Huh? Really?
You're too funny!
Huh? What?
What's wrong?
My purse is gone!
What?
Here, take it.
You had any issues lately?
None at all thanks to you!
Good.
Sorry to bother you.
This'll fix you up, right?
Yeah!
Oh, but this is all I can give you right now.
Then this's all I can sell you.
A city located in Southern Italy: Naples.
A famous tourist hub of such beauty that it is said
you should visit it at least once before you die.
Excuse us!
Can you tell us how to get to
the Church of Santa Chiara?
Oh, you'll find Santa Chiara by
going straight, then taking a-
See? Told you so!
I knew it was that way!
My bad, my bad...
Thank you so-
Easy, now.
Are you hurt?
Th-Thank you...
Umm, sorry about that.
Watch yourself.
Let's go...
Pardon...
You dropped this.
Thank you so much!
It's nothing.
Hey, that guy back there
was pretty cool, wasn't he?
I should have asked for a picture!
Did those butterflies just fly out of my bag?
Huh? They were probably just sitting on it.
Probably!
You should never
let your guard down in this city.
Excuse me.
I'll have a cone with a scoop of
chocolate and pistachio, please.
Make that two.
Coming right up!
Episodio 01  Gold Experience
Hey! How many times do I gotta say you can't work here without a license?
Take a hike!
Typical...
You only moved a single car length ahead!
How about it, sir?
It's faster than waiting in line.
Should we?
I'll get you to the heart of the city real cheap.
Huh? How cheap?
M-Mr. Luca!
Did I not already ask that you
pay your protection fee before doing business here?
Have mercy!
Did I not already make it clear that you had to
pay the protection fee before doing business here again?
But...
Did I not?!
But I have a family...
P-Please don't!
You should put our friendship
above your family!
Got it?
I'm not the only one doing
business behind your back!
Who else?
Give me names.
Giorno!
Giorno Giovanna!
Giorno?
That kid's been making a killing recently!
Well, be that as it may...
Hey, you!
You can't run a business here without a license!
Get out of here!
Buon giorno!
I'm finally here!
That flight took forever!
The air sure feels different here than in Japan!
Anyway, it's time to get to work!
Shiobana Haruno... What a strange name.
Guess I should find my hotel first.
I should drop off my luggage
so I can move around more freely.
Let's see... Where's the taxi line?
Whoa, that's really something!
Didn't I tell ya?
It's one hell of a show!
That doesn't even seem possible!
How the hell are you doing that?
That's so gross!
How the hell does your ear
fit inside your ear hole?
Now that's what I call entertainment!
Thanks.
Anyway, try not to attract
too much attention with that gig of yours.
Need a taxi?
No! N-Not really...
You sure?
I'm just about ready to head home,
so I'll cut you a good deal.
How does 180,000 lire
to get into the city sound?
180,000?
That's about... 10,000 yen.
Way too much!
That's double the basic rate!
Wow, you speak Italian
more fluently than I expected.
Huh?
Did you live in Italy before?
No, I just had Mr. Rohan make it so I could speak...
Well, never you mind!
Back on topic,
you're saying you'll drive me?
You look like you're still in
high school or middle school.
And didn't you just give something
to those security guards?
It looked like money.
What was that all about?
Now, now, you needn't
concern yourself with my affairs.
So, will you accept for 10,000 lire?
No tip necessary.
Into the heart of the city for just 10,000.
Huh? 10,000 would be about... 500 yen?!
N-No, I'm good!
I'll just wait in the taxi line...
Are you sure?
You won't charge me more than 10,000?
Of course not.
All I ask is that you
load the luggage yourself...
...seeing as you aren't tipping.
Put your belongings up front.
You can sit in the back.
I'm warning you, don't underestimate me by thinking
I'm just some naïve Japanese kid who's never traveled.
I just want us to reach my hotel
without any issues.
Sure. We'll arrive without issue...
That is, your empty luggage and I will.
Huh?
Wait... I didn't even get in yet...
You didn't see nothin'!
Don't tell me...
Wait!
Ciao!
Echoes Act 3!
Too bad for you...
Weren't you listening?
I said don't underestimate me.
Run away if you want...
All I care about is getting my stuff back.
Check it out!
Giorno actually fucked up!
That's what he gets for trying to trick a Japanese tourist
when he's half Japanese himself!
Not that anyone would guess he's Japanese
with that kind of hair and a name like Giorno Giovanna.
He couldn't be...
Huh? It's gone! How?!
Is this some kind of egg?
I-Is it a Stand?!
But that's impossible!
I only just arrived in Italy!
It's not a Stand!
The way that frog felt...
It's a real, living creature!
Seriously though,
how did my suitcase disappear?!
He had no time to hide it!
This is bad!
I don't know if I believe it, but...
Excuse me!
Umm, about that taxi driver I was with...
Should be about time...
Are you Giorno Giovanna?
We've never met before, have we?
Giorno, do you know who I am?
"Leaky-eye" Luca.
I heard you kept fighting someone
even after they stabbed you in the face.
Though the wound healed,
your eye is always tearing up, hence the name.
Here, have a seat.
Come on, sit.
Looking up is exhausting.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Fifteen?! You're so young!
You see, Giorno, there are three "don'ts"
I find important for maintaining a good friendship.
Just three "don'ts".
First, don't lie.
Second, don't hold a grudge.
And third, don't show disrespect.
Got that?
Those are the three "don'ts" of friendship.
What do you need of me?
I'm the one doing the talking right now!
Who the hell said
you could ask questions, moron?!
I heard you started a gig
working around the airport...
So tell me why I, "Leaky-eye" Luca,
have been disrespectfully denied my protection fee.
How are we supposed to be friends
with you pulling shit like that?
Let me see your wallet.
Mr. Luca...
I already paid my protection fee.
I'm out of money.
To who, the security guards?!
That has fuck-all to do with me!
What do we have here?
A family photo?
Where's my money?
I want it now!
Hand it over!
Mr. Luca...
Please don't make me repeat myself.
I've already paid, so I don't have it.
Please don't make me say it a third time.
You fucking punk!
What the hell is that thing?
It came back...
Slap it off!
The frog has nothing to do with this.
I won't slap it off.
That's an order!
I told you to pay the protection fee, too!
Are you going to refuse both orders?!
You're going to refuse orders from me,
"Leaky-eye" Luca?!
It's a living creature with
independent thought and free will.
So stay away.
I wouldn't dare slap it off.
You're... You're...
Don't!
It's harmless as long as you don't touch it!
You're fucking finished!
I told you not to.
It isn't fully loyal to me yet.
It's merely protecting itself.
It has its own life to look out for.
Any attack against it
is reflected back to the attacker...
It can cost you your life.
Besides...
I specifically asked that you
not make me repeat myself a third time.
Making me repeat myself
over and over again...
...is pointless.
I hate doing pointless things...
Pointless, pointless...
A piece of this boy's skin?
Yeah.
I want you to bring me a sample, Koichi.
I need the Speedwagon Foundation
to examine it.
Examine it?
Who is this guy?
His late father was
something of a unique case.
That's why we're investigating him.
I don't need much.
Even a small sample will do.
That's all.
Ah...
All of your expenses will be covered.
Huh?! Everything?
I don't mean to be rude...
...but this kid kinda
looks like you, Mr. Jotaro...
The address on the photo
must be somewhere around here...
How careless.
Don't worry about them.
No one around here is foolish enough
to take their briefcase.
Really?
This place must have good security, huh?
Hey, can I sit next to you?
Sir, would you like something to eat?
No, I'm sitting next to him!
N-No, I'm good!
Hey, Giorno! Have some tea with me!
What? Wait, I'll pay for you!
Quiet down, girls.
No, me! Me!
I like sitting alone.
Leave me be.
Fine...
See you tomorrow, Giorno!
Ciao!
Th-That's...!
Hey! Whose money is that?
Are you spending all my money?!
You again?
How did you find me?
Give me back my passport!
Where's my luggage?!
It pains me to say it, but it's gone. I sold it.
Now quit following me.
You're not getting away this time!
Where is this weight coming from?!
Is it possible...
That wasn't a breakdown earlier?
Impossible...
We have the same kind of ability!
What did you just say?
It's too heavy!
Gold Experience!
Come forth, life!
A new life force!
I think I just saw something!
Act 3!
He has disappeared!
That's impossible!
There's no way he could escape
3 Freeze's range so easily!
I'll only say this once more;
don't even think about following me.
I hate repeating myself
when saying things once should suffice.
Repeating oneself is pointless.
I say this for your own well being.
Never take pointless actions.
Knock him down, Act 3!
M-My attack on the tree came back at me...
I took something of yours...
Yet based on the damage you were dealt,
you were clearly holding back.
You're a good person.
It's clear to me now...
Giorno Giovanna...
He's... a Stand user!
Giorno Giovanna
Gold Experience
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: D
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Hello?
Mr. Jotaro, it's Koichi!
Oh, Koichi.
Did you arrive in Italy yet?
I found him!
The guy you asked me to find!
Shiobana Haruno!
That was fast.
Where do I even begin?
I ran into him almost
immediately at the airport...
O-Oh, right.
Long story short...
...he's a Stand user!
He goes by the name
Giorno Giovanna in Italy.
Didn't you say it yourself, Mr. Jotaro?
Stand users are drawn
to other Stand users.
We met by complete coincidence!
He's a student who acts like a gangster.
He stole my luggage and all my money!
And his Stand's ability seems to have something to do with
returning his opponent's attacks right back at them.
I'm sorry that happened.
I'll get you a hotel reservation
and wire you some money.
Thank you.
Also, unlike in the photo,
his hair is blond now.
I asked a few people who knew about him,
and they said he didn't dye it.
It suddenly changed color
not too long ago.
It has something to do with
his late father's genes.
Who exactly is his father?
Do you have some kind of
connection to him?
I'm the one...
...who killed his father.
His name was Dio Brando.
Dio?
You mean the same Dio
involved with the bow and arrow?
This year, I discovered it was possible
that Dio may have had a child.
That's why I wanted to verify if Giorno Giovanna
was really Dio's son, as well as if he inherited any of his traits.
But doesn't Dio's body
belong to the Joestar bloodline?
His hair turning blond may be proof that
Dio's blood awakened inside him, bringing out his Stand ability.
Something may have triggered it...
...such as a powerful Stand user
living within the city.
A powerful Stand user?
Don't approach him again.
It's too dangerous to proceed.
Understand?
One last thing...
Is he our enemy?
Or is he our ally?
What do you think?
You actually met him.
What's your impression of him?
I don't know...
But...
He had this...
...serene feeling about him.
Is this yours?
No.
Of course.
Guess it's mine, now.
Suppose you happened upon
a bag containing one billion unmarked lire...
Would you turn it in?
Never. I'd keep it to myself.
My, my, aren't you honest?
But what if I were a plainclothes police officer
and saw you take it?
I'd give you half
so you'd look the other way, I suppose.
Wow, good answer!
I can tell that's exactly what you would do.
You're not joking or bluffing.
I can really tell!
You're being honest.
Funnily enough, I can tell when
someone is being honest with me or not.
I'm rarely ever mistaken.
You know how your skin
glistens a bit when you sweat?
That's how I do it.
If I can taste the sweat,
it gives me an even better impression.
Who exactly are you?
"Leaky-eye" Luca was found on the ground near the airport
with the imprint of his spade smashed into his skull.
It was a life-threatening injury.
He'll never regain consciousness again.
I'm looking for the individual responsible.
Giorno Giovanna, nobody knows
what "Leaky-eye" Luca was doing at the airport.
However, the airport security guards
kindly informed me that you were present at the time.
That's why I came here
to ask you some questions.
Are you an actual police officer?
Of course not.
Luca's no ordinary thug.
He's a gangster.
He could have been taken out
for any number of reasons.
He's the kind of person
people hold grudges against.
However...
...none of that is any concern of the boss.
The boss feels slighted from
one of his own being incapacitated.
That's why he ordered me to
find and settle matters with the perpetrator.
So answer me this...
Did you run into "Leaky-eye" Luca at the airport?
No. I don't know who that is.
You aren't sweating...
Fine. I believe you.
That's all I wanted to ask.
Sorry for bothering you, Giorno Giovanna.
What was that?
Even though my hand was clenched...
That was Luca's right eye.
He was unconscious,
so I brought it with me.
This taste... is the taste of a liar,
Giorno Giovanna!
Well, well, well, well...
I said I was done asking questions,
but the situation has changed, Giorno Giovanna.
You lied to me.
I do believe I'm obligated to find out
just why you were lying to me, aren't I?
What are you staring at?
Jealous?
Would you like to hit him, too?
My name is Bruno Buccellati.
Now answer me.
This interrogation has already
turned into a torture session.
Well?
It's a pretty unnerving ability, isn't it?
Th-These are...!
They're Luca's fingers.
To tell you the truth...
The boss already disposed
of "Leaky-eye" Luca.
He saw no reason to keep him alive.
I took his fingers to assist in torturing you.
It happened again! What did he do?
Could he have an ability
like that Japanese tourist?
In addition to knowing whether or not
someone is lying, I can also do this.
I can put whatever I like in your mouth.
For example...
If I liked, I could put that
entire fire extinguisher inside your mouth.
Though you would
die in an instant if I did.
Now talk!
You saw the culprit!
Were you told to stay quiet?
Why don't you start by telling me
who had it out for Luca?
There's no doubt in my mind...
We have similar abilities!
Unless you hurry up and tell me,
the torture will continue...
...Giorno Giovanna!
This guy is dangerous!
I have no choice...
I have to use Gold Experience
to dodge his attacks!
Buccellati is Coming