We made it to Venice!
I'm diving into the canal!
Mista!
Get out of the car!
G-Giorno!
Y-You're... already starting to...
As I'm sure you're aware, Mista,
our top priority is to retrieve the object.
Our success lies in its retrieval!
The disc is right inside it!
Since we're surrounded by such a large body of water,
it will take longer for him to freeze the car.
That's why I did this!
Don't worry about me!
Hurry and get out!
I hear you, Giorno!
But your idea of success doesn't do it for me!
Killing him, then the two of us
getting what we came here for...
Now that's a success!
Like fucking hell you'll get off that easy!
Go right ahead and jump in, Mista!
I'll take my chances on whether or not
you can outswim my ice!
N-No!
Driving into the canal was a mistake!
The way he uses ice... is unbeatable!
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 19  White Album
Turn the car into a plant, Giorno!
The hood hasn't completely frozen up yet!
So hurry up and grow some plants
while you can still create life!
Trying to grow vines to use as ropes?
Fuck that shit!
I-It's no use...
As I thought, in order to make a vine that will grow fast enough to reach the bank, I need heat!
At this temperature, only short grass
like you'd find in a tundra can sustain life!
Who said anything about using them
to reach the bank, Giorno?
This'll do just fine!
Short grass is perfect!
But I need more! More! A lot more!
Keep making more if you wanna live!
We're gonna die if you don't hurry up, Giorno!
Gotcha!
Sucks that it didn't grow to the bank of the canal!
You did it, Giorno!
It froze over!
Now you're saved!
Th-That fucker!
He made me freeze the grass and turn it into a sled?
N-No... A snowboard!
Fucking dammit!
He's not gonna let me off that easy...
Of course not...
White Album!
Temporarily unfreeze the ice!
Th-The ice...
...melted!
Mista!
This is the static world of sub zero!
Nothing can move at temperatures this low!
It fucks everything up!
That's why my White Album is perfect!
I could stop the whole fucking ocean if I wanted to!
Hurry and reach the bank, Mista!
Mista!
Gather up the grass floating in the water!
The grass you were using as a snowboard!
Do it while you can still fire with your right hand!
Just give up, Mista!
Don't you get that attacking me is fucking pointless?!
Gathering up grass... I see.
Giorno, if you release your ability,
the short grass will turn back into car parts...
...which makes them perfect for attacking him!
What?!
D-Did that finish him?
No, too shallow.
We only have a temporary reprieve from the danger.
But Mista, you've bought us precious time!
Let's quickly grab the object, then get out of here!
We won't be able to employ the same strategy
if he catches us again!
Please go, Mista!
The disc should show up somewhere
if I destroy the lion statue...
I'll snatch it and hide in the city.
If I have a few dozen seconds, I can do it.
But will hiding be enough to lose him?
I think it will work, but I could be wrong.
Either way, this guy is seriously bad news.
If he runs into Buccellati and the others... That would be the worst case scenario.
We need to finish this here!
It's our only chance!
Wha...?!
Mista! What are you doing?!
Your ability is perfect? Yeah right!
If you're totally encased in ice,
then just how are you breathing?
That's it. I knew it.
Air's leaking out.
He's breathing from a hole at the back of his neck!
Get into position, Sex Pistols!
Number One and Number Two,
go around and flank him!
He's lookin' right at us!
He's gonna use another ice attack!
No, he's gonna go up for air first.
Once he reaches the surface,
I'm gonna fire right into his breathing hole!
He's trying to surface!
Here we go, Pistols!
We have to time this for
the instant he takes a breath!
Mista!
Number One and Two say they can't see the hole!
It's how he's swimming!
He's looking up!
It's hiding the hole!
O-Oh no! Let's scram!
That's enough, you two!
Hold your position,
Number One and Number Two!
Did you seriously hit my fucking forehead?!
Mista!
The fuck?
You shot at the fish swimming around me?
What the fuck are you trying to pull?!
He looked down! We can see it!
It's the hole! Now!
Here goes!
We got this!
Hooray! Bullseye!
Th-That noise...
That noise... It can't be!
So you found my breathing hole
and decided to target it...
Mista!
Too bad temperatures this low stop everything!
Gases turn to liquids, and liquids turn to solids!
Get a good look.
See how there's no airflow?
The bullet, Mista!
That's the sound of a ricocheting bullet!
What?!
White Album: Gently Weeps!
Mista!
I had already created a wall of frozen air!
It uses up a good chunk of my Stand's power,
but now you won't even be able to shoot a bolt into my head!
It stops anything that comes near me!
You're the one who made me learn my lesson, Mista!
Giorno was right...
This is all my fault...
It's my responsibility...
I should have focused on getting the object...
It's not under the trash can or bench...
Nothing that seems important,
and it's not like they'd hide it out in the open, anyway.
But based on how Mista was running around,
it must be somewhere it can be found quickly.
Where is it?
This photo should be a hint...
This is bad.
Our situation is dire.
Mista's beginning to act out of despair.
He's decided to take full responsibility for this,
even at the cost of his life.
But only those who possess true resolve
can forge a path through the darkness.
This is getting interesting.
Self sacrifice will be necessary at worst,
but if Mista and I share the responsibility for this...
...our combined resolve will forge a path!
Ghiaccio
White Album
Power: A
Speed: C
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
What the fuck is this?
It was in here the whole time?
Hiding inside the statue?
Dammit!
If I get close enough,
I should be able to shoot another bullet into his neck!
I just need to be able to aim through his wall of air...
Mista's become reckless!
He's willing to take responsibility for this
at the cost of his own life.
But what we need isn't bravery
born from being backed into a corner...
It's resolve!
What we need right now is resolve!
Resolve doesn't mean sacrifice!
A computer disc!
I knew it!
You were looking for something
to lead you to the boss!
I fucking did it!
Now we can go expose the boss's true identity!
All that's left now... is Trish!
I'll take care of her after finishing you motherfuckers!
Come on!
Fight until you lose!
I'll finish you assholes off!
Mista!
What the fuck are you doing?!
Resolve is the ability to forge a path
through the darkest night!
Guido Mista: Arrested at age seventeen for murder.
The result of the trial...
His plea that he acted out of self-defense was rejected, and he was sentenced fifteen to thirty years in prison.
My happy-go-lucky youth...
Is this really my fate?
Mista's outlook on life had always been optimistic,
but at this moment, his head was buried in his hands.
Damn...
Get up. You're being released.
You're the one who bailed me out?
Yes. I saw the incident on the news
and was convinced you acted out of self-defense.
To keep it short, I see how passionate you are and know how skilled you are at gunslinging.
But someone like you
wouldn't last two years in prison.
Which is why...
You pulled some strings for me.
Are you part of some organization?
Come with me.
There's an excellent ristorante nearby.
You have quite the appetite.
The bruschetta here is great, too.
Do you still have room for it?
Yeah.
Pardon me.
Yes, sir?
Could you get him some...
Actually, for everyone.
Could you get us four orders of bruschetta?
Actually, make that five.
I'll have some, too, while we're at it.
Right away, sir.
So, to pick up where we left off...
I'm in.
I think the two of us will get along great.
So count me in!
On one condition, though.
Treat me to some dolce, too.
Does this place have strawberry cake?
You're a strange man.
I guess this is fate, too.
Well, this isn't so bad, I guess.
Everything worked out in the end.
Mista learned that everyone's destiny is pre-determined.
Though people tend to stall
or take detours when they're young...
...they ultimately end up traveling
the path they were destined to take.
I see it! The path I need to take!
This time I'm sure of it!
It's there, Giorno!
I can see the path I gotta take through the darkness!
Yeehaw!
You fuckheads just don't get it.
The air is frozen because of how low the temperature is.
Just like this.
If I let air that's been frozen solid
into my suit and let it melt...
...it turns back to normal!
If I take it in like this...
Just like a diver with an air tank strapped to their back...
...I don't need a breathing hole anymore!
Th-The hole!
He deflected the bullets!
All six of 'em! O-Oh, no!
You better have the fucking resolve for this, Mista!
It's over.
Yeah, my resolve is there, Giorno...
If you hadn't given me your resolve,
I wouldn't have seen this path....
The resolve to take a path
where I'm willingly shot by my own bullets...
I-I can't see!
The blood froze and hardened to my face...
My path through the darkness...
...wasn't the one where my bullets
penetrated your wall of ice.
I-It was the one where
I splattered your face with my blood!
Shit! I can't get it off!
Hey, the metal pole from earlier!
Mista, your bullet shaped it into a-
Ow! That fucking hurts!
Something... Something... Something...
Something warm is-
You asked me if I had the resolve for this...
Well, I'm about to show you!
But you'll have to show some resolve of your own!
The resolve to be shot full of holes
and leave for the next world!
Th-The fucker's still standing!
He's hell-bent on shoving me further back!
Is he fucking nuts?!
He's gonna push my neck into the spike!
Shit! I need to get this out of my neck!
You're crazy!
The bullet's gonna come flying back!
You're not gonna last!
I have to make it through...
This is my true resolve!
Pistols, steel yourselves!
White Album: Gently Weeps!
Y-You can't take any more, Mista!
You're gonna die!
And that'll mean...
...we'll die, too!
N-Not yet!
I'm still conscious!
I can still shoot him!
Y-You did it!
It went all the way in!
You're... wrong...
The one with stronger resolve... is me...
Guido Mista...
I'll commend you for...
driving me so far up against the wall...
But the one who took better advantage
of all the blood splatter... was me!
I froze the blood that spurted out of my neck
to keep me fixed in place!
Now my neck can't be
pushed any farther into the spike!
I'm completely secured!
The spike won't go any farther!
Also... Aren't you forgetting something?
The last bullet you shot is still...
Right in the head!
I win!
There's no wound?!
Wha-
Mista...
Your resolve is illuminating the path,
shining even brighter than the rising sun.
And it's shining on the path...
...that we're meant to take!
What the fuck?!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Recently... I started noticing... that even though Giorno Giovanna... is so new at this...
...things always seem...
to play out exactly how he says.
The resolve I showed just now
was also partly Giorno's.
It made its way into my heart
before I realized it had happened.
He almost feels more like my capo than Buccellati does.
He drove me to act.
What's the deal with him?
Well, I guess now's not the time.
It's not my style to dwell on stuff like this.
Mista, we safely retrieved the disc thanks to you.
Hurry up and heal me.
I-I can't breathe...
I wouldn't have found that resolve
if I didn't have faith in your ability.
Hurry up and heal me before I die...
Of course.
But I need to make something clear to you first.
Gold Experience's ability
doesn't exactly have healing properties.
It recreates parts of the body.
My plan is to imbue the bullets embedded in your body with life
and to plug up your arteries and other injured areas.
Just quit talking and do it already!
Since I'm not exactly healing you,
your pain will remain.
Please don't complain to me later.
Oww!
O-Oww! Be more gentle!
Jesus, be more gentle Giorno!
I told you, I can't.
You're a gangster for crying out loud, so quit fussing.
You have about eighteen more wounds,
so you'll need to remove your clothes for me to take care of the rest.
Buccellati!
I'm picking up two signals...
Doesn't look like there's anyone else.
Proceed with caution.
I can only assume it's Mista and Giorno.
They must be bored out of their minds waiting for us
if it went so smoothly.
Ah! Giorno!
There they are!
Hey, Mista! Gio-
Be gentler!
Gentler, dammit!
Don't take off my clothes!
I can't take it!
Well, Narancia?
Have you spotted them?
Huh? W-Well, u-umm...
No! Huh?!
Something just got in my eye!
Giorno, no! Don't!
N-No more! I-I can't!
I can't see! I'm not sure that's even them!
For the love of god, be gentler!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Risotto's whereabouts are unknown.
Currently searching airports, train stations,
and the area surrounding Naples!
Damn Risotto...
He must be headed to Venice.
If he's taken out by Buccellati's crew, it's all the same.
One way or another,
my woes will be taken care of.
Final Order from the Boss