One of us needs to head
to the island and eliminate him.
It's perfect for the job.
Let's go get him!
Mista! He's already on the radio!
Shoot!
Damn, this is bad!
Shit's gonna get ugly
if I let this truck get away!
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 08  Enter the Sex Pistols Part 2
Ever since Guido Mista was a child,
he viewed life simply and lived a carefree existence.
He enjoyed sleeping...
He enjoyed watching the morning sun shining
through tree branches as the clouds lazily drifted by...
He enjoyed the scent of wine
and taste of cheese...
Whenever he spotted cute girls,
he would try chatting them up, even if they shot him down.
If he ran out of money, he would jump anyone lined up
in front of the local cinema who was badmouthing movie stars.
At times, he was beaten so badly that
the police were forced to get involved...
But Mista's life up until this point
was a happy one.
His carefree nature was
occasionally mistaken for foolishness...
...but Mista believed it wasn't good to overthink things
as it invited fear into one's heart.
When Mista turned seventeen,
he learned from a certain incident...
...that everyone's destiny is predetermined.
Though people tend to stall
or take detours when they're young...
...they ultimately end up traveling
the path they were destined to take.
One clear summer night, Mista found himself
wandering aimlessly through the streets as he always did...
Mista!
Yo! Wanna have a good time?
Sorry, we already have plans!
Ciao!
Later!
No! Get off me!
I told you to cut that shit out!
Now shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up!
Quit screaming!
The woman being brutalized
inside the parked car was half naked.
She was bleeding from her nose and mouth
and on the brink of losing consciousness.
Mista thought twice about
getting involved, but...
Y-You fucking asshole!
Due to his simple personality,
his body acted instinctively.
You son of a bitch!
What'd you do to our bro?
You fucking punk!
No matter how close you may be to your target,
you can never be absolutely certain that you'll hit.
It's all too easy to pull the trigger without
aiming your gun properly when panicked or rushed.
Both shots the hooligan fired
flew under Mista's arm and were swallowed by the darkness.
The fuck?!
S-Stay back!
You hear me?
Three, four, five, six shots!
Unbelievably, they were
all lost to the darkness.
His panicked friends
began to shoot, as well.
However, by what can only be
described as a miracle...
...Mista wasn't hit by a single bullet.
Meanwhile, Mista was astonished by
his own state of silent concentration.
What the fuck is going on?
Wh-Who the hell is this guy?!
Bro!
Wh-What are you-
After stealing one of
the guns and some bullets...
...Mista calmly loaded the cylinder
amidst the ensuing gunfire...
...then pulled the trigger as calmly
as a nurse inserting a needle into a patient's arm.
He pointed the gun at the three men's faces
and fired four perfect shots.
Of course, this was the first time
he had ever killed someone...
...but he felt no hesitation or remorse.
During this hopeless situation,
Mista steeled himself and carved a path through the shadows.
Eat lead!
The guy driving must be
the owner of the truck...
...because...
...his right leg is fine.
I wasn't planning on killing you, but...
O-Oww!
Shit!
You shot me twice, you fucking asshole!
Quit moving around!
I'm gonna aim for real this time, dammit!
Why did I just say such a stupid one-liner?
I shouldn't have said that!
What I should be asking is how the hell he's still alive!
He took a bullet straight to the head!
Did my bullet somehow miss
a vital part of his brain?
That's real fucking cute, Mista.
Your name is Mista, isn't it?
I know you have a friend with you
here in Capri...
...but you're the only one
who's seen my face, right?
Eh, Mista?
I got hit twice during your surprise attack
after getting caught in your little trap with the radio, but...
...if I fight you one-on-one
with my Stand, Kraftwerk...
...I'll have no problem deflecting the bullets
from that puny revolver of yours.
By the way,
I was a little too distracted to count...
...but how many bullets have you shot, huh?
You've fired four on the truck so far,
haven't you?
And I'm pretty sure you fired two
back at the watchhouse in Marina Grande.
Am I right?
Did I count that right, Mista?
So now I can get up close and personal
and beat the crap out of you without worrying, right?
Crap, I need to reload!
Wh-What the hell?!
Th-This can't be happening!
My left hand is stuck!
Whoa!
Hey, you!
How long you gonna keep driving forward?! Stop, you idiot!
I wish I could...
Someone stop us, please...
Someone stop the truck!
Nothing I do is working...
Think about it for a second...
Why would I be so kind as to
tell you that you're out of bullets?
You think I'm trying to help you out here?
Mista...
The only reason I told you is because
I'm confident you'll never escape this truck.
Also, the driver can't take his foot
off the gas pedal...
...or let go of the steering wheel.
I'm telling you this because I know you can't reload
with your left hand fixed to the truck.
Those are the bullets
that bastard's Stand deflected...
They're frozen there in midair,
like he fixed them in place so they'd move with the truck!
Fixed in place...
He must have used his ability to fix the bullets in place midair,
just like he fixed me and the driver to the truck...
He has the ability to fix
anything he touches in place!
The bullet I shot at him
stopped at the skin around his wound...
...which is why it didn't
hit anything vital and kill him!
To be totally honest with you, Mista...
...I'm really happy you decided to attack me!
Happy enough that
I'm willing to forget you wounded me!
I mean, it wasn't exactly obvious if
Polpo's fortune really existed or not.
It was just a rumor from
a bunch of thugs, after all.
But the fact that you attacked me
pretty much confirms it exists, right?
I can feel the hope and motivation
flowing through me, dude!
Now I can really stick it to Buccellati
and steal all ten billion from his smug ass!
I told you I'd have no problem
deflecting your bullets, didn't I?
Yee-haw!
Wh-What?!
Another bullet behind the first one?!
He fired two bullets in a single shot?
Is that Mista's Stand?
Still...
I can just barely deflect it!
Got him!
Nice work,
Sex Pistols Number 6 and Number 7!
And now that I knocked him off the truck...
...I have nothing to worry about!
O-Oww!
You fucking shot me again, you asshole!
But you're not getting away that easy...
This is for the ten billion!
You can't escape me!
There has to be a way to beat him...
But he's really strong...
That much I can tell...
Can I really do it?
Sale
Kraftwerk
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: E
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Blood...
A vehicle...
Mista and the enemy must be in a car
headed toward the top of the island!
Will I be able to catch up to them?
Regardless,
I need to find myself a car and give chase!
Four bullets?
What the hell is going on here?
I only have four bullets!
Why do I only have four left? Seriously!
It's 'cause ya spilled a bunch of bullets, Mista!
'Cause ya spilled 'em!
Four's super-duper bad!
Don't load all four!
It's askin' for trouble!
I-I can take my hands off the wheel!
Yes! My feet, too!
I can finally stop this thing!
Don't you dare stop!
Huh?
B-But you were telling me to stop earlier!
Forget that!
Now I'm telling you not to!
Got it?
I wanna go back to Marina Grande!
My backup is still at the marina.
There's gotta be another way back there!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'll even thank you if you take me back.
Got all that?
That asshole is stopping the bullets right at his skin
so they won't pierce his body...
The ability to fix things in place...
How am I supposed to beat that?
If I can land a shot in his mouth...
...it'll get past his defenses
and wreck his insides!
That might actually kill him!
But I only have four bullets left...
Damn, talk about unlucky!
Even three would have been better!
Now that I've seen his face and know who he is,
I don't need to do anything risky.
It'll be safer to meet up with
Giorno back at the marina.
I have extra bullets
with the rest of my stuff, too.
Th-That asshole!
No way!
He climbed all the way up the cliff?!
Hey, stop the truck!
Huh?
What is it now?
I said stop the truck!
Do it now!
Th-That's the guy from earlier!
Mista...
There's no way in hell I'm gonna
let you tell your buddies who I am!
I'll never let you get away, Mista!
He can fix rocks in midair
like he did my bullets?
Did he climb them all the way up like a ladder?
Why the hell did you
stop the truck, moron?!
Huh?
Get moving!
Step on the gas!
You better not stop this truck!
You wanna settle this here, huh?
So let's do this!
Driver, don't you dare stop this truck!
I just have to lightly tap it with my finger...
Even if I just tap it lightly over and over...
...it will keep building up potential energy.
I can't hit it too hard...
It will throw off my aim
and make it obvious which way it's gonna fly.
And with that... Here it goes!
What?!
It came back to you, Mista!
Those three Stands of yours
just lost control and flew off!
Just a little at a time...
Just gotta keep tapping it
with a little bit of force...
Just like tapping out SOS in Morse code.
It's impossible to aim perfectly,
so it's no good for moving targets...
...but I can definitely use it on you
in your current state!
Th-This really sucks...
Talk about bad luck...
The number four always screws me over!
Has ever since I was a kid...
The universe just works in weird ways...
Still... Any other number is good!
I only have one bullet left,
but that means the worst is over now, right?
The number is one now, goddammit!
Number 5! Number 6! Assemble!
We're gonna team up for this last one!
We only got one shot at this!
Yeah!
Stay right where you are, Mista!
Don't try shooting me again, idiot!
No matter what your Stands do,
or how many times you shoot me, especially at this distance...
...I have the upper hand here!
I have all the time I need to defend myself!
Haven't you realized by now
that it's impossible to beat me, Mista?
If I told you...
...that I only have one bullet left in this chamber,
would you believe me?
I'm being honest.
I only have one bullet left.
If I shoot it and somehow
you're able to deflect it...
...I'll be out of bullets.
I'm telling you this since
I know you'd figure it out, anyway.
If I screw up this last shot,
you'll know that I'm out of bullets.
Though now I'm just talking hypothetically...
I'm definitely gonna shoot you
with this final bullet!
What the hell are you rambling about, Mista?
I don't give a fuck
how many bullets you have left.
Whether you fire a single bullet or a hundred,
you'll never beat me!
I wasn't rambling...
You're gonna let your guard down
now that I've told you I only have one bullet left.
This is pointless.
He's gonna use his Stand!
We got this!
Let's do it!
Only one target!
All or nothing!
You're aiming for the inside of my mouth.
Isn't that right?
He opened his mouth on purpose!
He's not gonna protect himself?
We just gotta charge on in!
I knew it...
Oww...
I knew you were aiming there...
For the inside of my mouth!
That's what any normal person would think...
That I can't fix things inside my body.
It's a lot harder to defend myself,
so I opened my mouth for you!
You're kidding me...
He can even stop my bullets
by fixing them in his mouth?
Fuck! This shit really hurts!
But hey, at least you weren't lying
about that being your last bullet.
You would have shot me again.
You done now, Mista?
If you're finished...
The firepower in this baby...
...is more than ready, Mista!
I win! Take this! Release!
He really did let his guard down!
All 'cause Mista was outta bullets!
We just wanted to get in closer!
The closer we are, the better we aim!
Wh-What?!
Wh-When did they-
Fuck! They're too close!
Let's do it, fellas!
Aim!
Kraftwerk! Defend!
The bullet split in two?!
It won't matter if he gets another clean hit on me...
Wait... he's not aiming there, is he?
If he is, I'm fucked!
Oh shit!
He is aiming there!
That's-
I aimed for the same wound.
I shot another round at the one
still fixed inside your head...
...knowing that even if you fixed it in place,
it would still shove the first one even farther into your head!
I mean, I'd be screwed if you
lived through that, too...
We did it!
Yes!
Come on, Number 3...
I keep telling you to
not bully Number 5. Jeez...
He's barely hanging in there,
even though he got a bullet lodged in his brain...
Guess your Stand really is invincible.
I managed to stick to Buccellati's
order not to kill you, but...
Hey, take us back!
Back to the marina!
What do you want from me?!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
Shit...
They're really yanking my chain!
Telling me to stop, then go...
I'm not a fuckin' taxi, assholes!
How dare you threaten me?!
I'll let 'em off the hook for now,
but next time I'll really let 'em have it!
I'm terribly sorry,
but I'm pursuing someone.
Could you take me to the top
of the island in your truck?
Quit wasting time!
I'm desperate here!
You're going to take me there, got it?!
Y-Yes, sir...
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
First Order from the Boss