Doesn't look like we're being followed.
Buccellati, are we not leaving Venice?
The boss has a group of elite guards at his disposal.
No doubt they've already been informed of our betrayal.
Before long... they'll have their sights set on us.
But we have no idea what kind of abilities they have.
Correct.
If we attempt to cross the sea unprepared,
they may use the opportunity to strike.
We'll have to wait and see.
Understood.
Mista!
We're starving!
I'm so hungry!
We want food!
Our guts are running on empty!
Get a grip, you guys!
I know this is really bad timing,
but could we stop at a restaurant or something?
Well...
...I suppose our "guts" need filling, as well.
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono stay gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru hell no
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 22  The "G" in Guts
You guys ever heard of
vegetarians or whatever they're called?
Is it like, they can't eat cheese or something?
I think so.
I mean, milk and eggs
come from cows and chickens.
Probably means they can't have
cake with whipped cream on it, either.
What?!
They can't eat cake, either?
I wonder if that makes their bodies
work better or something...
Wait, wait, then what do they do
about shoes and handbags?
They're made of leather.
Well, if they're vegetarians
because they feel bad for animals...
...they probably wear sneakers and use backpacks instead.
Whew, talk about dedication!
So even as old ladies they'll be
walking around decked out in basketball gear?
They'll never get into restaurants looking like that!
Giorno, you'll accomplish nothing by staying on edge.
Come sit and eat with us.
Yes, I'm aware...
But we need to stay vigilant.
For example, we can't rule out that someone poisoned our food.
Y-You punk!
What the hell are you trying to pull?!
Huh?
How are you gonna make up for this, asshole?
You think you can pay for this?!
This suit is worth four million lire!
Let's take this outside!
You must be an enemy!
What?!
You the enemy, or not?!
Well, are you?!
You the enemy?!
Take that! And that!
H-Hold it, Narancia, Mista...
I don't think this guy's an enemy.
He's out cold.
He's just an innocent civilian.
Huh? For real?
This sucks!
What should we do?
Yeah, this stain's gonna be a bitch to get out.
Even one drop of wine
really sticks out on a white suit.
I can't afford to pay for this shit!
At least the spot it stained
almost looks like a button.
He can hide it by sewing a button over it.
While we have the chance,
let's use him to make sure our food wasn't poisoned.
Good idea!
Hey, that's enough.
Come to think of it...
What's going on with Buccellati right now?
After his fight with the boss,
I'm sure Buccellati's heart wasn't beating.
And when he was hurt earlier,
there wasn't a single drop of blood.
What about now?
Though this isn't a good time to ponder it.
I'll keep this fact hidden away in my heart for now.
So, Buccellati, what's the plan here?
The boss's Stand clearly erased time...
...and he alone is able to freely move inside of it.
He's invincible.
It doesn't matter who he's up against.
Any attack is rendered useless by his Stand.
But even so...
...the tide will turn once we figure out who he is!
If we can figure out what the boss looks like...
...we may be able to covertly eliminate him!
In order to do that,
we need to find out...
...who he really is.
But how are we gonna find him?
The boss isn't the kind of guy to
leave any traces of himself behind.
Trish.
Trish will give us some kind of hint.
Everyone was after Trish,
and the boss tried eliminating Trish.
Right?
A-About that...
I don't really want Trish
to be a part of this anymore...
I-It just feels wrong...
Trish doesn't know anything!
If she finds out her actual father
tried to kill her, she'll be in shock.
Buccellati, please!
Let's not talk about the boss's identity
and stuff like that in front of her.
That isn't necessary, Narancia.
I'm fully aware of what happened back there.
T-Trish...
I remembered something when you said
he wouldn't leave any traces of himself.
My mother once mentioned that
she met my father in Sardinia.
Sardinia...
When I was little, my mother told me...
...that the two of them had met while she was vacationing,
and he told her he would return to her...
That's when he disappeared forever,
not even leaving a photo or revealing his name.
Before he became the boss of the organization...
Fifteen years ago...
Does that mean he was born and raised in...?
I'm not sure about the details, but...
Sardinia.
His past and true identity lie in Sardinia.
Why are you telling us this?
We may end up killing him!
Truthfully, we've resolved to bring him down!
As far as I'm concerned,
whether or not you bring him down doesn't matter.
It's just...
There's something I have to know!
I have to know who my father is!
I refuse to die before I figure that out!
Hey, Narancia...
Looks like this girl is a lot stronger
than you gave her credit for.
Fine.
Sardinia...
That will be our next destination
once we've escaped Venice.
That will be where we find out
who the boss really is!
I had the impression that
Trish was just like me...
...but I guess she had already made up her mind.
I was caught up in the moment
and ended up tagging along...
...but I still can't tell if
this trip will be hopeless or not.
Huh?
An enemy!
There's an enemy here!
There's a shark in my soup!
Aerosmith!
Giorno!
Get Trish inside the tortoise!
Abbacchio, cover our right!
Mista, the left!
Where, Narancia?
Where's the enemy?
Inside my soup!
Somehow they were already inside of it!
Wh-Where are they now?
But they were just there!
I saw something that looked like a shark in my soup!
Don't see anything wrong with it.
You think we lost it?
Narancia!
What happened?!
Where did it attack you?
Where did it hurt you?
Narancia, what's wrong?
What's there?!
Just tell me what's wrong already, Narancia!
That's not it, Mista!
I don't think Narancia can speak right now.
What?
You can't talk?
What's wrong, Narancia?
What are you pointing at?
Water?
You want a sip of water?
H-Hey!
Th-This is bad! Look!
Narancia's tongue!
It's gone!
And even worse,
I don't think he's breathing!
This looks dire...
I can use Gold Experience to replace
the damaged part of his tongue, but it will take some time.
Seriously, come on!
He's about to suffocate!
Mista, do you have a pen?
A pen?!
Y-Yeah, I got one...
He's breathing again...
I'll imbue the pen with life
to replace the damaged parts of his tongue.
He'll be able to breathe
while I replace his tongue this way.
I see...
So that's Giorno Giovanna.
I'm starting to make sense of
the information the boss gave us.
The new kid is the one we have to be
most careful about dealing with.
Yeah... I'm surprised he managed to save Narancia.
I thought my Clash would be enough to do the job...
...but as it were, I'm going to need your assistance to ensure all five of them are eliminated...
...Tiziano.
As members of the boss's elite guard,
we're going to have to defeat him here.
Are you ready, Squalo?
All according to plan.
As long as we can lure them to water,
Clash is unbeatable.
Our plan will decide everything.
We'll take care of them one at a time, Tiziano.
Yeah, Squalo...
We'll use Narancia.
Clash
Squalo
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Are you all right, Narancia?
Yeah...
You guys saved me...
What did you see?
How did the enemy Stand attack you?
It... c-came from the soup...
Narancia, don't strain yourself.
I-It's fine. I can talk.
Hey, Narancia.
What was the enemy like?
Where'd it go?
It was...
It was built like a pebble!
It was really big and ran into that restaurant!
Huh?
Big and built like a pebble?
But earlier you were saying it was in your soup!
You're contradicting yourself.
Huh?
Did I really just say that?
So, would you say the enemy is about this big?
Nope.
Huh? No, wait!
How about this big?
U-Umm...
No?
Then how about this big?
Yeah, that's right.
Hey! Are you telling me that something this big
was swimming in your soup and ran into the restaurant?
Yup.
Huh? What?
This isn't giving us a clear image
of the enemy at all.
Are you saying it was really fast?
Nope!
It was slow as shit!
What?
Huh?!
If it was big and slow,
then why didn't we see it?
Did you actually see a Stand?
Of course I did... n-
You keep contradicting yourself!
You're not trying to act tough
because the enemy got you, are you?
I... I...
Answer me, dammit!
You didn't actually see anything, did you?
Of course I did...!
...not!
So you really didn't see anything!
This is a bad time to be messing around!
I don't see anyone suspicious around.
Guess it must be a remote-controlled Stand.
I can only assume the user
is watching us from somewhere.
Since that's the case,
we should leave here immediately.
We can follow the channel out to sea.
Good thinking, Giorno!
Let's do it!
Using the channel is a great idea!
Yes, Narancia.
That's what I just...
Narancia?
Narancia, why do you keep covering your mouth?
Let me look at it.
What the hell?
Looks totally fine to me.
Yup! I feel great!
I'm having no problems whatsoever, Mista!
So what's the plan, Buccellati?
Are we going out to sea?
No. Let's not follow the channel just yet.
This is our chance.
We're going to pursue the enemy
and take them down!
The boss wasn't expecting us to betray him,
which means there probably aren't many of his elite guards around here.
If we defeat the enemy now,
I'm sure we'll be able to get through the seas of Venice just fine.
Gotcha. That's a good point. I agree.
Yeah, same here.
Very well, Buccellati.
If you say so.
Abbacchio, could you use your
Moody Blues to replay what happened?
Yeah, sure thing.
Where do you want it to start?
From when the soup was still on the table?
Yeah.
What's up, Narancia?
Guys! The enemy's right over there!
Over there?
You mean inside the restaurant bathroom?
Narancia, I swear to god
you better have seen something this time!
Yup, sure did!
Pursue them!
We'll settle this here and now!
Hey, Giorno. Let's go.
Right...
Nice going, Narancia.
None of his friends realize that there's another Stand besides Clash, which travels from liquid to liquid.
Yes, they don't realize that my Stand...
...Talking Head, is attached to his tongue
and making him say the exact opposite of what he means.
All right, I'll kill the rest of them now. Grazie!
S-So that's what's going on! Dammit!
They're using me to get everyone
near the water, one by one...
Damn them for underestimating me!
I don't feel like anyone is here...
Let's figure out what they look like at the very least.
Moody Blues!
Transform into whoever was in here
a few dozen seconds ago, then pursue them!
Narancia!
Seeing who the enemy is through
Moody Blues is fine, but don't pursue them!
If it enters water,
they won't stand a chance!
Because of that, I'll do everything I can
to keep them away from water!
Over here...
Moody Blues is transforming.
Water will kill you!
Don't look in there!
Look at me! Look in here!
Wh-What the fuck? That's disgusting!
Come on over here, Abbacchio!
Look in here!
What the fuck are you saying?
Did you become a pervert or something?
We're trying to investigate
since you said you saw the enemy in here!
Did you really see them in here?
Of course I-
Seriously, what's your problem?
Buccellati, there's a good chance
Narancia was just seeing things in here.
We're probably better off looking at the table
if we want to pursue.
Agreed.
Cut the crap, Narancia!
I'm not gonna let you take us all down!
Narancia, what happened to your finger?
Did you snag it somewhere?
Here, I'll stop the bleeding.
That fucker is gonna try using
my blood to move around!
N-No!
S-Stay back, Giorno!
Yeah!
Heal me right up, Giorno!
There's certainly something strange about you.
Is something wrong with
the inside of your mouth?
They attacked your tongue earlier.
Does that have something to do with it?
I knew I could count on you, Giorno!
You're so smart!
Just a little more...
Just a little more,
and Giorno will figure it out!
You're bleeding profusely, though.
Let me take care of your wound first.
Come on, let me see it.
No!
You can't touch my blood!
Come on, Narancia.
This is bad!
Stay back! Back!
Hurry!
Aerosmith!
Narancia...
...it appears you're under attack by something,
but there must be a reason why you can't tell us what.
Yes! He figured it out!
Was there something left in your mouth
after the first attack?
Like, say, an ability that makes you say
the opposite of what you intend?
Yes!
That's exactly it, Giorno!
Sh-Shit!
Water is coming out of the pipe!
Giorno!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Clash and Talking Head