yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 16  The Grateful Dead Part 2
Pesci!
What the fuck are you doing?!
Stop the damn train already!
Pesci!
B-Bro!
Stop the train!
Bro!
I-I dunno how to stop it!
This will put an end
to you and your aging ability.
Then my crew will return to normal,
and Trish will be safe!
Fuck you!
Buccellati!
Bro!
What?!
Prosciutto!
W-Well done, Pesci!
Excellent work!
That was quick thinking!
A-Almost lost him...
I almost missed my chance...
Thank goodness I got him!
My hook will never let him go!
B-But this resistance I feel
is the weight of two people!
Buccellati's gotta be hanging on, too!
I seriously thought you'd
fucked me for good, Buccellati.
I called you a failure of a capo,
but I take it back.
I shouldn't have been so rude.
You're the kind of guy who knows
how to make tough decisions in a pinch.
Even when your life is on the line.
The boss was wise to pick you
to protect his daughter.
I'm seriously shocked.
Even so, Buccellati...
You're one hell of an unlucky capo!
Down you go!
A 150-kilometer-an-hour trip to hell awaits you!
Sticky Fingers!
Did you forget?
You're still aging as we speak!
Too slow!
The line your younger brother
sent out for you really saved me.
He wasn't aiming for me...
Am I the unlucky one here?
There's no way
that asshole Mista survived earlier!
I put three bullets right through his skull.
The fact that he's alive is more fucked up
than someone saying the sun rises in the west!
I told him how it works!
Any energy that hits the fishing line...
...gets sent back to whoever's hooked!
Impossible!
Buccellati!
It's one person lighter now!
Buccellati musta been thrown off!
We did it, Prosciutto!
Looks like his aging ability's been cancelled.
Now we just gotta deal with
the fishing line dude!
Yeah.
Earlier, my Beach Boy's hook
shoulda dug into Bro's right hand...
His pinky was on the right side of the hook...
But now...
...there's a pinky on the left side...
It's attached to a left hand!
Wh-What the heck's going on?!
Whose hand is that on the other end?
How'd it switch from
Bro's right hand to his left?!
N-Now that I think about it...
Bro was a bit heavier'n this...
H-Hey, you over there!
Make them stop the train!
I think everyone here is sick or something!
I feel better than I did
just a minute ago, but...
I lost a bunch of teeth!
Th-The effects of his aging are reversing...
Hey, you listening to me?!
Go get the driver to stop the train!
I-It can't be...
Don't tell me the weight
that fell off the line was...
It can't be!
It can't be true!
B-Bro can't be...
Are you listening to me, you clown?
I'm talking to you!
You, right there!
My bro, Prosciutto!
What should I do?
What should I do?!
Wh-What now?
Oh, no!
The guys inside the tortoise are gonna come out, too!
Wh-What should I do?
What should I...?
What the hell are you crying over?!
I told you to stop the damn train!
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Shut your mouth!
You some kind of mammone?!
Fine! I'm starting to feel better anyway,
so I'll just tell them my-
Wh-What's going on?
Stop... the... train...
The aging hasn't stopped!
Buccellati, y-you're...!
Impossible...
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me he...
What?!
Grateful... Dead...
Bro!
You were right, Bro...
You were so right...
You told me that I should never call back my Stand
once I'm close to defeating the enemy...
...even if it means losing an arm or leg...
B-Bro...
Th-There's no way he's gonna make it
with how messed up he is...
It won't be long before he stops breathing...
...yet Bro still isn't releasing Grateful Dead!
We've gotta get Trish, no matter what.
Right, Bro?
We can't turn back now...
I get it now, Prosciutto!
Your resolve...
I understand what you meant
not just in words, but also deep within my heart!
Once our mind's made up
to get someone...
...the deed's already been done!
That's the first time I offed someone...
Wasn't as big of a deal as I thought.
And now that this guy's gone,
there's no one left to call me a mammone.
Pesci
Beach Boy
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
I'm gonna finish this once and for all...
...before Bro's ability disappears!
Buccellati!
Hurry up and take the hook out!
Got it.
You opened up your hand with a zipper.
He can tell what I'm trying to do?
I can sense his every move!
The hook will enter his body through his left hand,
pass through his wrist, then plunge into his forearm!
The hook won't stop goin' up your arm!
It's out again!
It's no use...
Every time I try to remove it,
he can tell where I've moved down to a few centimeters!
On top of that, he's strong!
I'll never lose track of your body!
And I'm gonna honor
Prosciutto's will by nabbing Trish!
Buccellati!
The jerk's right below us!
If we can finish him for good, Giorno and the others will go back to their normal ages and take care of the fishing rod guy!
I know!
But that's easier said than done!
Have a taste of the pain
my Bro's going through right now!
Buccellati!
He's hanging onto something...
In that case...
Up you go!
You're gonna slam into the electric cables!
You're minced meat!
I felt an impact,
but it didn't feel like he fell off or got chopped in half.
I feel a pulse through the line.
Buccellati's still hangin' on.
He's inside the train!
Th-That was close, Buccellati!
You got no choice but to
get up close and personal!
Yeah... But that's easier said than done, too.
There's not enough time...
The hook just reached my torso!
What?!
The distance between the hook
and your heart is now twelve centimeters...
Eleven centimeters...
I misjudged the situation.
The man with the aging ability
wasn't the biggest threat on this train.
The truly terrifying one...
...is this man using the fishing rod!
So what's the plan?
The hook's gonna snag your heart soon!
Nine centimeters, eight centimeters...
Then I'll show him what I'm made of.
The only way I can defeat this ability...
...is if I show him that my resolve
runs deeper than his!
Sticky Fingers!
What're you doin'?!
Buccellati!
He disappeared!
I can't feel his pulse or the
vibration from him breathing...
Why?!
How did I lose his presence?
How?!
How could you do something
so crazy, Buccellati?!
I know you didn't have a choice...
But for real, are you gonna be okay?!
Keep... quiet...
Wait until he's gone...
This is what it means to have resolve...
Number Six.
Shit, I can't find him!
Buccellati can go anywhere
with his zippers!
Could he be headed here
f-from another direction?
No, wait. Calm down...
Jumping at shadows
is a sign of weakness!
That's what Prosciutto would tell me!
Have more confidence, Pesci.
It doesn't matter that you're on a moving train.
I'm sure you'll find him by sensing his heartbeat.
He's right!
There's no way in hell
Buccellati could move that fast!
He's still gotta be somewhere near the hook!
H-He's bringing out more of the line!
Pull yourself together
and get outta here!
For now...
...he's lost track of me...
I can get through this
as long as I stay still...
The fact that I'm sticking to my guns...
...shows my resolve.
His heartbeat... his pulse...
I gotta find them...!
Got one!
But it's not him!
This guy's too heavy.
It's another passenger!
Is this it?
It's weak, but it sounds like a beating heart!
N-No!
He's gonna find your heart!
Are you nuts?!
He said he'd do nothing...
...but he chopped his heart
in half so it wouldn't beat...
This is crazy!
How long can humans live
without breathing or pumping blood?
D-Dammit!
He's not here!
I can't sense anything else in that room!
D-Did he really go
somewhere else with his zippers?
Y-You're reaching your limit!
Where the hell did he go?!
Don't tell me... Buccellati...
...went to go finish off Prosciutto?!
Once the aging stops,
the rest of Buccellati's guys will come outta the tortoise!
Goddammit!
That ain't happening!
W-We did it!
He gave up on this room!
Your resolve threw him off!
You barely made it through!
Hurry and zip yourself back together! Come on!
Un... believable...
How unlucky...
Buccellati!
Pull yourself together!
The only thing I'm good at
is controlling bullets!
I don't got the energy to move big stuff like this!
He was more stubborn than I thought...
He... beat me...
Stop already, stupid piece of shit train!
Wh-What's going on?!
B-Bro!
I've taken an arduous path...
A path I couldn't have traversed
without a bit of luck.
Which is to say, the path leading me to you.
I'm gonna make you pay, Buccellati...
You got close to him!
Buccellati, your resolve won out!
...right in front of Bro,
before he's gone for good.
What?!
I'm surprised you saw through that attack!
His eyes and expression...
He looks as though he's experienced
a decade of utter turmoil.
I can feel the calm intensity in his eyes.
I won't be able to trick him.
Do it... You're... doing well... Pesci...
Do it... I'm watching... over you...
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
What?!
I saw that one coming!
I always went up the arm to the heart until now
since I wasn't confident I'd hit if I didn't!
But this time I knew I wouldn't miss,
so I went right for your heart!
From now on,
I'm going straight for everything!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
I'm gonna rip your heart out, Buccellati!
You're not supposed to say you'll "fucking kill" someone
until after you've killed them...
...in our world of gangsters.
Have I... lost?
Am I... gonna die?
But... I'm not... gonna go quietly!
Go ahead... Take her... and run...
I'll let Trish live...
He's got the tortoise!
Wh-Where am I?
But before I die...
I'm gonna drown your heart in utter despair!
The despair of losing your crew!
I'm gonna smash this thing into pieces!
That's bad!
That's really bad!
Earlier, I saw a noble resolve
glimmering in your eyes, like a hardened diamond.
But you've fallen.
Now you're just a
worthless piece of shit.
Fallen? Fallen, you say?!
The only ones falling and
getting crushed are these assholes!
You'll never make it in time!
Welcome to Hell, Buccellati!
Worthless pieces of shit like you
never win in the end.
Arri Arri Arri Arri!
Arri!
Arrivederci.
"So Long"
Prosciutto – Deceased
Stand Name: The Grateful Dead
Pesci – Deceased
Stand Name: Beach Boy
I figured as much,
but we definitely can't continue by train.
You got that right.
There's no way they didn't
talk to their buddies.
I'm sure they told the others about
the tortoise and where we're headed.
We'll have to find
a different mode of transportation.
I've been meaning
to ask you something...
Will you answer me?
I haven't been given permission
to answer any of your questions.
Our sole mission is to act as your bodyguards.
You will answer me.
Just who am I?
What is this supposed to be?!
What's this on the ground?
Why have I suddenly started
seeing such bizarre things?
Why am I being pursued
over a father I've never even met?
I knew it...
The boss's daughter is a Stand user!
Answer me!
Bruno Buccellati
Sticky Fingers
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: D
Precision: C
Growth Potential: D
The current time is 6:34 PM.
I arrived twenty minutes
after the train stopped.
Prosciutto is lying dead near the tracks.
Dismembered pieces of Pesci's body
are strewn across the riverbank.
Judging from the state of things, I can conclude that
Buccellati's Sticky Fingers was responsible for eliminating them.
Got it.
What about his team and the girl?
Long gone.
Can you track them down, Melone?
Yeah.
The measures taken by the now-deceased
should make tracking them possible.
I just procured a blood sample.
Buccellati's, as it were.
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (Girl, whatever you want I will give it, baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (Yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (Oh tell me)
What must I do (What must I do)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (Baby)
What must I say (Tell me)
What must I do (Yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Babyface