Oww...
Yeah, you'll need to go to the hospital for this.
No shit I will!
Just patch me up before then!
Fine.
H-Hey, Fugo, what are you-
Hey!
What did you do to me?!
Staples!
It's actually sealed up
like a comic book!
Narancia, could you wrap his stomach
with some gummed tape for me?
You got it!
This isn't gonna get infected, is it?
Don't sweat it!
Y'know, this actually kinda works!
Could you keep it down?
Good job, everyone.
Because of your efforts,
we safely reached Capri.
The assailant, Zucchero,
and the man Mista took out...
...are both passed out on the boat.
They won't be bothering us anymore.
Then take us to where
you hid the ten billion lire already!
Where'd you hide it, Buccellati?
Inside a hidden bank vault?
Or buried in some cave
here on the island?
Could you wait just a bit longer?
But why?
Why does it matter when you tell us?
Hey, fellas.
We're still in here.
Why don'tcha save the cleaning for later?
Does your name happen to be Toilette?
Huh? What was that?
If your name is Toilette,
this must be where you live.
You can call the shots
if this is your house.
But if it's not your house,
you have no right ordering me around.
Huh?
Hey, wait, dumbass!
Didn't you hear me?
I said we're still in there!
Wh-What the hell do you think you're doing?!
You want a piece of me?!
What?
Another enemy?
I'll fucking kill you!
Wait!
Everyone, stop Narancia!
Why are you stopping me?!
These two may be...
That voice...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Everyone, bow.
This is one of the capos of Passione:
Mr. Pericolo!
I'm here for the ten billion lire...
...Buccellati.
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 09  First Order from the Boss
I contacted him as soon as we reached the island.
Mr. Pericolo came all this way
to collect the money.
One of Passione's capos...
Thank you so much
for coming all this way, sir.
No, no, I'm the one who insisted on it.
Please, no need to bow.
You must be the new member.
Yes, sir.
Buccellati has told me much about you.
Now that you've joined Passione,
you're part of our family.
You may call me Mr. Pericolo, if you wish.
Thank you, sir.
You, there.
I'm sorry for earlier.
My companion here
isn't keen on being touched.
Yeah...
You-
Say "Yes, sir!"
Mr. Pericolo...
...why are you dressed as a janitor?
I have my reasons.
I'll tell you later.
But more to the point,
you do have it, don't you?
The ten billion lire for the organization.
Yes, sir. Right in here.
What?
What did you just say?!
He said it's right in here!
Here?!
Buccellati, where is it?
There's nothing but urinals in here...
I-It was inside a urinal?!
I mean, that's a really safe spot, but...
Sucks for the guys
pissing there this whole time!
I see... It's real.
This necklace alone is worth at least
seven or eight hundred million.
Buccellati...
...I won't trouble you with telling me
where you got this fortune.
The organization only cares
that you're handing it over.
Wait, y-you're already
putting it away?
C-Could I just touch it a bit?
Give it a good whiff?
This fortune signifies to us that its owner
possesses commendable intelligence and integrity.
Congratulations, Buccellati.
As of today, you're a capo.
A-All right!
He's a capo!
Buccellati's finally a capo!
You will inherit the territory
controlled by the late Polpo.
In addition, you'll oversee the gambling, money-lending, and smuggling at the harbor...
...as well as all of the
restaurants and hotels in Naples.
Half of the profits will go to the organization,
and the other half will be yours.
This is awesome!
He got authority just like that!
With Buccellati's brains and popularity,
he'll be rolling in dough in no time!
But really, the ball started rolling
after this newbie, Giorno, joined us.
Is he some kind of good luck charm?
By the way...
I realize you only just
assumed Polpo's position, but...
...he was assigned to a job
that he left unfinished.
Any unfinished business left by Polpo
is your responsibility, Buccellati.
Is that acceptable?
Polpo left an unfinished job?
A direct order from the boss, in fact.
The... boss?
The boss...
The boss no one has ever seen?
A direct order... from him?
Correct.
I'll tell you right now.
You'll be protecting
the boss's daughter...
...with your lives.
That's all.
Daughter?
The boss...
Did you say "daughter"?
The boss has a daughter?
The boss I'm trying to expose
and defeat has a daughter?
You'll be protecting her,
effective immediately.
She's in your care, Buccellati.
In my care?
B-Buccellati!
Could he be...?
No, not "he"!
She must be the boss's daughter!
That's her?
Do you mind if I use the restroom?
Not at all, Trish.
Go guard her, for now.
The order is already in effect.
Buccellati!
Her name is Trish Una.
She's fifteen years old.
Of course,
Una is her mother's last name, not the boss's.
Trish hasn't met the boss
once in her entire life.
Buccellati, as you're well aware,
no one knows the true identity of the boss.
But as you'd expect, even the boss has a past,
and an especially noteworthy youth.
About two months ago,
a woman named Donatella died of illness in Calabria.
A few days before Donatella's death, she suddenly had a search conducted for a man named Solido Naso.
That man was Trish's father.
She seemingly did it so that her only daughter,
having nowhere else to go, could find a place to call home.
Unfortunately...
Naso didn't exist.
The name was just an alias
used by the boss when he was young.
Correct?
Be wary of anyone
looking into the name Naso.
Anyone with any standing in Passione
knows that attempting to look into the boss's past...
...is tantamount to
challenging the organization itself.
Word about Donatella eventually spread.
It spread even further when
it was confirmed that she had a daughter.
The boss caught wind of it, too, of course.
He immediately took action.
Through his usual chain of command,
he gave me the order...
...and placed his daughter in my custody
soon after Donatella's death.
The boss must have known it instinctively...
He wasn't aware she existed until recently,
but now he knows beyond a doubt that Trish is his daughter.
Shortly after I took
Trish into my custody...
...we learned that someone searching for her
had just narrowly missed her.
If the boss's order had come even thirty minutes later, Trish likely would have been kidnapped, and then...
...murdered.
Who is it?
Who's after her?
Traitors in the organization.
We don't know how many there are.
They're attempting to defeat the boss
and assume control of his drug trafficking routes.
Drugs...
They seem to be under the impression that
Trish knows some sort of secret about the boss.
They want any intel
they can get to defeat him.
But Trish is just a frail little girl
who knows nothing of him.
How long will we be protecting her?
One week.
Actually, perhaps a bit less.
You'll watch over her until the boss
finds the traitors and disposes of them.
Leave this island immediately
and place her in hiding.
Only the boss and I
know that Trish is with you.
Mr. Pericolo...
Earlier you said the order
was given to Polpo, correct?
So I can only assume...
Your enemies are Stand users...
That's a safe assumption.
They're most likely
acting as a team, as well.
We don't know
how many of them there are.
I don't have a Stand ability, either.
This is all the help I have to offer.
I'll be in touch if anything comes up.
Umm...
M-Me?
Yes.
Do I have to stay... umm...
Will I have to stay with you
all the time from now on?
Yes, that's right.
With all six of us.
We'll risk our lives to protect you.
I see.
Then would you mind
removing your jacket?
My jacket? Why?
Just hurry and take it off.
It's not like I want to
see you shirtless or anything.
I-If that's what you want...
I don't have a handkerchief,
so go buy me one.
Also, get me some stockings
and Givenchy Blush No. 2.
Make sure they're
thigh high stockings.
Get the latest issue of Italian Vogue
and some mineral water, too.
I'd rather die than drink water
not from France.
Once you've finished staring at the scenery,
go get them all for me.
Protect the boss's daughter, huh?
So we suddenly have a connection to
the mysterious boss I've been searching for.
This is worth doing.
If we see this task through, Buccellati will
earn the same level of trust the boss had in Polpo.
But if we fail, it will mean our lives.
The six of us know this all too well.
What's the problem?
Calm down.
I just wanna pet you.
At 9:25 this morning at Naples Prison, Polpo shot himself in the head.
Hey, come on!
Quit squirming!
I can't read it! Jesus...
"At nine twenty-five this morning in Naples Prison,
Polpo shot himself in the head"?
Well, damn...
I was sure Polpo was the guy.
So who is it, then?
Who's the one protecting our elusive Trish?
Find them
Guess I don't have a choice...
"Find them," eh?
But who else is as reliable as Polpo?
Only a capo could land a gig like that.
And it's gotta be someone
with a Stand ability, too...
Is there anyone out there who could?
Shopping's all done!
Coast is clear!
Let's see...
If I head this way, then turn here,
I'll end up back on this street...
...and from there,
I need to go the opposite way.
Cool!
Narancia, listen carefully...
That list has all the food
and other things you need to buy on it.
Here's the keys to the car.
Narancia, you can do this.
I know you can pull it off!
That's not all.
No one knows there's anyone here.
Not even the people in the vineyard
who own the winery.
Once you finish shopping,
go in circles along the same path over and over again.
Throw in a few U-turns for good measure.
Constantly check if anyone is following you.
After that, you can come back here once you switch to
the car I arranged for you in one of the city's parking lots.
No one else knows we're
protecting the boss's daughter...
...but if someone is looking for us,
the last thing we want is for them to be able to follow us.
Do you understand?
Someone has to go shopping.
It's really important.
But we need to make absolutely sure that
no one finds out about our hide-
I get it, chatterbox!
I got this in the bag!
Good, then repeat everything
I just told you from the beginning.
Huh?
Once I'm done shopping,
I'll drive around in circles around the vineyard and-
Oww!
Wrong! Quit messing around!
From the top!
Huh?
Uh...
Drive around for a bit
so I don't get dizzy-
Urgh!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Help me out here, Abbacchio!
Tell Fugo to quit
stabbing me with the keys!
I'm older than him, dammit!
Now I'm worried about sending him out
shopping by himself!
Whether or not he gets stabbed
is between the two of you.
But even if someone does decide to follow Narancia,
his Stand ability should put a stop to them.
That's why Buccellati ordered
him to go shopping.
So basically, I just gotta make sure
nobody follows me back here, right?
No tagalongs!
This is weird...
It doesn't look like anyone's following me...
...but something feels off...
I have a bad feeling about switching
over to the car Fugo got for me...
Huh?
Guess I gotta do this, already.
Where do you think you're going?
Huh, Narancia?
That came from down here!
So, kid, where you headed?
You keep looking over your shoulder.
Someone tailing you or something?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, you're freaking me out!
Get the fuck out of my car, asshole!
I'm the one asking the questions here!
Don't answer a question with another question.
It's rude!
Shut the fuck up!
I said get out, dipshit!
Guess I gotta say it...
The name's Formaggio.
I'm a member of the organization.
You already heard
Polpo died yesterday, right?
Yet by complete coincidence,
you and your entire team happened to disappear all at once.
Oh no... This is not good...
He shouldn't know the truth,
but he's definitely after us!
That really ain't good...
I have something important I want to discuss with you guys.
I-Is he a Stand user?
Narancia, somehow I finally found you,
but where are the others?
Where are Buccellati
and the rest of your team?
No clue.
I have no idea where they are.
Did you check the local restaurants?
This car...
It's a rental, isn't it?
Buccellati was the one who rented it.
Why are you driving this car
if you didn't even know that?
Well?
I-I always drive around in Buccellati's cars...
I'm seventeen,
so I can't get my own yet.
That's why I'm borrowing his.
Oh, yeah, and did you hear?
Apparently the mortician is trying to figure out
how the hell to cremate Polpo's body.
Can't figure out how to
cram his body into the furnace.
They'll just have to chop him up
into itty-bitty pieces, huh?
Shut up!
Hey, you don't agree?
Huh?
Where'd he go?
There's no one here!
You really fell for it!
Guess you're just useless.
Narancia, I gotta ask...
Why would you go into hiding
during a capo's funeral?
Now you fucked up, asshole!
Since following you around isn't working,
I'm gonna make you talk!
You're gonna tell me everything
I wanna know right here and now!
Motherfucker...
Huh?
You motherfucker!
You're dead!
What the hell is that?
Aerosmith!
So he's a Stand user!
Little Feat!
Shit!
Look how much you made me bleed!
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
You're dead! You're dead! You're dead!
Th-This is looking dicey...
You're dead! You're dead!
Th-This guy!
You're dead!
Sh-Shit! He's out of his fucking mind!
He's going berserk
and shooting anything in sight!
And I'm stuck in this cramped car
with nowhere to run!
That's the diciest part of all of this!
A-A bomb?!
Light him up, Aerosmith!
How do you like that?
And that?! And that?! And that?!
You dead yet?
Oww! Fuck!
Did I do it?
H-He's gone!
Did the blast blow him away?
But wait...
There's no body parts inside!
Wh-Where did he go?
Guess he's clueless...
I'm right here.
I can shrink myself!
That's my ability!
Little Feat... Everyone always
tells me my ability is totally useless...
The way I see it, anything can be useful
with the right mindset.
That's how abilities work.
What the hell?
I can't find him anywhere!
This is weird!
Damn, where did he go?
Is he here?
He disappeared as fast as
he showed up in the car!
Well, good luck looking for me.
Where the hell did he come from?
I'm just gonna wait here
and buy myself some time.
He's gotta be hiding somewhere!
A woman...
This fucker bought stuff for a woman...
Stockings and blush...
And it's the good shit, too!
Who's he shopping for?
Is it for his mom or older sister?
No... Chicks are super picky
about that stuff...
...so they only buy fashion and
makeup stuff themselves.
The only kind of chick who'd
have a guy buy shit like this for them...
...is one who can't leave
wherever they're staying!
This is starting to get juicy...
Looks like my gut feeling was right!
It's them! It's gotta be!
Buccellati was ordered to
protect the boss's daughter!
Now that I know this, I'm gonna get Narancia
to show me where they're hiding.
My ability should start
taking effect any second now...
That motherfucker's gotta be
around here somewhere...
He's probably planning to
follow me back there...
But...
I'll find him and kill him first!
I just have to get back without being followed!
I'm gonna follow my orders!
Hitman Team