Destiny is mine osore shitte mo
Destiny is mine even if I'm afraid
subete no mirai togirenu you ni
So that our futures won't be cut short
Shoot a thread of light
itami o norikoeru tabi
Each time I overcome pain
kokoro wa eiri ni togisumasareru
My heart grows even sharper
(Never give up)
kurikaesareru shukumei no saihate de
At the far reaches of this looping fate
hikari chiru umi ni chikau
I pledge to the ocean that refracts light
Getting through ikiru imi o
Getting through to leave behind
sekai ni nokosu kara
What it means to live
Heaven’s falling down sora otoshite mo
Heaven’s falling down and the sky along with it
nozomi o kudakou kyouki no kami no
Yet I will still shatter the wishes of the god of madness
Destiny is mine osore shitte mo
Destiny is mine even if I'm afraid
subete no mirai togirenu you ni
So that our futures won't be cut short
tomosu honoo ga
I light a flame
inochi no kirameki - (Destiny will begin tonight)
The glimmer of life (Destiny will begin tonight)