This court sentences
the Defendant, Jolyne Cujoh...
You're one interesting girl.
So what'd you do?
What'd they nail you for?
I'm innocent.
...to serve fifteen years in
Green Dolphin Street State Prison.
What the hell is going on?!
You mean... you have an ability, too...?
Stone Free.
I'm going to break free
from this stone ocean.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 3  The Visitor Part 1
Stone Free.
In thread form, it can travel long distances.
However, it becomes less powerful
and more easily damaged.
It's stronger when it's clustered.
But as a result,
its range is limited to two meters.
Could I break through
these prison bars with Stone Free?
No, that wasn't possible.
The most it could do was...
The stone in the pendant
drew out my mental energy.
Using this power to break out...
...is beyond what I can do.
I need to start by learning
how this prison operates.
Hey, you.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Sorry, but can I borrow some change?
I've got some in my cell,
but my call's about to disconnect.
I'll go grab it for you as soon as I'm done.
Just a dollar will really help.
It's the first time I've
talked to my family in a while.
Sure.
Here.
Thanks! You're a lifesaver!
I'll pay you back as soon as I'm done.
Move it, bitch!
The fuck you think you're doing? No cutting!
Hold on!
I've been standing here in line
for thirty minutes waiting for that girl to finish!
You weren't even in line!
Dumb cunt. You new here?
You gotta reserve a phone in advance.
I wasn't told that!
Better remember, then.
The wait's usually about a month.
A whole month?!
Why do I have to wait so long
for just a few minutes on the phone?
One of the seven wonders of prison.
Hey you, can I buy your spot in line?
This is what we got wonders for.
I wanna call her...
I wanna hear her voice...
My mom's voice...
Jolyne!
Are you faring well?
Shut the fuck up and back off!
I told you not to talk to me!
Please don't resent me like that.
I just wanted to warn you.
What you did just now
was a big, big no-no.
What?
You loaned a dollar
to that blonde girl, right?
You better make her pay you back ASAP.
Actually, you better do it now
unless you want to be in deep shit.
What are you saying?
Of course I'll have her pay me back.
It's just a dollar.
Aha! "Just a dollar" she says!
That's the issue here!
The "just a dollar" mindset!
What?
Listen carefully, Jolyne.
At the Aquarium, loaning or borrowing money
with other inmates should be avoided at all costs.
Even "just a dollar."
Let's say you can't get blondie
to give you back your dollar.
What happens then?
You'll become like her.
"The new girl Jolyne couldn't even get back
the single dollar she loaned out."
The rumor will spread like wildfire...
...and they'll come looking for more.
Just like with her.
One after another, every single day.
You'll be forced to give up your body
and mind once you run out of money.
That's pretty much what
they say Hell's like, isn't it?
Hey, slow down.
You're exaggerating.
Am I, now?
She saw it as "just a dollar" at first, too.
You see blondie over there?
She just went back to her cell,
but it doesn't look like she's trying to find you.
I'm just trying to warn you,
for your own good.
Hi. Got a minute?
Oh, hello there.
I hear this one's a classic.
You read it?
No.
Anyway,
about the money for using the phone...
I just... wanted to know when I'd get it.
Oh, of course!
I didn't forget about the dollar.
Don't worry, I have it stored right up here.
I'll definitely pay you later.
You said the money was in your cell.
You went back, right?
Do you have it?
Will you put a sock in it?!
Saying I'll pay you later obviously means
I don't have it on me right now!
You some kinda cheapskate?
Come to think of it,
could you lend me ten more?
That way I can hit up my friends
on the outside for even more money!
Well? You have it, right? C'mon!
Huh...?
What?!
Sh-Shit!
Hey, you in there!
Do you, uh, mind hurrying up?
Can you hear me?!
C'mon! I'll pay you back!
I have the dollar!
Pay me back?
Weren't you gonna do that later?
Don't worry about it.
Take your time.
I'll pay! Please sell it to me!
I'll give you five... No, ten dollars!
Sold!
My bad!
But yeah, that'll be ten bucks.
Hey, you.
Go use the bathroom next.
Someone else is gonna be needing it soon.
It's up to you whether or not you can
get your money back, though.
The only one who can free you
from your current situation is you.
Wh-What the...?
I feel kinda...
That's right.
I need to free myself, too.
One way or another...
Inmate number FE40536.
I'm going back to my cell.
Please unlock the door.
Tomorrow at noon...
...someone will come visit you.
But you must not go.
You must not go to the visitation room.
If you do...
You and the people around you...
...will face something worse than death.
Was that...?
There's no way!
What's a kid doing in here?
Hey, you!
Didn't you hear me tell you
to stand back and wait?
No grabbing the bars!
Stand back!
Open the door!
Hurry!
I said no grabbing the bars!
Got word a visitor's
coming tomorrow at noon.
Not for you, of course.
For someone over there.
You get me?
Just some info for ya.
Oh, hang on...
You got them on backwards.
Your pants, I mean.
You're overreacting.
Sorry about yesterday, FE40536.
But it's your fault for
grabbing onto the bars like that.
Rules are rules.
I had already let go...
And you hit me twice...
What? Didn't quite catch that.
You say something?
No... Do you want something from me?
You got a visitor.
Stand up. I'll cuff you.
A visitor? Who is it? My mom?
How the hell should I know?
Arms out.
Feet planted on the markers.
I'll explain the rules.
The visit will be
no more than thirty minutes.
You can hold hands,
but no kissing or undressing.
Any gifts will be taken
and returned upon inspection.
No foreign languages.
The guards can end the visit
for any reason.
Wait there until you're cleared.
This is the boundary.
Give up on the visit
and go back to your cell!
You still have time!
Wh-Who are you?
What's a kid like you doing...?
I don't really get it either...
...but there are things in this world
even scarier than death.
Things that are definitely
happening in this prison.
So please, don't go!
Go back to your cell!
I can't.
The visitor has to be my mom.
I want to see her.
I know she wants to see me, too!
I need to let her know I'm doing okay
so she won't worry about me as much!
Take this with you.
Consider it a good luck charm.
All right, FE40536. Enter!
It's a bone!
What's the hold up?
Get in here!
Jolyne, did you get the pendant
I left with your mother?
Dad...
Star Platinum
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: Full
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: Full
Kujo Jotaro
Vehicular theft. A stolen wallet. Assault.
This must be a mistake!
My Jolyne would never...
Since she's just fourteen,
she won't be charged this time.
You're headed to Tokyo?
When this is happening
to your own daughter?!
Can't you postpone until tomorrow?
And you call yourself her father?
Wait... Hello? Hello?!
Jolyne, are you listening?
Where's the pendant?
That'll put me in
solitary for a while!
I wouldn't have come
if I knew it was you!
Hey, open the door! Hey!
Damn. Hit him too hard...
Get up already!
Gimme a break.
Jolyne, listen closely.
Your boyfriend Romeo isn't the one who planned
to frame you for murder and put you in prison.
Hey! Hey... Hey!
Johngalli A.
Currently being held
in the men's ward of the prison.
He's ex-military.
A trained sniper capable of hitting his mark
in winds up to twenty meters per second.
According to my investigations,
his vision's deteriorated due to cataracts.
He's the man behind it all.
Even the car accident.
One of Johngalli A.'s henchmen kidnapped
a passing hitchhiker and threw him in front of the car.
He also hired that greedy lawyer
and set up the trust-fund baby.
Johngalli A. coordinated it all from prison.
Help me, Jolyne!
Do you know what a plea bargain is?
I love you!
This court sentences
the Defendant, Jolyne Cujoh...
Fifteen years! Fifteen years! Fifteen years!
Son of a bitch!
You just had to hit me twice yesterday, didn't you?!
Fuck!
Why'd he do it?
Tell me why this asshole
wanted me thrown in prison!
Sit down.
Tell me!
I said sit down.
Listen.
You were Johngalli A.'s target all along.
He wanted to be able to eliminate you
from inside the prison whenever he chose.
But why?
Because we're connected by blood.
Joestar blood.
Joestar?
It's our ancestral family name
dating back a hundred-some-odd years ago.
Johngalli A. resents our bloodline.
Leaving a lasting impression on
someone's heart can be a wonderful thing.
But sometimes it leaves rubble in its wake.
Rubble that builds into a grudge.
A long time ago...
...I defeated a long-time
enemy of the Joestar clan.
Johngalli A. was a subordinate of that man.
We've never met,
but I'm sure of one thing.
Even though it's been
twenty years since then...
...his devotion to that man
is what's fueling his grudge.
I don't get it.
I thought you were just a scientist.
What's this about enemies and grudges?
Just know that you're being targeted.
I'm breaking you out ASAP.
We're going above the law.
Have you manifested a Stand ability?
Stand?
As my daughter, you have the potential
despite not inheriting one directly.
Did anything strange happen
after you got the pendant?
Seems so.
You have a Stand.
A Stand... So you do, too?
Use your power to break free.
Got it?
Give it a rest.
Don't get all fatherly on me now.
So you're finally here to rescue me.
You call that love?
You have no place in my heart.
But yeah, whatever.
I'll keep your "shocking" story
and that spiel about Stands in mind.
You can leave now.
And don't come back.
My handcuffs!
When did that...?
The brand changed.
Stranger still,
the guard never approached the desk.
Jolyne, get away from the door!
Star Platinum: The World!
Time, stop!
Wh-What the hell was that? Why?!
Hold still!
His attack's begun.
What's down the hallway to the right?
Any windows?
Yeah.
Two or three, but they're all barred.
This is the real deal...
It's a so-called "premium" sniper round
used in rifles.
Johngalli A. is definitely sniping us.
Hold on!
I thought he was just an inmate.
Inmates can't even have ballpoint pens.
Perhaps. But guns can be disassembled.
Broken down into small pieces,
they could be stowed in almost anything.
He probably had his subordinates bribe the guards
so he could bring in the items without inspection.
Little by little, slowly but surely.
Yeah, but we're in the women's ward!
There's no way he could aim at me from the men's ward!
We're inside a building!
There's obstacles everywhere!
A rifle and some kind of ability...
Basically, Johngalli A. is definitely a Stand user.
Look.
What's that?
You showed your face too clearly.
That obviously isn't just a pile of trash.
But it's moving.
It looks really light.
Like it's just drifting through the air.
Do nothing.
First, we have to figure out its ability.
It dodged!
That was reckless.
Can it see the thread?
Keep your voice down.
It's reacting to something.
But it wasn't your thread moving.
It's not moving in the same
direction as the thread.
Oh, is that what it's reacting to?
What's it called?
The way the thread moved caused it...
Like, the movement of the air?
Air currents?
So it knows where we are based on
the movement of the air currents?
But even if he knows where we are...
How can he fire live rounds at us
from the men's ward?
Good question.
Jolyne, you're lucky you survived earlier,
but it was a coincidence.
Don't move until we understand
how he's sniping us. Got it?
Don't order me around like
some pompous fucking asshole!
I already kn-
You... FE40536!
Do you have any idea
what you've done to me?!
Well?! Jolyne Cujoh!
It's coming for us!
It's reacting!
Your ass is going right
to solitary confinement!
Hey! Don't move!
No... I'll beat the shit out of you
before sending you there!
Calm down!
Jolyne, don't move from the wall.
I know!
Don't boss me around!
But we're fucked if I don't
knock this guy out again!
Who the hell do you think
you're talking to?!
You bitch!
Jolyne!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
The Visitor Part 2