His heart...
Why the hell isn't it beating?!
My dad isn't dead.
If I get his Stand back,
he'll come back to life.
I need to tell you something.
The name of the power that awoke in you...
...is called a Stand ability.
I gotta see her... Jolyne...
Cujoh Jolyne.
Punishment
Ward
Got it.
So Hermès knows about
Stands and the discs, too...
When she put the memory disc back
into that man named McQueen...
...he suddenly came back to life.
He was resuscitated.
If we can retrieve those discs,
then there's still hope for your father, Ms. Jolyne!
Tell me...
What did you do with the cleanup guy's discs?
I'm keeping them safe.
They're both here.
She said they'd be found during pat down
if she tried bringing them back to her cell.
I won't return the Stand disc,
but I'll give him back his memory disc later.
McQueen's memory disc...
There are memories
of Whitesnake on this thing.
Maybe even memories
about my dad's discs, too.
It's coming!
Help me close the f-fucking door!
I was just trying to
change the tractor tire!
All I did was touch it!
Come on!
Get the fuck outta there!
We gotta close the door!
Gimme a goddamn hand here!
O-Okay!
Thing weighs a ton...!
Put your back into it!
We almost got it!
Pull!
The hell's wrong with you?
I said pull harder!
Those aren't my arms...
Bro!
I know...
You weren't the one
not pulling hard enough...
...I was!
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 7  There's Six of Us!
Nice weather today, isn't it?
But Charlotte, what's all this fuss about?
Why did you gather everyone here?
Earlier this morning,
two inmates out at the farm vanished!
Seriously?!
Oh, that is terrible!
It's unthinkable that the inmates
escaped the prison from the farm.
Could they have fallen into the marsh?
Or been bitten by a venomous snake?
I think we have to look for them!
Why didn't you mention
that they could have been eaten by an alligator?
Maybe it was even female.
Who said that?
Who's spouting that malarkey?!
I didn't eat nobody!
I'm innocent!
So, anyway...
We're assembling a search party,
and you ladies will be in it.
There will be no compensation
nor sentence reductions for participation.
This is merely
an appeal for your sympathy.
Any volunteers?
Hold up, Jolyne.
You literally just got out of solitary.
Why're you trying to
wear yourself out already?
Maybe so I won't have to deal with you...
Huh...?
Good.
Five is plenty.
Guards, bring the goods.
In order to prevent escape attempts,
all inmates going to the farm must wear these bracelets.
"Like a Virgin,"
also known as invisible bars.
If you apply any force to these bracelets,
attempt to remove them...
...or manage to destroy them,
they will immediately explode.
They'll also explode if you exceed
fifty meters' distance from the base unit on my wrist.
Gonna be real tough
using the shitter with no hands.
All right you five, let's move!
Fifty meters?
He expects us to run?!
W-Wait up! Hey!
All right, from here we'll split up
and start searching.
See that grassy area?
That's an alligator-infested marsh right there,
so watch your asses!
Guess it's not in here.
Why'd you want to do this, Jolyne?
Well, this works out just fine for me.
I got a few questions for you.
About the whole disc situation
and that Whitesnake guy or whatever he's called.
Did you see?
What was on the disc?
The one from that inmate, McQueen.
Well, I tried to get a look-see...
...but it felt fucking gross.
Like it put some fucking
nasty-ass smell in my brain.
So you didn't notice, then.
Huh?
Whitesnake hinted at his intentions
in the footage on that disc.
McQueen...
This disc will suit you well.
It is yours.
Your Stand ability.
A tractor tire like they use on farms?
You telling me you saw one
loaded up with discs?
That's his goal.
He's been stealing and collecting Stands
and memories from other Stand users.
With the number of discs
he's gotten hold of...
...he'd need to hide them where other inmates
and guards wouldn't discover them.
So he went with a tire.
The discs with my dad's memories
and Star Platinum might be there, too.
Huh? Your dad's?
So you're looking for your dad's...?
Sorry. I don't really have
anything else on Whitesnake.
I'm gonna go find that tractor.
A tractor, huh?
Aren't there probably tons of those here?
That storehouse...
Yeah.
Hey!
You two look like you're havin' fun.
Havin' a little girly princess picnic?
You're not searching worth a shit, are ya?!
We are.
We think they might be in that storehouse.
We're going to look around.
Making us run after you earlier...
Who's really havin' fun here?
Hold it!
What the hell did you just say?
Nothing, really.
Just sayin' I'd sniff those guys out
like a good little doggy.
Damn! Loudmouth bitch...
Alligator shit?
I said hold it right there!
Are you disrespecting me?
A guard like me?
Oops!
Didn't mean to do that.
Can't help that my baton just
happened to hit your bracelet!
What's with the noise?
Why's it beeping at me?!
It's not like I hit it or nothing!
You only got yourself to blame!
I-It's not gonna explode, is it?
This isn't funny!
Please, stop the beeping!
Whoa, don't come near me!
What if it goes off while you're next to me?
Come on!
I'm sorry for what I said!
I really mean it!
Hey, careful now!
I told you to stay back!
I just want you to stop the fuckin' noi-
Boom!
Yeah! That'll show ya!
Eat alligator shit!
It stopped...
Come on, there's no need to freak out
and lose your balance, Hermès.
The beeping's just a warning sound.
Right, Mr. Guard?
So that's your ability, huh?
What the hell...
Just a tractor and
some bags of flour in there?
No point even going inside.
They wouldn't need a stupid search party
if they could be found here, anyway.
Seriously?
It's gotta be in here, Jolyne!
It's identical...
It looks exactly like the tractor
I saw in the footage on the disc.
Same number, too...
Stone Free
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Cujoh Jolyne
It's the same tractor number...
Number four.
Inside that tire...
If we take it off, we'll find the discs...
Listen up!
We're gonna do a sweep
of the marshlands!
The missing inmates
might've drowned in the water!
Now get searching!
Yo, are you for real?
You expect me to jump in the water?
I ain't doin' that.
Get a move on!
That thing works in water, too?
No fucking way.
God knows what diseases
we'll get goin' in there!
Is he serious?
Let's get it off.
We gotta remove the tire!
Hey, Jolyne...
Is it just me,
or does something feel off?
I mean, there's some
bizarre shit going down.
Yeah. If we don't get this tire off now,
the guard's gonna get too far away.
Not that!
Didn't the warden say
there was five of us?
Before we left,
he said five inmates was enough...
...but now there's six of us!
Hey Jolyne, what the hell is going on?
Including us two...
...there's six of us here!
There were definitely
only five of us when we left!
Unfortunately,
I didn't pay attention to their faces.
Jolyne, what do you think?
I'm not sure.
I was so focused on running.
But it looks like
we're all wearing bracelets.
How weird...
Were there always six of us?
The entire time?
H-Hey, you there!
You got the same idea?
You think there was only
five of us to start with?
Do you know who joined us and when?
Not really.
I could be mistaken.
And I don't think it really matters
how many of us there are.
She's been with me since we left.
I remember her.
Her name's Etro.
She's always getting bullied.
You volunteered so you could
get away from the bullies, right?
I don't know who you are.
H-Hey!
Wh-What's going on?
Why is my bracelet beeping?
Damn! Mine, too!
Same here!
What the hell?
They're all beeping!
The bike is fifty meters away!
But how'd it get that...?!
Th-The guard is gone!
Where did he go?
The bike's covered in blood!
Wh-Why?!
The fact that the bracelets keep beeping means
the guard's body is moving farther away from us!
Did he fall in the water
and get caught in a current?
We gotta find him!
He's gotta be within fifty meters!
This fucking sucks!
H-Hey!
My bracelet's beeping faster!
Th-The fuck?!
Sh-She's dead...
No way...
Did the extra person decide to strike?
Is it because we got too close
to the storehouse with all the discs?
Look fifty meters the opposite way
from where that girl blew up!
There he is!
We need to get to him!
If we get close,
the beeping'll stop and we won't blow up!
Stay sharp, Jolyne.
One of those three is the enemy!
And they're a fucking psycho!
That one's real suspicious...
That chick with the crop cut.
The girl who blew up
said she didn't know her.
It's gotta be her!
She offed the guard with her Stand!
We gotta get the bitch
before she gets us!
Hold on, Hermès.
Let's say crop cut girl
even is the killer.
Wouldn't that mean she was guarding the discs
in the storehouse since before we got here?
Yeah, that makes sense.
But that's impossible.
She's still an inmate.
There's no way an inmate
could keep watch 24/7.
Jolyne, stay back!
There's something there!
Where?
Just stay back!
Stay the fuck
away from the water!
Hermès, did you see something?
Nah.
It was nothing.
Still, I'm not getting
in that fucking marsh ever again.
Anyway, Jolyne...
We gotta stick together,
no matter what.
'Cause we still don't know
who the enemy is.
You're right.
And these bracelets just make things harder.
To get the discs from the storehouse, we have to stay within
fifty meters of the other inmates and the guard's body.
Hermès?!
What... was in this bucket?!
My face got sucked in!
Wh-What's that plankton thing?
What?
It split in two!
Wait, now there's four!
What are they?!
The bucket wasn't empty at all!
I just wasn't looking close enough!
There were already a bunch in the water!
K-Kiss!
Hermès!
Jolyne, stay back!
The water's dangerous!
They're multiplying!
They're like, proliferating or whatever!
Get away from the water!
You'll never catch up!
The Stand was counting on it!
Stone Free!
I'm gonna smash it!
Jolyne!
You're walking on woven threads?
But doesn't that mean
you're also losing a ton of body mass?
Jolyne, stay back!
I can save myself!
Ora!
No way!
Yeah... You're right...
It feels impossible...
Gimme a break.
I'd be dead right now
if I hadn't laid out so much thread.
Its power...
H-Her torso is hollow...
She let the thing punch her
so she could grab its arm!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Jolyne, we gotta get the fuck
outta the water!
Don't stand up yet, Hermès!
That's a bunch of tiny Stands
clustered together!
They were hiding in the water at the bottom of the bucket.
They dragged me in with them!
I know that.
That's why I'm telling you
not to stand up.
You gotta grab it underwater...
My thread is coming your way!
It's quick...
It's insanely fast and strong!
What the hell is it?
Stands are supposed to get weaker and slower
the farther they get from their user.
S-Son of a bitch!
Calm down, Jolyne.
I put a sticker on it.
Back when it had me in its arms.
This is my Stand.
Now to rip it off!
Land! Get on land!
I-It won't go on land.
I figured it could only
attack in the water.
Answer me, please!
This is inmate FE32125.
It's an emergency!
The guard got in an accident.
Somebody hurry up and help us!
What the hell were you two doing?
Looked like you were runnin' on water.
Hold the fuck up!
Don't move a fucking muscle!
You three, get away from the water!
Don't try pulling a fast one.
One of you three is the killer!
Looks like if we want to
get our hands on the discs...
...we'll have to beat the user first.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Foo Fighters