Father...
My incarceration has shown me
how truly foolish I once was.
The person I was, who felt compelled to steal,
unable to deny the allure of theft...
It brings me great shame.
You saved me, Father.
Would you consider
helping me receive early parole?
Recent studies have shown that...
...given proper training, even dogs and parrots
can learn to read, use fire, and comprehend art.
If this is true,
what is it that separates man and beast?
Your thoughts?
I couldn't say...
Anyway, concerning my parole-
A moment, please.
Pardon?
There.
The point, as it were...
After finishing the first cherry and leaving it in your mouth,
which tooth would you bite the second with?
If you bite the first seed that you took
such great effort to complete, it would not be good.
Right...
So, what about my parole?
I may be able to help.
Will you really, Father?
I'll recommend you to the committee.
Thank you, Fa-
I'm quite fond...
...of how light-fingered you are.
One lacking virtue cannot be saved.
However, you possess undeniable skill.
I shall put it to good use.
I cannot allow Jotaro's Stand
to leave this prison, you see.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 9  Debt Collector Marilyn Manson
Huh?
Whaddya mean you had F.F. hide it?
It's really important, isn't it?
The disc with your dad's Stand.
You sure you're okay
not knowing where she...?
Can we really-
I'm having a blast here!
It's nothing like the swamp!
Yeah?
We should play that game, too!
It's called Catch, right?
I trust F.F.
Whitesnake probably doesn't
even know she's alive.
It's safest this way.
Fair enough, I guess.
But it'd be even better just to get
the disc to your dad ASAP, right?
I know.
But after the jailbreak,
I had my phone and visitation rights revoked.
I'm still figuring out how
to get the disc out of here.
Hey, you!
What do you think you're slurping on?!
Huh? What's your damage?
I'm thirsty.
Put that cup back on the bench
right where you found it!
If you care so much,
you shouldn't have left it there.
Especially in a place like this.
Foo Fighters, I'll get you more water!
Don't make a scene!
Give that back!
Well, I guess it's fine.
Got more water than I started with.
Lucky me!
All right...
Let's play some Catch!
Huh?
Have you, like,
never thrown a ball in your life?
Whoa.
Bring your hips in.
Little more...
Getting the hang of it, now!
Jolyne, guess what?
We've tossed the ball
eighty-six times now.
And we haven't dropped it once!
Think we can reach a hundred?
A hundred dollars says you can't.
I'll bet you one hundred dollars.
Sorry, but who are you?
What do you mean "a hundred dollars?"
I'm Milaschön, inmate number FE26789.
I'm betting a hundred dollars that you won't
reach a hundred throws in a row.
I don't get your angle here.
Just killing some time.
Let's do it!
We just need thirteen more!
You keep your mouth shut!
I don't got that kind of money.
I can't match your bet.
I'm fine taking valuables, too.
Tobacco, drugs, chewing gum,
a phone call, vibrator...
Anything of value.
I'll be straight with you.
I'm not betting.
Hold on a sec...
Hey, Jolyne...
We should play along.
This could be our lucky break.
I can lend you the money.
F.F. might be shit at playing Catch,
but she still got to eighty-seven.
We got this!
Hermès, seriously...
Ah, you think this is one of
Whitesnakes's traps, is that it?
But I know this Milaschön girl.
We're on the same floor.
She's one of those greedy,
self-destructive types: a petty thief.
Think about it...
Even after you get your privileges back,
you'll need money to get phone time.
Hey...
You game or what?
I wanna do it!
We can win!
Good.
But do you even have
a hundred on you?
If you raise your voice or get too close,
the bet is immediately off.
Got that?
So we've already started?
But it's not a fair bet if you stand too close
or hold the ball for too long.
We'll stay at least three meters apart
and throw within ten seconds.
Good.
Okay, let's do this thing!
Throw calmly!
Don't forget you have
a whole ten seconds to work with!
Eighty-nine.
Just eleven to go!
Back away from the water, bitch!
F.F.!
Th-That was close!
Eyes on the ball!
That's not it!
It's her!
She got near my water!
I'm just watching.
You better stay away from my cup!
Fine...
Five seconds left.
F.F., throw the ball!
Damn, she's distracting me!
Here, I'll hold your cup for you!
One second.
F.F.!
Shit!
I-Idiot!
Jolyne!
That was too close!
But she got it!
Sorry. I panicked.
Try to be more careful next time, F.F.
I'm good, now!
See? A hundred throws!
Good.
I could go another hundred throws!
See? Easy win.
Now, cough up the hundred dollars.
Wait, didn't she bet with F.F. too?
So shouldn't that be
two hundred dollars?
Yeah! It should be two hundred!
Come on, fork it over.
A thousand dollars says you
can't throw a hundred more.
Didn't you hear me?
I'm asking you to play
for a thousand dollars.
Seriously?
You got that kind of money?
Of course.
But like I said,
I'll take any valuables, too.
Rules stay the same as last time.
How about it?
No, I'm done playing with you.
I'll be honest...
You're giving me bad vibes.
If you wanna keep gambling, then-
You're on.
Good.
F.F., hand me the ball and glove.
Okay!
Hermès!
Jolyne, she's giving me bad vibes, too.
Especially how much
she wants to keep betting.
But still...
Considering between both bets
we could be up twelve hundred dollars...
...there's no way I can pass this up!
Better be careful, though.
The game began
the moment you agreed to play.
The clock's ticking.
Hermès!
F.F.!
Another easy win!
Thirty.
Thirty-one.
Thirty-two.
Okay, the next one makes thirty-three.
All right ladies, pack it up!
Exercise time is over!
Five seconds...
F.F.!
Thirty-three!
Bitch!
Do we got us an attitude problem?!
Look, we're calling off the bet. Got it?
Suppose a meteor fell from the sky
and landed out here in the yard.
You would probably claim the game is invalid,
blaming the meteor.
Not to convince me,
but yourselves.
Are you really okay with that?
Perhaps you ran out of time because
you took too long to throw the ball.
If you can honestly say that you
didn't break the rules of the game...
...then you can go ahead and call it off.
Dammit...
Hermès...
Hope you're ready for some
alone time in solitary!
Please, sir...
Give me five-
no, even just three minutes.
I'll go make another round,
so make it two minutes.
F.F., hurry!
But a measly hundred bucks
only covers the ball!
The glove's going away.
Hand it over!
What the...?!
Dammit!
Shit...
I had a sticker ready just in case
something like this happened!
Hermès!
Whoa!
Let's keep going.
I'm just watching.
I won't act against you,
nor will I plot against you.
But, while I can't prove it...
Hermès...
She knows full well.
There's no doubt.
She just broke the rules.
I know this...
...because the debt collector,
Marilyn Manson, has appeared.
Hermès!
She's a Stand User!
Marilyn Manson
always collects its dues.
No matter where you hide it,
or what it is, nothing is left behind.
Still not enough.
Kiss...
It's game over.
Hermès!
Hermès...
If I sell this liver on the black market...
...it will make up for the
remaining 590 dollars.
Bitch! Take this!
I am the shadow of Hermès' heart.
You cannot attack me.
Hermès broke the rules and
lost the bet of her own accord.
I simply collected her debt.
Do you have any other valuables?
If so, I'd be willing to exchange them for her liver.
We're not done betting.
What?
One thousand throws.
If I win, you'll give back
everything you took from her.
All of it!
Good.
As such, I hope you're prepared
to wager something of equal value.
I am.
Fine, then.
The game has already started.
I'll see you again.
F.F.!
J-Jolyne...
Hermès, this isn't your fault.
Since Milaschön is a Stand User...
...there's a good chance
Whitesnake is involved somehow.
If he is, their goal must be
getting my dad's disc back.
Isn't that... a good reason
not to go along with this shit?
You basically got roped
into my family's problems.
I can't let you die.
But what will you do?
A thousand throws?
She seems unbeatable.
Yeah, which is why...
...we'll chase Milaschön down
and attack her head-on!
Her Stand might be unbeatable,
but the user isn't.
That's why she ran.
Let's go!
She's here.
She must have come through here.
There's a door to the back.
Maybe she escaped that way.
F.F.!
Jolyne! Don't throw it!
Shit!
F.F.! The ball's headed your way!
Where is it?
I can't see!
Don't move!
The ball will hit you!
Yes! I got it!
C-Close one!
You did it, F.F.!
Now keep calm and toss it back.
Over here!
Where's "here"?
Hurry!
It's already over.
F.F.!
Enough of this shit!
Foo Fighters.
I shot in the direction of her voice.
Didn't need to be exact!
Dammit!
What the hell is she?
It's almost time for lockdown.
All inmates, return to your cells
and remain standing until role call begins.
I repeat...!
She went right!
Ora!
Sucks for you.
There's nowhere left to run.
Now that I know that you're a Stand User,
I won't hold back.
W-Wait...
I'll give it all back!
Her liver, and even the money!
That's not enough.
Who gave you that Stand ability?
Huh?
Whitesnake?
Was it?
I want to know who its user is.
Wh-What are you talking about?
You have the time to play dumb?
I'm serious!
I just wanted to be paroled!
Is this a...?
It's an elevator.
It's for transporting cafeteria food.
How many more seconds?
Six?
Or maybe five?
Jolyne!
Two seconds...
F.F., the ball!
Throw it to me!
Shit!
So, now what will you do?
Eight seconds left.
Seven... Six...
F.F.!
Will this do, Milaschön?
What a tasty little request you cooked up!
Ask me again anytime.
This game of Catch...
...was just interrupted.
It's game over!
Cujoh Jolyne!
Marilyn Manson
always collects its dues!
No matter where you hide it...
...even if you don't know where it is...
...Marilyn will find it!
Jolyne!
I'll take your most expensive organ.
And for the remainder...
...your most prized possession:
your dad's disc.
And that disc...
...was on her person since the beginning!
I won!
Your organ!
Your disc!
They're both mine now!
This game of Catch isn't over yet.
B-But how?
The ball...
Impossible.
That's against the rules!
No.
We never agreed on my partner.
The guard counts too, right?
Seems the debt collector agrees.
So, how many throws do I have left?
Eight hundred?
Or was it nine hundred?
I can't be fucked to count...
...so here's a thousand!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
We did it!
MILASCHÖN
STAND NAME:
DEBT COLLECTOR MARILYN MANSON
BEYOND RECOVERY
Whatever it takes,
I'll give my dad his disc back.
Both it and the one still with Whitesnake.
I swear it.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Op: Savage Garden (Reach the Courtyard!)
Part 1