Hold the fuck up!
Don't move a fucking muscle!
You three, get away from the water!
Don't try pulling a fast one.
One of you three is the killer!
Killer?
Killing the guard and
trying to drown us just now...
I know it was one of you!
If we don't figure out which one
snuck into our group, we're all fucked!
What are you talking about?
I said don't move, bitch.
Didn't the girl who blew up
say she didn't know you?
What about you two?
Do either of you remember
seeing her when we started?
I don't remember you two, either.
Seriously?
You don't remember I was with you from the start?
Can't say I do remember you.
Hey!
Nobody knows
who the fuck you are, either!
Yeah, well I'm the one
who just called for help on the radio!
Maybe you're just playing us!
Wait a second...
You, with the black hair...
Your nose is bleeding.
What the...?!
I didn't get a good look earlier, but...
Hermès, when I punched the enemy Stand,
one of them stumbled a bit.
Back the fuck up!
Stay away from the water!
Hold on, you're wrong!
I'm bleeding 'cause that bitch
just hit me in the face!
L-Look! She's bleeding, too!
What the fuck?!
I barely scraped her teeth!
I know I've been here all along!
It's gotta be one of you two!
Listen, I remember what happened
with that alligator warden!
You were the one making a scene!
Yeah, that's true...
Honestly, you guys are
pretty suspicious yoursel-
Jo-Jolyne?!
Is it her? The black-haired girl?
How'd you know it was her?
To be honest, I have no idea...
...so I'll just beat all three of them up!
You...
You filthy fucking pig!
Sh-She's...!
I was going to finish you off
one at a time in the water...
Who would've thought she had some kind of
thread power to get her out of that one?
Wh-What the fuck
is wrong with them?!
I-It was all three of them?!
The fuck is happening?!
Which one's the user?!
You don't get it!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Each Stand user...
...has just one Stand ability.
The black-haired girl and crop cut girl
were here from the start.
I took care of them once they
got near the tractor.
Then I possessed their minds and bodies.
As for my own body...
I made it out of scraps
of the missing inmates' flesh!
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 8  Foo Fighters
That black goop's pouring out of them
and gathering together...
My divided body is whole once again.
For the sake of the memories and ability
Whitesnake's discs granted me...
...I will defend myself at any cost.
My mission is to honor my debt to him by disposing of
anyone who comes near the discs in the storehouse!
Dammit...
So where even is the Stand user?
You're not getting it, Hermès.
That thing is the Stand user!
What?
It's a living being.
A living creature born in the water
that gained an ability through the discs.
The discs weren't even
being guarded by a human.
L-Living being?
So it's just a bunch of those
tiny fuckers clumped together?!
It was able to defend the discs
in the storehouse on land...
...by using the water stored
in the bodies of its victims.
It survives on land
through fission and propagation.
However, it needs to replenish its supply of water,
like how a car needs gas to run.
If we want to get the discs, we need to beat
this thing while keeping it away from the water!
Even if all that's true, Jolyne,
how is that plankton-thing fucking talking?!
Foo Fighters!
Use my name when referring to me!
An astronomer named Fred Hoyle once said...
"It is probabilistically wrong to assume
that life was born spontaneously on Earth.
The power of intellect already existed in this universe,
and it created the origin of life."
This means intellect existed
long before the Big Bang...
...and all organisms and substances
already possessed intellect.
Wh-What the fuck is it going on about?
It's saying that being human
isn't the reason we have intelligence.
Even plankton like it can have memo-
Didn't I just tell you
to call me Foo Fighters?!
My intelligence far exceeds yours!
This is bad!
It wants to hide the discs
before we can reach them!
We'll never find them
if it buries them underground!
Jo-Jolyne, we're in trouble here, too.
Look behind us...
The one that attacked us
underwater earlier is here!
It's trying to grab the guard!
He's got the bracelet!
We're only safe within fifty meters!
W-We're done here, Jolyne.
Forget about the discs.
We need to focus on
keeping the guard's body safe!
Our bracelets are gonna explode!
I'll leave the bracelet to you, Hermès.
Huh?
Before I put fifty meters
between myself and the guard's body...
...you have to protect it
and keep that bracelet within my range!
It's the only way!
Hey, hold on!
Damn, this bitch is crazy!
Batshit insane!
Wh-Why would she leave that to me?
But goddammit...!
If it pulls the guard in,
then no matter what, we're both gonna explode!
I don't have time to stop and think!
Fuck yeah, I did it!
But I'm never gonna use
my sticker this way again...
Using it to give myself an extra arm...
This is gonna hurt like a bitch!
Just gotta carry him within
fifty meters of the storehouse...
Water?
You goddamn plankton!
That scream...
You think you've won?
This is the body of the crop cut girl
your buddy dried to the bone.
A body drained of all water.
And my sticker made a copy of her.
When I pull it off...
It'll absorb water like a maxi pad!
So in other words,
you're like a drop of water in the desert, huh?
Shut the fuck up!
You're in my way!
Get lost!
Jolyne...
We need to dry it out.
That's the only way we'll win
against these plankton motherfuckers!
I didn't think you'd make it.
I'll kill you both, regardless.
I was planning to take my time
and interrogate you after hiding the discs.
But no matter.
So tell me...
Will you step into this puddle?
Or will you try to escape?
How would you like to die?
I have some questions, too.
Do you know who he is?
Whitesnake?
Also, what is he collecting
these discs for and why?
Intriguing.
I can understand why
you attack in self-defense.
Even fighting to protect your allies...
I can't relate,
but I understand the reasoning behind it.
Yet above all else,
I don't understand why you would come here to die.
So, who is Whitesnake, you ask?
Who knows? I've never seen him.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Thought you could distract me?
A pathetic plan!
These puddles are all part of me!
Were you trying to break open
a bag of flour to soak up the water?
However you look at it,
I fully grasp the extent of my ability...
...and have crafted a no-lose scenario.
Living inside your body for a short time
may not be so bad.
Wrong.
You already lost.
This scenario you crafted by
spilling water all over the floor...
You fucked yourself.
It seems like you didn't hear me
start up the tractor with my string.
The water drowned out the sound.
You were too preoccupied with killing me...
...which means you've left
the discs unguarded.
D-Damn you!
You'll never have them!
Those discs are my...
The dirt in these fields is a lot softer
than the stuff near the wetlands.
It's sucking up all the water in your body.
And where you're going,
there won't be any water!
I won't let you lay
a single finger on those di-
Jolyne won this battle of wits.
They're not your discs anymore.
You're finished!
Dry up and become crop fertilizer!
Jolyne?
Jolyne, what the hell's gotten into you?!
I'm giving it water.
I guess I'm saving it.
Uh?
Foo Fighters...
He wasn't guarding the discs
out of loyalty to Whitesnake.
I can see that now.
Even though his body was falling to pieces,
he kept chasing after the tractor.
He protected the discs
to protect his own existence.
Because his intellect and ability
were granted by the discs...
...he risked his life to repay the debt
he felt he owed for being given life.
He doesn't care about Whitesnake at all.
Yo, you really wanna save it?
It murdered five people!
The thing's not even human for fuck's sake!
Can you really blame him for anything
if he isn't even human?
Whitesnake's the bad guy here.
Whitesnake only gave him
enough information to take advantage of him.
And I have another reason
for saving his life.
Let's make a deal.
Keep guarding these discs,
same as you have been.
But do it for us.
Protect them from Whitesnake.
We don't want to steal
the discs from you.
I only want my dad's discs back.
And I want to know
what Whitesnake's planning.
Well? Will you help us?
All I ask is you stop killing people.
Jesus...
You're something else...
I don't quite understand your feelings,
but I no longer wish to fight.
And I have lost...
Utterly and completely.
DISC
OBTAINED
SUNBURN: NO CORPSE
CROP CUT: NO CORPSE
BLACK HAIR: DRIED CORPSE
ETRO: DIED IN EXPLOSION
Foo Fighters
Power: B
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: B
Power: B
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: B
Foo Fighters
They really were in the tire!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
We finally found it!
It's Star Platinum!
Jolyne?!
Are you okay? Hey!
No doubt about it...
This is Star Platinum's disc.
My dad, Kujo Jotaro,
can recover using this!
I finally found it!
But I'm not seeing
his memory disc anywhere in here...
Where could it be?
Say...
You think I'd die if I were to
jump from that skylight?
C-Come on, give a gal a break! I'm him!
Foo Fighters!
But F.F. is cool, too.
I put her back together with whatever pieces I could find
and slapped on another inmate's bracelet.
I think I wanna live in her body
for a little while!
These fingers are kinda useless now, though...
Did you say, "live in her body?"
You mean you wanna live in her cell,
as a prisoner, pretending to be her?
Jolyne...
I want to protect you.
According to the memory in this body,
my name is Etro.
Inmate number FE39423.
Her childhood dream was to get kidnapped.
But when she grew up,
she ended up kidnapping a child herself.
She wasn't after a ransom.
She just kinda... did it.
Huh?
Your arms are bleeding.
Does it hurt?
Nothing I can do to heal them, though.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
Water! It's water!
So, like... Your whole plan to, like...
go to the prison...
Maybe save it for when you
learn to drink out of a cup...
A cup?
I can do that, no problem!
Drinking from a cup is easy!
Hey, I have a question
for you about Whitesnake.
Does he come here often?
Nah, he never comes near here.
Never seen the user, either.
These are the discs that he didn't need.
No matter how strong the Stand is,
the body rejects the disc if it's incompatible.
So these discs are
basically worthless to him.
He must keep the good ones
tucked away somewhere.
That's why the memory disc
you're looking for isn't in the pile.
His goal wasn't to steal a strong,
unbeatable Stand from your dad.
He wanted his memories.
Your dad must be keeping
one juicy secret.
A secret...
Guards are here.
What's the plan Jolyne?
What are you gonna do
with Star Platinum's disc?
The next step...
...is to find a way to smuggle the disc out of prison,
then get it to the foundation that's treating him.
If we don't get him back soon,
his body will start to decay.
The disc with his memories...
I'm getting it back, sooner or later.
You wanna smuggle it out of prison?
It's harder sneaking stuff out than in.
And once the guards get here,
they're gonna pat us down.
Lemme see that disc for a sec.
Let me just give myself
a little upper body boost...
You like?
F.F., raise your hands so you don't get shot.
You, too, Hermès.
The guard was attacked by an alligator.
We saved him.
Unfortunately, we have no idea
what happened to the other inmates.
That's our story, got it?
She was mere bait.
The daughter was merely bait
to lure in Jotaro.
I assumed there would be
no risk in leaving her be...
Cujoh Jolyne...
Did she defeat my guard
and take the discs by herself?
Or could the two surviving inmates
have aided Jolyne?
'Scuse me, but the sun's about to set.
We need to head back to the prison.
Are you that worried
about the missing inmates...
...Father Pucci?
A while longer.
After all, I'm on overnight duty
until I lead service on Sunday.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Debt Collector Marilyn Manson