wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don’t wanna say (There’s no chance)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let’s get started, count (One, two, three)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don’t stop beatin’ don’t stop beatin’
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don’t stop beating ’em up
Don't stop beating 'em up
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today