Hey... Did you know this, Pucci?
The Louvre in Paris receives an average
of forty-thousand visitors each day.
Every day since its doors
first opened in 1793...
...more than forty-thousand people flock to
view the Mona Lisa and the Venus de Milo.
No one leaves without
having seen both pieces.
Is that not incredible?
Incredible?
You mean the number of visitors?
Not quite.
Moreso that master sculptors and painters give
physical form to their souls, which the naked eye may behold.
As if creating Stands
which transcend time and space.
Do you disagree?
Well, it's certainly intriguing...
...but does that mean Leonardo da Vinci
and Alexandros of Antioch were Stand users?
You know, I was referring to you, as well.
Your Whitesnake can
give form to and store souls.
Will you betray me one day?
Why do you not attack me?
You know of my weakness to sunlight
and how I sleep in darkness during the day.
You could cut off
my head while I slept.
If you turn The World
into a disc and take it...
...you could become a king.
Do it.
The thought never
even occurred to me.
I'm fond of those
who help me grow.
You are a king among kings.
I'd like to follow you
as a witness until the end.
I love you as I love God.
My apologies.
I seem to have offended you.
I never could have conceived of a human being
capable of calming my soul with their words.
I feared you would disappear.
You have the makings
of a proud clergyman.
Please, accept this.
A token of my remorse.
I have taken it from my own flesh.
Wherever you find yourself,
my power will be with you.
Episode 22  Time of Heaven and New Moon! New Priest!
Jo...
Jolyne!
Whitesnake.
Read Jolyne's whereabouts
from the memory on that disc.
Respond.
What happened?
Is that you?
Respond.
Can you not hear me?
Why is there
a transceiver on the ground?
Whose voice is this?
Who?
Wh-Who on earth is this?!
Copy.
I understand.
So serious you can't respond, huh?
I just left the Medical Wing.
This is...!
...Weather Report!
Th-This rain...!
The disc!
That little...!
She had Weather Report summon rain!
I cannot let you escape!
Th-This is...!
I can't see!
Where is she?
A-And now there's fog...
This sound of stones
knocking against one another...
It's Morse Code!
Make the fog thicker...
I'm being pursued.
Whitesnake's user is Father Pucci!
I've been had...
My true identity exposed...
...to Weather Report!
Five hundred three...
Count the prime numbers.
Five hundred nine...
Five hundred twenty-one...
No one can divide prime numbers.
The reason people lose...
Five hundred twenty-three...
...is due to their shame.
Men die because of shame.
Five hundred forty-one...
Regret born of shame bears thoughts
such as "Why did I do that?"...
...which weakens men
and leads to their defeat.
The guard's transceiver
escaping my notice was not a failure.
It was a trial.
I must reframe it as such
to emerge triumphant.
It's not as though my identity has been
revealed to Cujoh Jolyne as of yet.
Nothing has changed yet.
I haven't completely lost her, either.
True victors...
...are those who reign supreme
over the circumstances they're dealt.
So you made it out alive.
Weather Report!
Where are Jolyne and the others?
Annasui...
There's no way I could ever
thank you enough.
Thank you.
You've kept me safe.
But why did you
do all of this for me?
Finding out Whitesnake's identity and getting
my father's memory back are my problems, and mine alone.
Jolyne, how can you say that
when you very well know of my feelings for you?
You've already given me so much.
I see hope in you that I've found nowhere else,
neither here in prison, nor outside.
That's why I'm here.
Hey, what's this?
What is it doing?
Got me.
"Got me" isn't an answer!
It's chewing on my hair!
It's eating dirt, too.
So is it actually a plant after all?
Does it need nutrients?
But it goes right to sleep, huh?
Jolyne, get down!
Something is coming.
There's two of them,
and they've already closed in on us!
F.F.!
Jolyne... I know who Whitesnake is...
It's Father Pucci, Jolyne!
It was Father Pucci all along.
That was a close one...
If Weather Report hadn't
come for me, I'd be dead.
F.F.!
Listen, I'm fine.
I just got rid of my body.
But Jolyne,
what happened to you guys?
Let me heal your eye.
What you said just now...
Yeah. Father Pucci was trying to figure out
the baby's location from D&G's memory.
All we have to do now is corner him.
We're this close to winning!
And now Weather Report is here, too.
Weather Report.
Jolyne...
Are your wounds from
the factory healed up now?
Yes. I hope you've been well.
Hey, what the fuck is this?
What do they think they're doing?
They're hugging.
No shit!
Tear them apart, F.F.!
Do it right now!
Me?!
Yeah, you!
Remember that agreement of ours?
That douchebag's B.O.
is getting all over her!
Calm down! It's just a greeting!
See? They're done.
You're so melodramatic.
We just learned
Whitesnake is the priest.
There's no time for petty bullshit.
Hey, are you giving me sass?
Who do you think you are?
How dare you forget our promise?!
You're just fucking plankton!
Jolyne, now that we know who Whitesnake is,
we don't need this thing anymore.
It serves no purpose.
Let's kill it.
Just say the word, Jolyne.
H-Hold on!
It's not an ally, Jolyne.
It's not even human!
It shouldn't even
exist in the first place!
That thing is less than an animal,
and never should have been born.
Something so incomprehensible
should be disposed of.
Just say the word.
Hey! Watch it, Annasui.
Does that include me?
Watch your mouth!
Hands off!
Now isn't the time, plankton.
Weather Report,
you know the situation, right?
Tell me to do it.
No. I can't do that.
You're the one who will die.
Wh-Who the fuck
did you bring here, F.F.?!
D-Damn you...
D-Dammit! I'm done for!
No way!
Th-This isn't... It can't be!
He's not Weather Report...
He's...
He's...!
We were seeing... an illusion...
You have my sincere gratitude
for bringing me here, Foo Fighters.
For the opportunity to arrive here
before the real Weather Report catches up!
Five hundred forty-seven...
Five hundred fifty-seven...
Prime numbers can be
divided by no one.
It's been so long...
Twenty-two years I've waited...
Climbing toward a destination
beyond the greatest heights of humanity...
There's no doubt I've arrived!
We finally meet,
my means of reaching Heaven!
Though it is still
incomplete and unripe...
...I need now only follow the memories
sealed away by Kujo Jotaro!
The new moon rises tonight!
Dio!
The time of Heaven, ideal for your awakening
and for me to master thy power!
Over thirty-six of the worst convicts' souls...
Something new is born of them!
This green-colored being...
Oh, of course.
Before I begin...
...I must send you to
the utter oblivion of death.
Stand, daughter of Jotaro.
You alone defended yourself a split second faster,
thus avoiding a fatal wound.
If you won't be
the first to strike, then I will!
I never thought I'd uncover
the real you like this, Whitesnake.
That this is how
we would meet again!
There are three things
I need from you...
My dad's memory...
...the disc you took from F.F...
...and your life!
Ushaa!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
What is the meaning
of these handcuffs?
Never worn them before?
Ever since your little ploy brought me here,
I've had to put up with them almost every day.
Do you honestly believe you've
trapped me with these things?
What do you think handcuffs are for?
They aren't to keep someone
from running away...
They're to make them submit!
It seems you aren't
aware of what you've done.
These handcuffs keep us
in direct contact.
Do you know what that means?
I wonder,
which one of us is trapped here?
Your Stone Free
has turned into a disc!
I've loosened it
for easy extraction.
Do you see now?
Between the two of us,
who is truly in dire straits?
Yeah, I don't know shit.
That much...
...I do know.
A few millimeters.
A few millimeters,
and this fight will be over.
If I can get within a few millimeters of
your attack range, I can bash your face in.
Some swallows die from flying
directly into the sides of cliffs.
It is a result of their parents
never teaching them how to drop safely...
...which leads to them flying
at a dangerous angle.
However, this isn't for lack of
the parents wanting to teach them.
They cannot teach them,
for their own parents have never taught them, either.
Members of this family of birds
tend to have short lifespans...
...without realizing why
they are so prone to dying in accidents.
Jotaro, too, had a short lifespan.
Your Stone Free will be mine!
Ora! Ora!
I-I used her own disc to impede her vision...
How did she know where I was?
Was it through
the vibrations in the handcuffs?
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
N-No, it's her conviction!
Sh-She sensed my attack
through sheer conviction!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
When she first entered the prison,
I believed she possessed no Stand ability.
I took her for a sobbing little girl,
upset that a man deceived her!
Ora!
This is bad...
Whitesnake is ill-suited to fight her!
A-At this rate, I will...
But above all else,
this life that was born will...
What did you throw just now?
What did you do?
Tell me what you threw
right fucking now!
A disc is a soul given physical form.
It can preserve it in perpetuity.
However...
What if a disc entered the body
of one who is dying?
The disc would perish
along with their life.
It was Jotaro's memory disc,
the one you were willing to give your life to reclaim!
I return it to you!
I pierced Annasui's
dying body with it!
So what now?
Will you retrieve the disc?
Or will this handcuff
death match continue?
Letting go of Jotaro's disc is a risk...
...but I've already read and memorized
the means by which I shall attain Heaven.
Now it need only be done!
What will you choose, Cujoh Jolyne?
Is the choice not obvious?!
Your father is withering away,
dragged to his death alongside Annasui!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
All I need now is to
obtain the newborn life!
I won!
As I thought, she chose her father!
Spiral Staircase...
Rhinoceros Beetle...
Desolation Row...
Fig Tart...
Rhinoceros Beetle...
Via Dolorosa...
Singularity...
Giotto...
Angel...
Hydrangea...
Rhinoceros Beetle...
Singularity...
Secret Emperor!
You've expressed interest.
Will you approach me?
Will the curtains finally rise?
Now we can depart
together into your world!
Hallelujah, Dio!
Annasui!
Th-This can't be happening...
No... this can't...
It can't be!
S-Somebody!
Is anyone there?
A guard! I'm right here!
Please, I need a doctor!
Hey!
Di...
Somebody! Can't anybody hear me?! Hey!
Diver... Down...
Hey... Can you hear me?
Anyone will do! Someone, call for help! Please!
F.F...
Help me!
Jolyne is mourning...
Hey... It's your fault this happened...
Shit...
I've been cold for a bit...
So damn cold...
My heart's already stopped beating...
Seems her dad's memory disc
was put inside me...
I'm gonna die
and take it with me...
I tried ejecting it,
but my consciousness is fading fast...
Looks like you're crumbling away, too...
I'll give you everything I have.
It has to be you.
Use my intellect.
Use whatever life
I have left in me, too...
It's yours, now!
Take control of my body
and eject the disc for Jolyne.
Only plankton like you can do this...
Answer me, F.F.!
We had a deal!
You said you'd obey my orders!
I'm holding you to that!
You have to live!
You can do what you will
with my body.
Just quit wasting time!
My consciousness...
It's... going...
Th-This can't be happening!
Annasui!
No, Jolyne...
Don't worry...
This isn't how it looks.
You did it...
Annasui...
...got the disc back for you.
F.F... Is that you?
Is that you talking to me?
The one thing I feared
more than anything...
...was losing the ability to even think about
saying goodbye to my friends.
But...
...in the end,
I was able to have those thoughts.
Jolyne...
...please give Annasui
this message once he wakes up.
"Your body is yours."
"I used your intellect and life force
to fill your wounds."
Wait!
Wh-What are you saying, F.F.?
Goodbye, Jolyne.
I can't stay here any longer.
Foo Fighters is disappearing.
What are you talking about?!
D-Don't give me that shit!
Look at me, Jolyne!
This is my soul!
This is my intellect!
I lived a life!
I-I swear I'll get your disc
back from the priest!
Foo Fighters' disc!
Then you can come back to life!
That would probably be
a different Foo Fighters.
I doubt it'd be me.
This is me.
I'm here to say goodbye!
I'm so happy I got to say
farewell in the end... Jolyne.
It's okay, Jolyne.
Everything will be fine.
I'm glad you got the disc back...
F.F...
Respond, F.F.
I've lost you, F.F.
Where are you?
F.F.?
Answer me, F.F.
F.F...
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Jailhouse Lock!