Destiny is mine - Even if I come to know fear
To keep all of our futures from being severed
Shoot a thread of light
Every time I overcome pain
My heart is sharpened even further
(Never give up)
At the far end of this looping fate
I pledge to the ocean that scatters light
Getting through - To leave behind
the meaning of living
Heaven’s falling down - Let heaven fall on me
Yet still I will shatter the wishes of the god of madness
Destiny is mine - Even if I come to know fear
To keep all of our futures from being severed
I light a flame...
Destiny is something you choose for yourself
So that the wings of freedom will never be stolen from me
(In the darkness)
Should my prayers shine upon a faintly visible path
Then it's worth taking a risk on it
Stay with me - Let's go together
Even if my body were to crumble
Heaven’s falling down - Let the world rot away
Yet still the justice dwelling in my blood will never wither
Destiny is mine - Never shall I surrender
As long as my heart is beating, I will let loose hope
Shoot a thread of light
The star passed down to me
The deeper it is buried in darkness, the stronger its shine
Destiny is mine - Even if I come to know fear
To keep all of our futures from being severed
I light a flame, the glimmer of life
(Destiny will begin tonight)