Hey, you...
Can you do it?
Sure thing. Okay.
I can protect her.
Cujoh Jolyne, that is.
This old man's
gotta be taken care of!
Southeast, 127 degrees,
30 minutes and 20 seconds.
But this time with
no chance of survival.
Southwest, 225 degrees, 0 minutes.
F.F., behind you!
I told you,
your enemy is my old fart of a user!
His arm is gonna hit F.F.
on the back of her head!
Was that a coincidence just now?
That prisoner's glasses flung up
and stabbed F.F. in the face!
A misfortunate direction.
I'm beginning to understand.
He's using feng shui.
There are people in East Asia
who practice feng shui.
He uses that dragon-like Stand
to choose the direction of his attacks.
F.F., right now this is
your misfortunate direction.
Just above your left ear.
My attack overlapped with
the orientation of your death!
F.F.!
This is bad... Really bad!
Stop.
It's no use.
You and I have our own
misfortunate directions.
And once they've been set in stone,
not a living thing can run or defend themselves from them.
This proved it.
His next target...
...will be you.
Haiya!
No.
When I said this was bad,
I wasn't talking about her head getting sliced up.
I would feel better if she was
seriously injured with blood gushing out.
The lack of blood is
what makes this so bad!
The damage she's taken has drained her
of the water she needs to survive!
The Foo Fighters inside her body
are about to be destroyed!
G-Good thing nothing spilled out...
But talk about misfortune... Seriously...
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 18  Fiery Blaze, Foo Fighters
What?
Return to me, dragon!
Way to cut it close, ya old fart!
Never...
Never again!
Never again will I so carelessly
step away from the direction of safety!
Sh-Shit!
He retreated to find a safer direction!
Still...
I'm starting to understand how these directions work
and how to get around them!
A mirror... I need a mirror!
If there was a mirror hanging somewhere,
I could reflect the dragon on it.
If I could use an optical illusion to make
the old fart move in an unsafe direction...
...it would give me
a chance to take him down!
I need to find water.
I can use it
to make a mirror.
I need water to
heal my wounds, too...
But right now, it's more important
that I use it to make a mirror in the air!
L-Long ago,
over thirty-thousand believers...
...learned my teachings
and followed in my footsteps.
But ever since the day I came to this prison,
I've endured a life filled with mockery.
Everyone here
mocks me and laughs.
I was even ridiculed
by a heinous child kidnapper!
Forty years...
I've suffered this for forty years!
Glory... I once had glory!
Forty years ago,
I shone like no other!
And those days will return!
The wisdom found in feng shui which allowed me alone
to survive that fiery blaze has come forth as my Stand!
People will be calling me
the founder again before long!
I may fail to break out of here,
but people will still follow in my footsteps!
Once I've finished you off, at least!
This is the end!
Now show me!
Dragon's Dream!
Reveal to me
the direction of the finishing blow!
F.F., just past the stairs!
There's a fire hose!
Hey, tough guy!
Enough gawking and talking!
Help F.F.!
You're a Stand user, aren't you?
Help F.F. fight and
finish off the old man!
Only if F.F. dies.
I made no promise
that I would help her.
Our deal only
concerns protecting you.
Besides, F.F. told me
that she doesn't need my help.
F.F. told me to keep you safe from any attacks
here in the Disciplinary Wing after she saw your injuries.
Where is it?
How do I turn the water on?!
Where's the valve?!
Take care not to touch.
This is the direction of your absolute worst misfortune.
Keep your guard up.
Or brace yourself
for another decisive blow!
Now's not the time
for drinking water!
Was that deliberate?
F.F., what do you
think you're doing?!
You just made it so
the next attack has been set in stone!
What are you thinking?!
It seems no cost
is too high for F.F. to get water.
She prioritized it above avoiding
a decisive attack or falling into misfortune.
She intentionally got rid of her arms
so she could fit inside the hose!
She did it!
She finally has wa-
That's your arm.
Let the assassination feng shui begin!
You're clearly in need of water,
but you will never, ever have a commanding position.
My attacks will only
bring about your utter misfortune!
Such is the way of assassination feng shui,
Dragon's Dream!
This is what it means
to have your fate set in stone!
She couldn't reach the water.
She didn't even touch it!
Wh-What will happen now?
Underneath the Disciplinary Wing
is the execution room.
The death penalty is legal
under Florida state law.
Each year, two or three prisoners
are electrocuted on the 2,800-volt electric chair.
D-Dammit...
I was so close
to touching the water...
At least I opened up the tap.
I need to get
that water upstairs somehow!
If... If this keeps up, I'm...
Especially for plankton,
it would mean instant death.
Th-This chair!
It can't be!
Wh-What?
D-Don't tell me it's already on!
Does that sound mean
the electricity is ready?
Goddammit!
I won't let it turn on!
Let's see what kind of an end
you'll meet from my attacks!
At this point,
anyone could predict what will happen here!
But first,
I'll have a few drops of water from the ceiling!
It appears it was already set in stone
that you would sit in that chair!
Uoshaa!
Haiya!
You'll never get any water!
And now is the perfect time!
Time for you to be
finished for good!
Foo Fighters
Power: B
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: B
Power: B
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: B
Foo Fighters
F.F.!
The direction of a decisive attack,
and the direction of perfect defense!
Assassination feng shui!
It took forty years,
but now I can say I've mastered it!
The founder is born anew!
With this, I'll go down in history
as a man equal in wisdom to the Buddha!
You know, I'm supposed to stay neutral,
so there's something I didn't tell you, old man Kenzo.
F.F. got her water.
She got it just now,
the moment you kicked her!
She really had you running,
you 78-year-old fart.
F.F. had you running up
a good sweat, she did!
And you know what sweat is?
It's water!
Looks like she whipped up
a mirror using sweat.
With enough sweat to fill a third of a cup,
she made a floating mirror.
Basically,
since you're looking at my reflection...
...this isn't a safe direction at all!
A simultaneous strike.
The only thing that can defeat perfected
assassination feng shui is a simultaneous strike!
F.F. braced herself
for this moment!
Take this!
I got what I needed!
As long as I can
share my misfortune with you...
The direction of safety...
F.F...
It's over.
Onto the next task.
You're searching for a bone, right?
I would advise you
to start thinking about that.
At the very least, you're no longer at risk of
Kenzo attacking you with his assassination feng shui.
It was certainly an unrivaled Stand.
F.F.!
No way!
Cujoh Jolyne,
what are you doing?
Your body has suffered
more damage than you realize!
Besides, those 2,800 volts of electricity would have
wiped out the entire plankton colony inside F.F.'s body.
You should know that!
Th-The dragon...
The dragon is still here!
She must have let go of him
a bit too early.
Probably because plankton are
weaker to electricity than humans.
Kenzo is still alive!
Wait! Are you planning to
use your Stand in your condition?!
Has a savage need for
vengeance consumed you?
There's no way I can let him go!
Stone Free!
There's no way
you can hit me!
I'll finish you and
reclaim my rightful place as founder!
I see it now.
So that's the direction of safety.
I see.
You wanted to know
where Kenzo escaped to.
Once you figured out the completely safe direction
where you'd never be attacked from...
...you knew it would also be safe for F.F.,
who scattered along with the water that created the mirror.
She should have also been safe
from the 2,800 volts of electricity.
You attacked the old geezer
to find this exact spot.
The Foo Fighters are still alive!
Gimme a break.
Jolyne!
You think you've won now, do you?
You think you've defeated me?
Cujoh Jolyne!
My plan to defeat you
still hasn't changed!
You didn't notice, did you?!
You already stepped in the direction
of my assassination feng shui!
Stone Free's thread
is inside the dragon!
My attacks are absolute!
Your greatest misfortune
has just been set in stone!
No matter what form my attack takes,
it has been determined that it will end you!
I won!
Now kneel before me!
Likewise, my plan to be reinstated
as founder hasn't changed!
What? H-Hey...
D-D-Did I not hit my mark,
Dragon's Dream?
Assassination feng shui is absolute!
And my instant death kick
definitely hit Jolyne, didn't it?!
Yeah, you sure got her
with that killing blow!
Then why is Jolyne unscathed
while I'm up here clinging to this guardrail?!
Dragon!
Show me the direction of safe-
Hey, dragon!
Where are you going?
Tell me the direction of safety!
Why won't you come closer?
You took the words
right out of my mouth!
You're the one moving away!
You let go and started falling!
What are you doing?!
I said tell me the direction!
Like I said,
you're the one moving away!
Look at your legs, you old fart!
Something's not right.
Your legs are acting all weird!
Did something happen to you
when you attacked Jolyne?
Oh, that's...
What the heck?!
That's not Jolyne's thread Stand!
What is that Stand
coming out of Cujoh Jolyne's body?
Diver Down.
I submerged it within her body.
If the attack against Jolyne
had been set in stone...
...all it had to do was protect her
the exact moment the attack made contact.
What the hell?
This man who
came with F.F., Annasui...
He put his own Stand inside my body
and destroyed Kenzo's legs in an instant.
No...
He disassembled his flesh and bones!
Then he put everything back together,
rearranging his legs like a fucked up spring!
It's a suspension of
flesh and bones now!
But Kenzo still isn't
feeling any pain.
And neither am I, thanks to the Stand
that manipulated the guards into fighting.
Still...
Even my hips!
I need the direction of safety, dragon!
I can't reach it!
No, not that way!
Is he an ally?
He's capable of
really hurting people.
Just who is this guy?
That's it. Very good.
You can stare all you like.
Gaze at me with
those beautiful eyes of yours.
The direction of safety is east-northeast,
and your lucky color is cerulean blue.
But y'know...
I think this is it for you.
For a fight that only lasted a few minutes,
you sure aged a lot.
KENZO (78 YEARS OLD)
STAND NAME:
DRAGON'S DREAM
BEYOND RECOVERY
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Are you okay, Jolyne?
Yeah...
I just started feeling pain again
all of a sudden.
But I have to find the bone
and the short guy who picked it up...
Wait a second!
I'll fill your wounds.
Hurry...
I have to hurry and get it back...
My dad's disc...
Birth of the Green