He's currently sleeping.
During his wakeful periods,
he retains a monk-like posture...
But after several hours
of wakefulness...
...he sleeps for
twenty-four hours.
Outskirts of Dallas, Texas
inside the
SPW Foundation Facility
Naturally.
After all,
he has no memories.
How has his ability to learn
progressed since he was revived?
He's at normal levels.
So far he's learned
about thirty English words.
However, he doesn't seem to comprehend
that Kujo Jotaro is his name.
Nor does he recognize his family...
Even pictures of his daughter
haven't elicited a reaction.
His brainwaves and EKG
are within normal parameters.
However, his muscle mass has decreased.
Without any memories,
he lacks any sort of drive.
His muscles will atrophy
quickly in this condition.
What can we do, Doctor?
I'm not sure.
Recovering his memories may be
our only means of helping him.
Doctor, don't touch his head!
He's hurt!
Treat him, now!
I-I'm so sorry, doctor!
I should have warned you.
Did he unleash his Stand ability?
Yes, but not because of any memory.
He acted instinctively
to protect himself.
"Jolyne..."
"Jolyne"?
N-No... That's impossible.
I've always...
I've always cared for you.
That's weird... Your wounds...
I gave you first aid.
I'm sure I healed you.
Your wound kinda
looks like writing, doesn't it?
Should I try healing it again?
Wait.
You don't need to heal me.
I can't explain it, but...
I just know it.
This is from my dad...
He had so much to protect
even before I was born.
That's why he was always gone...
To keep the dangers like the one I'm in right now...
...away from Mom and I.
I understand him now...
Deep down,
I feel like I just understood my dad.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 19  Birth of the Green
Oh, F.F...
On these stairs...
concerning Jolyne's legs...
Would you grab them
and make her trip?
You want me to what now?
Again, just make her trip and fall.
I won't allow her
to hit the ground.
I intend to defend her by
catching her in my waiting arms.
Wha...?
Jolyne may not fully understand
that my actions protected her.
Just once more,
I want to hold her in my embrace.
Go on, do it.
Trip her.
How about you do it?
That's sexual harassment!
We've been over this.
Jolyne and I are to be wed.
You're going to help facilitate this.
Are you the type to
break a promise?
Do it.
I'm sorry, Jolyne...
The short guy!
There he is!
He was spying on us
from the next floor!
He's got it!
He's holding the bone!
This guy sure moves like a weirdo!
But he's not getting away!
Wait!
What's with his back?
Weren't you saying he was short?
He was certainly short
until a moment ago...
But something is...
Sunbathing...
Is he not growing taller?
Nearly my height...
No, even taller!
Hey! You're done running!
Turn around real slowly and face us!
The sun feels so good...
Light...
I said turn around, motherfucker!
What the fuck
is wrong with him?!
The light is...
...warm.
All gathering... Happily... So warm...
The fuck?
Something just splattered!
Is he a Stand user?!
Stay back.
This doesn't look like a Stand.
I don't know what he is,
but don't touch him.
Where's the bone?
He was just holding it.
Where did it go?
What the...?
The other prisoners...
a-are already...!
They seem to be plants
from the look of it.
And they're growing.
What happened to these people?
Who did this?!
And why?
Should I assume this is a Stand ability?
Of this bone's...
The power and what appears to be
force of will that made this happen...
It seems as though it's preparing
to give birth to something.
It created flower blooms and accelerated
the growth of these plant-like things to maturity.
Until ultimately...
So... what should I do with the bone
that was dropped by that short guy?
I've deduced that carelessly touching it
or anyone who was in contact with it is dangerous.
Don't take another step, Cujoh Jolyne!
Stop where you are!
Show me your face!
Turn around!
What?
Nothing...
Stay like that...
I want to investigate something.
Hey!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
Hey! Annasui!
F.F., don't say a word.
The people in this Disciplinary Wing
became like this due to the bone.
It isn't an enemy Stand.
If it were an enemy ability,
then surely we would have been attacked first.
And I noticed something, Jolyne...
I believe I saw your thread touch the bone
when it was still in his grasp.
The bone!
It's rolling away!
Sh-She's infected!
Jolyne!
No way!
Diver Down!
Yes!
Annasui!
Weed them all out from the inside! Quickly!
There's more!
What are you doing?!
Telling me to "weed them all out" or saying
"they're sprouting" are not correct expressions.
It's her body itself
that is changing!
I don't believe they can be
safely pulled out.
Jolyne, are you in pain?
No.
Looks like I ended up
touching that bone...
Anyway, you should stay away from me
now that I'm like this.
I could infect you.
These are just plants.
Nothing more, nothing less.
I can't tell what species they are...
...but their stems are filled
with chlorophyll, not blood.
Either way,
I'll take care of this...
I promise.
The sunlight!
Get in the shade!
If the light touches you,
or you move toward the sun...
...the plants will rapidly grow!
But if you move away into the shade,
they seem to calm down!
Damn! What does it want?
I don't know.
But whatever it is,
I still need to get that bone!
But how?
You'll turn into a plant
if you touch the bone, Jolyne!
I'm doing it.
It's already happening.
Don't go anywhere with sunlight, Jolyne!
Where is the bone?
Where could it be?
I thought I saw it rolling
toward this flower.
A star shape?
What is this bruise-like mark?
I can see something inside there...
A... A baby...
A green baby!
Yo-Yo Ma
Power: C
Speed: D
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: C
Power: C
Speed: D
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: C
D&G
What is it shaped like?
People are always finding stuff like carrots shaped like Snoopy
or radishes that look like breasts out in the fields.
That's all it is.
It just looks like...
I-It's alive! But how?!
Jolyne! Forget that thing!
Get back here!
Didn't you notice?
Your legs are starting
to fuse with the vines!
What is this thing?
Is it a plant? Or is it human?
It turned the prisoners in the Disciplinary Wing into plants,
joined their roots, and became a fruit!
The bone was probably
absorbed by the green fruit.
Whitesnake is here in this prison
because he wants to find out what will come of this.
To know what will
be born from this...
...and what will happen after!
I told you to get back, Jolyne!
More sunlight is getting in
now that the sun is facing west.
You'll be in big trouble
if you don't move back!
You're taking it with you?
We call this "forceful appropriation," F.F.
I won't let Whitesnake have it!
Come, Jolyne.
We need to move
away from the sunlight!
Annasui!
The entrance to the wing
is due west!
We won't be able to
escape this shithole!
Not to mention there's at least one more
enemy Stand user hiding here somewhere!
Escape, huh?
H-H-Help me...
P-P-Please help...!
I-I'm begging you!
A-After everyone drowned,
they turned into weeds and died!
It's awful!
I'm begging you!
Take me with you!
Before I turn into weeds, too!
Fine.
What's your name?
Are you hurt?
What are you saying, Annasui?
He could be our enemy!
Is she right?
Are you our enemy?
I-I-I don't know what
you're talking about!
My name is Guccio!
I-I really just don't wanna
turn into a clump of weeds!
Calm down.
I said it was fine.
Stand up, Guccio.
Surely you can do that much.
Make it quick.
Did you know?
Humans have twelve pairs of ribs.
Twenty-four in total.
Whether man or a woman, tall or short,
we all share the same number of ribs.
Good. Now go.
Huh?
So he wasn't an enemy?
Doesn't matter either way.
My only concern is if we'll have safe passage
through the east side of the building.
Is that wrong?
The key word being safe passage.
We'll exit from there.
A green baby...
I wasn't made aware of
what the situation would be here...
...but my job is simple.
Eliminate Cujoh Jolyne.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Do as ordered without fail.
Where are they?
Where did Cujoh Jolyne
and the other two go?
Did they already escape?
No...
They couldn't have
left the building under my watch.
Hey, you.
What are you doing here?
Hey, I asked you a question!
Where is that group of three?
Why aren't you a plant?
Walk... outside...
Save me...
How terrible!
Someone turned his body
into a living trap!
It hurts so much!
Mommy, he hurt me!
I don't want this stupid
broken arm anymore!
That was horrific...
I was simply instructed by Whitesnake
to make everyone fight each other using Survivor.
But I did it...
I can leave!
GUCCIO
STAND NAME
SURVIVOR
BEYOND RECOVERY
Anyway, it looks like we got
away from that other Stand user.
They're withering...
The effect was only temporary.
The issue now is that
someone from the prison...
...is going to notice the situation
in the Disciplinary Wing soon.
Sounds good to me.
That means Whitesnake will also notice
from wherever he's hiding.
He'll have to be close.
I'll have another chance
to get my dad's memory disc back!
Jolyne, that's...!
Stone Free!
Ora!
It's an enemy Stand!
Must belong to that
gladiator-looking motherfucker!
It took the fruit!
You're not getting away!
You...!
Diver Down!
Wh-Wh-What's going on
with its body?
More!
It stinks... badly!
Deeper, deeper! Please!
Sh-Shit!
I'm not going inside this thing!
Please punish me!
I can feel it
through my Stand!
My body's starting to stink
from the inside!
Oh! Your shoes!
Did my bodily fluids soil them?
I'm terribly sorry!
Please, have a seat over here!
Allow me the honor of licking your shoes clean!
Slurp! Slurp!
Care to peruse this comic book
I pilfered from the guards' break room?
Careful! There's a bee!
My user is named D&G.
When last I saw him
in the Disciplinary Wing...
...he was crying and screaming after
his arm was yanked off and went flying!
It's a remote-controlled Stand!
Yes! Yes! Punish me!
It's trying to snatch the fruit
and bring it back to its user!
Time's up!
The guards are coming!
Jolyne, we have to leave for now.
We'll head toward the wetlands.
Perhaps we'll find
a bike or boat to use.
When picking wild strawberries...
...the ones with yellow blooms
are fake, so don't eat them!
Shut your annoying fucking mouth!
We can't just ignore this Stand.
We have to get the green baby
out of its stomach.
I know.
F.F., our only choice here
is to take it with us!
Finds its user
and assassinate him!
Yeah, can do!
So shall I be accompanying you
on your voyage, Masters?
This vessel was specifically built
to traverse the wetlands, Masters.
Its finely crafted propeller engine
propels it forward with assistance from the wind.
Dammit!
How do I start the ignition?
Is it locked somehow?
It utilizes a throttle lever, Master.
Ordinarily,
it must first be put in neutral, like so.
This stick is the rudder.
Push forward to turn the tail to the right,
and pull back to turn to the left.
Unfasten the rope.
Aye, Master!
Jolyne, don't take your eyes
off that Stand.
While you have eyes on it,
it will be your faithful servant.
It's creepy, but useful.
But turn your back on it
for one second, and...
F-Fuck...
I never expected an attack like that.
Jolyne, Annasui...
Don't let it out of your sight!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
F.F. - The Witness