Do not pursue the bone.
Leave it be.
Allow it to do as it pleases
and act of its own accord.
Meanwhile, I will combine it with Kujo Jotaro's memory,
thus reaching the truth!
The bone was probably
absorbed by the green fruit.
Whitesnake is here in this prison
because he wants to find out what will come of this.
To know what will
be born from this...
...and what will happen after!
Finds its user
and assassinate him!
F-Fuck!
I never expected
an attack like that.
Its bodily fluids... Its drool...
attacked my mouth before I knew what hit me!
Slowly... Bit by bit...
What should I do?
Catch up with Jolyne's boat?
No.
I'll stick to the plan
and assassinate the Stand user!
That's our best bet!
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 20  F.F. - The Witness
Hey...
Head toward that thicket.
Why stop the boat
in the middle of all this grass?
Hey, kill the engine.
Don't make a peep.
Don't you hear it?
Hey! I told you to hurry and
kill the engine, you idiot!
An emergency has been declared
around the Disciplinary Wing!
The entire area is on
Level Four security alert!
Remain vigilant!
That's an M2 heavy machine gun
with a 12.7mm cartridge.
Effective range is
one to two thousand meters.
A glancing blow is
enough to take off limbs.
It would turn our boat to splinters.
Hey, keep it down!
You're gonna make waves!
Step away from the handle!
Calm down.
If we had been spotted,
their machine guns would have fired on us.
Ten o'clock.
I saw some strange waves
near those bushes.
Some kind of fish or alligator?
They're coming!
We have to go!
So, umm...
If the Masters would take some leaves...
I said keep it down, nimrod!
Oh, don't misunderstand!
Just fold the leaves in half...
...and interweave them.
Lean them against the boat...
...then fix them in place.
Ah, yes...
Let's paint your face.
Yes!
Let's all do it together!
Emergency report!
Return to the Disciplinary Wing immediately!
Repeat: Return immediately!
They want us back?
I don't know the situation,
but it sounds serious.
Let's go.
Wh-Who are they?!
D-Dammit!
Hurry and start the engine!
Th-There's no time!
They'll shoot us
before we start moving!
You there!
What did you do at the Disciplinary Wing?!
Listen!
Don't move a muscle!
Put your hands on the ground
and don't move!
I said don't move, scumbag!
On your knees!
Our boat!
We'll steal another.
That means you.
What was that?!
I'm taking this boat.
I'm sure you don't mind.
Don't let the gators get you on the way back.
Diver Down!
Jolyne, are the plants
still growing inside you?
Let's continue due east.
The sun is still setting.
How cruel!
As if I'm some thing...
...But it's fine.
Hey, Jolyne...
I'm sorry, but could you stop whistling?
I need to listen for our pursuers'
engine sounds in case they find us.
What are you talking about, Annasui?
Annasui! Hey! I'm talking to you, Annasui!
I... I can't talk!
Annasui! My voice is already...!!
Annasui!
This bastard...
Its goal wasn't just to
run off with the green baby!
It's also attacking us!
Is something the matter?
You seem to be short of breath.
I get the same feeling, Jolyne.
Can you feel
the beat of my heart?
It's because you
made a move on me...
Have my feelings for you
finally come through?
Not my eyes!
My tongue! Tongue!
Are you trying to say
you're speechless?
I know the feeling.
But we needn't say a thing...
I feel just as you do.
You want to kiss me, yes?
But I must ask, are you the type
who jumps right into tongue play?
When and how were we attacked?
I didn't notice anything!
I need to keep my eyes on it!
Jolyne...
Which is it?
Do you want to kiss me, or not?
Or is this some kind of
odd kink of yours?
You're very particular
about the angle of your kiss...
An auto-tracking Stand.
It follows our orders like a slave
and acts docile like a servant.
It seems harmless...
...but that's its trick.
It's a Stand that somehow knows when its targets
have dropped their guard and attacks automatically!
We're both fucked
if this keeps up!
Bring it!
Show me what you got!
I have to make Annasui notice!
Yo-Yo Ma.
That's my name!
See, if one wishes to tan a frog's hide...
...create a thick and creamy mixture of fat and brains,
and rub it into the back of the frog's skin.
This ensures the hide
will become elastic.
If Master wants,
I can procure another ten frogs...
...and whip up a super fetching
mini-skirt or the like with their hides.
I'm certain it will give the appearance of long and slender legs,
as well as accentuate those crazy wide hips!
Jolyne, what's the matter? Seriously.
If it needs to be triggered,
I'll just have to find the trigger for its attacks!
And if it's automatic, then...
I was waiting for this!
I coated my skin in threads,
waiting for something to touch it!
It automatically attacks us
when we turn away.
That's its ability!
And now I know
how it attacks!
Mosquitoes!
Jolyne! Wh-What's...?
Jolyne!
W-Was I wrong?!
It's not mosquitoes?!
N-No! This just means it has another way
to attack besides the mosquitoes!
"Be All Eyes"
NEVER LOOK AWAY
You... You sick fuck!
Does Master wish for me
to continue driving?
Or would you prefer
we fight one-on-one?
Or perhaps esca-
I-I was wrong!
It's not just mosquitoes!
It has other ways to attack!
Oh yeah, I want more!
It has some way of attacking
without being seen!
Get away!
I do believe this is
your last chance to escape.
I hope you're ready...
Ready to regret ever being
born into this world.
Diver Down
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: E
Durability: C
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: E
Durability: C
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
Narciso Annasui
Go to the back corner
of the boat on the port side!
Show me everything you're hiding!
Put it all at
my feet and show me!
Two rhinoceros beetles...
A karaoke microphone...
Some low-calorie sugar packets, three frogs...
One raw frog hide, a head of broccoli,
four fake strawberries, and two used matchsticks.
Its things don't matter!
We're upwind of it,
yet we keep getting attacked!
An auto-tracking Stand...
You have a set target, is that right?
Yes, sir, I've had Cujoh Jolyne locked as my target
ever since I first touched her.
Your user ordered you
to target her.
You won't attempt to flee
until you've finished her off, correct?
Yo-Yo Ma.
And so long as Master
stays at her side...
...I will simply
finish off the both of you.
Is it the drool?
Yo-Yo Ma.
Have I not enlightened you?
I can never,
ever be stopped or destroyed.
Your only chance for survival was to
run from me as quick as you can!
Should I try stopping the boat?
This spraying water...
If it already mixed the drool it's been
using to attack us into the water, then...
Get up and go sit
in the driver's seat.
Increase our speed.
Get up, now!
No, that's worse!
If we go faster,
the boat will start spraying us even harder!
Certainly!
If that is what Master wishes.
Ribbit!
Jolyne. Its attack seems to have stopped,
despite the fact that it hasn't sped up the boat yet.
Yo-Yo Ma.
S-Something is not well...
B-Birds! Must hide! Must hide!
Diver Down.
Its method of attacking us
ultimately didn't matter.
Since it's a perfect
auto-tracking Stand...
...I buried a frog inside its head,
and connected the frog's brain to its tracking sensors.
Go ahead and track us for
the rest of your life while feeling like a frog!
Wait... What was I about to do?
I'm an auto-tracking Stand...
My mission is to finish off Cujoh Jolyne
and return with the green baby...
I have no time for this nonsense!
I have to spray my spit
to attack Annasui!
I'll build up a static charge by creating friction
between the plastic and the propellers...
That should send
my spit flying everywhere!
He won't have
a clue what hit him!
But these birds are
making me lose my mind!
Must hide!
Gross!
I did pee-pee like a frog!
Woah, look at that cutie!
Nice body, baby!
Come give me a ride, sweet thing!
Oh, a rhinoceros beetle!
We can ignore it now.
We just need F.F.'s help
to heal our wounds.
We'll wait here until she's
taken care of D&G and comes back for us.
What the hell happened
to the Disciplinary Wing?
Where are all
the guards and prisoners?
We couldn't have been gone
longer than ten minutes!
And why are there
plants everywhere?
How do we explain this?
What's his status?
Can he talk?
Prisoner number ME14067, D&G...
He's in critical condition.
His right arm is almost torn off.
We can't question him yet.
I'm gonna pump your brain full of F.F. bullets
for sending that creepy fucking Stand after us!
Isn't that guy the chaplain
of the prison, Father Pucci?
What is he doing here?
Shit, forget him!
My main priority is
making sure D&G is killed!
Three hundred fifty-nine...
Three hundred sixty-seven...
Three hundred seventy-three...
Three hundred seventy-nine...
Three hundred eighty-three...
Three hundred eighty-nine...
Three hundred ninety-seven...
Now the four hundreds...
First, four hundred one...
Then, four hundred nine...
D&G is gravely injured, which means...
I can only conclude that
Cujoh Jolyne is still alive.
As for the large number
of withered plants...
I suppose it is the work of Dio's bone.
This means Dio's bone has begun using prisoners
to achieve something beyond my wildest dreams.
Magnificent.
Truly magnificent!
I can only conclude
that it has begun.
I've waited twenty-two
years for this day!
As for what D&G bore witness to...
...I must hear it from him directly!
Don't you agree,
Survivor's Guccio?
It appears you weren't witness to it,
but something must have been born of these plants.
Is this not cause to give praise?
Soon I will have it in hand!
What is true happiness?
I will attain Heaven!
Sing His glory!
That which has been born
is Heaven itself!
It signifies the curtain rising
upon a world born anew!
Glorious!
Praise be this moment!
Handel's Messiah
is a true masterpiece!
How befitting it is...
It's as though light shines
through the sound...
Some say that Handel, a mere day before his death,
was still performing this angelic masterpiece!
All right, leave D&G to the medics.
Question him once he's stable.
The rest of us will search for
the missing prisoners and guards.
Move out!
Yes, sir!
No, I believe I'm going
to question him now.
It would be problematic to lose track of
that which has been born this day.
All right, start the ambulance.
Yes, sir.
Th-That woman...!
The face beneath that hat!
Eat this.
Auto-tracking Stand users are vulnerable
once the situation has turned on them.
That's the risk you take!
It's Foo Fighters!
Why is she here
in the Disciplinary Wing?
When did she get here?
This is dire!
She was pursuing D&G!
A disc!
Whitesnake is close!
Wh-Where is he?
Where did he throw that disc from?
Four hundred seventy-nine...
Four hundred eighty-seven...
Four hundred ninety-one...
Four hundred ninety-nine...
No...
The asshole who threw it...
...was you!
This won't do.
I cannot abide this.
The fact that you're here attacking D&G tells me
that his Stand, Yo-Yo Ma, is currently tracking Jolyne.
His true identity is...!
How is this possible?!
He and I have matters
yet to be discussed.
I won't allow him to die.
Whitesnake's true identity is...!
Supposing it was me,
which do you pick?
What is your highest priority?
Is it me?
Or does eliminating
D&G come first?
It was him...
Father Pucci!
Fuck you!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Awaken