5:35 P.M.
Rain...
October 28th,
The rain never stops...
Hey, what the hell are you doing over there?!
Quit making that fucking noise!
It's over... I can't go on...
I was caught in the act last night...
...by a male prison guard...
I can't live like this!
I want to die! Goddammit!
Hey, what's your deal?
Why the freak out?
What's your name again?
Wasn't it like... Jo-something?
Jolyne, right?
You were caught?
Doing what?
Well, you know, I was, like...
Th-The "M" word...
Huh?
So basically, I was just...
Speak up!
I'm saying I was... ma... mas...
Mastur... uh... bating...
What?
H-Hold up...
Now I'll never get married!
Wait, you're telling me you got caught?
A prison guard saw you
flicking the bean?
Wh... Wh... Which guard was it?
This morning,
I woke up before the sun came out...
There was just something about the moonlight
glimmering through the shape of the window bars...
I don't know, it just...
...turned me on.
So, I... Yeah...
When I came to my senses
and looked up from my bed...
You know the youngest guard here?
He looked at me in complete disbelief...
...while he stood right in front of my cell!
I wanna hurl myself off a building!
I've seen him!
He's that one kinda
handsome guy, ain't he?
Oh, my god.
So what did he see?
Actually, better question...
How low were your panties?
Are you seriously asking me that?
I'm not telling you shit.
But I've made up my mind.
I'm never going to touch myself again!
I swear on my life!
Not sure I buy that.
How did those steel bars get you goin'?
Fuck off, snotty!
Don't butt in acting all high and mighty!
As if you've never done it before.
My mind's not in the gutter like you sluts.
You think you're hot shit?
Wanna bet who'll last longer?
How's that a bet, you dumb bitch?
You only do the deed in secret.
How're we gonna prove we ain't doin' it?
What if I told you that the joint
on your left ring finger tells all?
You're here because
you're a sex offender, aren't you?
Your ring finger says you're a pro.
Detainees 21, 22, 29...
You're up for transfer.
Up against the bars.
Arms out of your cells.
That true what you said
about ring fingers?
You a fortune teller?
You Japanese-American?
You're one interesting girl.
So what'd you do?
What'd they nail you for?
I'm innocent.
Episode 1  Stone Ocean
You were charged...
...with theft and hit-and-run.
Visitation
Room
Because you have two prior convictions of theft
on your record, you won't be granted bail.
In other words, Jojo, you will be transferred
to the holding block at Green Dolphin to await trial.
Don't call me Jojo.
Only my mom calls me that.
And what record?
I was just borrowing a bike.
I was only fourteen!
I'm telling you, I'm innocent!
You better sprout wings and fly to my defense!
I'm paying good money!
Of course.
I will do my best to
serve you and the law.
Christ...
So when can I see my mom?
She's a big crybaby, you know.
She's a bit worn out.
I think she's just worried about you.
She brought you a few things.
You aren't required to wear
a prison uniform while you await trial, of course.
Here's your clothes, book, and magazine.
She also brought your homework.
What's... this?
Some kind of charm, I believe.
There's a small stone inside.
Your divorced father apparently asked your mother
to give it to you if you were ever in trouble.
What did you say?
Oww!
That fucking hurts!
Are you okay, Jolyne?
What's all the racket?
Pipe down!
I'm fine!
It was just a small cut.
What's up with this stone?
I mean, like...
What does my dad have to do with this?
Your mother's been trying to reach him.
His daughter's in a crisis, after all.
But your father is a marine biologist.
He's currently conducting research in Africa,
and it's taking some time to contact him.
She's trying to reach him?
He'll never come.
He's...
That asshole...
I don't need his stupid junk!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
When are you coming back?
I'll see you in two days at
Green Dolphin Prison's holding block.
Hey, Jolyne, I thought you were innocent.
I know it's the holding block,
but it's still part of Green Dolphin Prison.
If they're transferring you there...
The trial will clear my name.
I'm not going to prison.
We're about to cross the bridge.
Should be there in about ten minutes.
That was fast.
Ten minutes until we're there.
What? Says who?
I heard the driver say it.
You can't hear them from here.
We're about to cross the bridge.
We'll be there in ten minutes.
Roger that.
How'd you know?
Another fortune of yours?
Good question... How did I hear it?
Beats me.
You're an odd one.
I'm Hermès Costello.
I robbed a convenience store.
It's my second time,
so I'm definitely getting locked up.
Nice to meet you, Hermès.
November 6th
2:32 P.M.
Green Dolphin Street State Prison
and its adjunct holding block.
Green Dolphin Street
State Prison
Collectively known as "The Aquarium."
The premises cover 120 square kilometers.
Imprisoned here are 708 men, 523 women,
and 452 minors under the age of eighteen.
Hey, Jolyne...
Got any cash on you?
Maybe.
Hey, I'm warning you.
If you don't have at least a few hundred
bucks on you, you're not gonna make it.
If you don't got it now, you better
get someone to visit and give it to you.
Why are you acting like I'm already fucked?
Just a friendly warning.
As if you've got cash yourself.
The guards would've found it at the pat down.
That's cute, Jolyne.
There's plenty of ways to smuggle stuff in.
You mean like rolling it up
and sticking it up your ass or up there?
Barf!
I thought that only happened in movies!
Dumbass...
That's the first place they look.
Then where?
Don't tell me it's in your boobs.
You slid in some cash with your implants?
No way! You did?!
No hiding from you...
Don't tell anyone.
See how small the stitches are?
It bleeds a little when I take them out...
...but I got five twenties in one
and a fifty in the other.
We're at Green Dolphin Street Prison's holding block.
Detainees 21 and 29, get off.
Number 22, Hermès Costello...
...this isn't your stop.
Welcome back, Hermès Costello.
How'd you fuck up this time?
Robbery? Assault?
Huh?
Did you say something to me just now?
Eyes in front, 21!
Spill it, Hermès.
You're trying to smuggle
something in, right? Bit of cash?
Smuggle?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I-I can hear them!
Something weird's going on!
Can the guards really not hear this?
It's like before we crossed the bridge.
I can hear people from far away!
I-Is this...?
Spill it, Hermès. Now!
This is your second time in the Aquarium.
I know you got some!
What the hell is going on?!
No talking, 21!
Can't they see this weird... thread-thing?
F-Fine, I'll give it to you.
You know, Hermès...
This isn't enough for the two of us.
Bet you got more on you somewhere.
Oh no, all of a sudden the bus is braking!
Please just take the fifty!
I don't have anyone to visit me.
Please...
I won't make it in there without cash!
You got big tits for a muscular girl.
That's pretty weird.
Let's have a look.
Hold her still.
Gotcha.
No... Stop!
Let go!
Who do you think I am, bitch?
Take this!
What was that?
What is this? Did...
Did that stone do this?!
What the hell did my old man send me?!
November 8th
11:00 A.M.
Hey... Remember when I tossed
that pendant back at the detention center?
Holding Block
I wonder where it went.
Who knows?
I don't really remember.
Anyway, let's discuss your case.
Since you're pleading innocent,
we have to be clear on this.
During the hit-and-run,
were you the one...
...in the driver's seat?
October 28th
5:32 P.M.
West Palm Beach,
Florida
So about your nickname...
Romeo, can I start calling you "Rocchu"?
Sure thing, babe.
But only when you're gargling mouthwash.
What, you don't like it?
Why not?
Rocchu, I'm so hungee!
You like? Pretty fly, right?
No way.
What if my friends hear?
But it's so cute and lovey-dovey.
My mom's called me "Jojo"
ever since I was a baby.
I want you to call me Jojo, too.
No freaking way.
Anyway, I'm thirsty.
Give me a sip of that.
You can't.
This cocktail is ten percent alcohol!
It'll be fine.
No means no. So no.
Romeo!
Romeo... Did you just...
This can't be happening! No!
Th-This is bad!
W-We need to get help!
Romeo, call an ambulance!
Jolyne! Please, Jolyne!
Please don't. Don't call!
What are you saying?
We need to help him!
Come on, he's already dead!
You want to run away? No!
It was an accident!
We can't run from this!
This car is evidence!
We'll say it was stolen!
But...
Jolyne!
Jolyne, if they arrest me,
our future together is over!
Even worse, they'll throw me in prison.
We'll never be together again!
Please listen!
Does our love mean nothing to you?
Our love is everything to me!
But this is...
A car is coming...
I'm screwed if they see me!
Jolyne! G-Give me a hand!
Look, he's really dead!
Please!
Help me, Jolyne!
I love you!
Jolyne!
Jolyne, the police believe you were under the influence
and stole the car that caused the accident.
And what's Romeo saying?
He claims his car was stolen.
Christ...
I wanna hurl myself off a building...
Was Romeo the one driving?
I can't say.
Fine, then here's the deal.
Jolyne, do you know what a plea bargain is?
If you plead guilty to your crimes,
they'll overlook the drunk driving.
You'll only be convicted of
theft and involuntary manslaughter.
Your sentence will be suspended
after a year or two.
I told you to fight for my innocence!
I understand,
but that's the offer on the table.
If you're found guilty at trial,
you'll get at least five years.
We're out of time, Jolyne.
We have to decide before the trial starts!
Defendant Cujoh...
Do you plead no contest of your own volition
to the contents of your plea bargain?
Yes, Your Honor.
This court recognizes that the Defendant,
Jolyne Cujoh, accepts conviction for the crimes herein...
...and will take into consideration
said crimes not being premeditated.
However, this court cannot condone
the act of disposing of the victim...
...in a nearby swamp while he was still alive,
effectively murdering him.
"While he was still alive"?
What's going on?
What is he saying?!
"Effectively murdering him"?!
This court sentences
the Defendant, Jolyne Cujoh...
...to serve fifteen years in
Green Dolphin Street State Prison.
Adjourned.
What? Hold on...
Fifteen years?
What did you just...?
Didn't we have a deal?!
I accepted the charges!
Didn't I, Mr. Lawyer?
I've done what I can.
Take care, Cujoh Jolyne.
Wait. Where are you going?!
Are you fucking serious?!
What the hell does he mean, "fifteen years"?!
I didn't agree to that!
H-Hold still!
I said wait!
You fucking asshole!
You can rest easy now.
The sentencing is over.
She took the plea bargain.
She won't be able to appeal.
There won't be any further investigation.
Congratulations, Romeo.
Thank you.
You seriously saved me.
Please thank your wealthy father.
Y-You son of a bitch...
Romeo... Romeo...
Romeo!
Fifteen years! Fifteen years! Fifteen years!
My entire youth! Fifteen years!
From here on out, in addition to the name you got
when your mommy pushed you out like a little turd...
...the state has graciously
assigned you an inmate number!
This prison is security level four!
Maximum Security!
FE40536.
Whether you're eating or taking a shit,
you better respond when your number's called!
Beat that into your thick skull!
FE40536, we will now
conduct a physical examination!
Put all of your personal belongings
into the tray and...
Strip! Right now!
Remember, the first step is
always to educate the trash.
You gotta humiliate 'em.
What's taking you?!
"Strip" means taking off your panties, too!
Show me your ass!
You want me on all fours?
Or maybe my back?
Or I can do a bridge pose if you want.
You...
You asshole...
You think you can just
stroll on out of here?!
It sure is humid in here...
My shirt is soaked.
It feels like it could rain in here.
Would you like to sit
in the warden's office?
It's air-conditioned.
Oh, I'm fine.
All the documents have been submitted.
This heat is nothing
compared to my client's fate.
A fifteen-year sentence at her age...
If only I could have done more...
Not at all.
You're a wonderful lawyer!
Oh, speaking of your client, Jolyne Cujoh...
She asked me to give you this letter.
The content's been cleared.
Huh.
Pass this on to him, too.
Feeling comfy?
But you will keep sweating.
Now... and forever.
What the hell?
I can't reach you right now...
...and I'm totally powerless...
...but I'm not waiting fifteen years!
I will find you.
And Romeo...
Farewell, my first love.
Between the prison and my car...
...the air is so much different.
To think this job forces me to breathe
the same air as the scum of society.
Can't breathe...
Something's wrapped... around my neck...!
I think the AC's... drying it out...!
Have to... turn it off...!
That's one other way of using this.
It reacts to my thoughts and lets me
manipulate it with the force of my mind.
Was the pendant his way of
telling me to protect myself?
This thing is interesting.
Stone Free