Wh-Who is he?
It's Cujoh Jolyne!
Not Lang Wrangler!
Presumably he failed and she took the disc.
Likewise, someone or something will likely
arrive at the courtyard to receive it from her.
It's the chaplain of this prison.
What is he doing here?
Have I been exposed?
No, she would have attacked me
if she saw me as an enemy.
Wait! F-Father!
Please... Don't sound the alarm!
I'm not trying to make a scene
or cause any problems!
What should I do?
Knock him out, or...?
Obviously I should.
With Dad's life at stake...
punching him is nothing.
This already is problematic, is it not?
You stole a fellow inmate's work permit card
and used it to make me open the door.
Where is the owner of this card?
Your fellow inmate, Lang Wrangler.
I know we just met,
and I don't expect you to believe me...
But I'm not lying, Father.
That inmate assaulted me.
I was defending myself.
He's passed out
in that hamper over there.
I have to report this to the authorities.
Of course, Father.
But can you wait until
after I reach the courtyard?
Just two minutes...
No, just one minute, Father!
I just want to go to the courtyard. That's it.
You would have me turn a blind eye?
It's a matter of life and death.
My dad's life and soul are at stake.
Surely a priest like you can appreciate that.
Are you here alone?
Is anyone else nearby?
No, I'm alone.
I just lied to a priest...
I'm sure a small fib can be forgiven...
I can't tell him about the disc, either.
I'm begging you.
Just one minute.
When doing someone a favor,
a reward is expected in kind.
To be kind towards others
is to receive kindness in return.
Such unconditional love doesn't exist.
True unconditional love...
...is the reward of
reaching the gates of Heaven.
You may go.
But we never met.
As requested, you have one minute.
You must return to the gate by then.
I had no choice.
Someone is hiding behind that barrel.
If they are her ally,
I cannot reveal my true identity...
...Whitesnake,
and risk being caught disposing of Jolyne.
The Speedwagon Foundation
said I'll know how to hand over the disc...
...once I get to the courtyard.
You...
You got a pass on you?
Guess not.
I take it you're trying to escape.
What?!
Wh-What just...?!
I never intended to sound the alarm.
How fortunate that I had a guard
patrolling the courtyard in the event this happened.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 12   Flash Flood Warning
The year was 1988.
I met and befriended a man from Egypt...
...who claimed that
he had the power to stop time.
Unprompted, the man said to me...
Perhaps there is a way one could reach Heaven.
He was young and alluring...
...yet had the aura
of a man who had lived for centuries.
I was sixteen at the time;
a student aspiring to attend a seminary.
Hey, I see that look on your face.
I am not telling you to die.
The Heaven I speak of has to do with
the soul and the path it takes.
The power of your soul
must evolve with you.
They must arrive at the same conclusion.
Surely one such as yourself
must see the truth in my words.
True happiness lies there.
But only if you reach Heaven.
I am well aware that happiness cannot be reached
through wealth, status, or a powerful body.
Those who are truly victorious...
...are the lucky few to glimpse Heaven.
There is nothing I won't do to reach it.
And just how are you going to do that?
This notebook explains the process.
Come visit Egypt sometime.
I will show it to you there.
Your aid will be necessary...
...to verify my methods.
However, before he made
his methods known to me...
...his notebook was burned to ashes.
It was burned by Cujoh Jolyne's father, Kujo Jotaro.
Jotaro read through the notebook himself...
...then sealed away its contents within him forever.
Along with the life of Dio Brando,
the man who sought to reach Heaven.
I waited for over two decades after that,
biding my time to obtain Jotaro's memories.
It was in his memories
where the contents of the notebook lay.
And now, his memories are finally mine...
...along with Star Platinum,
whose strength surpassed even Dio's.
Soon, the mortal shell that is
Jotaro's body shall decay.
And though his daughter's actions have led to
unexpected complications in this prison...
...that little disturbance is now dealt with.
Sh-She was shot!
Jolyne got shot!
But by who? A guard?
Or was our rendezvous point exposed
and Whitesnake was waiting for us?
Jolyne!
The guard will retrieve Star Platinum.
My involvement is no longer necessary.
My chapel awaits me.
What was this thing again?
It's a disc.
Oh, right...
I was ordered to retrieve it.
I also had orders to
finish her off completely... but, uh...
Who was it, again...?
Who ordered me to do this?
Either way, I was ordered...
to put a bullet... through her fucking brain...!
It's hopeless...
I've done everything I can to help...
Saving you is beyond my reach...
Go to hell...
...Cujoh Jolyne!
What the fuck?!
Weather Report...
...has the ability to control the weather.
This is all I can do...
Jolyne... I may not be able to save you...
...but I know I can still protect the disc.
And if you still have the resolve...
...you might be able to survive.
Between the years of 1887 and 1974,
in Florida, USA alone...
...there were more than fifty reported cases of fish,
frogs, snakes, and sheep falling from the sky.
The leading theory suggests tornadoes
and whirlwinds lifted them up in the air.
In this instance, they were poison dart frogs,
treetop dwellers indigenous to Central and South America.
They carry a subcutaneous poison so deadly
that it is commonly used in blowgun darts.
What the fuck are these frogs?!
Th-These are...!
Th-These frogs...!
Aren't these deadly poison dart frogs?
Once their poison enters its victim,
their heart and respiratory system shut down in mere seconds.
And now that exact poison is splattering
everywhere with their bodily fluids!
Whitesnake!
Th-This ability...
Could this be his weather manipulation powers?
Weather Report...
He should have lost his memories...
Was he the one hiding behind the barrel?
This is dangerous! The keycard!
Th-These frogs are poisonous...
Wh-What the hell happened to me?
Was I shot?
How deep was I hit?
M-My threads...
Their body fluids are seeping through my threads!
Someone, open this gate at once!
Anyone!
Calm yourself.
I must remain calm.
What is my best course of action?
Two... three... five...
I must stay calm...
Seven...
...and count prime numbers
to keep my composure.
Eleven...
Prime numbers are lonely numbers
which can only be divided by one and themselves.
Thirteen...
Seventeen...
They give me courage.
Nineteen...
Twenty-three...
Twenty-eight...
No, twenty-nine...
Twenty-nine... Thirty-one... Thirty-seven...
Curses...
These frogs are clinging to my eight hundred dollar pants!
Weather Report is in the laundry room.
Too far away.
I cannot make him stop the frogs.
Escape is the only option.
Forty-one...
Of course!
The guard in the courtyard.
I still command him via the disc.
What happened to him?
Guard, do you hear me?
Do you hear me speaking to you?
I order you here at once!
Father!
Help me...!
Please ask God to save me!
Forty-three...
Forty-seven...
Fifty-three...
Fifty-nine...
Wh-What potent poison...
Sixty-one...
Tell... The Lord to have mercy on me!
Can you hear me?
Give me your keycard!
Will I... Will I be saved?!
Hey! Don't pull it out yet, you dolt!
Father!
Si-Sixty-seven...
Seventy-one...
What the hell's going on here?
These frogs...
I-I'm saved!
I want you to open this gate, immediately!
F-Father? What's going on?
How should I know?!
A tornado, perhaps.
Just move, and quickly!
Understood! Right away!
Th-These frogs, they're...
What are you doing?
There's a guard lying unconscious here!
Now hurry and let me out!
An unconscious guard?
W-Wait, father!
I'll go and get help!
Wait! Where are you going?!
Just throw the switch and open the door!
I-I know how...
...but what if I need permission?
I need to ask my supervisor!
Stay calm!
Just calm down, Father!
I am perfectly calm.
The only one here who isn't...
Seventy-three... Seventy-nine...
...is you!
Do you mean to abandon me?!
I'll be right back, Father!
Whitesnake!
Give me a disc!
I may not be able to control all of them...
...but I can control a single frog!
Explode after flying ten meters!
I command you!
My eyes!
S-Save me!
Please call for help!
Father!
Please, Father!
Eighty-three... Eighty-nine... Ninety-seven...
I'm right here.
You believe that if I leave here and call for help,
you will be promptly treated.
Is that not what you're thinking?
Then it would be best if you move
toward the sound of my voice, yes?
Father!
Kujo Jotaro's Star Platinum disc...
What should I do with it?
I've eliminated Jolyne,
but I cannot leave her there.
D-Did the gate open?
Please take me with you...
...Father?
Father, where are you?!
I-I'm at my limit...
I can't keep the poison back!
The disc that I dropped...
I don't even know where it is anymore!
The rain stopped.
Where is Cujoh Jolyne's corpse?
The disc must be near.
As harrowing as that was,
frogs could never defeat a snake.
Find it.
Whitesnake's range is twenty meters at most.
This is a tremendous risk...
The consequences for being spotted here would be dire...
But I have no choice.
The souls of deceased felons return to the earth
as frogs for want of companions in the afterlife.
I've heard there are
similar legends spoken of in the East.
Does that not perfectly describe this scene?
And that which we seek
must be somewhere in the vicinity.
Whitesnake...
Sweep the area between
your location and the entrance gate.
The guard may have taken it.
It must be thereabouts.
I found it!
I have retrieved the disc.
Thanks a bunch.
I've been waiting for you to find it.
Goddammit...
This is nasty...
They're all over my face.
It feels so... "bleh"...
The frogs only excrete poison
if they make impact on landing.
As long as they don't splatter on impact,
they're harmless creatures.
That's why I made a net of live frogs
to soften the impact of the ones that were still falling.
I just had to lay here
and wait 'til you found the disc.
An act of futility!
I'll kill you and desecrate your grave!
They were already here...
The contact from
the Speedwagon Foundation.
I'm surprised they're not even human.
They're here just in time, too.
It weaved through the raining frogs
and made it to the courtyard.
That dove is named Savage Garden.
Just like a trained carrier pigeon,
it'll carry that disc to where it needs to go.
Whitesnake!
The guard dropped a gun near the gate!
Shoot that dove out of the sky!
That brainless guard!
He used up all the ammunition...
Damn him!
I won.
Don't underestimate me!
This changes nothing.
Even with Star Platinum,
your father remains a broken puppet!
He will never remember you again,
his own flesh and blood daughter!
Hey, look!
We've got a guard down!
Don't step on the frogs!
Sweep the courtyard!
Someone might be there!
I-I can't... pass out yet...
Its user must be close...
I have to find Whitesnake's user first...
Its user has my dad's memory disc!
This is my chance to find out who he is!
Hey! Look out the window!
Holy shit!
It's a miracle! It's gotta be!
But who's gonna clean up this mess?
This changes nothing.
Stealing Jotaro's Star Platinum was merely to
satisfy my own desires. To avenge my dear friend.
The memory disc is what truly matters,
and I still possess it.
Things are proceeding as planned.
Jotaro's memories may be
the only place where I might find Heaven.
It was an abnormal occurrence where frogs
rained down only on the prison courtyard.
In the chaos of this inexplicable event,
Jolyne's escape attempt was overlooked.
Furthermore, the Speedwagon Foundation
obtained Kujo Jotaro's Star Platinum disc.
However, without his memory disc,
Jotaro's soul will never be restored.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Sportsmax...
I wanted to ask you about this bone.
With your ability,
I would like you to try something.
Is that a human bone?
Who's it belong to?
You needn't concern yourself.
Let's just say it belonged to
an old friend of mine.
The bone of my dear friend, the mighty Dio.
Kiss of Love and Revenge Part 1