The bone of my dear friend, the mighty Dio.
Wh-What is happening?
Wh-Where is the bone?!
Tell me where it went at once!
I can feel the bone's presence
in the Ultra Security House Unit.
Ms. Jolyne wanted to get sent to
the Disciplinary Wing so she could find the bone?
Yep.
But she really didn't think it through.
If I get my hands on it first,
Whitesnake will come after me.
And with him...
...my dad's stolen memory disc!
That short guy...
I have to find him.
He has the bone!
Is he hiding somewhere?
I have to find the bone...
...before that short guy is beaten
by someone else and I lose track of it again!
Wh-What?!
Wh-What the hell happened here?
They're already done fighting!
And everyone in the Disciplinary Wing
is weirdly bloated!
It's a Stand ability!
How many other
Stand users were sent here?
Did those guys do this?
What the hell did they even do?
No, Stands are
one ability per user!
Only one of their two abilities
could have taken out these prisoners!
Just how many other Stand users
were sent to this Disciplinary Wing?
One thing's for sure, a Stand user who can stimulate
people's minds to make them fight is still hiding here!
Oh, even with those gaping wounds,
you can still stand up?
You have quite the curious Stand!
A Stand made of threads!
Especially so, given how
it's impossible to predict.
But what I find most intriguing
is your mental strength.
Despite the toll it took on your body,
I can see that battle made you grow stronger.
When Whitesnake mentioned he was sending
four Stand users, yours truly included...
...I wondered if sending
so many was truly necessary.
But now, I find myself
a touch more convinced that it was.
If, indeed, he wishes for you
to be eliminated for certain.
My name is Kenzo.
I'm 78 years old.
The secret to my longevity is
eight and a half hours of sleep a day...
...and a daily cup of urine as part of
my urine therapy regimen.
Forming and keeping good habits
is of vital importance.
Are you familiar with urine therapy?
If you want to fight,
I won't back down.
American-style.
French-style.
Japanese-style.
Italian-style à la Naples.
A nice selection of
international "fuck you" gestures.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Allow me to get
right to the point.
These prisoners were all drowned.
Episode 17  Fiery Blaze, Dragon's Dream
Their bodies became lifeless
and bloated because I drowned them.
Furthermore, it seems that you won't be
the first opponent I must contend with.
F.F.!
Dammit!
He caught me sneaking up on him
from behind the bloated bodies!
My sneak attack was a total bust.
Doesn't help that a corpse randomly
got in the way of my F.F. bullets!
Heavens, how dangerous!
F.F., how did you get here?
I got here just in time.
But just barely, huh, Jolyne?
Gimme a sec and I'll
take care of those wounds.
That man...
Who was he again?
Oh, right, he was with
Weather Report in Emporio's hideout.
But first things first, Jolyne...
This old man's
gotta be taken care of!
Southeast, 127 degrees,
30 minutes and 20 seconds.
Your sweat...
It will drip.
But will you open your mouth?
Would you like to drown?
Drown?
I dunno what you're up to,
but I'm a big fan of water!
Take your best-
A trained person takes between
five and seven minutes to drown in water.
Of course, that's assuming
there's air left in their lungs.
But in such a situation where one's
forced to expel all of the air in their lungs...
...they would drown near-instantly
with just a few drops of water!
I directly struck your fourth cervical vertebra
by going through your throat.
It contains nerves
connected directly to your kidneys!
Your adrenal glands!
They produce hormones that regulate your respiratory organs
in much the same way oil lubricates an engine!
It may only be a few drops, but the pain that's surely coursing
through you must feel like being drowned by an entire ocean!
I can't breathe!
Right now I'm inhabiting
the body of Etro, an average human.
This sucks!
Her body won't last!
F.F.!
Would you like to drown by her side?
Cujoh Jolyne!
Hossha!
So what are you
supposed to be?
Are you even human?
Don't get up.
You'll be safer watching them from afar, for now.
Shouldn't you be trying to determine
what kind of Stand the old man is using?
Listen to me carefully.
Our main concern here isn't
the technique he used to drown these prisoners.
It's that he dodged
every single shot fired at him.
It may seem unimportant,
but how did not even a single bullet hit its mark?
Doesn't that seem
far more dangerous?
Why did you even come here?
Your name is Annasui, right?
I love you.
I could hardly wait
to be here by your side.
Uh... come again?
The old man has been
imprisoned here for forty years now.
He's a fool who
drinks his own piss.
I hadn't seen him in the male wing for a while,
but who could have guessed he was here all along?
And worse yet,
he became a Stand user.
During fall of 1969, the old man murdered
thirty-four people, all young men and women.
He was sentenced to
280 consecutive years.
Though he's old now,
he was just thirty-seven when he received his sentence.
His claim to fame
was founding a cult.
His sect became so popular
that even the Hollywood elite started to join.
However, his cult's activities clashed with society,
prompting the police and the FBI to intervene.
Cornered and out of options, the old man locked himself
and his thirty-four followers inside his estate here in Florida.
His goal was to
burn them all to death.
He made sure to drug them
before attempting to set the building ablaze.
They all burned to death,
yet he, the founder, survived.
Bizarrely enough, a section of the building
happened to fall right on top of him...
...shielding him from
the smoke and fire.
He was rescued
on the brink of death.
It's undeniable that
he had intended to die.
So what am I getting at here?
Who knows.
I couldn't tell you.
Either way,
the old man was the sole survivor.
He wasn't put to death,
but he'll never leave this prison.
Those are the facts
surrounding this man.
I'm unsure just what you are,
but I know your greatest strength.
The secret to your strength, as it were.
I sense the presence of something
other than blood running through your veins.
Is it your Stand?
Or an altogether
different life form?
Not that it matters
for the purpose of defeating you.
You share the same body structure
and weaknesses as every other human...
...right down to the blood
flowing through your veins.
Would you like to drown again?
But this time with
no chance of survival.
Southwest, 225 degrees, 0 minutes.
Th-This again!
He called out something in his hands!
What is that?
And what's with
the funky footwork?
And the orientation of your dragon is...
F.F., behind you!
Nope.
That's not gonna do you any good.
Enough with the attacking!
Dragon's Dream
Power: None
Speed: None
Range: None
Durability: A
Precision: None
Growth Potential: None
Power: None
Speed: None
Range: None
Durability: A
Precision: None
Growth Potential: None
Kenzo
Nope.
That's not gonna do you any good.
Enough with the attacking!
I told you,
your enemy is my old fart of a user!
You people just don't listen, do you?
I'm not choosing sides here.
Your attacks just
whiz right on through me.
Turn around!
You're in danger!
The old fart's coming!
I have no business meddling here.
It's just the old fart.
The old fart is your enemy.
Th-This thing...!
Was this the thing that helped
the old man dodge my bullets?
He's coming!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
His skill...
How can a 78-year-old
punch and kick like that?
Now I can enter the dragon!
What the hell is this?
What did he just do to his arm?
His arm is gonna hit F.F.
on the back of her head!
H-He almost got her!
But blocking him that way
was classic F.F.!
The moment he touched that dragon-like Stand,
Kenzo's arm disappeared.
Did he do it to obfuscate
the direction of his attack?
What the hell is
that dragon-like thing?
Does your arm fly off
when you touch the dragon?
Too bad you still
hit like an old man!
Wrong again, F.F.
I can already foresee
what will happen.
It's not as though someone else
could have predicted it...
Whoa!
Quit piping up for no reason!
I've heard enough out of you!
There's no picking sides here!
Keeping it to yourself's not fair!
Just tell 'em already!
You opened your mouth!
F.F.!
Was that a coincidence just now?
That prisoner's glasses flung up
and stabbed F.F. in the face!
A misfortunate direction.
I'm beginning to understand.
He's using feng shui.
There are people in East Asia
who practice feng shui.
You can tell he's using it
since he always moves in cardinal directions.
As if predetermined,
he launches his attacks from a single direction.
Furthermore,
the Stand in his hands...
He uses that dragon-like Stand
to choose the direction of his attacks.
Feng shui?
What's that?
He chooses the direction
of his attacks?
Feng shui.
It's a form of divination akin to tarot card reading
or astrology, except it's not fortune-telling.
According to Eastern philosophy,
there are natural forms of energy such as wind and water...
...that flow through
the mountains and valleys.
It's said that by knowing the direction in which they flow,
one can determine their path in life.
For example, feng shui is used to determine
the fortunes found within an area, house, or even just a room.
If the land or house faces
a misfortunate direction...
...it's said to affect the wealth, well-being,
and fortunes of those living there.
During times of war,
the feng shui of an enemy's castle was determined...
...to decide which direction to attack from
in order to make the castle fall more easily.
Conversely, by building temples and similar structures
to counteract the misfortunate energy...
...emanating from those sides of the castle,
their enemies could fortify their defenses.
Additionally, the philosophies behind
feng shui can be applied to human anatomy.
Assassination feng shui
is one such application of it.
If one uses feng shui to determine the most fortunate
direction of attack against a nearby enemy, a human...
...no matter how alert they may be,
or how they defend themselves...
...it becomes possible to approach
without alerting them of the intent to attack.
Thus making the assassination trivial.
Put another way...
MISFORTUNE
...they were misfortunately oriented.
This is, beyond a shadow of a doubt,
the secret of Kenzo's Stand.
Sneaking up on F.F.
from a misfortunate direction...
The dragon Stand points in the most
fortunate direction for a lethal strike.
And when the old man's attacks
overlap with the dragon...
...F.F.'s fate is then set in stone.
Who would have thought that Kenzo
mastered assassination feng shui...
...during his forty years in prison,
later manifesting it as his Stand ability!
So feng shui tells him
which direction he should go!
A-And the same
applies for defense.
Not a single one of
F.F.'s bullets hit the old man.
So that also means...
...he used this feng shui thing
to beat the odds and protect himself.
Am I right?
Undoubtedly.
When the dragon is in his hands,
he can determine the safest direction.
He moves himself in that direction
to ready for an attack.
The dragon is pointing in the most
fortunate direction to kill again!
F.F.!
Those glasses hitting you
wasn't just a coincidence!
Don't let the old man
move toward the dragon!
I still don't really get it,
but you can't let the old man touch the dragon!
You hear that, Dragon's Dream?
You kept running your mouth
and they figured out my trick!
Oh, shut up, you old fart!
I'm not just your goon!
Don't you think feng shui
should be for everyone?
But it's true,
the old fart is best equipped to make use of me.
F.F., right now this is
your misfortunate direction.
Just above your left ear.
This area is on absolute
maximum emergency warning.
Your lucky color is yellow,
and images of goldfish will bring you good fortune.
If you have any, that is!
F.F., he's circling behind you!
Going for a chop, are you?
It isn't even necessary for me
to orient myself with the dragon.
He converted the defensive motion
of his arm into an attack.
Must be from tai chi...
Your mouth belongs to me!
Another case of
the defensive stance leading into an attack!
You vile wench!
It would seem taking advantage of
the dragon's orientation is the surest path to victory!
I made your hand
overlap with the dragon!
But that effectively makes it
my attack against you!
Your own arm
is going to attack you!
My attack overlapped with
the orientation of your death!
What the fuck did you
just do to me, bastard?!
What did you do
to my fucking arm?
I told you, that direction
represents your absolute misfortune!
The power of that direction is at play!
I can't predict what will happen next,
but if I were you...
...I would try to keep the damage
you take to a minimum.
F.F., get the hell away from there!
The meteorites fucked up the supports!
The fan's gonna fall on you!
Oh, no, the fan isn't
the real danger here!
The boomerang is!
F.F.!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Fiery Blaze, Foo Fighters