wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 2  Stone Free
Inmates...
I am the warden of
Green Dolphin Street State Prison, Roccobarocco.
The lovely lady to my right
is my assistant, Charlotte.
Nice to meet you all!
Charlotte, please explain to the newcomers
what life here in prison will be like.
Sure!
Just like our country itself,
this prison is built on freedom and equality.
You may freely explore
the facility and exercise as you please.
You are also free to use the
phones, showers, and library.
Exceptionally well-behaved inmates
may even own a TV.
You can also work or study
and earn college credits.
Why yes, that's right!
Yes? What is it, Charlotte?
But Warden, there are rules
that must be followed, right?
You are absolutely correct, Charlotte!
First, you are not permitted to remove
the wristband with your inmate number.
No lending or borrowing
of items between inmates.
No possession of metal objects.
What about earrings?
The warden's still talking!
Shut yer yap!
Earrings are prohibited,
FE40536, Cujoh Jolyne.
If you have further questions,
please ask the guards.
Well, that's it from me.
All right!
Everyone, face left!
It's so spacious.
So the prison covers the whole island?
Oh, a crocodile.
FE40536.
Cell 206. You'll be staying here.
Free time for today is over.
Cells open at 6:30 A.M.
Breakfast begins at 7:00,
but you're free to sleep in if you so choose.
Try to get along now.
Nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Jolyne.
I'm Guess.
You hungry?
Thanks.
But I've had a really long day,
and I'm not in the mood to eat—
Ouch! What the—
Bottom bunk is mine, bitch!
Got a problem with that?!
I don't want to fight you.
I thought the top bunk was yours
since your things are up there.
W-Wait, is that...?!
Hands off, idiot!
Don't touch my stuff!
Can I just see the charm?
There should be a small stone
and a picture of my parents inside!
I think that was mine!
I bought it for two bucks
from a new person the other day.
It's such a pretty little thing.
Come on, just show me!
What was that?!
Watch your mouth, gorilla girl!
Okay, I'll buy it off you.
How much do you want?
Two hundred dollars.
What the hell?
You heard me, bitch.
I said two hundred dollars.
Y-You...!
Lights out!
What's going on?
Too much is happening all at once.
I have so much to process.
The loneliness is enough to make me cry...
Wh-What the fuck?
I'm sorry.
About last night, I mean.
Huh?
It's morning...
Here...
I don't mind if you take a quick look.
But...
There was nothing inside it.
No pictures, no nothing.
See?
There was nothing else inside?
Like a stone?
Nope. Nothing.
Anyway, I'm sorry for how I acted last night.
I get nervous around new people.
Huh?
Oh, you don't need to apologize,
it was my fault.
I don't know how things work here yet.
You're a good person, Jolyne.
Let's be friends from now on.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Anyway, it's breakfast time.
Catch you later!
Wait, let's go together!
What the fuck?
Did she spill water?
My pants are soaked!
This is bullshit!
What do you mean "sold out"?
I didn't eat yet.
It's like it says.
You're free to sleep in.
You're also free to be late.
Isn't there enough for everyone?
You don't have any milk or bananas?
One of the seven wonders of prison.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, Jolyne, took you long enough.
I'm so full.
Wait, Guess!
You had two milk cartons and two bananas!
Two?
What an odd thing to say.
Oh, I just remembered.
I accidentally spilled water from the sink.
I'll wipe it up later.
I already got it...
Oh, thank you!
You're too kind, Jolyne.
That's...
Jump for me. I know you can do it.
I love you...
...and you love me.
Come on...
Anything is possible if we trust each other.
Just do it.
Good, good, good, good boy!
Aren't you the cute-cutiest
little cutie pie, Chirpy-Poo?
You did well!
Here's your reward!
Good morning!
No, Chirpy-Poo.
We don't say "good morning."
We say "I love you!"
It's just so cute when
you say you love me!
I love you!
Good, good, good, good boy!
You're such a good boy, Chirpy-Poo!
Next, perch.
Give me a cute little hop.
Risk-taking is part of
building trust, Chirpy-Poo.
What's wrong?!
Do it, already!
Whoa...
What? "Whoa"?
What did you just say?!
What kind of bird goes "whoa"?
I love you! I love you! I love you!
Trying to pull a fast one, are you?
How can I trust you
when you lie to my face like that?
Say something!
This isn't working.
We're through.
What was that?
A banana?
What is this?
They're tiny, but these are real...
That woman...
...already killed them!
Guess... You...
She must've picked up some sort of ability
from the stone in the pendant, too!
But what was up
with that tiny person?
Wha—
What's going on?!
Goo Goo Dolls
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: B
Durability: D
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: B
Durability: D
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
Guess
Th-This is...
Did my body somehow...?
I knew it was you.
How did you steal away my Chirpy-Poo?
Jolyne, Jolyne, Jolyne, Jolyne!
Jolyne!
You know,
I'm really starting to grow fond of you.
What's going on with my body?
What did you do to me?!
Listen, Jolyne.
Please don't talk.
That person inside the parrot—
Hey! I said no talking!
Get in.
I already scooped out its guts.
There was a flaw to using a parrot.
Birds don't have hands
to grab or hold things.
Rats, on the other hand, have front paws.
This guy was a prison guard
who got fired for slacking off.
The warden and prison staff
think he went home.
Also, even though I told you not to talk...
...I don't mind if you do
as long as you throw in some cute squeaks.
You can say, "I'm squeaking going!"
or "I'm squee hungry!"
Got it? Okay?
You're just as cute
as I thought you'd be!
Time for training!
Faster, faster, faster, faster!
No slowing down!
Lift, Chorokichi.
Ch-Chorokichi?
Everything has a name.
"The word was in the beginning with God,
and all things were made by Him."
This is why I gave a name to the power
from within my heart that I used to shrink you.
Goo Goo Dolls.
That's the name of my mental ability.
Let's add another one.
You cheater...
Did you think you could
pull a fast one on me?
So... You've chosen to betray my trust?
Are you telling me we're fucking through?!
Just kidding!
You passed, Chorokichi!
You can't do this job if you're not clever.
Very, very good!
You see that?
The control room is down this corridor.
Inside there's a switch
that can deactivate every lock in this place.
You can pass through.
See what I'm getting at?
We're breaking out of here.
For some reason, I can't shrink myself.
But if we work together, we can leave.
It's vital that we trust each other.
We won't actually
break out until later, of course.
For now, I just want you to
scope out everything beyond this corridor.
Do you really think we can escape?
Hey, hey, hey!
I squeakin' told you to
squeak when you talk!
How the squeak do I
get into the squeaking control room?
So cute! You're a doll!
How the fuck would I know, dumbass?
Finding that out is your job.
Look up.
There's a surveillance camera.
But the area beneath
this handrail is a blind spot.
Go underneath it.
Put your head on.
Come on, go!
Hey! What are you up to?
Yeah, you with the hairband!
State your name and number!
FE18081.
Name's Guess.
As for what I'm doing... Nothing, really.
If you're just loitering,
back away from the door!
Go somewhere else!
Sure, Mr. Prison Guard.
There are four steel doors.
Which one's the control room?
And there's two cameras here, too.
What's going on?
All of a sudden...
...it's getting real tight!
What was that noise?
I heard it, too.
It was close.
My body...
...is getting bigger!
Coffee's done.
Maybe you heard the coffee maker.
No, it sounded different
and wasn't from that direction.
This is bad! What's going on?!
Distance?
Is it because Guess left?
Is her ability affected by distance?
I definitely heard something!
Whatever it is, it's close!
Sh-Shit!
It's right under there!
Hey, get out of the way!
I said move!
Augh! H-Hot!
The hell is wrong with you?!
Huh?
I told you it was the coffee maker!
My bad...
I've scoped out enough!
If I don't get back fast enough,
I won't fit through the bars!
Wha—
What is that?
Goo... Goo... Dolls!
Th-This thing...
This thing...
It looks like a doll, but it's translucent.
It's just like my thread.
Others can't see it.
It's the manifestation of Guess's energy.
Goo Goo Dolls.
That's the name of my mental ability.
It shrank me and tore
the guard in the parrot to pieces!
The piece of shit was
inside the rat with me!
And Guess...
She doesn't know her ability
wears off if she gets too far away.
My body's going back to normal.
This thing thinks I'm ditching,
so it's chasing after me!
And even worse, it's trying to kill me!
Goo... Goo... Dolls!
Shit!
Why is this happening to me?
Is this thing really going to kill me?
I'm stuck!
Goo Goo!
Threads...
A cluster of threads...
This must be the manifestation of my energy.
A cluster!
When the threads cluster together,
they become solid!
I get it now!
Scream, you piece of shit!
Call Guess here!
Make it fast!
Jolyne...
You mean... you have an ability, too...?
Guess!
Stop!
Stop gripping my Goo Goo Dolls so tight!
Shut up!
Shrink me enough to get out of here!
Only a little, got it?
Okay, fine,
and I'll even give you the bottom bunk!
Please don't hate me
because of what happened!
But could you still
squeak every now and then?
Just hurry the fuck up!
G-Good.
Now, the pendant.
Give me the stone
and tell me who sold it to you!
O-Of course...
Two hundred dollars, was it?
Shut the fuck up, bitch!
Tell me who sold it to you!
Fine!
Uh, I think she said her name
was Hermès or something.
Hermès?
I don't know much about her.
Here.
Kidding...
Got you!
Guards! We got a problem!
This bitch here crossed the gun point!
Better get here quick!
Wh-What are you doing there?
How did you get in?
Jailbreak!
Code 999!
You're fucked now!
The prison guard's coming back
with a shotgun as we speak!
And he's totally allowed
to shoot your ass!
No questions asked!
Jolyne!
Serves you right!
That's what you get
for trampling over my heart!
Gimme a break, Guess.
You said everything has a name.
I'll name this ability of mine, too.
Stone Free.
I'm going to break free
from this stone ocean.
Hear me?
Stone Free. That's its name.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
If there's a pecking order
in this prison, I'll follow it.
As long as I'm the one giving orders.
Now let me cross over.
Hey, where'd she go?
She disappeared.
Huh?
You sure you saw her?
Well, I just saw her back, so...
Huh...
Dad...
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
The Visitor Part 1