wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 5  Prisoner of Love
What's this?
Looks like you're finally up.
Was everything we saw
until now just a dream?
Yeah...
We're being dissolved, now.
Right inside this room.
You've gotta break down the door...
...with your ability, Star Platinum!
Hurry!
Ora!
You did it!
Now drag me out!
Let's get out of here!
Hold on.
What did you just say?
Did you say "Star Platinum"?
My Stand's name?
How do you know that, Jolyne?
Looking back, it seems everything up until
I told you about Johngalli A. was real.
Which means...
...you haven't seen my ability yet.
Even if you could sense I had a Stand
since I'm your father...
...there's no way you'd know
it's called Star Platinum.
This isn't adding up!
This isn't reality!
Stone... Free...
Jolyne...
You finally...
opened your eyes...
That took a lot out of me...
My thread dissolves way too fast.
Jolyne...
You had a dream, too...
Dunno about yours,
but mine was a fucking nightmare.
I see...
So we were both shown dreams,
like watching a movie.
Guess so...
Could have used some popcorn.
I can't move anymore.
Not even a finger.
What about you?
Can you move?
What's happening around us now...
...could still be a dream.
If you can't move at all,
then this is reality.
The undeniable reality
that we can't escape.
So it is...
We're screwed at this rate...
The ability the pendant gave you...
Call out the Stand that woke me up.
Stone Free?
Yeah.
Can you call it out as a cluster?
Your power, that is.
I get what you're asking, but it's no use.
It took everything I had
just to wake you up.
No way in hell I'm
breaking that door.
No, just call it out.
That's it.
Keep going.
Can you make it come out more?
Just a few centimeters closer to me.
Better more to the left, but...
Okay, good enough.
Not ideal, but it'll work.
Let's get the hell out of
this visitation room.
Ora!
That was my Stand, Star Platinum.
Pull me out.
This is reality. For sure.
G... Goddammit...
Motherfucker...!
This pain... and this anger...!
You... how dare you...?
You may have broke us out,
but now I'm pissed!
And that's no fucking illusion!
Here, give me your hands.
What now?
Ora!
Let's go.
Oh, right...
Any idea what this is?
We're alive because of it,
but I just don't know...
It's a human bone.
Specifically...
...it's the sacrum from
the pelvis of an adult female.
The surface looks like
it was dissolved with some kind of acid.
Dissolved?
Because of earlier?
Can't say.
I don't know why you have that,
but it doesn't matter now.
I'm the only one who saw that boy,
but he's definitely here!
I'm not sure how,
but he's here in this prison... and that's reality!
Code 909, emergency level 4.
Emergency alarm activated
by visitation room outer door.
Emergency level 4, code 909.
So, what's the plan?
Guess you're the newest member
of the felon club now...
I thought I was clear earlier.
I'm breaking you out of here.
You have the pendant on you, right?
It's extremely important.
Don't ever lose it.
Let's go. We're breaking out.
To think that they could
escape this room...
Is it just me,
or are there barely any guards?
It's because we're in a public area.
Look at this.
We'll escape through the window
marked with an X.
It's a window facing the beach.
We'll board a submarine at the beach
and escape by sea.
A submarine?
I go way back with an organization
called the Speedwagon Foundation.
They arranged it for me.
Doesn't seem to be
any cameras down this hall.
The target window is
just down here, to the left.
From there it's about
twenty meters to shore.
We have a lot to think about,
but it can wait until we're outside.
Ora!
Let's go.
Oh, just a fan?
Jolyne.
That hurt!
Where were you looking?
Stay calm.
Here, stand up.
What's wrong?
Give me your hand.
I-It's just that...
Well... Thanks...
But I can stand up by myself.
That's not what I meant.
Look.
Be careful when you trip.
What would you do if you lost this?
What is it?
I told you it was important.
Never let it go. Take it.
You're headed to Tokyo?
When this is happening
to your own daughter?!
And you call yourself her father?
Wait... Hello? Hello?!
You haven't changed at all.
Always so cold and calculating
about everything.
When I almost died from a fever as a kid,
you didn't even come home.
And when I was accused of theft
just because I went on a little joyride...
You just fucked off somewhere
on a plane then, too.
Sound about right?
I turned out just fine, anyway.
Even now, I'm just some pain in the ass
who doesn't feel anything even when I fall down! See?
Lucky me! Woohoo!
What are you talking about?
If it's so fucking important,
hold it yourself!
Wait.
Fuck off. I don't want it!
Not that.
Something's felt off for a while now.
Something is stalking us.
Jolyne, get down.
Nobody down this hallway.
Maybe they went the other way.
Oh, it's just a guard.
C'mon, open your eyes!
The bars are all bent up!
The convicts went through here!
Come in...
Th-That's...
...Johngalli A.!
It's him...
He came to finish us off himself!
Jolyne!
Head for the window!
I'll handle h-
That's Johngalli A.'s Stand.
But wasn't his attack on us just a dream?
Eat lead!
Impossible!
We're still dreaming?
No! This is reality!
Stop, time!
Our enemy...
Our enemies...!
There's two of them!
He not only forced us to dream,
he even included Johngalli A.'s actual Stand!
This was all a setup...
...leading to the moment when I'd be forced to
stop time to protect my daughter!
This entire time...
...they were targeting me!
Time resumes!
Jolyne!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
You were one move behind.
Kujo Jotaro, how I've waited...
...for this moment!
Ripe for the taking.
Perfect...
From you, a man without rival,
I have taken the object of my desire!
This is Whitesnake's ability!
Those bullets!
His Stand is here!
How?!
I thought his Stand was
just part of our dream!
Anyway, while he's reloading,
I'm gonna...
Ora!
I see the shore! We're close!
Go on without me.
I'll catch up.
Did you really...
...get shot back there?
Listen...
Stand users can only have one Stand ability.
Which means we were
against two enemies all along.
Johngalli A., and whoever made the sludge.
Leave without me.
Take the pendant.
Don't lose it.
It's embedded with a transmitter.
They'll know where to find you.
The submarine's programmed
to automatically track its location.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Just make it to the shore
and the sub will find you.
The Speedwagon Foundation
I mentioned earlier will find the sub.
If you understand, then go, Jolyne.
This pendant...
But earlier, I...
No... You couldn't have...
I've always cared for you.
Wh-What's wrong?
Your chest... You're not...
No! Why?
Go, Jolyne.
It's just a little blood.
I'll be right behind you.
Liar!
You stood up for me earlier...
...and that other enemy
took something from you!
That's why you couldn't dodge the bullets!
Don't tell me I'm wrong!
What was that...?
Don't tell me... your Stand?
Jolyne!
What?
Th-These are...
They're threads!
When did she...?
Take this!
Oh, fuck off.
We're going to jump out the window
and head for the beach.
And you're gonna stay out of the way.
Got it?
Sh-She...
When the hell did she
get a Stand like this?
If her Stand's this powerful,
they should have known about it way before she got locked up!
Understood. I'm dropping my gun.
Not like it matters,
but I never told you to drop it.
I was just looking for the best angle.
The best angle to
knock you the fuck out, that is.
The only angle I see working
is having your chin tilted just a smidge to the right.
I'm starting to think...
I should have left Jotaro and shot this bitch first!
Going for Jotaro first was a bad move!
Does Whitesnake know about this?
Cujoh Jolyne...
Without a doubt,
she's Kujo Jotaro's daughter!
And a Joestar!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Jolyne...
Back when... we were dreaming...
...you said you would stay behind in prison...
for some kid you just met...
He grabbed my arm
like he was trying to cling to it.
I'm going back inside.
I know it was just a dream...
But...
Dad!
Dammit!
The beach is right there!
Dad!
Find them!
Lethal force is authorized!
A guard's been gunned down!
Convict is armed and dangerous!
We are cleared to shoot to kill!
Where is it?
I'm already at the beach...
That organization you work with,
the Speedwagon Foundation...
I don't know who they are,
but if they really did send us a submarine...
...they gotta have some seriously
advanced tech and a shitload of money!
His wound... A gunshot wound like this...
They've got to be better equipped
to treat you than any regular doctor is!
Where's the sub?
Where the hell is it?!
Everything you said was true...
The sub's already at the beach!
We're saved...
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
You can't...
No, this can't be happening!
It just can't!
I know he was shot,
but the wounds are shallow.
His vital organs weren't hit!
This can't be fatal!
Then...
Then his heart...
Why the hell isn't it beating?!
I'm sure now.
You have Joestar blood in you.
Jolyne, with your indomitable spirit...
...I know you'll survive.
Found them!
Something's moving
on the other side of the fence!
Watch for the gun!
No, I'm not on the other side.
If you're looking for me, I'm right here.
You bitch!
Wait, hold your fire!
Her hands are up.
But...
Do not fire!
She's unarmed.
Do you surrender?
But there should be
someone else with her!
That tall guy who visited her!
He's around here somewhere! Find him!
So that's where you were.
Why? Why, lady?
Why didn't you run?
I'm sorry, but your father is already dead.
The power in his spirit
was stolen by the sludge.
But you barely
made it out alive!
So why didn't you run?
Because the attacker
ran inside the prison.
Not out, but in!
Their goal, and their ability,
is to turn Stands into physical objects and steal them!
Once our attacker finished the job,
they ran back inside the prison.
And they aren't leaving.
It's someone inside these prison walls!
Wait, are you saying...
you want to steal it back?
You think that will bring your dad back?
That's exactly why I'm going back in.
I know the truth is painful, but...
His corpse is going to rot away.
That melted bone I gave you
was my mom's.
That sludge stole her spirit,
then she died.
I see...
I was born here in this prison.
My mother was an inmate.
I've been hiding here ever since.
What's your name?
I'm Emporio.
Emporio.
Your mom saved our lives.
Thank you.
But...
For some bizarre reason, I'm sure...
...that my dad isn't dead.
If I get his Stand back,
he'll come back to life.
That's why...
...I'm going back!
You did it...
You finally got your hands on
the unrivaled Stand that stops time!
Yes.
And I have you to thank for it, Johngalli A.
We make a good team, you and I.
Please, take me back to the men's prison.
I let my guard down...
Do you, uh... know where my gun is?
Here.
You were the only one
who knew my true identity.
The sin of murdering the guards
rests entirely on you.
It all works out peacefully this way.
To leave a lasting impression on someone...
Jotaro said it is a wonderful thing.
I'm of the same mind.
Here lies the means to do just that.
Hermès' Stickers