wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Heed my words carefully, Sportsmax...
Episode 15  Ultra Security Disciplinary Wing
Much like how the surface of Earth is
composed of 30% land and 70% water...
...it would seem the number of souls of
living beings is likewise cleanly determined.
The more humans that inhabit the Earth,
the fewer other organisms can coexist with them.
The total number of souls
remains constantly fixed.
Now, suppose there exists a human being
who could possess dozens, nay, tens of thousands of souls...
What would such a person see?
What would lie in wait for them?
No idea.
Couldn't even begin to tell you.
It's an interesting thought, though.
I'll give you that.
So, uh...
What exactly do you want me doing?
Sportsmax...
I wanted to ask you about this bone.
With your ability,
I would like you to try something.
Could you attempt to revive it?
Is that a human bone?
Who's it belong to?
You needn't concern yourself.
Let's just say it belonged to
an old friend of mine.
You're asking me to revive it,
but all you have is that one tiny piece.
Or do you have the rest of
the skeleton stored somewhere else?
Can a single bone even be revived?
Dio...
This is all that remains of him.
The rest of his body turned to dust
and no longer exists in this world.
Regardless,
you must try, Sportsmax.
And let me be perfectly clear:
If you are incapable,
you will return the skill I bestowed upon you.
I-I know that!
The thing is,
I... already did it.
It's done.
Wh-What is happening?
Wh-Where is the bone?!
Wh-Where did it go?!
His bone!
What did you do?!
Tell me where it went at once!
I-I don't fucking know!
Wh-What even is that bone?!
M-My ability can't control it!
I can't believe that bone
went and started moving by itself!
B-But I can feel it!
I can feel it moving around nearby.
Find it!
Leave, now!
N-No, stop.
Wait, Sportsmax.
I no longer have any doubt...
The power he spoke of
to reach Heaven must surely exist!
Do not pursue the bone.
Leave it be.
Allow it to do as it pleases
and act of its own accord.
Meanwhile, I will carefully observe...
...until I combine it with Kujo Jotaro's memory,
thus reaching the truth!
I can feel the bone's presence
in the Ultra Security House Unit.
Perhaps someone has
taken it for themselves...
Hermès retrieved that memory by pure coincidence.
It belonged to Sportsmax.
Jolyne already watched it too, of course.
Ms. Jolyne wanted to get sent to
the Disciplinary Wing so she could find the bone?
Yep.
But she really didn't think it through.
Now that Sportsmax's memories
were revealed to us...
...Whitesnake is gonna do
whatever it takes to eliminate Jolyne.
If Jolyne stays there all by herself,
she's as good as dead!
I owe my current existence to Jolyne.
But I don't know what to do here...
I want your help.
I can't...
Weather Report is still recovering in the infirmary,
and even he can't get in there.
I-I really wish I could help, but...
The Maximum Security Disciplinary Wing,
or Ultra Security House Unit, is southeast of the male wing.
You can only get there by
leaving the premises in a transport car.
There's not even any
secret passages inside.
I've never been there myself.
So yeah, I don't know
any way to protect Ms. Jolyne.
I'm not asking you to protect her.
Just help me sneak
into the Disciplinary Wing.
Hey, you...
Can you do it?
Don't expect anything from him!
Annasui won't cooperate.
But isn't he a Stand User?
Hey, were you born with your ability?
Didn't you hear me?
Annasui won't help.
No matter the reason,
he won't cooperate with anyone.
Why's that?
It's because...
I'll do anything!
If you take me to the Disciplinary Wing,
I'll do anything to repay you!
F.F., stop!
He's not the kind of guy
who helps people out.
What I'm trying to say is, well...
Wait, have you never heard
the name "Annasui" before?
He's a murderer!
Annasui's full name is Narciso Annasui.
Ever since he was a child,
for some inexplicable reason...
...he's had a weird habit.
Well, not really a habit.
It's some kind of syndrome.
A syndrome that gives him the urge
to disassemble everything.
He's compelled to
disassemble anything he sees.
When he was ten, he disassembled his neighbor's Porsche
and was institutionalized for six months.
Another time,
he disassembled a high-voltage telephone pole.
And when he was 21, there was an incident when
he went over to his then-girlfriend's apartment.
She was in bed with another man.
Annasui disassembled their bodies on the spot
so they could never be together again.
The psychiatric evaluation after his arrest
came back surprisingly normal.
That's how he ended up in the Aquarium.
Without Weather Report keeping him under control,
who knows what he's capable of?
That's who he is.
So please, give up on him.
But I can't reach Jolyne by myself.
I need backup.
His backup,
at the very least, is absolutely...
But how bizarre...
This feeling...
If asking him won't work, then...
...I'll use a "Foo Fighters Bullet"
to make him obey...
But...
For some reason,
I can't visualize my first shot hitting the mark.
I don't even know where to aim for.
I'll never get him to listen to me unless
I approach this like I'm going in for the kill.
That's what my gut tells me,
but I still have to try.
That's what I came here for.
Sure thing. Okay.
I can protect her.
Cujoh Jolyne, that is.
I'll cooperate.
And if she wants to find
this bone of whatever it was...
...I'll help with that, too.
Let's move.
She may be under attack
as we speak.
Wait, Annasui!
What are you planning?
Planning?
Like I said...
I'll protect her with all I got.
B-But...
I took a liking to her...
...and everything about her
from the moment we first met.
The fact that she willingly went to
the Disciplinary Wing for the sake of her father...
That conviction made me
like her even more.
If I successfully protect her to the end,
I'm going to marry her.
That's my condition.
Understood?
F.F., was it?
You said you were
willing to do anything.
So, give us your blessing.
That's what our wedding needs.
Do what now?
He said he's gonna do what
with Jolyne just now?
Diver Down!
What's going on over here?
What the hell was that loud bang?
I-Inside the wall...
With a time lag...!
That's the ability of
Annasui's Stand, Diver Down.
Now give us your blessing.
Survivor
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: E
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: E
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Guccio
Say, I'm curious about something, Dio.
Of all the Stand abilities
you've encountered...
...which one was the weakest?
It can be one you encountered
while traveling the world...
...or a newly created one.
Any ability...
...can be incredibly potent
in the right hands.
A king has his strengths...
...as does a cook.
That is what it means to live.
The same is true of Stands.
Preconceived notions
of strength are irrelevant.
Sorry, I phrased it poorly.
I was thinking like how children argue
who between Stallone and Van Damme is the stronger one.
Think of it at that level.
A Stand I named Survivor
is the weakest.
However, it is a handful.
Survivor?
It has a strong-sounding name.
The year was 1982.
In France's Lorraine region, a group of six had gone hiking,
went missing, then were later found dead.
The investigation team found evidence
that the six had fought one another.
They had killed each other.
The men and women alike put such intense
strain on their muscles that they broke their own bones.
One of their teeth was knocked loose by a punch
and embedded itself in a nearby rock.
That is how brutal it was.
Even the victor was unable to
descend the mountain due to his injuries.
According to what I learned thereafter...
...the six of them had stayed
in a lodge the night before.
They had gotten into a quarrel
with the lodge owner.
One of the women ridiculed
the lodge owner's body odor, saying he smelled foul.
And the lodge owner
was a Stand user.
Correct.
But what had
the lodge owner done to them?
And what compelled the six
to fight to their deaths?
To answer the former,
he did nothing.
He did nothing to them,
but there was a slight anger...
...that surged within his mind.
That anger became a small,
weak electric signal inside of his brain...
...that traveled down through his nervous system
and flowed out into the ground.
It was Survivor.
The electric signal traveled along the ground
all the way to the six hikers.
The ground and the hikers' shoes were damp,
allowing the electricity to travel easily.
At seventy millivolts, the electric potential
sending signals to the nervous system is quite small.
The Stand dwells in
that minuscule pulse of energy.
Survivor's attack is mostly unnoticeable
and doesn't cause direct harm.
It causes no injuries to people,
nor does it take control of them.
It is incapable of inflicting pain
or putting one to sleep.
It is capable of no such feats.
All it does is create anger.
It stimulates the limbic system
of the human brain ever so slightly...
...awakening its fighting spirit.
Because a single woman chose to
ridicule the lodge owner's body odor...
...all six were made
to fight to their deaths.
You told me earlier it was a handful.
What I mean is that
it is a useless Stand.
It cannot distinguish friend from foe.
If subordinates began fighting one another,
their organization would collapse.
Could you give me that ability?
If you don't intend to use it,
I would take that Stand.
You mean to extract the ability
and store it on a disc?
Perhaps that is wise.
In the right hands...
...the time may come
where it is needed.
These mushrooms seem to be edible.
Pretty tasty, too!
Shower time!
Get up, FE40536!
Bright!
Hell yeah!
Check it out! I got her!
She hid from me!
Hid like a dirty fuckin' cockroach!
I win this cell!
That puts my winnings
up to twenty smackers!
Sorry!
Damn.
I only got fifteen bucks on me.
C'mon, gimme a discount.
Guess that'll have to do!
N-Never mind that...
Anyway...
...I need to keep investigating
with my thread and find the bone.
Why is that bone here?
I don't know the answer yet...
...but for some reason,
it's somewhere inside this Disciplinary Wing.
Could someone here have it?
If I get my hands on it first,
Whitesnake will come after me.
And with him...
...my dad's stolen memory disc!
Hey, dipshit!
Who said you could stand up?
Oh hey, you think the Marlins
are gonna knock it out tonight?
I wouldn't count on it.
Their pitcher just broke up
with that reporter chick.
He ain't throwing any strikes.
Wanna bet that fifteen bucks on it?
Hell yeah.
Aren't you hurting for money?
I'm telling ya,
he'll throw like shit.
No, their pitcher can do it!
You're too fucking easy.
Can't wait for the game tonight!
Oh, my bad.
The valve's kinda finicky.
Just be careful.
My spare uniforms are
back in the main building.
Hey, what'd you hit me for?
I said it was my bad.
I didn't splash you on purpose!
Oh, did I just hit you?
The fuck is your problem?!
Did it hurt that fucking bad?
You want some?
You just had to
go and hit me too hard!
You fucking prick!
Asshole!
You son of a...
All right, cut the crap!
I said cut the crap!
Stop, stop!
I'll apologize!
I'm fucking sorry!
You can borrow one of
my uniforms if you need it.
We square now?
Just let it go.
What's gotten into you?
Calm down.
You in a bad mood today?
We're friends... ain't we?
That fucking hurt!
You hit like a truck, motherfucker!
I can fucking take you!
What the hell is wrong with them?
I-It can't be...
I'm gettin' pumped!
His physique...
I can see where all
the strength in his body is!
His superbly developed muscles!
Beautiful...
I can sense
his strongest muscle groups!
I love the thrill of the fight!
Wh-What the...?
What's happening to their bodies?
What are those things
that seem to shine?
Here I come!
I'll show you how much tougher I am!
I'm the fucking strongest!
I-Is this an enemy's attack?
Is that guard my enemy?
No, the real enemy
still hasn't shown themselves.
But this has to be a Stand!
This fucked up situation
has to be a Stand attack!
"Give not that which is holy unto the dogs...
...lest they trample them under their feet...
...and turn again to rend you."
Matthew 7:6.
Sportsmax has gone missing.
I can't fathom
how they learned of it...
...but I can safely assume that
they've read Max's memory.
The number of Stand users
I sent to the Disciplinary Wing...
Four total!
If Cujoh Jolyne entered
the Disciplinary Wing in search of Dio's bone...
...I cannot let her
live a moment longer!
I will use everything in my power
to eliminate her!
What happens in the Disciplinary Wing
is of no importance.
I'm certain the four of them won't stop
until Jotaro's daughter is eliminated!
He's sending in everyone, huh?
I can see where your strengths are!
Motherfuckers!
I can see...
...the strongest parts of
each fighter's body from here!
It's time for Fight Club!
Bring it on!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Guard Westwood's Secret