I got my hands on a disc.
Just one.
I can bring him back, guaranteed.
All I know is that my father
can be resuscitated with it.
We will refer to this as
Operation: Savage Garden.
You should let him.
He can aid your cause.
His name is Weather Report.
Jumpin' Jack Flash!
Weather Report!
But where did he go?
I gotta get the disc back!
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 11   Op: Savage Garden (Reach the Courtyard!) Part 2
Emergency alarm activated.
Corridor 7B.
Yes, that's correct. Corridor 7B.
We're assessing the situat-
Has something happened?
We aren't sure yet.
But Corridor 7B is only meant
for going to and from the factory.
There's no chance
that it's a fire or a riot.
No need to worry.
Oh, no, I'm not worried.
I maintain the utmost trust
in this prison and its prisoners.
There was quite the commotion, and so my curiosity
got the better of me... I just had to stop in.
Surely you are aware that no prisoner has managed
to escape from the Aquarium in the past twenty years?
Also, on the other side of
this corridor is the courtyard.
Nobody would be stupid enough
to try to escape from there.
Quite right, you are.
Leave the rest to us, Father.
Yes, I believe I shall.
One more thing
that piqued my curiosity...
Is that clock on the wall accurate?
Yes, of course.
Uh... 11:58 a.m.
Almost lunchtime.
11:51 a.m.
A call to the Speedwagon Foundation.
I have my usual request...
I'd like to hear the recording
of this outgoing call.
From the women's ward,
phone booth 16.
The call from about seven minutes ago.
Weather Report...
Now you're under zero-G too,
'cause you touched me.
No sign of our "pal," either...
We gotta get the disc back, fast!
Don't panic.
He must be within this
laundry facility somewhere.
He's hiding.
The courtyard is on
the other side of that door.
Your objective lies
just beyond that doorway...
...but it is most likely locked.
You'll have no choice but to open it by force,
via blast or some other means.
There's just...
one little problem...
It's kinda hard to talk about
in this situation...
Kinda personal, too...
But... it's urgent,
and I need to go, now.
So, like...
I don't know why it became
a problem so suddenly...
But, well...
I think it's something
everyone's experienced!
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on!
It's the P-word,
one of those things you do down below!
Thank god it's not
"number two"!
You know, "the call of nature"!
You need to urinate?
Don't gotta say it to my face!
Seriously dude, I gotta go.
Just pick a corner.
Goddammit, why'd I even bother
talking to a guy about this?
I relieved myself already.
See?
It's floating right over there.
In zero gravity, the blood in your body
will suddenly rush to your head.
That blood is usually down in
the lower parts of your body due to gravity.
The space between your skin and bone
becomes swollen and spongy with blood.
It's called "moon face".
However, too much blood
going to your head is dangerous.
Your kidneys automatically work harder
to reduce the amount of blood in you.
This triggers a strong diuretic effect.
They try to thin your blood
by expelling salt through urine.
B-But...
Don't worry,
I'll use my clouds to absorb it.
H-Hey, wait, what is that stuff?!
It's floating!
It's spilling out of your clouds!
W-Weather Report!
M-My blood!
It's being sucked out
through the gap in the wall!
Mine too.
It's blood from
the wound I got earlier.
My nose won't stop bleeding!
Getting... harder... to breathe...
No, it can't be!
Jolyne!
Ora!
Everything I touch enters zero gravity.
I touched the walls, the floor, and the door.
That means the room itself is zero-G?!
The air!
Air doesn't stay put in zero gravity!
The surrounding gravity's gonna
force all the air out of here!
We gotta close the gaps!
Otherwise we're gonna suffocate in here!
Not quite, Jolyne...
The bigger worry is...
...how the blood in our veins will start to boil,
killing us long before we suffocate.
In a vacuum,
your blood boils like water.
In a zero-gravity vacuum, your blood dries up
in twenty seconds, well before you'd ever suffocate.
Guess I'd better reload...
He's going to fire.
We need to hide somewhere!
What are you talking about?!
M-My nose is bleeding too much!
We need to stop the airflow!
Weather Report!
Don't breathe too deeply.
All I did was collect what little air
remained in this room...
...and covered our bodies with clouds.
C-Cloud suits...
This room is basically a vacuum now.
These clouds contain
all the remaining air.
Your nosebleed's stopped.
How long can we k-keep breathing?
I'd rather not answer that question...
...but probably around two minutes.
These cloud suits
merely keep death at bay.
So if we don't
take him out in that time...
...we're definitely gonna be left
stranded in the vacuum, right?
Precisely.
Now, where is he?
We need to find him.
Even if we do nothing...
...he'll still come after us.
Hey, now that I'm not bleeding,
something's been bothering me.
Listen, Jolyne.
I said two minutes,
but it could be only one!
We must focus on finding him!
The CO2 is building up
as we speak!
The laundry hamper...
It's not floating.
That hamper over there.
I touched the walls, shutters,
and floor of this room.
It's why the whole room entered zero gravity,
and why everything's floating.
But why are that hamper
and those barrels not floating?
They're stuck to the floor.
As for the enemy...
How the hell's he
breathing in this vacuum?
Shouldn't his blood
be boiling over, too?
What I'm saying is...
...that's the range of his ability!
There's a maximum range
to his zero gravity!
It doesn't cover the entire room!
His maximum range, huh?
From here to the hamper is
about twenty meters or so.
The zero gravity ends there!
If we can just make it...
The air's gotta be normal there!
You should go first, Weather Report.
He's outside of the vacuum.
If you don't get a supply of air now,
we'll never be able to reach him.
I'm inclined to agree.
Outside that hamper...
Get going, Weather Report!
The air pressure in this suit's
starting to feel weird.
Go, before these cloud suits
evaporate into the vacuum!
Don't think I'm letting you
out of my range!
He's trying to shoot him down!
I won't let him!
I'm gonna play defense
for Weather Report!
Weather Report
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Weather Report
He's trying to circle ahead of me!
Then I'll charge ahead!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
He's just a few meters
away from breathable air.
Once Weather Report gets to that air,
he's going to corner you!
If you want air that badly,
you can have it.
You don't even have
to reach the hamper.
My attack...
...just finished.
I wasn't trying to ricochet
the bullets to hit him.
I shot and damaged the barrel itself!
There's a little bit of air
left inside that barrel, you know?
Air inside the barrel,
pressurized by the vacuum...
...and just about ready to burst!
Weather Report!
He's been pushed back
into the zero gravity zone.
He's as good as dead.
He doesn't have enough air left to
propel himself and stop his momentum.
Weather Report!
It's no use.
Th-The cloud suit itself
is about to collapse!
J-Jolyne!
What are you doing?!
Y-You must go back!
He'll shoot you down!
That, and the propulsion alone's
going to take the rest of your air!
She's good at
thinking on her feet.
She's looking to tackle that cloud asshole
so he stops moving...
...then she'll try to knock him
outside of the zero gravity zone again!
But...
...I'm not gonna make it easy!
I get it already...
Your Stand's very powerful.
My rotating bullets aren't fast enough,
and you'd just flick them away in self-defense.
That's why I've been preparing...
I've been looking around...
...and nabbing them from
every dark corner I could find.
And man, were there plenty.
Rats! They're alive!
C-Could they be...
Stone Free!
Get 'em the fuck away from me!
C-Can't see!
Okay!
Never thought you'd put up
this good a fight against my zero-G, but...
You can't defend yourself now!
Suck on this, Cujoh Jolyne!
Mission fucking accomplished!
Jumpin' Jack Flash is fuckin' sick.
I feel like I could
take on the world!
I'm glad I got sent to this prison.
With the ability I picked up here,
there's probably nothing in the world I can't do.
I've got a bright,
invincible future ahead of me!
I'll be handing this disc over to Whitesnake.
Could destroy him too, if I wanted.
With my own hands!
I knew...
I knew you'd do that.
I was waiting for you...
to reload.
While you were reloading,
I wove my threads through your ammo and waited...
And then you fired at me.
Th-These threads!
When the hell did you...?!
Stone Free!
Ora!
What the fuck?!
Look who got sucked
into his own vacuum.
And without a suit, your blood's gonna boil
and blow up faster than ours!
We win!
If you don't wanna die,
you better turn off zero grav right fucking now!
The crime that put me in this prison...
How many times did I stab her?
When I killed that female university professor,
the prosecutor said I stabbed her sixty-nine times.
I feel like I did back then...
For the first time in ages,
I can feel it surging...
Shit!
I'm not letting that bitch
get the best of me...
Fuck her!
Add hydrogen peroxide to manganese dioxide
and it decomposes into oxygen!
Just like the oxygen in this bottle,
I feel it surging...
That feeling from back then,
of wanting to fucking murder someone!
Suck on this!
I'll make a headstone out of
your piss-soaked body with this glass!
With those fresh cuts on your body, Cujoh Jolyne,
your blood vessels will fucking blow before mine do!
They sent me to prison for
cutting a bitch!
And with your cunt ass out of the way,
nobody can fucking stop me! I'm gettin' outta here!
Take mine.
This should be enough
to take the disc back...
...from our mutual "friend."
Weather Report!
What the hell?!
D-Dammit!
My body can't take anymore!
If I turn off the zero-G now,
air's gonna come rushing in...
I might be able to
get out using that airflow!
Zero gravity, release!
Jumpin' Jack Flash!
Should've turned it off
the first chance you got.
The air pressure might've blasted you
out of the room, letting you escape...
...if you'd turned off zero-G back when there was
still a good distance between you and Stone Free.
Now the air is
blowing you back toward me!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
How much longer until
the Speedwagon Foundation gets here?
Three minutes?
Maybe two?
There's a corridor on
the other side of that door.
There are windows facing toward
the courtyard along the right wall.
There, you'll see a gate
to a revolving door.
That gate leads to the courtyard.
The gate's unlocked
and accessible during the day.
Your next problem is
how to open this door.
I'll have a guard open it.
We've got Fuckface's
work permit card here.
I'll trick them into opening up.
I see.
Once they open the door, you'll knock the guards out
and force your way to the courtyard.
Just as well.
Not only will you be charged
with attempted escape...
...but you'll also be placed in solitary confinement
for six months, where you can't even exercise.
Suits me just fine.
I'm going to the courtyard and giving this disc
to whoever's coming from the Speedwagon Foundation.
At this moment,
that is my life's goal.
Guard's coming.
Weather Report,
go find somewhere to hide.
I'm going it alone from here.
You're severely wounded...
...not to mention the guards might
lock the gate the second they see your blood.
Good point... Got it.
Is something the matter?
Why are you beating on the door so?
It's you...
"It's you"?
What's wrong, Wrangler?
Why so tense?
One moment,
I will open the door for you.
If you are returning
to the men's ward...
...then let us visit the chapel
on the way, Lang Wrangler.
I would like to
have a word with you.
He's not a guard!
Wh-Who is he?
Not a guard...
And not a prisoner, either!
And what's with his getup?
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Flash Flood Warning