Green Dolphin Street
State Prison
Hold it right there!
What's going on here?
What the hell are you doing?
Ultra Security
House Unit
Prisoner FE40536!
Name: Cujoh Jolyne.
This is now the second time
you've made trouble for us!
First attempted jailbreak, and now...
...we find you in the mausoleum with a female inmate
dead from blunt force trauma to the head.
Yet here you are,
acting tough and not saying a peep.
Don't think we're blind to the beaten inmates
and dead bodies you leave behind.
We have no proof
you're behind it all...
...but the fact remains,
you're a shit starter.
So, from here on out...
...you're gonna learn to play by our rules!
Starting now, you're confined indefinitely
here in this Ultra Security House Unit!
Fuck! Fuck! Motherfuck!
It's a chick!
The newbie's a fucking chick!
Smells like a lady!
You can smell her scent
coming from the door!
Is this...?
Fuck yeah!
I got shit on her face!
My own shit is all over her fucking face!
I wanna fuck her up real good!
My mental strength is the one thing
I can't afford to lose here.
All of this stress
and the physical toll it takes...
I've got a job to do
here in the Ultra Security House Unit!
I have to see it through,
no matter what!
I can't let any stupid shit wear me down!
No...
I'll become even stronger!
Perhaps there is a way one could reach Heaven.
23 Years Ago
Hey, I see that look on your face.
I am not telling you to die.
The Heaven I speak of has to do with
the soul and the path it takes.
The power of your soul
must evolve with you.
They must arrive at the same conclusion.
Surely one such as yourself
must see the truth in my words.
True happiness lies there.
But only if you reach Heaven.
I am well aware that happiness cannot be reached
through wealth, status, or a powerful body.
Those who are truly victorious...
...are the lucky few to glimpse Heaven.
There is nothing I won't do...
...to reach it.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Let's say I put a sticker on this pen...
Episode 13  Kiss of Love and Revenge Part 1
Now I have two of them.
That's my ability.
I call it Kiss.
If I peel the sticker off...
...the pens merge back into one.
But it leaves a crack behind.
I'm taking this ability
as a sign from the heavens!
He'll remember in no time...
Kiss is my license for revenge!
Good morning, Father.
May I have one of these flowers?
I've found myself growing
fond of them recently.
By all means, please have it...
...Sportsmax.
F.F., she just cut in front of you.
Hey!
Did you hear what I said?
I know.
Y'know, I get the feeling
nobody here really accepts me.
Feels like they look down on me.
Wait your turn, bitch!
Tell her!
Don't think I will.
You can't force these things.
You should change yourself for the better
before seeking the approval of others, right?
So yeah, I decided I'm gonna do
the exact opposite of what I'd normally do.
What's the opposite of coffee?
...Tea?
Right.
Etro's body is craving coffee.
So I drink tea instead.
On purpose!
You feel me?
Instead of bread, I eat rice.
Instead of my right hand,
I use my left hand to eat.
I'm trying to change myself
by doing everything opposite.
F.F., listen to me...
The wounds I got when I was shot...
...still fucking hurt.
Like I already said...
All I can do is
fill the holes with plankton.
The rest is up to
you and your body.
Okay?
Jolyne, what's the opposite of pork?
I don't know,
chicken or beef I guess?
The opposite of pork is salmon!
Pigs are lazy fucking bastards.
Salmon swim upstream
like total badasses!
You're so right!
You got cut again...
Back of the line, cunts!
Come on, tell them off!
I just told you,
I'm doing things opposite now.
Like letting more people
cut in front of me.
Come on everyone,
keep it coming!
What the fuck is your problem?
You can't cut in front of me!
Hands off, bitch!
Back of the line, dumpster slut!
What'd you call me, skank?
Wow, getting our food is easy now.
Too easy.
Oh yeah, where's Hermès?
I haven't seen her in a few days.
What, haven't you heard?
She's following a man?
Our Hermès?
Yeah.
Every morning for a while now.
I think it started around the time
you were shot full of holes.
I can't find Jolyne anywhere...
Something's going down in the courtyard.
Looks bad.
H-Hey, Hermès!
Just leave her alone.
The prisoner Hermès has been tailing?
Yeah.
You know all the gossip around here.
I'm glad you came to me, Jolyne.
Oh, but you weren't expecting me to
just spill the beans for free, were you?
Call it my finder's fee.
I'll even give you
the friend's discount.
Found it.
"The body of a female victim thought to have been
caught in the crossfire of gang violence...
...was found by the river
just before dawn."
A local Florida paper from six years ago.
Just like that Guess chick said.
Gloria Costello...
She was Hermès' older sister.
The Next Day
For the last few days...
...I've been keeping a close eye on you,
waiting for the right moment.
I don't know what caused
your change of heart...
...but I saw you sweeping
the old prison's graveyard.
You left flowers at one of the graves.
Were they for a fellow gang member
who got zapped in the electric chair?
I also caught you making stuffed
birds and alligators, of all things.
How'd a sick fuck like you
suddenly take an interest in crafts like taxidermy?
Guess it don't matter.
But there's one thing
I still gotta know...
Jolyne! F.F.!
You look well, Hermès.
Here, I got some breakfast for you.
Hermès...
About that man you've been tailing...
Tailing?
Don't know what you're talkin' about.
Don't bullshit us.
His name is Sportsmax.
I mean sure,
he was a notorious gangster on the outside...
But now he's just doing time
here in the men's ward.
Wow, fascinating.
As if I give two shits.
Hermès...
You were sent here to Green Dolphin
for robbing a convenience store, right?
Were you trying to get
locked up on purpose?
You want to get revenge
on Sportsmax for your sister's death.
Jolyne...
Good rule of thumb,
don't snoop here in prison.
Oh, yeah?
Well, today I'm doing opposites.
This doesn't concern you.
Go back to the ward.
Hermès is right, Jolyne.
You got your own mission to worry about.
I guess...
Not much longer, Gloria...
I'll avenge you with
my own two hands.
Hermès...
Think of me as your mom from now on.
Ever since that day...
Gloria...
No matter what,
she always put our family first.
Hermès!
It wouldn't kill you to help
with the business sometimes, you know.
I want the two of us to inherit
Dad's restaurant someday.
As if I give a fuck about this place.
I'm outta here.
I'm gonna get through college
on a track and field scholarship.
Don't act like you're all that
and can just boss me around.
Hermès!
Wait!
H-Help me!
I want you to grab
that stick with your mouth.
Not like a dog chewing a bone,
but a baby sucking on a pacifier.
She never meant to peer into the shadows,
and she definitely never would've reported what she saw...
She felt that what happened
in the shadows should stay in the shadows.
Otherwise, there's no way she could operate
a restaurant in such a fucked up city.
But that night...
Gloria was forced to put herself
in danger and call the police.
Just to protect me!
But then...
To the defendant, Sportsmax...
I sentence you to five years for tax evasion
and causing grievous bodily harm.
Five years?
That's fucking it?
We needed a stronger witness
to get a conviction.
This was the best we could do.
He fucking had her killed!
There was no evidence supporting that.
Fucking bullshit!
Wait! Wait, damn you!
Calm down!
You motherfucker!
So you remember.
Good.
Never forget Gloria.
Gloria!
I've been waiting for this chance...
A chance to catch you alone so
no one will hear your screams but me...
I even scoped out
the perfect place to do it!
Everything you did to make Gloria suffer...
Sportsmax...
...I'll make sure you fucking remember!
Kiss
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Hermès Costello
What the hell is this?
What are you doing to me, bitch?
Your sentence is up in
about a year from now.
Once you're free,
you'll have bodyguards.
But right here and now,
you're my bitch!
Yeah. Fits you perfectly.
These prison pipes aren't
big enough to fit a person.
But as your coffin, it fits perfectly.
Was that the sound of him falling?
Hey, let me out of here!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Let me out of here right now!
You still don't know who I am?
That's right,
use your last moments to think about it.
You left Gloria's body in raw sewage.
Her death made our dad
get sick and die.
I... lost everything.
You can fucking beg for their
forgiveness in hell, Sportsmax!
If you can even spit it out
with your mouth full of shit!
I put a second sticker on the pipe.
Consider it the final nail in your coffin.
Now it's sealed shut.
Go ahead and scream your lungs out!
Damn you!
Go on, call for help.
Only the cockroaches
and rats will hear you.
Now you're in raw sewage, too, fucker!
Let me hear you fucking scream, Sportsmax!
Those who rise from the darkness,
Limp Bizkit, rise and come with me...
We will share joy in the darkness, Limp Bizkit...
Wha...?
Something's here...
And... And it's headed right for me!
Wh-What the fuck?!
It can't be...!
Sportsmax?!
Usha!
Goddammit! My finger!
This is a Stand!
I don't know why I can't see it...
...but I definitely felt it!
It felt like a bird!
S-Sticker!
Usha!
D-Did I win?
Did I crush it?
I couldn't have known that
he gained a Stand ability.
How's that?
Sportsmax, you've gone
real quiet on me, asshole!
Did you get crushed inside the pipe?
Or did the shit filling you from your mouth
to your asshole drown you to death?
What now?
Sportsmax is still alive?
This invisible thing means
that motherfucker's still alive inside the pipe!
It's bigger than the last one...
S-So fast!
This power...
Is it that stuffed alligator
from the workshop?
The first one was a bird...
Their invisible corpses
gained the power to move.
They're the ones attacking me!
Damn that fucking asshole!
He's trying to bust the pipe and break free!
Hermès?
What are you doing up there?
Hermès!
Jolyne was worried about y-
Jolyne! F.F.!
Don't come any closer!
F.F.!
There's an enemy, Jolyne!
It's an alligator!
There's invisible,
dead creatures crawling around!
Well shit, there goes my leg.
Hermès,
what the hell is going on here?
Is this a Stand attack?
Yeah, it is.
It's that motherfucker, Sportsmax!
He gained a Stand ability
without me knowing!
Run!
It's right behind you!
It's getting ready to strike!
Stone Free!
Ora!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Kiss of Love and Revenge Part 2