Perhaps there is a way one could reach Heaven.
And just how are you going to do that?
This notebook explains the process.
However, before he made
his methods known to me...
I waited for over two decades after that,
biding my time to obtain Jotaro's memories.
It was in his memories
where the contents of the notebook lay.
Their goal, and their ability,
is to turn Stands into physical objects and steal them!
I'm sure that my dad isn't dead.
If I get his Stand back,
he'll come back to life.
I won.
Don't underestimate me!
This changes nothing.
Even with Star Platinum,
your father remains a broken puppet!
Its user has my dad's memory disc!
This is my chance to find out who he is!
With your ability,
I would like you to try something.
Is that a human bone?
Who's it belong to?
You needn't concern yourself.
Let's just say it belonged to
an old friend of mine.
The bone of my dear friend, the mighty Dio.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 14  Kiss of Love and Revenge Part 2
Well shit, there goes my leg.
Hermès, what the hell is going on here?
Is this a Stand attack?
Yeah, it is.
Run!
It's right behind you!
It's getting ready to strike!
Stone Free!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Jolyne!
Is this a Stand ability?
If it is, he probably got it
from one of Whitesnake's discs...
So that means...
Now I get it.
Jolyne, take F.F. and run!
This is my problem!
It's none of your business!
No, Hermès!
This isn't just your problem anymore.
Sportsmax must have some kind of goal.
Whatever it is...
...I'm sure it's related to
my father's stolen memories.
He's trying to find
something inside the prison.
And I bet we can figure out what he's planning
if we read the disc inside his head!
Jolyne, just focus on getting
the fuck out of this hallway!
It won't be long before the sewer water
in the pipe drowns him to death!
His Stand ability will
disappear once he dies.
Something feels off...
What?
Where is it?
That invisible stuffed alligator...
There's no way it can move without
touching the threads and giving itself away.
The wall!
The hell?!
Fuck!
Up or down, ceiling or floor...
None of that means a thing to an invisible corpse!
Stop!
I'm your enemy, not her!
You're wrong, Hermès!
He's not just your guys' enemy anymore.
That asshole ate my fucking left leg.
I wonder where is it now...
Still in its stomach?
You bet your ass it's my enemy, too!
Stay back, F.F.!
We don't know where it is!
It's gonna bite you!
S-Stop, F.F.!
Yeah, it sure did bite me.
Not much else it can
really do, after all.
But this is good.
Because now I'm inside its mouth!
I did it...
I definitely took it down!
Isn't this a part of
your mauled shoulder?
Damn, does it even fit?
It ripped your shoulder to shreds.
Here, F.F.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, Hermès, come here.
Hermès, am I right to say the thing that
attacked us was basically an alligator ghost?
And Sportsmax was
the one controlling it?
No, you got it wrong.
It was way too vicious.
It was an invisible corpse, not a ghost.
What?
One of the living dead
that instinctively looks for blood.
That bastard has the ability
to make invisible zombies.
Wh-What the...?
What's wrong, Hermès?
What happened to Sportsmax?
Did he drown down there?
I can't tell.
It's too dark.
He might be lodged
deeper in the pipe.
Or maybe...
Wait, are these handprints?!
Sh-Shit…
My throat feels so sticky...
I need to rinse out my mouth.
What was I even doing?
Where was I going?
Oh, that's right...
The chapel…
I was going to the chapel.
My mission… is to find that bone.
Listen carefully.
If you fail...
...I expect you to return the skill
I so graciously bestowed upon you.
Of course...
My ability, Limp Bizkit, can do this.
I'm certain I can find the bone
Whitesnake ordered me to look for.
I have to...
Dammit...
I wish I had time to
take a breather first...
I want to wipe myself off
and clear my throat with something.
Something refreshing...
That woman there…
Perfect timing.
That skank, uh...
What was her name again?
Don't remember.
Guess "Skank" will have to do.
Damn.
Won't even acknowledge me
holding out a bribe.
Hey, how you doing?
You on duty?
I could use a drink.
Want to hit up the café with me?
When we're done, we can find
a secluded corner somewhere and have some fun.
Feel each other up and
let our bodies do the talking.
Asshole!
How dare you fucking touch me?!
You better pony up
before you try that again!
What are you talking about?
You son of a bitch...
How dare you touch her before you've even paid?
Dammit...
Where did Sportsmax run off to?
He must have gotten out of the pipe
while we were distracted by the alligator.
Or maybe...
...he himself already
became an invisible corpse...
I just gave you a little kick...
Stop messing around!
Messing around?
You let someone treat you like that
and you're finished, Skank.
Do what you gotta do
to make him pay.
Now come here and
help me find his cash.
You listening to me?
Help me out here.
He's got something on his sleeve.
Huh?
Oh, so you decided to pay up?
Why didn't you just say so?
I did say that.
Pay attention, idiot.
He doesn't got anything else
hidden on him, does he?
Like in his mouth or something.
Huh?!
Wait, you wanna do it? Right here?
What?
Wh-What do you think this is?
C-Come on, stop fooling around!
I don't do any of that kinky shit.
I'll be taking this.
Seems he was hiding something good.
Wh-What the hell is this?
This isn't a drug!
It's seeping out of my skin!
This smell…
It's sewage!
It's the stench of sewage!
My body…
The disgusting water
seeping out of my body reeks of…
Fuck!
No, I can't already be…
Wh-What the hell?
It's flowing from midair!
What is happening?!
I didn't want something to drink earlier...
I wanted to devour something!
I wanted to consume flesh
and satisfy this craving!
Yes, the brains!
Oh, now I remember.
I already drowned in that pipe!
Shit!
It's all her fucking fault!
Gloria Costello's younger sister!
How dare that fucking bitch
do this to me?!
How dare she?!
I-I thirst!
Hermès, look!
Be careful.
I knew he found a way out of the pipe!
What did he do to her?
D-Did he bite her to death?
How the hell could human teeth...
...fuck up a body like this?
He's not human anymore.
Not in intelligence or morals.
But one thing's for sure!
He still has his disc!
I'll do whatever it takes to get it.
Jolyne, I told you to wait outside!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Damn, he slipped out!
Stay close to me, Hermès!
We're locked in!
He is intelligent!
The same as a human!
Stay away from the wall!
We already found out the hard way that
he's not limited to moving on the floor!
We'll track him in three dimensions!
There you are!
You decided to hang from the ceiling.
Sounds like I broke some bones.
Wha...?!
With a broken arm?!
Right, he's a corpse!
Stone Free!
Got him!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
No!
Jolyne!
That's not Sportsmax!
He was using that
woman's corpse as a decoy!
Jolyne!
Limp Bizkit
Power: None
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: E
Power: None
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: E
Sportsmax
Jolyne!
Osha!
Wh-Where'd you go?
Where the fuck are you, asshole?!
Jolyne!
Stop it!
Quit moving, Jolyne!
This prick is my enemy, not yours!
Sportsmax is my own,
personal problem!
Like I said, Hermès...
We're at the point where you can't say
this is revenge, or just your problem.
No... We're not just at that point...
I should say we're way past the point
to even think we have the time or luxury for that!
Look.
H-He can't be...
This entire time...
...he's had us cornered
right where he wants us!
He already revived them.
The invisible corpses are already...
I can't tell their numbers
or where they're moving!
We're surrounded, Hermès!
Right now,
our only option is to escape!
We need to prioritize survival.
We have to get that door open
and get the fuck out of here!
I'll extend my thread
as far as I can to reach F.F.!
We have to retreat!
Retrieving the disc and
getting your revenge have to wait!
Hermès!
Revenge...
That's the key word here, Jolyne.
Even to Sportsmax, lurking somewhere in here,
that word should really mean something.
He wants to get revenge on me
for drowning him inside that pipe.
His need for revenge is
probably consuming him right now.
He wants to maul me to death
and fill his mouth with my blood.
What are you-
I know for sure he wants to sink his fangs in me
and land the killing blow himself!
Hermès!
Listen, Jolyne.
Some would say getting even
isn't going to bring my sister back.
As if they have any idea
what I've been through.
They might also say
it's important to forgive.
Gloria!
But...!
Forcing myself to live as if my family
wasn't tossed in the fucking gutter?
I could never.
I've braced myself for this moment!
Revenge is how you settle the score
with your own destiny!
Hermès, are you...
...gonna take him down with you?
No!
Hermès, step back!
I'm calling for F.F. right now!
Five, no, seven corpses are
severing my threads and closing in!
Don't do it, Hermès!
Hermès!
Wh-Which direction
will he come from?
I-I'm blacking out...
Hermès!
Sh-She split her head
in two with a sticker?!
Kiss is my license for revenge!
Got you, Sportsmax!
I knew you would try something.
Just like when you
trapped me in that pipe...
I knew you would use your sticker
that splits anything in two.
Your ability won't work
against me anymore.
That's because...
...I'm a corpse like all the rest!
Damn, I can't touch him!
Where the hell is he?
Guess you can't hear me, huh?
I'll say it anyway...
This is all your sister's fault
for looking where she shouldn't.
Her... mès...
Shit!
Missed again!
Because of your sister...
...you got one over on me,
and look how that turned out!
I doubt I'll ever be okay with this!
Not you!
Listen to me...
Even if I eat your brains...
...and stuff the shit in your guts
into your empty fucking skull...
...I'll never get over
what you've done to me!
You're finished!
I'm the one who's gonna
make you meet your end!
Hermès was waiting for
this exact moment!
The moment he removed the sticker
so he could chomp on her real head!
Remove the sticker,
and the two things turn back to one!
Including the parts Sportsmax
already bit off and swallowed!
Now I know right where you are!
Just gotta aim a bit above...
...the midsagittal plane of your face!
Sh-She did it!
Now you listen!
This kick is for Gloria!
Sounds like a few bones
in your face just cracked.
Consider it Gloria who
fucked up your face!
And this...
...is for Gloria, too!
Make mincemeat out of
this fucking bitch!
Trying to run and hide again?
Well, tough shit.
A sticker split your head in two.
Peel it off,
and it goes back together.
This next one is for Gloria, too!
And this one, and this one!
This one and this one, too!
And the next one!
They're all for Gloria!
This one!
And this one!
And this! And this! And this!
They're all for Gloria!
I don't know why,
but suddenly I'm getting all weepy-eyed...
I just wish...
...I could cry by your side.
But I don't know if I have
enough time left for that...
F.F.!
Where are you?
Come heal her!
Hurry!
Open the door!
SPORTSMAX
STAND NAME:
LIMP BIZKIT
—ANNIHILATED
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Emergency alarm!
Commons Area 1A, Mausoleum!
Freeze!
What's going on here?
Don't move!
Inmate FE40536.
Name: Cujoh Jolyne!
After reading that disc, I get it now.
I know exactly what
I need to do in here.
Ultra Security Disciplinary Wing