Ms. Jolyne wanted to get sent to
the Disciplinary Wing so she could find the bone?
Yep.
If I successfully protect her to the end,
I'm going to marry her.
That's my condition.
Understood?
Diver Down!
Now give us your blessing.
At seventy millivolts, the electric potential
sending signals to the nervous system is quite small.
The Stand dwells in
that minuscule pulse of energy.
Survivor's attack is mostly unnoticeable
and doesn't cause direct harm.
All it does is create anger.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 16  Guard Westwood's Secret
Motherfuckers!
I can see...
...the strongest parts of
each fighter's body from here!
It's time for Fight Club!
Bring it on!
You motherfuckers piss me off so much
you make me wanna puke!
An enemy Stand user
must have been sent here.
They're in here with us!
Someone's making
the inmates fight each other!
And as for the bone lurking somewhere inside
this Ultra Security House Unit...
...I'll do whatever it takes to find it!
I won't let anyone get in my way!
Whoever it is,
if they try anything with me, I'll ki-
What the... kill them?
D-Did I seriously just think that?
This burning sensation
bubbling up inside me...
I-Is this my fighting spirit?
I feel like dominating anyone working against me
without worrying about what happens.
Where did this come from?
This prison guard...
He wants to beat me up
just like he did his fellow guard.
But in the end,
he's got nothing on Stone Free.
Ora!
Stone Free!
I can see it, FE40536...
Your greatest strength!
There's some kind of thread
coming out of your muscles...
It's beautiful...
So that's your mightiest power.
The way he just moved...
His fight with the other guard was fucked up and brutal,
but it was just a normal brawl.
But what he just did...
...is beyond how a human can move!
In order to beat this prison guard,
I need to move quickly and give it my all!
His muscles...
What a beautiful shine...
Also, that series of moves...
To think someone can ignore their fear and pain
to attack with such power and jump with such force!
But if the beautiful lights shining from
his muscles indicate his strongest parts...
...then that left leg of his
I'm looking at...
That's the leg I attacked!
It must mean I hurt him!
I can feel it!
My attack did some
heavy damage to his leg!
Bastard!
Don't you fucking dare
walk in front of me!
You're pissing me off!
Everyone else is fighting now, too!
You're mine!
Ora!
This prison guard...
I need to knock him out as fast as I can
so I can focus on finding the bone!
Ora!
Usha!
Good thing you didn't sever
your own head with that punch.
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Now go the fuck to sleep!
What the fuck just happened?
What just happened to me?
Th-This prison guard!
What did you do?!
Th-That's...!
He's a Stand user, too!
There are multiple Stand users
in the Disciplinary Wing!
He was already given
a skill through a Stand disc!
But what did he do, and how?
I didn't leave an opening
for him to counter me...
And I didn't see any signs of a Stand moving,
so how did he attack me?
It's deep...
Fuck, he got me deep!
You don't get a wound like this from
a hidden razor or knife or anything like that!
What the fuck did he do?!
If he has a power-type Stand,
it should be easy to see!
FE40536.
Thread attacks, huh?
I can see clusters of threads
inside your body.
Using those to fight
is your greatest strength.
That's why you're so strong.
Beautiful...
They're shining!
When did you become a Stand user?
Yesterday?
A moment ago?
Ora! Ora!
I... I see it!
Its form!
His Stand materialized!
A Stand user...
If this asshole is the assassin
sent to eliminate me, then...
Threads don't need power to defend.
A straight punch can easily have its
trajectory changed by just barely throwing it off...
You fell for it.
Since you used both of your arms,
I can stop you from moving.
Basically...
...I'll cover you with my jacket!
Stone Free!
Ora!
You'll never come back from this!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Wha... What?!
I-It's happening again!
Wh-What the fuck does
his Stand even do?
I-I don't see anything!
So what's...?
Gotcha!
You're such a piece of shit!
Just had to go and
make a fool outta me!
How fucking dare you?!
Prisoners are the scum of society.
Nothing pisses me off more than when
one of you fucks plays me for a sucker!
I think about that
every fucking day of this job!
You fucks looking down to me!
It's time for some payback!
Real fucking payback!
This payback is for you!
This good fucking payback!
Payback time! Payback time!
I'm gonna enjoy this fucking payback!
I'm the fucking strongest!
It's payback time!
Payback time! Payback time!
The glass ceiling?
Don't tell me...
H-His Stand...
Th-This is bad!
If this keeps up...
I-I gotta escape!
I-It's coming!
The truth behind his Stand ability...!
I got you now!
You're in my lock!
Ora!
Hey!
I'm a prison guard, remember?
I make a living restraining you fucks
every goddamn day!
It might look like
your right arm is free...
...but this deadlock is doing more
than just holding your neck in place!
I'm also twisting the joint
in your left shoulder...
...so that your right shoulder
locks up and can't move.
Your right punch will
never reach my face!
And this deadlock has only one weakness,
one I'm well aware of!
Your right hand is free
to grab my balls!
Under different circumstances
I'd actually like if you gave 'em a squeeze, though...
But as long as I
defend myself against that...!
I-It's coming!
If I don't do something,
his Stand's true form will...!
The ceiling!
The hard glass ceiling...
There's cracks!
I have to break free!
Stone Free!
I tore his eardrum!
His grip loosened!
The universe is full of countless
space rocks and debris.
Many such rocks are drawn in
by the Earth's gravitational pull.
While the majority disintegrate
before reaching the surface...
...if a space rock retained an optimal angle
and velocity while entering the atmosphere...
Planet Waves
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Viviano Westwood
Oh, you decided to come with?
I'm more than capable on my own.
I'm the one who calls the shots
and gives out orders here.
I asked for your help,
but what I say goes.
Also, if Whitesnake is
dead set on eliminating Jolyne...
...he must have sent two assassins to the Disciplinary Wing...
No, probably more than two.
He must have sent at least
three Stand users to attack her!
You and I will take 'em out,
then meet back here.
Got it?
Fine.
I intend to return
before that guard wakes up.
Also, we already agreed that
Jolyne and I will be wed.
Don't forget that.
Yeah, about that...
What the hell do you mean?
You're so confusing!
M-Meteorites!
The prison guard is attacking me
by drawing meteorites to himself!
That's what was hitting me!
His Stand attracts
meteorites from space!
But they always burn up
before they can hit him...
Another one's coming!
He's gonna attract another one!
So before that...!
Gotcha!
There's no fucking way
this one'll miss!
I'll be the beautiful, shining victor!
I'm the fucking strongest!
Stone Free!
I'll rip your skin off
from toe to head!
Now let me go
you stupid son of a bitch!
His grip is slipping!
Ora! Ora! Ora!
I-It took everything
I had to dodge them!
I even tried redirecting
the meteorites in his direction...
...but the same thing
happened again!
Not even a single meteorite
is hitting him!
They're disintegrating
just before making contact!
The prison guard's Stand ability attracts
falling meteorites toward his body like a magnet!
But no matter what I try,
they only ever hit me, even when I'm right near him!
Pretty weird, right?
Burning rocks from the sky
keep falling near me.
Are they meteorites?
Could this be my greatest strength?
FE40536...
How many hit you so far?
Those wounds look deep.
Looks like they got both your arms,
your left ribs, and your right leg.
That makes five.
Or is that six?
This next one is gonna be
the end of you!
You're bluffing.
You can barely
stand up straight.
You're just making a show
of standing up to me.
Truth is, those arms of yours
got no fight left in 'em!
I can see those
pitch-black muscles of yours!
Not a single muscle is shining!
How 'bout we have some fun?
Let's make a game of seeing
how bad the damage is!
What's wrong?
C'mon, gimme a good swing!
I'm not even defending myself!
Here, hit me.
What kinda punch
you got for me?
Hell, I'll even close my eyes if you want!
Th-That's...!
Over there, that's...
...the bone Whitesnake is looking for!
That's it!
It's right over there!
You're fucking done!
Your plan to defend yourself from
the meteorites by clinging to the wall...
...was too fucking predictable!
I already got meteorites coming at me
from the other side of the wall!
I win!
I knew you were too fucked up
to block my attacks!
"Two prisoners looked out
from behind bars...
One saw the wall,
the other saw the stars."
Which one am I?
And here's another one for ya!
The bone is right over there.
I'll do anything to
get close to Whitesnake.
I'll drink sewer water if I have to.
I'll become stronger
than everyone else!
I win!
No way your punk ass is gonna
escape that meteorite now!
Of course I'll be the one
that sees the stars.
I want to see the light of the stars
until I see Dad again.
Gimme a break...
Here's comes the finishing blow!
It's fucking over!
His final blow is gonna hit me.
Without a doubt,
there's no way I can defend myself with Stone Free.
I'm fucking stronger than you!
But...
I did manage to slip
your right boot off.
She even stuffed pieces of brick
in my boot after taking it off!
Sh-She took the hit,
but only half the damage!
She threw it off course!
The meteorite will disintegrate.
It will never, ever hit you.
But that's just the meteorite itself.
My boot!
Seriously,
gimme a fucking break.
You fucking bitch!
Stone Free!
Wh-What is up with th-this bitch?
She never learns...
She never gives up...
Fuck me...
Y-Yeah, if the meteorite hits something else first,
that thing can hit me...
What bullshit...
What a fucked up thing
to do to someone like me...
This woman...
I can see the stars.
Match fucking over!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Fiery Blaze, Dragon's Dream