Tomorrow at noon...
...someone will come visit you.
But you must not go.
You must not go to the visitation room.
You got a visitor.
Give up on the visit
and go back to your cell!
Dad...
Johngalli A.
He's the man behind it all.
Johngalli A. is definitely a Stand user.
Just know that you're being targeted.
I'm breaking you out ASAP.
My handcuffs!
When did that...?
Jolyne, get away from the door!
Star Platinum: The World!
Time, stop!
Wh-What the hell was that? Why?!
Hold still!
His attack's begun.
Air currents?
So it knows where we are based on
the movement of the air currents?
Don't move until we understand
how he's sniping us. Got it?
Don't order me around like
some pompous fucking asshole!
I already kn-
You... FE40536!
Who the hell do you think
you're talking to, you bitch?!
Jolyne!
You...
Don't move!
Keep your voice down.
It will find us again.
Johngalli A. uses his Stand
to sense air currents.
It may even be able to
react if our breathing changes.
Plus, it's like a satellite.
He aims his rifle at his Stand
and has it redirect the rounds.
A satellite sniper.
Attacking Johngalli A. in the men's ward
from here is impossible.
We have to take down that satellite Stand.
Any damage we deal to his Stand
gets dealt to him, too.
I know.
Problem is, once we make our move...
...we expose our positions to the Stand,
and he picks us off.
Back against the wall, Jolyne!
It can sense you!
Jolyne...
What are you thinking?
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don’t wanna say (There’s no chance)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let’s get started, count (One, two, three)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don’t stop beatin’ don’t stop beatin’
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don’t stop beating ’em up
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 4  The Visitor Part 2
Your muscles cannot be trusted.
When your skin is exposed to wind...
...the muscles underneath will
slightly relax and contract from stress.
This is an uncontrollable, reflexive action.
As such, I support the rifle with my bones.
Bones feel the firmness
of the ground beneath them.
The gun becomes one with the ground.
It's stability you can rely on.
Meteorologists say you can't
read wind movements.
But that isn't to say
it cannot be read at all.
Is this fly moving randomly?
No.
It maneuvers itself by feeling
the air currents and sensing wafting scents.
The fly and the wind move as one.
As the guard informed me,
Kujo Jotaro is here.
He's here to see his daughter, Cujoh Jolyne.
At this very moment,
descendants of the Joestars are in the visitation room.
They're within range
of my Manhattan Transfer.
Joestar... Joestar... Joestar...
Joestar!
My life will finally begin once
I've dealt the killing blow to your bloodline!
I'll have my revenge for being
robbed of my spiritual guide!
I see...
You said we have to take it down, right?
Look at its movement.
It can't read the air currents
with all this water.
Now!
Stone Free!
No, wait!
Look closer!
It's evading every drop of water.
It's moving in reaction to
the air currents from the droplets.
Jolyne, back against the wall!
He's going to shoot again!
This is bad!
The guards will stir up the air when they get here!
Please listen to me!
Move the block
at the base of the pillar, fast!
Kick it really hard!
But you're...
Don't worry about me!
Just hurry!
Okay?
Please don't forget what I said.
I want you to live!
I don't know what's going on,
but this hole between the walls goes down somewhere.
It's some kind of passage.
Maybe the sewers,
or the ventilation system.
What is this?
It may lead outside.
Let's go, Jolyne.
It's our only option.
It vanished...
Wrong.
It's close.
It's looking for
the perfect angle to snipe us.
No, you're wrong.
It went after...
the boy behind this door.
He wants to finish him off
for showing us the way out.
Jolyne, get in the tunnel!
I came here to break you out!
Before I entered this room...
...he grabbed this arm of mine.
I'm sure of it.
It seems unbelievable, but he's here.
He's like any other kid
you might see playing at the park.
We don't even know each other.
We're total strangers.
But...
...he grabbed my arm
like he was trying to cling to it.
The warmth of his hand
somehow felt calming.
I'm going back inside.
Before he shoots that boy...
...I'll take down Johngalli A.!
Gimme a break.
The visitation room!
The visitation room fire alarm's going off!
We don't have cameras in there!
Situation unknown! Arm yourselves!
Where? Where did he go?
That boy...
Where in the prison did he come from,
and where did he disappear to?
Move it!
Get to Visitation Room B!
Did the boy dig this hole?
This wall... He went through here!
Height: roughly 140 centimeters.
Small build, almost childlike.
I can't identify him,
but the hole that suddenly opened is a vent.
I can tell where it leads
by reading the airflow.
However...
I need to make sure he doesn't lead Jotaro and Jolyne
through the vents and out of my bullets' range!
I won't lose track of them again!
I'll finish the small one first!
Jolyne, this is one hell of a heavy situation.
Right now, all our Stands can do is defend.
He'll feel a change
in the air currents if we attack.
This is real fuckin' heavy.
Hey, you!
You can't just leave the room!
This side is the prison!
Gimme a break.
Visitors leave through the other door!
What the...?
There it is!
I knew it would go after him!
But there aren't any windows here...
How could he shoot bullets
here from the men's ward?
No... wait... he's...
That boy is...!
Nice thinking!
Good luck for us, too!
Since he went underwater,
he won't stir up any air currents!
Especially inside a pipe!
It lost track of him!
On top of that,
there's no windows down here!
There's no way he can get him now...
He's hitting the...!
But how? And from where?
That's impossible!
321 meters from target.
9.5 centimeters of bullet drop...
...and a slight ocean breeze
of 3.2 meters per second.
Round will be off-target by
4.2 centimeters to the left.
Target acquired.
Locked on to the heart.
Dammit!
Stone Free!
Threads!
Cujoh Jolyne... It's her Stand!
She followed him
all the way down there?!
Has she lost it?!
She thinks that will stop me?
New target: Jolyne.
Locked on to her forehead!
Fire!
What?!
I'm glad I had already broken this pipe.
I punctured the gas line
the moment I got here.
Because gas is light.
It made a layer of gas
separate from the oxygen in the room.
I figured it would throw off his aim.
Glad I was right...
What's going on?!
Too late!
I got you now!
Stone Free!
Looks like you couldn't
read the writing on the wall.
Manhattan Transfer
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: C
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: C
Johngalli A.
Who are you?
How's a kid like you
able to roam free around the prison?
Hit myself...
This...
That's right.
You gave it to me.
What is it?
It looks like a bone.
What's going on?
You told me not to go
to the visitation room.
What do you know that I don't?
C'mon, tell me!
Not yet...
Now's not the time...
But you mustn't let go of it.
This smell...
Did you do that?
That Johngalli A.
or whatever-his-name's sniping Stand...
It was nothing special once I caught it.
I smashed it to pieces.
Right.
Seems like you've gotten the hang of
fighting with your Stand.
Like I had a choice...
He's here! Over there!
He's moving!
Hide! He has a rifle!
He's hiding behind that pipe!
He went up above the tank!
That's impossible.
He was targeting us from two to three
hundred meters in the men's ward.
There's layers of iron bars between us.
Not to mention he's virtually blind.
How could he make it here so quickly?
How should I fucking know?!
If I say he's here, he's here!
Take cover!
He's right above you!
Okay. I believe you.
Ora!
Prepare yourself.
The gas has been
building up for a while.
We did it!
Hey, we're safe now!
Huh?
Where did he go?
Hey, are you still hiding?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Come out and explain everything to us!
Hey. What are you doing?
I'm looking for that kid.
Did you see where he went?
I don't follow.
Who's this kid you're talking about?
Oh, right.
You never saw him, did you...?
I talked to a little boy
outside the visitation room.
Johngalli A. tried taking him out first.
"Taking him out"?
I'm not following anything you're saying.
You got here by yourself.
I just followed you down here.
Wait... Our stories don't line up.
Didn't you hear him talking?
No, I know you did!
He's the one who told us
about the secret passage!
You heard him too, right?
Are you hearing ghosts?
What secret passage?
Fuck off!
You think now's the time to screw with me?!
You got here by following me
down a secret passage!
Wait...
There's something off about you...
Your wound...
What happened to your bullet wound?
Wound?
The wound from when Johngalli A. shot you!
Through your left shoulder...
But you aren't bleeding,
and your clothes...
I don't have a wound
from being shot, either!
And this guy...
He's not Johngalli A.!
He's that prison guard!
But I saw him get
shot through the head!
His head is fine!
What do you mean he was shot?
And who's this "Johngalli A."?
What the fuck is going on?
Something's wrong here...
Nothing's adding up!
What the hell is this?!
You and the people around you
will face something worse than death.
You must not go to the visitation room.
The visitation room...
That's right...
Something was off from the start...
When did my handcuffs disappear?
And that bullet...
Was I really shot back there?
Me and my dad aren't hurt at all.
Was Johngalli A.
even attacking us to begin with?
This is way off...
None of this makes any fucking sense!
This isn't reality!
I'm hallucinating...
No, someone is making me see this!
This is... This is...
...a dream...
Was I... dreaming?
How long was I...?
Looks like the part where I
knocked out the prison guard was real.
Johngalli A.'s photo...
Dad showed it to me.
The accident with the hitchhiker...
He told me it was all a setup...
That was all real...
Then I tried to leave the room...
That's when I realized
my handcuffs were gone...
From that point...
No, I woke up sitting right here...
So before even that...
We never even left the visitation room...
So that means...
Johngalli A.'s Stand...
...was just something my mind made up?
The secret passage, too...
All of it...
The instant we stepped foot
into the visitation room...
...we fell into his trap
and were forced into a dream!
We're slowly melting
as if being digested by a giant snake!
The boy in the garbage can
who gave me this bone...
He was real!
I woke up because I hurt my hand
clutching the bone.
Without the pain from the wound,
I would have stayed asleep forever.
This ability is the real Johngalli A.'s attack!
My thread!
I can't even unravel it
a few centimeters!
This is bad!
Shit...
Feeling... sleepy again...
Need to... get out of here...
Out of this visitation room!
Stone Free!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Prisoner of Love