Green Dolphin Street Prison.
Also known as "The Aquarium."
For some time, it's been the birthplace
of mysteries and powerful energy.
Of things no ordinary person can see.
Furthermore, the mysteries and
powerful energy are becoming clouded...
Punishment
Ward
Ms. Jolyne received an additional five years for the jailbreak,
and has spent the last few weeks in solitary.
After that, it begins... Everything...
Infirmary
Ward
But first,
I need to investigate something else.
Something to do with another inmate.
Her name is...
...Hermès Costello.
Ms. Jolyne has already
met this woman once before.
Hey! The fuck you think you're doin'?!
Hey! Hold the fuck up, asshole!
Am I in...
...the infirmary?
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Dammit! Was that someone on cleanup?
Episode 6  Hermès' Stickers
Took the last of my cash, too...
Son of a bitch!
Oh, that's right.
I hurt my palm...
...and I had a fever.
'Least the wound's almost healed.
Was that a dream?
No, wait a minute...
It's all coming back now...
Just before they sent me here
to serve five years for robbery...
...I picked that thing up off the ground.
In the visitation room
of the holding block...
But it gave me a gnarly cut
on my palm and pissed me off...
What was that woman's name again?
Guess!
That's right, I pawned it off to her.
That same night...
...I passed out for some reason,
and now I'm here.
Have I been stuck in bed this whole time?
So my wound healed, and...
Wait, what the...?
But I just peeled this sticker off my palm...
Am I losing it?
In 1492, Columbus sailed the ocean blue!
Bugs Bunny was born on July 27th!
Nope, memory's fine.
The fuck?!
I know I threw it away!
Wait... My shoes...
There's... uh...
One, two...
Three, four, five, si-
Huh?
Fucking oww!
Ah, f-five?
I-It's back to normal!
D-Did that fever make me
start seeing double?
But that sticker just now...
It's the one I just threw away...
No fucking way...
N-Nasty!
The fuck's wrong with you?
Shut the fuck up already!
I-It's nothing!
Go back to sleep!
Dumb bitch...
N-No...
The fever didn't make me
start seeing double...
I can feel it in my hand.
It's got weight to it.
This sticker...
When I stick it to things, it doubles them!
And when I peel it off...
...it definitely does damage,
but the two turn back into one!
And these stickers...
It sounds fucking crazy,
but it's gotta be true.
They're coming from inside of me!
But hey, maybe this'll come in handy!
Fucking sweet!
No use overthinking it.
Basically, I got stickers
coming outta my hands.
That's just how it is.
You better give me back the shit
you swiped off me, fucker!
Wh-What... is this...?
H-He's gone now...
It's like he didn't notice anything wrong...
I kinda just grabbed this
thing since it was right there...
Speaking of...
What the hell even is it?!
Your fever's gone down.
You're clear to go back to your cell, now.
Uh, actually...
Who was doing cleanup earlier?
They a model prisoner?
What's their na-
None of your business!
Next!
Who was on cleanup?
How the hell should I know?
Dunno, beats me.
It looks like a CD...
...or some other kind of disc.
Looks and feels about the same, anyway.
But it's soft and stretchy.
Also...
...he had another one in his face.
He had two on him.
The hell? It's showing something!
This money I got from those sick inmates...
It's all mine...
I got five thousand dollars hidden.
No one'll find it here.
Th-This footage...
McQueen...
Would you like to work with me?
As partners?
McQueen!
What... What the hell was that?
It was like watching someone's memory!
I heard...
...you've been slinking around
asking about me.
I've done some stalking,
but never been stalked back by a woman.
Yup, this one's a first.
And just who the fuck are you?
I saw those disc-things
sticking out of your face!
Disc?
Boohoo...
I can't remember anything!
What're you talking about?
I'm such a failure!
I can't remember!
Wh-What's got you blubberin' out of nowhere?
You stole my cash back in the infirmary!
Just this morning!
Money? Th-That's right.
I had a bunch of money,
and I hid it somewhere.
But...
I don't remember where!
Hey, are you okay?
Or are you just fucking with me?!
Did you just ask if I'm okay?
You're too kind!
How many years has it been
since I last spoke with a woman?
No, it's my first time.
I've never had a heart-to-heart
with a beautiful woman before!
I'm so happy right now...
Someday I hope I can cross paths with
a woman like you and spend the rest of my life with her!
But that's just a pipe dream, huh?
I'm just a loser, huh?
Nothing but trash, huh?
Guess I'll just kill myself.
Wha-
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
What?!
Wh-What's going on...?!
Highway to Hell
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: A
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: A
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Thunder McQueen
McQueen...
Pure evil lies within you.
You possess neither malice nor animosity.
You do not believe you are a nuisance.
You make yourself the victim,
and yet despite your disinterest in others...
...you wish time after time
that you might be saved.
But this is what makes you truly evil.
You drag others down with you.
The purest form of evil.
I like you very much, McQueen.
Should you encounter my foes
within these prison walls....
...you will surely take care to
sweep them out for me.
H-He hanged himself...
and now my neck...!
S-Somebody...!
Somebody help me...!
I-I'm blacking out...
Maybe I can save myself if I save him first?
Sticker!
He's got weird powers like I do...
Guess I'm not the only one!
Goddammit...
Who the fuck even are you?!
Why'd you hang yourself all of a sudden?
Did you save me?
I owe you my life.
Answer the fucking question!
What the hell do you want from me?!
You got some kind of ability, right?
An ability?
I don't know what you mean,
but don't worry.
I won't do it again.
You really opened my eyes.
I owe you one for saving my life.
Someday,
I'll definitely repay you.
R-Repay me?
I mean, you really don't gotta...
The fuck are you doing now?!
What?!
Those scars...
He must be suicidal!
And it seems like
he doesn't know about his ability!
This is fucked...
I'm even posing like him now!
Shit, he pushed me away!
You fucking idiot!
D-Dammit!
The disc!
I don't know what the fuck is going on,
but the disc's gotta have something to do with it!
Let me die...
I said I'd repay you,
but a guy like me'll never be able to...
...since I'm a piece of trash!
I don't want shit from you!
Not even friendship!
Back the fuck off or
I'll fucking end you!
Yes, please end me!
A lovely lady like you ending my life
would be so nice!
She fished out some kind of disc
from the toilet just now, didn't she?
For some reason,
I think it was mine.
I wonder if she'll give it back...
Nah, probably not...
L-Let me through!
Here's my discharge letter!
I'm going back to the women's ward!
Fuck me!
I gotta put more distance
between me and that fucking psycho!
Gotta get back...
...to my cell!
I knew it.
Your power has awakened.
I need to tell you something.
The name of the power that awoke in you...
...is called a Stand ability.
Stand abilities
attract one another like gravity.
For seemingly no reason.
That's why you ran into
that man on cleanup duty.
Wh-What's a kid doing here?!
You picked up and sold
Ms. Jolyne's pendant.
That's why she told me
to keep an eye on you.
Jolyne?
What happened to her?
Our enemy is someone
with the ability to steal souls.
We're looking for one of the souls he stole.
A soul?
The culprit's name is Whitesnake.
Please help us if you know anything!
Souls...
You mean something like this disc?
Th-That's...!
It's from the man who was on cleanup.
So, what exactly is the deal with this thing?
Wait, weren't there two of them?
Two? Uh... Yeah, there was.
A memory disc and a Stand disc.
They come in pairs.
Two discs make up the spirit.
If we can get the other disc,
we might be able to figure out who Whitesnake is!
No way...
Again?!
It's still clinging to me...
No way!
I'm nowhere near him anymore!
Wh-What's going on?!
E-Electricity!
The motherfucker's zapping himself!
I-It stopped...
Electrical resistance.
Your skin being zapped by a hundred volts
of electricity isn't enough to kill you.
It's electrically resistant.
That's why it stopped.
His suicide attempt failed.
But...
If he decides to try
electrocuting himself again...
...he's probably already
looking around for some saline.
A saline solution would increase
conductivity to almost one hundred percent.
The electricity would reach his heart
and completely fry it.
Saline?
It's used as IV fluid and disinfectant!
The infirmary's loaded with the stuff!
This is as far as I can go...
There are too many inmates by the stairs!
I'll fuck him up
and rip the other disc out of his head!
It's the only way!
S-Stop! Don't do it!
Look at my left arm!
It's burned the same way as your arm!
You've got some weird ability...
Every time you hurt yourself,
I get hurt the same way!
Stop thinking about killing yourself!
There's so many fun
and exciting things in life!
Four years ago...
I was just cleaning...
Cleaning the shotgun in my apartment.
But for some reason, it was loaded...
...and went off by accident.
I lived on the tenth floor.
It just happened that a woman on the eleventh floor
tried offing herself at that exact moment.
Like winning the lottery...
Some people win a few million bucks...
...and some people get screwed over.
She was supposed to
hit the ground and die.
Everyone thought I purposely shot
and killed that woman on the eleventh floor.
The judge even called me
a cold-blooded murderer.
That's the kind of guy I am!
H-Hold on!
Oh, my panties!
Ever had a girl give you her panties?
How lucky would you feel if a girl
just randomly gave you her panties?
I know you're going through hell right now...
...but imagine if a girl gave you
her hot-off-her-press panties!
It'd mean good things can happen
even when everything's fucked, right?
Ah, I'm so embarrassed!
But they're for you!
You can have what I'm wearing right now!
You'd really give them to me?
I'm a woman of my word!
Just remember...
Nobody likes it when it's almost Monday!
Knowing the next fun Saturday's
just around the corner is what keeps us going!
Not every day's a Monday!
I was arrested on a Saturday...
You're saying nice things
to give me courage...
...but it's probably just
a bunch of bunk to save your skin.
Th-That's not...
You're pretending
to be nice to get out of this.
You didn't mean a single word.
Am I wrong?
Everyone always does me dirty like this...
Nobody likes trash.
Hell, I'm worse than trash.
Everyone just sees right through me!
W-Wait!
Sure, I'm only talking to you
to save my own skin...
But just fucking listen to me!
That Whitesnake asshole is using you!
He's taking advantage of how you think!
If you stop thinking about suicide,
nothing will happen!
You're the one being selfish here,
you fucking prick!
You really are a nice person! Seriously!
You're breathtaking!
You really meant all that.
I'm so lucky...
I got to meet such a beautiful woman
before I ended it once and for all...
Thank you!
Oh, thank you!
If we die together...
If I can spend the rest of eternity with you...
...then I truly am blessed!
H-He's straight-up evil!
This motherfucker's
rotten to the fucking core!
I'm not lonely anymore!
Finally!
Fuck you!
Drop the fucking switch!
That was close...
Too fucking close!
I got a sticker on him...
The sparks from the electricity
should burn it.
Once it burns up,
whatever was split up by the sticker will...
...merge back into one!
Shit, man...
The shock jolted my memory...
He hid some money away, didn't he?
Five thousand dollars...
Consider that my fucking payment.
And then there's Whitesnake...
That asshole put me through this shit.
What the hell is he planning?
Hermès Costello: Stand Name "Kiss"
I gotta see her... Jolyne...
Cujoh Jolyne.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
There's Six of Us!