Eat this.
Auto-tracking Stand users are...
It's Foo Fighters!
Why is she here
in the Disciplinary Wing?
A disc!
Whitesnake is close!
Wh-Where is he?
No...
The asshole who threw it...
...was you!
Whitesnake's true identity is...!
It was him...
Father Pucci!
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
One thing I know for sure is now's not the time to bitch and moan
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
Tugging on my thread of fate, I get a move on
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
Bobbing and weaving through the traps and hate scattered along the way
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
No time for breaks in these survival days
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
If I wanna stay true to myself...
(Got to be tough)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) Wake up (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Who I was yesterday just ain't gonna cut it
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Break out! (Hey) No matter (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
How many skilled attacks come at me
genkai wa houkai
My limits crumble
Give up wa rongai
No option to give up
unmei tenazukeru made
'Til I rein in my destiny
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Don't stop beating 'em up
Episode 21  Awaken
What F.F. fears most...
...isn't the annihilation of her body,
but of her intellect.
That day...
When I met Jolyne in the farmlands...
I have a perfect memory of
everything after that.
Like the weird doodles
on the pay phones...
...the lint-covered blankets on the bed,
and the smell of garbage.
The guards' shouting...
...the sounds of doors opening and closing,
and of flowing toilet water.
Fooling around and having a laugh
with Jolyne and the others... I remember all of it.
But everything before that day on the farm...
Even though I probably lived there for years...
All my memories of that place
are purely mechanical.
They all blend together.
I was just following orders and protecting
Whitesnake's discs without knowing why.
But now I understand...
...that to live means
to make memories.
That's the only thing
I'm afraid to lose.
Jolyne is acting for
the sake of her father...
...and is willing to risk her life
for the people she cares about, like Hermès...
...because I know she holds
good memories inside her.
That's the energy powering humanity.
Memories give courage to cells.
That's something the old Foo Fighters,
the old me, didn't have.
That's right.
That's...
That's what it means
to have intellect!
What is your highest priority?
Is it me?
Or does eliminating
D&G come first?
You thought for a moment!
That hesitation will be your end!
It was I who bestowed you
with intellect and an ability!
Now you will return it!
When I think of Jolyne,
I can feel courage well up inside me.
This is what memories are.
This... is intellect!
Wh-What?
Inconceivable...
Surely Foo Fighters isn't-
Her body fluids are inside him!
I-Impossible...
Am I...?
It appears F.F. succeeded.
She must have
taken out the user.
It's empty!
What is that?
Has it been born?
Is this what Whitesnake is after?
What the hell even is it?
Why was it born?
Why does it exist?
Were the prisoners turned to plants
just to give birth to this thing?
Now that it's born,
my body isn't turning into a plant.
I don't matter to it anymore!
Don't you dare let
Foo Fighters escape!
Read the memory within the disc!
Find out where the being
borne of Dio's bone is immediately!
Will I last even thirty seconds
with my body exposed like this?
I need water!
I have to let Jolyne know
who's behind Whitesnake!
Shit!
I have to tell her
it's the chaplain, Enrico Pucci!
Are you attempting to
reach an outdoor faucet?
Before you leave,
I have a question I must ask!
Eat this! Foo Fighters!
What I want to ask, Foo Fighters...
...is but one simple question.
Did you see it?
The being that emerged from
within the Disciplinary Wing?
What was it?
Was it a plant?
Was it beautiful?
Why don't you tell me what
a priest like you is doing here in prison?
Please, I asked my question first.
If I take back your memory and read it,
I'll know what was born in short order.
But first, I would like to
hear your thoughts on it.
Whether you felt it looked soft
or were taken by its beauty.
Those would be impressions,
not memories stored on a disc.
Are you worried it will
get away from you?
Or leave your sight?
Can it already move that quickly?
Beats me.
I'd be more concerned
that it might get destroyed.
Or worse,
maybe it already was destroyed.
The guy with Jolyne is
pretty much a complete asshole.
If he thinks it's trouble,
that thing is fucked!
Destroying it is impossible.
Utterly impossible.
No one can destroy it,
that much I know for certain.
My only concern is losing track of it
due to any unforeseen actions by Jolyne.
Jotaro's memory alone is enough
to control this newborn being...
...and that is still
in my possession.
As of now, I am but a single step away.
What was it shaped like?
Did it grow faster than you expected?
I thought it was gonna drown in water.
And then, what else was there?
Let's see, hmm...
She's stalling for time!
Turn around!
I did it!
Foo Fighters' brain,
the control tower, isn't here.
It's in the other half!
Now I have water!
I can tell Jolyne everything!
Brain, you say?
It isn't for you to decide
where your brain is.
It was I who bestowed you
with a Stand ability disc.
You disgusting plankton!
Don't you dare condescend me!
M-My body!
Th-This water...!
Wh-What the fuck is
spraying all over me?!
It can't be!
It's steaming hot water.
There isn't a single aquatic lifeform on Earth
that can survive in water above thirty-two degrees Celsius.
A different Stand ability
that turns cold water hot...
...was inserted into your other half!
The location of your brain
is entirely up to me!
Your newly acquired ability will
boil every drop of water you touch!
Jo...
Jolyne!
Green, Green Grass of Home
Power: ?
Speed: ?
Range: ?
Durability: ?
Precision: ?
Growth Potential: ?
Power: ?
Speed: ?
Range: ?
Durability: ?
Precision: ?
Growth Potential: ?
The Green Baby
Where is it?!
Where did it fall?!
It couldn't have drowned!
N-No...
Does it have its own will?
I mean, since it's trying to escape.
No...
It's probably acting on pure instinct.
It could just be some kind of weird plant for all I know,
but I don't want it going anywhere!
I won't let Whitesnake have it!
Jolyne!
Wait, Jolyne!
Don't move!
Look at the rock at your feet!
Listen to me.
Don't take another step.
Turn back and face me.
The pebble turned into
a boulder as it rolled.
Except for you, Jolyne,
it was the opposite...
Stop!
I told you to stay away from it!
Wh-What is this, Annasui?
Wh-Why did you shrink?
What the fuck is this, Annasui?!
Calm down, Jolyne.
By the way,
what size does the baby look to you?
N-Normal size.
Just like before.
Annasui, you're the only thing
that looks smaller.
What's happening?
The baby looks
normal-sized to me, too.
Only the pebble
we kicked shrunk down.
Jolyne!
Do not move!
Stay right where you are.
You're back to normal.
Is this the baby's ability?
The closer we get to it,
the more we shrink.
I have no clue.
That's a heavy question to answer.
So, listen.
If I'm halfway toward the baby...
...my height shrinks by about half.
Thus doubling the distance needed to walk.
Right.
Furthermore, if both of us were
a fourth of the way toward the baby...
...our distance from it
would grow by four times.
At one-eighth,
we walk eight times as much.
One thirty-second...
One sixty-fourth...
One one-hundred and twenty-eighth...
The more we shrink,
the more the distance multiplies.
So here's the question...
Will we ever reach the baby?
I don't believe we will.
But I'll never get
my dad's memory disc back...
...if I let that baby get away!
Jolyne!
Think later, Annasui!
We need to act now!
It's that focus...
The way Jolyne becomes
fixated on reaching a single goal...
That side of her must be
what drew me to her!
The ability to focus
enhances one's beauty.
Those eyes...
Someday, I'll have you gaze at me
with that same intensity in your eyes.
Stone Free!
Just a bit farther!
I almost have it!
That's enough, Jolyne!
Reel your thread back!
Reaching that baby is impossible!
I don't accept that!
It has to end somewhere!
It's right in front of us!
What do you think if
I jump from up here?
I'll eventually have to
reach an end point.
That point is the ground!
I will land!
Jolyne, stop! Don't-
Yes!
The ground is right there!
I'm almost there!
What?
My thread!
What the fuck is that?!
Don't tell me...
Is this the baby's Stand?
Shit!
How long until I reach the ground?!
I-It's not only growing in size,
but also power!
Its power multiplied!
This Stand appeared
just to drag me down!
It's trying to stop me from escaping
this world of endlessly falling!
Stone Free!
If this is the baby's ability, then catching the Stand
is no different from catching the user!
Ora!
I-I'm shrinking!
It wants to reduce me to nothing!
The ground wasn't the end point at all!
It's this Stand!
Diver Down.
The closer you get to the baby,
the more you shrink.
You'll eventually turn to nothing.
I don't know why this baby with
such an invincible ability was born, but...
...eventually it will
become our enemy!
Jolyne!
The baby is your enemy!
B-But...
If it really is invincible, that's just another reason
we can't let Whitesnake have it!
Annasui, hold on tight!
It threw the rock!
Does this mean it's thinking for itself?
It's thinking and using
its ability with purpose!
Here it comes! Climb!
We need to get away
as fast as possible!
Run!
No matter how long we give chase,
we'll never reach that baby.
At least now we've
captured its Stand.
Jolyne, do you still not see
what we were climbing for?
It was a gamble...
The baby is intelligent and curious.
It touched the bottle
I threw near it.
Anything it touches
stays its normal size.
In other words,
the bottle has stayed the same!
If we can't catch the baby,
we'll have the baby come to us!
We finally reached the bottle!
Now the Stand is inside it with us!
All we have to do now
is trap it here!
B-But...
How are we getting out of here?!
Right now, Diver Down is diving...
...through the walls
of the bottle itself.
It's bringing the exit right to us.
Let's go, Jolyne!
Run for it!
We finally caught it...
We have its infant user, too.
It's rolling to cut us off!
Bottle and all!
Annasui!
Stone Free!
Ora!
Jolyne!
Don't destroy the bottle!
We're finished if it
breaks out and traps us!
D-Did it roll the bottle
knowing this would happen?!
Dammit!
How could this happen?!
Don't break the bottle!
But...
You won't make it!
A-Annasui, look...!
Wh-What the hell?
Wh-What's going on?
Jolyne, it looks like...
...it was drawn to the star-shaped
birthmark on your left shoulder.
And since it touched you,
we were able to return to normal size.
The baby has
the same birthmark on its shoulder.
What is this thing?
It's acting like it's
known her for a while.
H-Hey, I think it's getting
kinda attached to me.
Wh-What should I do?
Attached? No.
Of that, I'm certain.
It's going to turn on us.
All I can sense is endless darkness
from this baby's ability.
Though we may need this baby
to get your dad's disc back from Whitesnake...
...I have to kill it while I still can.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny
I'm thinking about
All the things
I'd like to do
In my life
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away
From today
Time of Heaven and New Moon! New Priest!