Is it possible that while we were sleeping...
Me and Giorno... Mista and Trish...
Did our minds leave our bodies and swap places?!
Don't attack just yet!
That Stand!
It's Sticky Fingers!
It's Buccellati's...
...soul!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
None can escape their chosen fate
Only the result in which you are destroyed remains
This enduring dominance is mine alone to relish in
Sing your sorrowful tune in this world bereft of time
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 35  A Softly Playing Requiem Part 2
Yes!
Buccellati's all right!
He went right for the arrow, too!
Before even the boss could!
From the way you're speaking...
...I can only assume Narancia is in there.
Am I right?
Y-Yeah!
And you two...
I'm Giorno.
A-And I'm Trish.
You're quick, Buccellati.
I'm impressed that you already
have a grasp of this bizarre situation.
That voice...
Are you the man I talked to earlier?
Yes.
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff.
I was killed by Diavolo.
But because my soul was swapped with this tortoise's...
...I've been able to cling to this world like a phantom.
That over there is my Stand.
The power of the arrow made it go berserk, turning it into Chariot Requiem.
It's the one responsible for swapping our souls.
Wait...
If our souls have been swapped...
...then the person in my body...
He hasn't woken up yet.
He's out cold.
You're... Mista?
Yeah.
Glad to see you're safe, Buccellati.
The boss, or should I say Diavolo,
swapped minds with you and is being watched by Pistols' Number Seven.
He hasn't moved at all.
He's definitely asleep.
Buccellati!
Requiem is getting up!
We already know how to use the arrow!
If we can take control of it...
...this will all be over!
Sticky Fingers!
What's going on?
Pick up the arrow!
Requiem is charging at you!
I'll knock the arrow away!
Hurry and pick it up!
Something's wrong!
Don't tell me that was...
Take this!
I'll blow a hole in your brain!
The pillar next to you!
Mista, dodge it!
Spice Girl!
I'll splatter your brain across the ground!
The ground!
Let ants crawl all over you!
Let flies swarm all around you!
What the...?! N-Number One?
Where the hell did you come from? Hey, stop!
Hey, stop that!
Wh-What's the matter, fellas?
What...?
It can't be...
H-Hey!
It's gonna get the arrow back!
It's gonna take it from us!
What the hell is going on?!
What just happened?!
If I had to guess,
this is Requiem's Stand ability while it's going berserk!
This is the first time I'm seeing it, as well!
Now that Requiem's gone berserk, it inherited the will
from the depths of my heart and has become a defensive Stand.
All to ensure that no one else could have the arrow!
Anyone who tries to touch the arrow
will be attacked by their own Stand in retaliation!
The arrow has the power to control people's minds...
Are you saying this is part of that?
If that's true, what the hell are we supposed to do?!
Our Stands powered up...
B-But still...
If we try to get the arrow with that power...
S-Stop that!
Benedict!
There, there... It'll be okay.
Mista!
Number Seven is keeping watch and started freaking out!
Buccellati's body...
He woke up!
Diavolo? It can't be!
We'll have to go after the arrow later!
Position yourselves so you can see his body!
Mista! Shoot him!
What are you doing?!
Shoot him!
B-But that's your body, Buccellati!
Bullet wounds...
...can be fully healed by my Gold Experience.
We need to ensure he won't be able to move.
That's what you're saying...
Right, Buccellati?
He stood up!
He's walking towards us!
He's convulsing!
He won't be coming for us anymore!
I didn't see a reaction from anyone else but us.
No one's coming to save him!
We did it.
Now we just need to get the arrow back,
and this will all be over!
Once we get back to Naples,
I'm gonna go to school!
I wanna get a piping-hot slice of pizza, too!
True margherita from back home
baked over an oak wood fire!
I'll get some porcini mushrooms on it, too!
And then...
...if I see Fugo...
...it might feel kinda nice for him to
mock me and call me dumb again.
Abbacchio's gone, though...
Trish!
I'm gonna protect you until the end!
We all will!
Narancia...
Mista...
Just to be safe, shoot both his legs.
G-Gotcha!
Trish, you've got my bullets.
Give 'em to me.
They're in my boot.
S-Sure...
Hurry up, would you?
Hurry up and hand 'em over!
M-Mista...
Time just skipped ahead a few seconds!
Yeah! There are bullets on the ground,
but I don't remember hearing them fall!
But that's impossible!
I didn't see anything happen!
He never summoned or recalled King Crimson!
How could he have?
He's been in that spot the entire time!
Trish, drop one more bullet from my hand...
Hurry and do it!
There's four bullets on the ground right now!
I can't handle the number four!
I can't stand the number four being anywhere near me!
If they fell when you handed them to me,
then you gotta drop another one!
Is he really Diavolo?
Trish, when we woke up, you mentioned that you couldn't sense the boss's presence from that body at all, right?
What about now?
Do you sense the boss nearby?
But that's impossible!
You swapped with Narancia,
and Mista swapped with Trish.
That means Diavolo switched with Buccellati!
That's Requiem's ability while it's berserk!
I'm not quite sure what's going on,
but if time was just erased...
...it must mean that Diavolo isn't inside
that body since he controls King Crimson!
Narancia, what's happening in our immediate area?
Is anyone else coming close to us?
Narancia?
Trish, please...
You need to drop...
...drop one more bullet from my hand... please...
I'm not sure...
I'm not sure why I can't...
...sense the boss!
I can't sense him anywhere...
Move. Move!
Let me through!
Out of my way!
Please, move out of my way, everyone!
Impossible!
This never should have happened!
Keep watch of our surroundings, Mista!
Watch our backs!
Narancia!
Cut the iron bars, Buccellati!
Hurry and get Narancia down from there!
Leave it to me, Mista!
Leave this to me!
You need to load your gun, Mista!
He'll come for us again!
His attack has already begun!
Sticky Fingers!
Now heal him!
Hurry up and pull the bars out of his wounds!
The civilians outside the Colosseum are waking up.
Where is he?
I haven't sensed the boss's presence at all!
I don't understand why his presence
isn't disappearing and reappearing anymore...
King Crimson's range is
two to three meters at most.
So then how did he do it from over there?
H-Hey! You did it!
Narancia's awake now!
Yes!
Th-That was a close one...
No... Mista...
This is... an empty... shell...
It's an empty shell.
The wounds from where he was pierced...
...have already been completely healed by my Gold Experience.
But... he's already gone.
Narancia...
...isn't...
It's... completely empty.
His soul...
...has left his body.
He's already gone...
There's... nothing I can do...
I didn't make it in time...
I can feel myself slipping back into my body...
and even switch back and forth between the two...
It's already...
...empty...
Narancia!
This is too sudden...
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Silver Chariot
Where is he?
Where could he be?
This is inconceivable!
The only way this could be possible
is if there are two Diavolos!
Two of them...
That kid and Diavolo...
There can't possibly be two of them...
There's only one body, but two minds!
Buccellati!
I figured it out!
Diavolo has two personalities!
There's no other explanation!
The person in that body
is the kid I encountered earlier!
The kid and Diavolo share a single body,
but their minds are separate!
Sometimes, under certain circumstances, people's minds can be scarred and split due to a traumatic childhood experience.
As they grow older, the split can
develop into a separate personality.
That split personality starts to appear
much more distinctly as they reach adulthood...
...and eventually one personality
will become the dominant one.
That's the theory of multiple personality disorder!
Listen. What I just told you isn't a hypothesis.
I've even heard reports from Germany and England of people's faces and bodily features changing depending on their personality.
Requiem's ability tore his souls away from his body.
One of them, the kid,
ended up in Buccellati's body...
...but the other one...
...perhaps by complete coincidence,
ended up in someone else's body!
That being Diavolo!
King Crimson attacked from their body!
What are you talking about?
Two personalities?
That's who the boss really is?
People are slowly beginning to wake up out there...
...so I don't know where he's hiding.
But he will come again!
He'll attack us again soon!
That's possible...
...but he may have already left the area.
Diavolo is after the arrow, too.
That's why he attacked Narancia first.
He broke our radar.
He did it so that we won't be able to tell him apart from the crowd while he's pursuing the arrow.
That's why he took down Aerosmith.
This just means you'll have to
obtain the arrow's power after all.
Either way, in order to defeat King Crimson...
...you need to reach the arrow before he does,
then find a way to claim it.
Which way did Requiem go?
To the left.
It looks like people are starting to
wake up in the direction he's headed.
R-Reach it? But your body is...
What about your body, Buccellati?
I didn't hit any vitals.
But he won't be able to stand up or move.
I made sure of that.
We're going to have to leave you here...
Now nobody... will ever hurt you again...
Not ever.
And I promise you...
...we'll take you back home.
Be wary of anyone who approaches us.
Let's go!
Trish! What are you doing? Stay close!
R-Right...
Hey little lady!
You're under arrest!
You're coming with me down to the station!
I-Is something wrong, Mista?
Nope! It's all good!
That guy got close,
so I thought it was the boss...
...but it was just some cop.
It certainly does seem that Requiem...
...doesn't have a destination in mind, nor any emotions.
It hasn't even glanced at me or the direction it's headed.
I would agree if you said it resembles a living creature...
...but if you said it looked like some
strange black plastic, I'd agree with that, too.
It hasn't even recognized me as an enemy.
It seems slow and weak.
And it's a corporeal Stand.
Normal people can see and touch it.
It's no use...
It won't let us approach it.
It's not just our Stands.
Anything we try touching it with
will come flying back at us.
This arrow might truly be invincible.
The more difficult this becomes, the more convinced I am
that it has some kind of isolation power that repels everything.
It's getting back up.
How can we pick up the arrow?
It's right in front of us!
Hey.
Requiem won't allow Stand users to pick up the arrow...
...but what if someone who isn't
a Stand user tried to pick it up?
Well, what do you think would happen?
What're you asking me for?
How the hell would I-
H... H-H-Hey, guys!
I'm nothing but a soul
desperately clinging to this tortoise...
I'm not a Stand user anymore...
...so I can touch it!
Mista!
Hurry up and pierce your Stand with this arrow!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Diavolo Rises