If only... my daughter...
...if only you had never been born...
Fear truly does stem from the past.
You have angered me greatly!
What?
You said you would rise above, did you not?
You were right, Trish.
Now you can rise above not only your past...
...but above their heads as well.
Trish!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
None can escape their chosen fate
Only the result in which you are destroyed remains
This enduring dominance is mine alone to relish in
Sing your sorrowful tune in this world bereft of time
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 37  King of Kings
T-Trish!
No way! He...!
He's clinging on!
He punched straight through Trish's soul and himself!
This body has served its purpose...
...as have you.
H-Her soul!
It's moving away!
Trish's soul is...
...disappearing into the sky!
The arrow!
The arrow will fall into my hands!
It pierced me!
The arrow's power...
...is a gift bestowed upon me by fate!
It will take my King Crimson
to the apex of this world!
Did it pierce me?
I-It didn't!
Wh-What...?
Something is wrong!
No... I haven't even grasped it!
M-My King Crimson's hand is translucent!
And it's crumbling!
What?!
Th-This is...!
M-My soul is leaving her body...
This wind is...
I-It cannot be!
Could it be that all you're
capable of predicting, Boss...
...are the trajectories of arrows and bullets?
You weren't able to predict
what I was about to do, were you?
D-Damn you...
You're the one who figured out
how to destroy Requiem.
These things behind our heads...
Or rather, the things behind each one of our souls.
They just need to be destroyed.
You wanted to retrieve the arrow,
so you left Requiem alive...
Don't... Don't, Buccellati...
But if I completely destroy this...
...the ability of the berserk Stand, Requiem, will disappear.
Don't, Buccellati!
Look at me!
Consider who is truly worthy to wield such power!
Buccellati... Y-You're...
Who is the king worthy
of possessing this arrow?!
Buccellati!
Controlling the arrow is not a task worthy of the weak!
All the souls that have been swapped...
...will go back to where they belong!
Trish's soul!
I-It's Trish!
Mista!
Look fellas!
You did it, Buccellati!
It was close, but she's coming back!
The rest, Giorno, is up to you.
B-Buccellati...
Y-Your body is back at the Colosseum...
That body is-
Giorno, I came back to life.
When I first met you back home in Naples...
...and when I betrayed the organization...
...my heart was dying a slow death,
but it came back to life...
...because of you.
I'm truly content now.
My time has come.
Don't worry.
Give the others my regards.
How dare you?!
All for my impertinent daughter!
You putrid piles of vomit
spewed into a toilet by a pissant!
You dare oppose me?!
I, Diavolo, shall be the one
who controls the arrow!
We...
We did it...
You really outdid yourself, Buccellati...
That was a close one...
...but Trish should be okay now.
Giorno... Heal us...
Buccellati's still at the Colosseum,
but I'm sure he'll be here in no time...
Right? Hey!
Don't worry about me, Giorno.
I'm going to where I should have
gone in the first place.
Back where I belong...
That's all...
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Chariot Requiem
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Benedict!
I'm unsure who said this, but...
"We are all soldiers chosen by fate."
But I've learned some truths
of my own about this world.
Fate bestowed upon me the ability
to predict the future and skip time.
It is a fact.
The undeniable truth.
The fate of this world...
...was for my King Crimson
to stand invincible at the top!
I am no soldier...
Shit!
And in spite of all this...
the arrow has somehow still evaded my grasp!
How dare you?!
There's no way...
There's no way that I, Diavolo,
would fail due to something like this!
I need to retreat for now.
I need to hide from the arrow
and await the ideal moment for my counterattack!
Retreating here is not admitting defeat...
I have the ability to return to the top!
Don't let him get away, Giorno...
No matter... what you do...
If he gets away, he'll go into hiding...
He plans on running away, Giorno...
I just felt it...
He took a step back!
Wha-
He has the arrow!
The person who will control
the arrow after Requiem...
...is Giorno!
It's no use...
I cannot run from this place, after all!
My pride will vanish if I retreat...
I am the king!
My goal is to ensure my enduring dominance!
If I flee now, my pride will be lost!
There is... no next time!
He's not running away!
He's going for him...
...even though it's pretty much pointless!
Gold Experience!
He did it!
Giorno's Gold Experience is going to
surpass the power of the arrow!
No! You're wrong!
I thank you, my daughter!
Because you insulted me
by proclaiming that I would run...
...I've managed to keep my pride!
It's fortunate that I chose not to retreat.
Had I fled,
I would not have seen this vision.
This unexpected vision from King Crimson's Epitaph!
Gold Experience!
He did it!
Giorno's Gold Experience is going to
surpass the power of the arrow!
B-But why?
It pierced him...
but the arrow fell to the ground.
How fortunate it is that I didn't flee!
How very fortunate!
To be honest,
my heart was overcome with despair.
If my daughter hadn't
insulted and looked down on me...
...I would have decided not to pursue you.
But because I did,
I witnessed a vision of the arrow falling to the ground!
Giorno Giovanna...
You pathetic amateur...
This proves that you weren't a suitable vessel.
He's already disappeared,
but do you remember what Polnareff said?
The arrow chooses those worthy of controlling it.
I can't help but reiterate
how fortunate it is that I didn't flee.
The arrow has rejected you!
Giorno, run!
You're finished!
I, Diavolo, will remain king, as I always have!
G-Giorno!
Wait, Mista!
That thing peeking through the cracks...
Could that be...?
Th-That's...!
What am I witnessing right now?
I cracked his head open!
Shouldn't I be seeing
his brains spilling out right now?
It isn't his brains coming out...
Th-This can't be!
The arrow is being drawn up his arm!
The arrow!
Dammit!
You're finished, Giorno Giovanna!
Th-That's...!
Giorno wasn't rejected!
He wasn't unworthy
or cast aside by the arrow!
No... Actually...
The arrow is forever Giorno's!
The boss will never have the arrow now!
Am I seeing the truth?
I must be seeing this wrong somehow.
I should be looking at Giorno's corpse
with his head cracked open!
This cannot be the truth!
It's Requiem...
That's Giorno's Requiem...
Gold Experience Requiem!
Gold Experience surpassed
the power of the arrow!
What?!
Only the truth of this world
will remain in the end.
Righteous actions born of truth will never crumble.
My friends may have perished...
...but their will and actions are indomitable.
They handed this arrow to me.
So tell me, are your actions born of truth...
...or are they superficial and born of evil?
We'll soon see.
Can you avoid utter destruction, Boss?
Wh-What's going on?
What's about to happen?
Don't tell me our souls are
about to be swapped again!
I'm not sure... No one is...
Giorno probably doesn't know, either.
But after what just happened,
I'm sure Giorno has complete control of his Requiem!
It hasn't gone berserk!
I couldn't see it...
I couldn't see the moment it attacked!
But I was able to predict it.
The reason it didn't do more damage...
...is because I predicted the hole appearing in my hand!
I can just barely dodge its attacks.
Gold Experience's attack may have
been tremendously powerful...
But... that's all it was.
It merely powered up.
I can predict it like any other threat!
This is not something I cannot overcome!
Fate has chosen me to stand at the apex!
I, Diavolo, am the king who has overcome all threats!
Don't speak as though you know
better than me, Giorno Giovanna!
I won't even allow you
the chance to regret your death!
King Crimson!
Time shall be eliminated
for everyone but myself!
I can see it...
I can see his Stand's movements!
I can perfectly see what it is trying to do!
I can easily figure out
what those pieces of trash are planning!
This should halt Gold Experience's movements!
Even when time begins anew in a few seconds...
...your eyes will never see
King Crimson or me again!
The pinnacle of truth lies within my abilities!
Yes! I've won!
I will be just a moment faster!
My vision shows me
tearing his heart right from his chest!
The future has chosen the actions of my King Crimson!
This is the end!
Wha-
What?
Don't tell me this is...!
Is this Requiem rewinding the time that I erased?!
N-No!
Everything is returning to normal!
But my vision still favors me!
Take this, Giorno Giovanna!
Wha-
What is this?
Wh-What am I seeing?
A-Am I dreaming?
Am I witnessing some kind of illusion?
No... that cannot be true.
The only person who can witness erased time is me!
This is... Requiem.
What you are witnessing is indeed the truth.
These are the movements created by your ability...
...but you will never arrive
upon the truth of what will transpire.
None who stand before me
shall ever reach it...
...regardless of their abilities.
This is the power of Gold Experience Requiem.
Even the one who controls me,
Giorno Giovanna, is unaware of this.
Giorno Giovanna!
I won't even allow you
the chance to regret your death!
What am I saying?
I-I...
...never moved to begin with!
Th-The vision I had...
It is the indisputable truth and must transpire!
My invincible King Crimson
should be achieving victory!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Gold Experience Requiem