kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 28  Beneath a Looming Sky
Which means the only signal
Aerosmith is tracking right now...
I would have won...
I would have won for sure, but...
But you had already thrown the scalpels at them...
Boss...
He's down!
Aerosmith shot straight through him!
All right.
I'll go check who it was.
Wait, Abbacchio.
We don't know how many pursuers
are on the beach right now.
Before anything else, I need you to replay the moment
that photo of Trish's mother was taken on this beach fifteen years ago.
It's too dangerous to
stay here longer than necessary.
But there's only one of them on the cliff!
Buccellati, I didn't forget about
the Stand we faced on the plane.
Even though Mista made sure the enemy was dead, we were still attacked.
I won't feel at ease until I know
who's up on that cliff.
Narancia, is the enemy up there dead?
He's still hanging on.
But he's barely breathing.
He hasn't moved a millimeter.
Got it.
Narancia and I will go investigate.
Abbacchio.
Start Moody Blues' replay straight away.
On it.
Whatever happens,
we can't stay here for long.
How much time do you need
to complete the replay?
The event took place fifteen years ago...
...so probably about eight to ten minutes.
Do it in five.
Giorno, Trish, and Mista need to be told to come outside the tortoise, as well.
We're leaving here the moment
Moody Blues' replay discerns the boss's true identity.
Narancia, use Aerosmith to signal for
Giorno and the others to get out here.
You got it!
I finally... figured it out...
Your identity... I...
Before I die...
...show me... your face...
I won't allow this conversation to
continue here any longer, Risotto Nero.
Having Buccellati and the others alerted
to my presence was the last thing I needed.
Having made it this far, you should die
a proud death as the leader of the Hitman Team.
Surely your subordinates
in the afterlife shared that sentiment.
You're going to die at any second.
And Buccellati will be here to investigate shortly.
Before he arrives,
give me back the iron you stole from my body.
In return, I'll end your life.
What could be more disgraceful than dying a slow
and miserable death in front of Buccellati and his men...
...considering they took the lives of your entire team?
They already consider you all pathetic enemies.
I... on't... alo...
What was that?
I couldn't hear you.
Restore my iron immediately, Risotto Nero.
I said... I won't die alone...
Within the chunks of flesh that Aerosmith blew off...
Within the parts of my body that scattered...
Now it's my turn to take advantage of...
...Aerosmith!
Eat lead!
What the hell?
Aerosmith is...
That bastard stuck itself to my Aerosmith!
King Crimson.
I blew away just half a second of time.
Everything within this world
during that span of time has disappeared...
...leaving only the results
following that half second.
Only the result of those bullets
directly hitting you remains.
Well done, Risotto Nero.
You died before you lost your pride.
And as a result,
I remain in the same predicament as before.
This isn't good.
I have to act...
Are you sure, Narancia?
Yeah.
Something made its way into Aerosmith!
Shit!
They're coming...
I have to hide... and find a way...
to replenish my iron...
This is far enough.
We need to assess the situation
carefully from here.
Got it.
It's all right, Buccellati.
He isn't breathing anymore,
and his Stand disappeared.
He's definitely dead.
I shot him in the face,
so I don't think we can figure out who he is anymore.
This man was probably
the leader of the Hitman Team.
How can you tell?
The fact that he came here without any teammates
to back him up means he either had a lot of confidence in himself...
...or everyone on his team was already gone.
And furthermore, he was just killed by another
confident assassin for getting in their way.
Buccellati, are you paying attention?
It was my Aerosmith that turned him into a honeyco-
You're wrong.
You were used.
Someone else was here.
Look at his right foot.
If that were done by Aerosmith,
it would have left burn marks.
But that foot isn't burned at all.
It looks like the wound came
from it being torn off.
But... I'm sure there was only one person on Aero's radar!
I still don't see another signal!
And who would need to do that, anyway?!
My guess is that both sides
underestimated each other...
...and whoever survived
is now badly injured.
Though I'm not sure why
they're hiding their breathing...
Narancia, you sent out a signal for
Giorno and the others to gather, didn't you?
They should already be headed
to the building from the photo.
All right, let's continue our pursuit.
From now on, don't overlook even the smallest
hint of breathing, even if it's from a lizard or a mouse.
The other killer is still nearby.
He's bound to be a dangerous
assassin sent by the organization.
Curses...
To think I would have to endure this hell...
...in my home of Sardinia...
...all because of those traitors!
I'm getting more hits
along the rocks than I expected.
If I increase the sensitivity to pick up things like
frogs and field mice, there's too many signals!
And if I make it too broad...
...I'll still be picking up car exhaust and those tourists breathing.
Shit!
Should I just light this whole place up?
Calm down!
Frogs and field mice will try to
hide behind rocks or in nearby holes.
You can ignore any movements like that.
Look for something trying to get away from us.
Someone trying to get away from us...
I have to hurry...
Abbacchio...
I need to stop his Stand!
I think this is it!
H-Hey, where are Narancia and Buccellati?
I can only see Abbacchio on the beach.
An enemy must have appeared.
The two of them are likely in pursuit.
Abbacchio doesn't seem to have started the replay yet.
Trish recalled that the photo was taken
fifteen years ago in June...
...but she didn't know the exact date or time.
Moody Blues is using its timer to find the exact time.
Once Moody Blues pinpoints that time...
...it will transform into the boss!
Let's go.
Hey, let's play over here!
You're the goalie today.
What?
I don't wanna!
Rock-paper-scissors, then!
Well?
Can you tell them apart?
I found it, Buccellati!
There's just one!
It's about eighty meters to our right!
Wait... It isn't moving very fast...
...but something is headed
toward those tourists!
Narancia, don't attack it right away!
We need to figure out
what we're dealing with first.
They stopped moving!
Buccellati?
Blood?
All right... You, over there!
I'm about to attack you!
If you're unable to fight,
come out from behind the rock.
I promise I won't kill you.
You have until the count of three. Got it?
Three!
You must be up for a fight!
Sticky Fingers!
Hey, come on!
Where were you trying to kick that?
You stink!
Oh, come on!
It's your fault it landed there!
Just shut up and go after it!
You go get it!
It's already the 25th.
June's almost over.
How much longer?
June better be the right month...
June fifteen years ago.
Higher!
Reach up higher!
Throw some rocks at it!
Shake the branches!
Climb up there!
Hey!
Quit yelling, kids!
Go play somewhere else with more space!
We're trying to!
Who even kicked it up there?
Hey!
Stop throwing rocks!
Just reach a bit more!
Jeez, I know!
That's as high as I can go!
Guess it's up to me.
Come on, step aside!
What the hell is this?!
Wait...
Don't attack, Narancia!
He's just a kid!
He's one of the tourists who was on the beach!
Someone stitched his mouth shut
with his own shoe laces!
Only a Stand user could have done this.
They must have switched places with him.
From the looks of it,
he's already lost a lot of blood.
But where did it all go?
What the fuck?!
Where's the asshole who did this?!
How did he just disappear?!
He was almost dying just a second ago!
I don't know...
What's going on?
Thanks!
All right!
C'mon, let's go!
Thanks, mister!
Thanks!
Hey, wait up!
The place of your birth
truly is a special place.
I'm very lucky.
Let's go!
Kick it right this time!
You're the one who kicked it over there!
Who, me?
Leone Abbacchio
Moody Blues
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Uh... What are you doing under there, officer?
Sorry to bother you while you're eating.
I'm conducting an investigation.
I'm looking for fingerprints.
There was a robbery across the street last night.
The victim was struck with a bottle.
The shards went flying everywhere.
But they weren't all on the sidewalk.
The neck of the bottle in particular.
I'm digging through the recycling since we
received word the perpetrator threw something away here.
I should be able to find some prints.
That's what I'm looking for.
You're gonna go through all of that?
Well, it's my job.
Right...
That's true...
Uh, I just...
Yes?
Well... I just wanna know for my own reference.
I'm just curious, but...
What if you don't find anything?
What if there's no fingerprints?
Hell, let's say you do find them...
...and the perp hires a corrupt lawyer
who gets him an innocent verdict...
What keeps you motivated even knowing
that kind of stuff could happen?
Well...
I'm not chasing after the results.
If the result is all that matters to you,
you start taking shortcuts.
And when you take shortcuts,
you start to lose sight of the truth.
It will kill your motivation, too.
I think pursuing the truth is what's most important.
Even if a criminal manages to get away with a crime,
eventually you'll find the truth if you keep trying, right?
Since that's your only goal.
Am I wrong?
I envy you.
I wanted to become a police officer at one point.
Ever since I was a kid,
I wanted to become a respected police officer.
Once upon a time,
I was even motivated like you are.
But I fucked it up.
People like me...
...are just hopeless.
Never seeing things through to the end.
Always fucking up somewhere along the way.
That's not true, Abbacchio.
You've done well.
We share the same motivation.
The motivation you had
when you first became a police officer...
...has now returned to your heart...
...Abbacchio.
H-How...
...do you know my name?
Come to think of it...
...I feel like I've met you before.
Where are you going, Abbacchio?
I'm getting on the bus!
I remember now...
That's right!
I have to go!
I need to get back to my comrades!
Did you already forget, Abbacchio?
You came here on that bus.
This is the last stop.
You can never return.
Y-You're...
That's right! You're...
You're the one who died
because of the bribe I took!
Abbacchio, you've done well.
Yes...
Well enough to make me feel proud of you.
No way...
No way!
Fuck!
No way is this happening!
Hurry up and heal him, Giorno!
I said hurry up and heal him!
Don't make me kick your face in, asshole!
It happened in an instant...
At close range, and in less than a second...
We were too late...
We were too late.
How could someone like Abbacchio...
...let him get that close?
Mista...
Don't let Trish out of the tortoise.
The enemy will likely
strike again to finish off Trish.
We need to leave here immediately.
This is my fault...
We can't gather any more clues
about the boss here.
Wh-What are you saying, Buccellati?
Abbacchio is gonna wake up any second, I'm telling you!
It's just taking a while!
He'll wake up if we wait for him!
Right, Giorno?!
That's what happened before, right?
H-Hey!
That's enough, Narancia!
It's too dangerous here!
You need to call out Aerosmith and survey the area!
What are you talking about, Buccellati?
What the fuck are you talking about?!
I'll kill the enemy
right here and now if he shows his face!
If he's close, I'll face him head-on!
Mista!
And you, too, Giorno?
Hey, Mista!
We have to leave this place, Narancia.
Like Buccellati said!
Wh-What was that?
What did you just say?!
Giorno!
Did you actually even try, you asshole?!
Bring him back!
Do whatever you have to, asshole!
Cut it out, Narancia!
Shut up!
Narancia!
Abbacchio...
Are we just gonna leave him here or what, Buccellati?!
Are we gonna leave Abbacchio all alone?
I don't wanna leave him here by himself!
That was an order, Narancia!
Abbacchio came here fully aware
of what could happen!
We're leaving.
Wait, Buccellati!
That's...
Buccellati, just one moment.
This must mean something.
It has to.
He's holding onto something.
What is it?
It looks like a stone fragment.
It must mean something.
Gold Experience!
Return to where you came from!
Hey, look!
Abbacchio was able to finish the replay!
This is a death mask!
His replay's death mask!
Right before Abbacchio's
Moody Blues disappeared...
...it took the last of its Stand energy
and pressed its transformed face into the stone pillar!
Abbacchio left this for us
in the last moments of his life!
This is the boss's true face!
Abbacchio, you've done well.
Your motivation to seek out the truth...
...has been felt by those who will live on for you.
Nothing is more important than that.
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind
destino