Time, begin anew!
What?
Who are you?!
How long have you been standing there?!
Wait!
Who are you?
What is the shape of that bruise on your neck?
Wh-What is this?
What is going on?
Why did the arrow fall from my hands?
You!
Stop right this instant!
Show me... your... face...
Why am I sitting down?
It must have been on top of the wall where Chariot melted...
Could it be... that arrow...?
M-Mista!
Something's wrong...
Th-This feeling...
It's affecting everyone...
Just what... is happening...?
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
None can escape their chosen fate
Only the result in which you are destroyed remains
This enduring dominance is mine alone to relish in
Sing your sorrowful tune in this world bereft of time
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 34  A Softly Playing Requiem Part 1
Wh-What happened?
Did I fall asleep?
What's... going on?
The sun's already up.
Yeah...
I don't know why,
but it feels like we were sleeping for hours...
Wh-What the hell is this?
What's on my hands?!
Is this blood?
Wh-Why?
Did someone attack us?
Giorno, does it hurt anywhere?
Giorno!
Take cover in the stone walls!
You're a sitting duck right now!
We need to get you healed up if you're hurt!
I-I can't see him from here, but is Giorno hurt?
Hurry up and hide, Giorno!
Wh-Where the hell did Giorno go, anyway?
I can't see him anywhere around here.
Can you tell me where he is, Trish?
If he's hurt, we gotta go help him!
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Nothing you just said makes any sense.
Wha-
Where the hell did these come from?!
H-Hey, what the fuck is going on?
Why do I have these things?!
N-No, wait!
I'm missing something!
It's really gone!
The thing I'm missing is a lot worse!
Hey, Giorno!
How'd you get that blood on your hands, anyway?
What are you looking at?!
I'm talking to you! You!
Y-You're talking to me?
I mean, it kinda caught me off guard,
but even with all this blood it doesn't hurt.
I must have gotten it when the mold attacked me.
I had Giorno heal me,
but I guess the wound didn't close yet...
...so it looks like I'm bleeding
from my shoulder or something.
When the mold attacked?
But you...
What... in the world...
...happened?
Did I fall asleep?
I feel really strange...
Wh-What the...?!
Th-This face...
G-Giorno's body and my body...
No, wait.
It's our souls! Our minds!
Is it possible that while we were sleeping... Me and Giorno... Mista and Trish...
Did our minds leave our bodies and swap places?!
T-This can't be... I... I...
What's wrong with my face?!
This body!
I-I smell!
My armpits...
...smell awful!
H-Hey, get a grip, Trish!
We've got bigger fish to fry here!
We were attacked by a Stand.
The boss's King Crimson sure as hell didn't do this...
Why me? No!
...but for some reason we swapped minds!
Goddammit!
Did the boss send another member of his elite guard to attack us?
No, Narancia.
The boss is already
somewhere near the Colosseum...
...so I doubt he would rely on one of his subordinates.
Mista and Narancia mentioned an attack just now,
but is that what this is?
Only our minds were swapped.
We didn't sustain any injuries.
What could have...?
H-Hey, Giorno...
No matter what happens,
I-I'm still older than you, got it?
Eek!
There's hair growing on my fingers!
My nails are so gross and misshapen!
And they're so dirty!
This is too much for me!
I knew it!
They smell awful, too!
Why?
Why did I have to get Mista?!
H-How am I supposed to know?!
It's probably because we fell asleep next to each other.
Is that seriously what you think of me?
Am I that smelly?
Hey!
Where do you think you're putting your fingers?!
H-Hey, y-you got it all wrong!
I wasn't trying to touch it!
The band was just getting itchy is all!
Don't you dare stick your fingers into my panties!
O-Okay, I won't!
If you spread your legs even a little, I'll kill you.
Okay, I get it!
Not my fault you wore panties that are so tight and itchy
just to make your butt look bigger!
This push-up bra ain't helping, either.
Let me be clear!
If you ever stick your hand up my skirt again, I'll kill you!
I swear to god...
...I'll curse you to death!
Narancia!
That's Giorno, remember?
And kill who? Yourself?
Stop that!
Hey, guys...
Uh, something is weird here.
About Buccellati...
So, me and Giorno swapped,
and Mista and Trish swapped.
If we swapped with whoever was closest to us...
...then who did Buccellati...?
I've been watching him for a while, but he isn't moving.
Is Buccellati okay?
Don't go near him, Narancia!
Huh?
Someone else should be inside of Buccellati, too.
But we don't know who.
Is that what you're saying, Giorno?
This should all be explained by what happened
at the Colosseum before we arrived.
Who was closest to Buccellati?
And what became of the boss and
the man who was waiting for us here at the Colosseum?
Narancia, scout the area with Aerosmith!
I've been trying to, but...
Aerosmith isn't... Something's wrong...
M-My Stand ability...
Come out! Aerosmith!
It's not working!
Aerosmith won't come out!
D-Don't tell me our Stands-
No, Narancia. It's not that.
Look closely.
Aerosmith!
I-It's so fast!
It flew by so fast that I couldn't even see it!
But what the hell?
I dunno what's going on, but I feel way better!
Who knows what's happening, but...
...we're feeling a lot stronger!
My Stand is still with me, but it's like it powered up!
I busted six iron railings in one shot!
My mind is running on overdrive!
Just what kind of Stand ability
is capable of swapping people's minds?
What's the meaning of this?
This Stand user...
I can't imagine this being the case,
but are they our enemy?
Nobody else is nearby.
I can't tell if any of these people are the boss.
Everyone around the Colosseum...
...is still fast asleep.
Even with my radar,
I can't tell how far this is going.
Wait, hold on...
Some of them are starting to move!
A few are even waking up!
Man, that was a sweet dream!
Wh-What the hell is going on?!
I was beating on some lady cop
and even got her handcuffed.
Tweet... Tweet tweet...
So all the people around here got swapped, too?
Yeah, looks like it.
Everyone looks confused as hell.
Christ, this ability is a complete pain in the ass.
Hey, Giorno.
What are you doing?
I should be able to sense
the energy of a soul through the ground.
Yet for some reason, I can't...
Who is this?
Who did Buccellati swap with?
Narancia... Or rather, Giorno...
If you're thinking that the boss
and Buccellati were swapped...
...then let me put your mind at ease.
That didn't happen.
I'm certain that isn't the boss's soul.
If it were him, I would have sensed it.
Though oddly enough,
I can't sense the boss anywhere near here.
Somehow he disappeared.
Buccellati...
So you're saying we won't know
who he is until he's awake?
We can't take our eyes off him until he wakes up.
It hurts...
Our enemy here is Diavolo, and him alone.
Understand?
I-It hurts...
Please listen to me, Narancia... No...
Are you Giorno Giovanna?
Gold Experience!
No... I'm not talking to you from inside the tortoise.
It's me. I'm the one talking.
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff.
I'm the one who arranged to
meet you here at the Colosseum...
...but Diavolo backed me into a corner,
and I could no longer fulfill my promise.
Who Swapped With Who
Mista
Trish
Giorno
Narancia
Buccellati
Tortoise
Polnareff
Who the hell is this guy?
Who's "Polnareff"?
Let me speak my piece first...
I only did this because Diavolo
left me with no other choice.
This strange phenomenon
affecting all of you right now...
...is the result of the arrow's power
that I was supposed to give to you.
In order for me to tell you this,
I've been desperately clinging to my soul...
The arrow?
So you're saying the arrow is responsible for this?
To be more precise, it's because my Stand,
Silver Chariot, took hold of the arrow.
My body up those stairs is already dead.
The only reason I was able to swap souls
with this tortoise and survive is because of the arrow.
There really is someone up here!
It's some dead guy
who got knocked out of his wheelchair!
Only my body is there?
Where's Diavolo?
Hey! If what you're telling us is true...
...then your Chariot can turn us back to normal, right?
No... I don't have the power
to control Chariot or make it disappear.
I'm not even sure where it is right now.
Chariot has essentially gone berserk.
Your own Stand went berserk?
How irresponsible can you-
No. More importantly,
what's going on with the boss?
What happened to him?
Where is Diavolo right now?
I don't know.
Diavolo was right in front of me, but he disappeared.
All of you, heed my words.
The arrow is not your enemy,
nor is it your friend!
Simply put, I'm about to explain your only hope!
Such a trivial, trivial coincidence occurred two years ago.
While I was still clinging to dear life after being
incapacitated by Diavolo, I hid in a small farm village.
That's where this trivial occurence happened.
The arrow we had retrieved in Egypt
fell between the wall and a piece of furniture.
It was such an insignificant thing.
For most people, it would have been simple
to reach behind the furniture and pick it up.
But with my body, it was an arduous task.
I considered leaving it there,
but then I realized Chariot could retrieve it for me.
That's when it happened.
Chariot hurt its finger on the arrow.
It was a complete coincidence.
The arrow draws out a Stand from those with potential.
But beyond that, if the arrow pierces a Stand...
I don't know how old that arrow is...
...but I had begun to understand
what the person who created it was thinking.
Stand power can reach even greater heights!
Far beyond anything we've witnessed!
Suddenly, birds began falling out of the sky...
...bugs hid beneath leaves,
and cattle laid down on the ground.
Even stranger, the farmers fell asleep on the road.
I felt a bit unsettled,
but a much bigger change had happened to Chariot.
Something about it felt off,
so I immediately took the arrow away...
...before it could go berserk.
And as if nothing ever happened,
everything returned to normal.
That's when I realized that
if someone powerful were to use this arrow...
...they would gain the ability to control
the minds of all living creatures!
But as of right now,
I don't have that kind of power...
And that's why I waited...
...for people like you, who were searching for Diavolo's true identity, to appear.
Though in the end, I was no match for Diavolo.
So this controlling minds thing...
Is that what's going on right now?
It just swapped our souls?
No.
Remember when I said that this
was just a part of its power?
I can't control it,
so I couldn't see its potential beyond that.
But it definitely exists!
Claim the arrow!
Stop Chariot before the boss, then claim the arrow!
The only way to defeat King Crimson...
...is for you to master the arrow's power!
So in order to take back the arrow,
you're telling us to kill Chariot.
Am I wrong to assume as much?
Do what you must.
Once you take the arrow,
Chariot will be destroyed regardless.
Besides, I've already been defeated.
There's one other unbelievable and
important thing that I need to tell you.
Are you the girl called Trish?
Yes, though my knuckles
are a bit hairier than normal...
I see...
The boss is a duo.
Earlier there was a kid who was somehow able to
disguise himself as you and trick Buccellati.
Diavolo and this kid acted
as a well-coordinated team.
What?
B-But how?
That's impossible.
The boss trusts no one.
That's how he kept his identity a secret for so long.
I'm not sure what happened, either...
But I'm sure there was a mysterious kid.
If not for that kid,
I never would have let Diavolo get so close to me.
Two... So the boss is a duo?
What's...?
Giorno!
Something's moving!
Nine o'clock. Uno signal.
It's a person!
There's a person running towards the gate on the right!
H-He's...!
That face!
The boss!
No... Diavolo!
Narancia...
Get Aerosmith behind him...
Wait, Giorno!
The left!
Look at the shadow on the left!
There it is!
That's my Stand, evolved by the arrow...
Chariot Requiem!
He's...!
Th-This is bad!
Diavolo was looking for Chariot!
He's trying to get the arrow!
Wait, Giorno!
Don't attack just yet!
That Stand!
It's Sticky Fingers!
Th-That's Buccellati!
It's Buccellati's...
...soul!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
A Softly Playing Requiem
Part 2