By the time you healed me, my life...
...had already ended.
What?!
Above us!
It's a helicopter!
They're trapped now.
Now whoever Buccellati and his team
had intended to meet in Rome...
...will be eliminated by Green Day.
We need to take care of him
before the mold reaches the Colosseum!
Buccellati...
...we can leave the man
beneath the ground to you, right?
Go, Giorno!
Hurry, Mista!
All right!
Let's go, Giorno!
Whatever happens...
...I'll deal with you first...
Buccellati...
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 31  Green Day and Oasis Part 2
Buccellati...
You never should have ambushed me back in that village...
I won't fall for your tricks again...
How dare you pull a blast one on me?!
No, wait a sec...
"Last one...?" No, hold on...
It's not "past one", either...
A vast one...? A cast one...?
A fast one?
I know what I meant!
You some kind of language teacher?!
Y-Y-You jerk!
Oh yeah... I was supposed to film this...
Shouldn't take long to take care of you.
Let's see...
Sticky Fingers!
H-He's...
This speed and strength...
I-If we're doing this... one-on-one...
...I won't even need to dive into the ground.
Th-This ability...
It outclasses my Sticky Fingers...
...in both speed and strength!
It's recoil...
He's hitting the ground with his elbows.
By making the ground elastic,
he can use the recoil to strengthen his blows!
That's why he's fast!
It's just like a boxer using
the ring's ropes to their advantage!
Oasis!
Take this!
I don't have time!
I knew it...
The mold won't grow on you even though you fell...
Cioccolata's Green Day kills anything that's alive.
What's up with your body?
Since it doesn't work on you for some reason,
I'll just have to beat you to a lifeless pulp...
...w-w-with my Oasis!
Giorno Giovanna!
He's the new guy if I recall.
His ability is to imbue objects with life.
The bullets that missed...
They must have spawned this plant
that grabbed the helicopter!
They're coming...
Do they think I'm a fool?
Your life energy is
no match for my Green Day!
I'll rot your vines to dust!
We're taking this helicopter up, Green Day!
Keep spreading mold!
We're breaking free of the vines!
Wh-What?!
I can't take off!
The helicopter won't move!
Th-This is bad!
Good!
It's more or less fully grown!
It's turned into a tree!
That helicopter won't be flying anytime soon.
Mista!
Climb up with me to the helicopter!
Don't need to, Giorno.
It's well within range of my bullets.
Yee-haw!
Go, Pistols!
His brain is the target!
Huh?!
Mista!
The guys're saying he's not in the helicopter!
Where'd he go?!
What's going on?!
He can't be hiding from us!
And he couldn't have left!
Let's find him, guys!
Find hi-
Number Two!
Number Three!
N-Not good!
Mista, hurry and call them back! Hurry-
Mista!
Number Two! Number Three!
What happened to you?!
N-No way!
Why isn't he here?
Stands should only have one ability!
He has the ability to attack living things
with mold if they go lower than they were before.
He shouldn't be able to do this!
Get out of here, Number One...
Number Six! Seven!
We can't... beat this guy...
Hurry up and get out of the helicopter!
He's...
...too dangerous!
Mista!
Hurry up and call your Pistols back!
Undo your Stand ability!
I can't... They won't come back...
He captured my Pistols...
I-I underestimated him...
Mista!
I'll bring 'em back!
I'll bring 'em all back here!
No, that would be pointless, Number Five.
He's holding the wounded Pistols hostage...
...since he knows Mista won't be able to
recover until he recalls his Stand.
I can't heal him.
N-No...
I can only assume he's waiting for you in there.
If he manages to defeat you,
the last of the Pistols, Mista will die.
It turns out we're going to have to fight him directly!
Mista!
I'm leaving Trish and Narancia here.
Okay...
I'm counting on you!
Mista! Mista...
Follow him... Number Five.
Back Giorno up...
Take this bullet...
Okay...
I can feel life energy...
Why couldn't the Pistols find him?
I can't pinpoint his exact location,
but he's still inside the helicopter.
So knowing that...
Gold Experience!
I didn't feel any resistance.
What is he doing?
How is he hiding in here?
Medical supplies?
He's a doctor?
The damage caused by the mold...
...is spreading toward the Colosseum!
I'm running out of time...
Our plan will fail unless I defeat him soon!
Th-The enemy is...
Come to me, Number One!
Stay away, Giorno!
It's a trap!
Muda!
What?!
Wh-What was that thing?
Giorno, be caref-
Giorno!
Curiosity...
...is the most important
contributor for mental growth.
I've never been as grateful as I am right now
for the human experimentation I did as a child.
I carefully observed which parts of the human body I could sever while keeping the subject alive...
And of course, I'm well aware which veins I need to close in order to prevent myself from bleeding out.
If I cover the places I've severed with Green Day's mold,
I can still move despite being in pieces...
...and hide in cramped spaces.
You can't fall, Giorno!
If you go any lower,
the mold's gonna get you!
G-Giorno!
Oasis
Secco
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Hurry and climb up!
You've had times in your life where you felt truly happy, haven't you, Giorno Giovanna?
I believe that there are two circumstances
which bring about happiness.
The first is when despair is replaced with hope.
That will make you happy.
When your plant grabbed onto the helicopter...
...I felt true panic from the danger of the situation.
I was overwhelmed with despair.
But I persevered.
I turned that despair around
with my experience and mental strength.
And now I couldn't feel happier.
Gold Exp-
Don't even try getting up here!
Giorno!
Did you already forget my legs were still hiding?
The second circumstance that brings about true happiness...
...is looking down upon someone in utter despair!
I win!
Before you even hit the ground...
...the mold will dissolve your body into a fine powder!
Giorno, take this!
Jump back in, Giorno!
Get back into the helicopter!
Grazie, Number Five!
Let him have it!
What a foolish move.
This won't change the outcome at all, Giorno Giovanna...
The outcome where I, Cioccolata, emerge victorious!
The branch you just grew is alive!
Meaning if it drops even a little bit...
...my mold will consume it!
Jump for the helicopter, Giorno!
Hurry!
Giorno!
I did it!
Now, show me that expression!
Show me your despair!
Let me see the moment you
lose hope and die in all its glory!
Show me your despair
as you fall to your doom!
Bene!
I found the perfect angle to hit the propellers.
The mold destroyed the branch since it was alive.
However...
...the segment of the branch
that fell from its root no longer holds life.
It's just a piece of wood.
Since you destroyed it,
the wood reverted back to a bullet.
By the way, your idea of happiness
that you kept droning on about...
I can't say seeing you in despair
has made me feel happy.
I've had the upper hand
against you from the beginning.
Y-You did it!
I can't believe it, Giorno!
You barely made it!
You beat him before the mold reached the Colosseum!
Please take care of Mista's wounds, Giorno!
That was a close one!
Now the rest of the Pistols will be back, too!
Could you move just a bit to the right, Number Five?
Huh?
I may just be paranoid, but...
Was your name Cioccolata?
I may be wrong...
...but you're just playing dead, aren't you?
I know what you're thinking...
Giorno?
You think if you can move your body
just a few centimeters before I reach you...
...you can fall off the ledge and escape.
You'll be able to reactivate the mold...
...and have won this fight. I can tell.
Indeed... To tell you the truth,
my right lung has been punctured.
My subclavian vein has been severed.
Four of my ribs, my right humerus,
and my right hand bones have all been shattered.
I'm honestly not sure how quickly I can reach you.
But my Stand is Gold Experience.
It's a close-range power type
with a range of two meters.
Given just one moment,
I can end your life.
H-He's dead!
You shot him through the head!
Perhaps.
I'll merely incapacitate you if you remain still, but I promise I won't go beyond that.
I'm giving you a choice.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to begin climbing now.
Stay the hell away from me!
Look behind you, idiot!
I've taken Mista and the tortoise hostage!
You fool!
While you were busy running your mouth...
...you failed to notice my left arm
sneak up on you from beneath the tree's shadow!
I'm going to sever Mista's neck now!
If you come after me,
Mista will be beyond help!
Mista!
Victory is still mine!
Take this!
It's true.
I ran my mouth to buy some time.
Just enough time for the bullet that
pierced your head to grow and return to your wound.
The piece that remained in your head
lured the bullet and reverted into a stag beetle.
When I aimed for the propellers...
...I imbued the blade with Gold Experience's life force...
...so that I could finish you off for certain, whether you were dead or alive.
B-But you said... th-that if I stayed still...
y-you wouldn't do anything...
Oh, spare me.
Did you really think such a favorable outcome...
...awaited scum like you?
Y-You're a monster!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Wryyyy!
No!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Muda!
Burnable Waste Pickup
Mon, Wed, Fri
Giorno!
Mista's waking up!
Mista! Mista!
What's that doing there?
Is that Cioccolata's...?
Don't tell me...
Was he on his phone during our battle?
But with who?
What did he tell them?
Why, though?
Cioccolata...
Why aren't you picking up?
I'm calling you, but you're not...
Umm, it's flashing...
What's this mean again? Umm...
O-Oh, right!
This thing flashing means I have voicemail!
How many do I have?
Two! When did he call me?
Was it while I was chasing Buccellati?
Secco, it's me.
I-It's Cioccolata!
I finished off the gunslinger, Mista.
Yes!
Now the new guy, Giorno Giovanna,
is attempting to reach the helicopter.
But it doesn't matter. I've won.
Concentrate on Buccellati.
I'll give you a back scratch when I return.
I bet you'd like some sugar cubes, too, wouldn't you?
I'll toss you some.
You deserve it.
How many would you like?
Umm... Uh...
Two?
No! I want more! More! More!
Just kidding! I have five for you!
I'll toss five at once.
Can you catch them all in your mouth? No hands!
Listen well, Secco...
Together, we're invincible.
It's the right of the strong
to rule over the feeble and weak.
No, it's their duty to rule over them. It's destiny!
That even includes the boss.
I plan on taking down the boss during this battle.
You're going to do this, too, Secco.
You're strong!
Giorno's here. I need to hang up.
You know...
...I love you, Secco.
Let's go.
Now that I've made it this far,
surely the underground man...
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Green Day and Oasis Part 3