kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 26  A Little Story From the Past ~My Name Is Doppio~
This is a little story from the past.
Summer, 1965
It all began during the summer of 1965.
Prisoner 696!
What's the matter with you?!
Did you eat something spoiled?
She's pregnant?!
This is a women's prison on a remote island.
The inmates and guards are all women!
Not to mention this prisoner...
...was sentenced to ten years
for bank robbery and assault.
She's been doing time here for two years!
Push! Just a little more!
When could she have become pregnant?
She didn't look this far along earlier today!
But now...
Hey, prisoner!
Just who exactly is this kid's dad?
He's... dead!
For more than... two years now!
That's bullshit!
You'd have an easier time convincing me
you grew a barnacle in your knee.
Looks like the baby made it...
Yes... But something's not right...
His eyes have been open
since the moment he was born.
And he isn't crying at all.
This should go without saying,
but we can't raise a child here.
We'll find him a home.
Where are you from?
Sar...di...nia...
A priest from a small village
on the island took the baby in.
Time passed in the blink of an eye, and the boy gained a reputation for being cowardly and a bit slow as he grew up.
June, 1985
Well, I gotta get going.
Bye bye, Mr. Froggy.
Hey, watch it!
Oh, it's you.
Stay closer to the side, idiot!
And don't tell the priest about this.
Th-That was a close one...
I'm just glad you weren't squished.
Do you like frogs?
I like them, too.
I don't like bugs, though.
Or guys who stink, for that matter.
I don't like anything that isn't pretty.
You from around here?
Y-Yeah...
It's kinda hot,
so would you like to get a drink?
I think...
...I will, actually.
I feel like sparkling water.
Hard water from France.
Your treat, I hope!
You'd like to become a sailor?
Yeah.
Well...
You're certainly a simple man.
That sounds like a perfect fit.
Oh?
He walked all this way?
Good for him.
Perhaps I should buy him a car.
In order to build a garage next to his room...
...the priest began digging into the floor with a pick.
What's this?
A dead body?
No, it's too...
After carefully picking away the surrounding concrete...
...he found a woman underneath.
It was the woman who gave birth
to the boy the priest took in.
Sh-She's alive...
She was incapable of moving or talking,
but somehow she was kept alive.
How many years had it been?
The woman had lost all sense of time.
Hatred? Love?
All that remained in her heart was darkness.
This hair color...
That night, a great fire and strong winds
led to every house in the village burning down.
It's unknown what caused it.
Seven people died, and several others went missing.
On the list of the deceased were the names of the priest and the boy he had taken in.
Olbia, Sardinia
Present Day
C'mon!
Hey, kid! Look out!
I know, you pest.
There's a truck coming, right?
Idiot!
Where the hell do you think you're going, dumbass?!
O-Ouch...
Aww... Ouch...
Misjudged that one...
You appear down on your luck.
Having a rough day?
Or perhaps you've been
experiencing misfortune for much longer.
Sounds about right.
I've had nonstop problem after-
How about I tell you your fortune?
I'll make it cheap.
Huh? Nah, I'll pass...
You call Sardinia your home, do you not?
It's been quite some time
since you were last here, hasn't it?
I'd hardly call that fortunetelling.
One look is all you need
to tell that I'm a traveler.
Anyone could figure that out.
You're... living with a secret.
Light and shadow, exposed and concealed.
You may see it as leading two separate lives.
But due to your unyielding personality and
willingness to use your dark secret to your advantage...
...you have enjoyed an endless streak of victories.
What do you mean?
Oh, please forgive my rudeness.
You possess a quality that would compel
any fortune teller to want to tell you your fortune.
Please, allow me to do it for you!
I'll make it 20,000... no, 10,000 lire.
Everyone has at least a few little secrets.
Aren't you just saying things that could apply to anyone?
You're looking for someone.
You're currently looking for
someone very important to you.
Come on...
Everyone spends their lives looking for someone.
A beautiful girlfriend or a good friend...
But I have to admit it feels good
for someone to read me so well.
How do you tell fortunes?
With that crystal ball?
No... I began telling your fortune much earlier.
I could tell simply by the shape
of the mud stain on your pants.
It's been said for thousands of years
that in Romani fortunetelling...
...the strongest conclusions are derived by studying shapes formed by chance.
That is the symbol of your fate!
Your daughter...
Yes.
The person you seek is your very own daughter.
You returned to Sardinia to find the child
of the woman you left fifteen years ago...
Huh?
No... That can't be right...
You're rather young...
I know what I just said, but this is very odd...
Whose child? Mine?
But you have one. I'm sure of it.
Let me see your palm!
Hey!
Please!
My pride as a fortuneteller is at stake here!
Let go of my hand... Don't touch me...
I won't make you pay!
In fact, I'll pay you!
20,000... No, I'll pay you 100,000 lire!
Please!
You're getting on my nerves!
Hands off!
What good will it do for you, huh?!
Especially now that I'm going to kill you!
Your face... Your age...
You... do not seem to be a Stand user.
You built your business with the wisdom to see people for who they truly are.
Nothing could have brought you greater misfortune.
Those who know even a hint of my true nature cannot be allowed to exist in this world.
Though you've demonstrated to me
that you are a skilled fortuneteller.
I will respect that skill by giving you
a quick and painless death.
But I must ask you something first.
This man is named Risotto.
He has betrayed me.
He's searching for my daughter
in order to uncover my true identity.
Tell me where he is at this exact moment.
Where he is?
I can't tell that much...
But I'm certain you'll soon encounter him.
He's here in Sardinia...
His heart is filled with vengeance,
and you will certainly encounter him here!
I see. Very well.
That will do.
I knew it! I was right!
Light and shadow, exposed and concealed.
Two personalities!
So long as you hold onto this secret,
the death of others will bring with it good fortune...
...and you will bask in eternal splendor!
What a beautiful palm!
I've never seen a hand like this before!
Huh? This isn't right.
It looks strange, somehow...
The lifeline has completely changed!
I see!
This is my own hand!
It changed before I even realized it!
King Crimson.
You...
I'm so happy you weren't squished!
Crawling around on the sidewalk is dangerous.
Go on, shoo.
Be careful. Go on.
Huh?
Where to, sir?
Costa Smeralda, please.
Gotcha.
Now onto our next story.
We'll be investigating the site of
the crash off the Olbia Coast in Sardinia.
However...
Mr. Driver, do you have a phone
I can use to call someone?
Mine is broken.
Sorry, I don't.
I see...
C-Could you stop for one second, Mr. Driver?
I'll get out here!
This is fine!
I'm fine getting out here.
That's the building.
I'm sure of it.
I just need to keep watch over there.
Sardinia, Costa Smeralda.
For a time, this area was forgotten by history...
...until a millionaire from India became enamored with the sight of the winds meeting the cliffs off the coast and decided to call it his home.
Hey, wait a minute!
There seems to be an extra digit on your meter...
You trying to say I'm ripping you off
by rigging the meter?
You really think I'd do that, huh?
N-No... But 800,000 lire to go
from the city to here seems a bit...
...I just can't afford it.
Like hell a tourist can't afford it!
I know you hid something
in your pocket earlier.
You hid an envelope in your pants.
Don't...
Come on, cough it up!
Don't touch me... I-I'm getting a headache...
See? I knew it!
You idiot!
Those who bear witness to that which should remain unseen
cannot be allowed to continue existing in this world!
Y-You fucking...
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Hey... Did you hear that phone ringing just now?
Huh?
Where did it come from?
Hey! I asked you a question!
That phone is too busted up to have been ringing!
H-Hell if I know!
What are you-
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Ring ring ring!
There it is again!
Where is it?
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Hey, why didn't you say something?
You have a car phone!
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Hello?
Yes, this is Doppio.
Boss!
Yes, I just arrived.
It's the place from the photo.
I just need to keep watch here, right?
Huh? I don't need to eliminate the driver
since he didn't see what was in the envelope?
If I may interject, Boss...
...I'm fairly sure he saw the photo
you told me not to show to anyone.
R-Right. I apologize, Boss.
Yes, I'm about to start watching the building.
You're about to start watching the building?
No, my Doppio!
Slowly, but surely, look to your right.
Don't make any sudden moves.
The only thing being watched right now...
...is you, Doppio.
Th-That's... Risotto!
The traitorous hitman!
He appeared just like the fortuneteller said!
Apparently, because of the plane crash...
...he learned of the existence of
the photo at Trish's house in Sardinia.
He must be eliminated first.
Otherwise, he'll interfere when Trish arrives.
I will be the one to finish him off...
...but you must get close to him
without revealing who you are.
Risotto's ability is a mystery to me, as well.
Drag him out so that he gets
within two meters of you.
At that range, King Crimson will surely eliminate him.
I believe in you.
I'm hanging up, my Doppio.
Yes, I understand, Boss.
Click!
What's this?
My head... really hurts...
O-Oh, yeah.
Now isn't the time to worry about a headache!
I just finished talking to the boss!
My mission is to keep an eye on that building and... uh...
What was it again?
Get closer?
Right!
I have to get closer!
But to what?
I won't go anywhere near you.
Look this way.
Wh-What the...?!
I... feel like I've seen him before...
Wh-Who is he again?
Move your hand.
I can't see your face.
I-I don't have any money!
B-Blood!
Why does this always happen to me?!
I must have imagined it.
The ignorance and fear in his expression aren't an act.
He wouldn't be acting like this if he were from Passione.
Not to mention, he's more unguarded than a baby.
He must be a civilian.
Please don't!
Quit screaming.
I'm just picking up my knife.
I don't care about you anymore.
I-I don't feel so good...
My head hurts...
T-Two meters...
That's right...
There was one thing you did
that seemed like an act...
When you fell...
...you reflexively hid the envelope
so I wouldn't see it, didn't you?
It's right under your left shoe, isn't it?
What are you hiding?
I'll leave if I'm satisfied with what I see.
What's your problem?
I-I don't have any money!
Just let me go!
I didn't sense any murderous intent or hostility, but your expression just now seemed faked.
Stand up, move your left leg, and show me.
I told you to stand up!
Stand up!
Oh, it's just an envelope.
Looks like it's empty.
Your trembling certainly isn't an act...
...and I can tell you're a coward who's incapable of lying.
But now... I'm even more interested in you.
You're definitely a Stand user.
You heard that sound, too, didn't you?
Just now, you glanced at the source of the sound.
That's the sound of scouting.
Something is scouting this area.
That sound and shape...
...is Aerosmith!
They're finally here!
And who are you to show up
to such an important location?
It must mean the boss
has complete trust in you!
But at the same time,
you clearly have true fear in your heart!
You're a walking contradiction!
Shut the hell up!
You're the one who's about to be shaking in your boots!
I see...
Since you're running at me,
you must be a close-ranged power type.
Your range is about two or three meters.
As long as I know that, I can kill you.
What... the... M-My throat!
Th-These are...
...actual razor blades?!
T-Two meters, dammit!
I'll take these razor blades
and shove them right up your ass!
I just said I know how to kill you.
Impossible!
I'm not done yet, dammit!
H-He disappeared?
That's his...
That's his hitman ability...
But how...?
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
I can hear a phone ringing somewhere!
I can't believe it!
By complete coincidence,
there happens to be a payphone here!
Click!
Beep!
Hello?!
My Doppio...
Wh-Where are you, Boss?
Are you nearby?
Please come quickly if you are!
I cannot.
I am unable to join you
until you get close enough to him.
This will all be for naught
if he's able to see me and escape.
B-But...
You must get closer!
You need to be within two meters of Risotto.
Boss!
I don't know what his ability is!
He could attack me again at any second!
Doppio...
Oh, Doppio...
My precious Doppio...
Have you already forgotten that I gave you a portion of my King Crimson's ability?
Now is the time to use it!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
King Crimson vs. Metallica