yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 21  The Mystery of King Crimson
Ugh, Narancia!
Are you seriously trying to eat
all the chocolates behind our backs?!
Give 'em back!
I spent my own money on them,
so give 'em back!
Narancia, I swear...
There's only three left!
Selfish bastard.
We're all hungry and want some, too!
The ladybug brooch is moving from the top of the tower.
I can feel it.
It's headed down to the charnel house
to try to cross through here.
Buccellati must have planted the brooch somewhere on the boss's clothes.
Giorno, if you don't mind,
could you grab me a water?
I'm thirsty.
Also, watch what you're doing.
We were ordered not to set foot on the island.
You should stay on the boat.
Right.
Huh? Eh?
D-Did you eat them, Mista?!
Cough 'em up, asshole!
What the hell did you get on your cheek?
Huh?
Ah!
Don't "Ah" me, you jerk!
S-So sweet!
When did you even stuff them in your mouth?
Come to think of it,
did I thank you yet, Giorno?
For getting the water for me.
This situation... is bizarre...
I'm unsure what it is...
...but something feels off.
Hey, idiot!
Was your head up your ass when the boss told us not to set foot on the is-
...land?
This isn't normal!
Something strange is afoot!
This is bad! Buccellati!
Where the hell are you going, Giorno?!
Giorno?
Buccellati!
Yes, I know he's on the move.
I know exactly where the brooch
you put on the boss's body is.
Right now, he's at the bottom of the stairs
leading to the charnel house.
He's right near the pillar that's
about two meters away from the stairs.
But wait, Buccellati!
Something tells me... you're in trouble!
Buccellati, your mission to escort Trish...
...has come to an end.
Y-You conniving...
For him to purposely try to restrain my arm...!
Sticky Fingers!
But... King Crimson...
...has already...
I see you.
I know where you're moving.
I can see your every move toward the future!
Within the domain of King Crimson's ability, all time is erased.
Not a single human besides myself can recall
where and how they moved within this time.
Even the clouds in the sky remain
unaware that they've broken apart.
If a flame is extinguished,
it will not perceive the moment it was snuffed out.
Only the results of this world remain.
In a world where time is erased,
every move is rendered useless!
Only I alone can react to these moves.
I can see every single move you intend to make!
That is King Crimson's ability!
Th-This ability...
No matter what kind of person you are...
...you'll experience ups and downs in life.
You win some, you lose some.
But if you witness the pitfalls open up right before your eyes,
ergo the future, and choose to avoid them...
...you will never incur another loss for the rest of your life.
You will experience unending pleasure.
Don't you agree? Well?
Now that we've met in person,
I know for certain we're related.
Without a doubt in my mind,
I can sense that you are truly my daughter.
Which means...
...if you were conscious at this very moment,
you would sense it, too!
Trish...
I must avoid any pitfalls along my path!
The time has come to sever
the blood tie that bonds us!
Trish!
Wh-What?!
It's Giorno!
Giorno's Gold Experience's ability...
He planted the tortoise's cells
in the brooch and imbued it with life...
...which gave birth to a tortoise with a Stand ability.
After our call was interrupted,
he must have sensed danger and activated his ability.
He always gives me courage...
I didn't think I could move anymore,
but... I'm not finished.
I have to...
...go on for a bit longer...
My mission has come to an end?
Boss, you're wrong.
It's far from over!
As for Trish...
I order myself to protect her!
If he can read any attack I throw at him...
...and I can't even perceive when he's dodged them...
...then his ability is more powerful than I could have imagined.
Even so!
His ability doesn't allow him to
read movements for very long!
It seems to have a short duration.
Perhaps five to ten seconds.
Distance...
For now, I need to put distance between us!
Enough distance so that the boss can't catch up to Trish!
My battered body, please move!
Giorno afforded me this chance...
I need to escape from the basement at the very least...
So there's another traitor among you.
It must be the new recruit.
If my intel is accurate,
his name is Giorno Giovanna.
I suppose he must have joined my organization
with the intent to betray me from the beginning.
You seem to have thought you could escape merely by putting distance between us...
...but escaping from the tortoise
the instant before it was swept away was trivial.
Your efforts appear to have been for naught, Buccellati.
How can you still move?
Is it pure force of will?
A moment's rest won't be enough for you to reach the first floor,
but it should be plenty to make it to the afterlife.
To start with, I'm going to eliminate Trish.
Don't you dare move, Buccellati!
The chance Giorno afforded me wasn't for nothing!
If success here hinges on who reads the other's moves...
...then I've already won by reading yours!
I figured that before you were swept into the sewer...
...you would probably use your ability to escape!
Now, Sticky Fingers!
King Crimson!
Th-That was close...
But within King Crimson's domain...
...whether or not your actions were futile changes nothing!
Take this!
You're finished!
My attack wasn't aimed at you!
It was aimed at the pillar!
Zip up!
What?!
As I thought...
Your ability is invincible...
But it's clear now that you can
only read movements for a short time.
You're not reading ahead of time!
Go ahead and try to read my future movements, Boss.
Try to figure out what I'm going to do in a few seconds.
Try to look beyond time!
If you succeed,
you'll have seen that I make it to the first floor.
Buccellati! Trish!
This wound...
What happened in the basement?
Where's the boss?
He wouldn't have fled.
He must be close.
I don't know the full situation,
but the boss will never let Buccellati go after this!
Buccellati...
N-No...
Buccellati!
His pulse...
I-It can't be! It's gone!
I replaced his damaged organs and stopped the bleeding!
Buccellati, please breathe!
That must be Giorno Giovanna.
His unknown ability gave Buccellati
the chance to escape.
However...
...neither of them will make it any farther!
This can't be!
I'm sure I made new organs!
There's no reason his heart shouldn't be beating!
Giorno, it's me.
Call Abbacchio and the others.
Get out of here.
That voice...
I just told you to call Abbacchio and the others...
Get out of here!
Leave this church!
Hurry!
B-Buccellati!
Th-Thank goodness!
You're alive!
Hurry!
Hurry up and call the others!
B-But we haven't...
There's no way we can uncover
the boss's identity right now!
We need to get out of here, Giorno!
While we still have distance from him!
They're within my range!
It's over!
I'll explain later!
Hurry up, Giorno!
Gold Experience!
I see Giorno over there!
Hey, what the fuck, Giorno?
Get over here!
How are you gonna make up for
defying orders and stepping foot on the island?
Buccellati's here, too!
H-How the hell did you get so beat up?!
Why are you coming back with Trish?
What's the meaning of this, Buccellati?
I'll explain later.
Right now, we need to get out of here as soon as possible.
Buccellati, I commend you.
I commend your excellent decision making skills.
Even though I possess the ability to eliminate time...
...if I were to face six Stand users at once,
I would be unable to avoid exposing myself to at least one of them.
For the time being...
...they've managed to escape my King Crimson.
But this is far from over.
I will never...
...let them escape from Venice!
Now I understand not only how the boss has
reigned supreme, but why he's so feared.
We can't defeat the boss... Not now.
Either we have to uncover his identity...
...or a weakness in his ability...
...assuming it even has one.
King Crimson
Is this...?
What the hell's going on, Buccellati?
We deserve an explanation.
What the hell are you doing?
All right.
I'll just come out and say it.
I won't go into detail since
we're still in danger and don't have much time.
The reason I brought Trish back here
is because I just betrayed the boss.
This is where we'll part ways.
If you choose to act alongside me,
you, too, will be branded as traitors.
Wh-What?
I-I don't think I heard you right...
Wh-What did you just say?
He said... he betrayed the boss...
Wh-Why?
I probably shouldn't tell you more...
...since none of you are involved in this.
I think it would be best if you explained.
Some of them may choose to follow you.
We need allies we can trust.
Giorno, what the fuck is your deal?
First you go inside the church without permission, and now...
Buccellati!
What's wrong?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I feel a bit faint from the blood I've lost...
That shouldn't be possible...
His blood should have been replenished
after I replaced his organs.
Did I miss a wound?
I guess I've just used a lot of energy...
Does he not feel pain?
I didn't see any blood come from his wound, either.
Am I seeing things?
I'm sorry.
You freaked me out for a second!
Seriously.
Buccellati, please...
Yeah, Buccellati.
We want to know the details.
The boss had us act as bodyguards
so he could kill his daughter with his own two hands.
He's afraid someone could uncover his identity
through his blood relation with Trish.
Once I figured this out, I...
I couldn't forgive him.
I couldn't come back here and feign ignorance.
That's why I betrayed him!
How could you?
Are you crazy, Buccellati?
There's no way you're not aware of what happens
to traitors after they've made themselves known.
The boss has never let anyone get away!
Hell, Venice could already be
surrounded by the boss's elite guard!
You're right.
Which is why I'm going to need help.
If any of you are willing to accompany me...
...come down these stairs and get on the boat.
However, this is not an order.
I don't expect any of you to come.
This was my decision to make.
None of you are obligated to join me.
This may come off as arrogant,
but I'm going to say it anyway.
I did this because I know I'm right.
I have no regrets.
In spite of the state of the world we live in,
I want to follow a path I know is right.
We just need to find his weakness...
Though I'm fleeing for now,
I will defeat the boss, no matter what.
I will find his weakness, no matter what!
I understand your reasoning,
and I'll admit that you did the right thing, Buccellati...
...but I'm going to be blunt with you.
It pains me to say it,
but none of us will step on that boat with you.
How could you let your
emotions get the better of you?
I may be in your debt,
but that doesn't mean I'm going to accompany you.
You've lost sight of reality.
No one can survive in this world on ideals alone.
We can't survive without the organization.
Fugo's absolutely right.
You've pretty much committed suicide.
No matter where in the world you run,
you'll never find peace.
Besides, I've only pledged my loyalty to the organization.
I didn't pledge a damn thing to you.
That said...
I've never had a place where I belonged or could call home.
The only time I've felt at ease...
...is while I've been with you, Buccellati.
Abbacchio...
Y-You can't be serious, Abbacchio!
If somehow we figure out how to kill the boss...
...considering my skills...
...I'd say I'm next in the running to become a capo!
Buccellati's a smart guy.
He's the kind of guy who won't
pick a fight he knows he can't win.
We're gonna strike it rich for sure!
Mista! Not you, too!
Fugo, what are you gonna do?
You've all... l-lost your minds!
We're going to be completely isolated!
Wh-Where are you going to run to?!
Worse yet,
you probably won't even make it out of Venice alive!
Narancia, what are you going to do?
I-I... d-don't know...
Hey, Buccellati...
What should I do?
Should I go with you?
Are you afraid?
Yeah... I-I'm really scared...
B-But just give me the order!
Your order will give me the courage to do it!
Nothing can scare me as long as
you order me to do it!
No.
This is one thing I can't order you to do.
You need to decide for yourself.
You need to forge your own path.
B-But I don't know what to do!
I seriously don't!
I'll warn you right now...
Don't come, Narancia.
You aren't cut out for this.
Are you sure about this?
You're all going to die.
There are things in this world that
you just can't change, even if you're right.
Our line of work has always been questionable.
How was this any different?
While I agree, I need to be true to myself.
Let's go!
Once this boat has left port, we'll all be traitors!
Why?
You're all out of your minds!
All this for a woman you just met
and have hardly spoken to!
You don't even know what kind of music she likes!
Trish was abandoned by the people she trusted...
I was abandoned before, too...
I was abandoned by my dad
and my most trusted friends...
I'm pretty much just like her...
It's none of our business what
the boss does with his daughter!
I'm pretty much just like Trish!
Giorno, hand me the tortoise.
Let's put Trish inside it.
Of course.
Buccellati, please turn around.
Buccellati!
I'm coming! I'm coming, too!
I wanna go with you!
Don't order me not to come along!
Trish is me! And I'm Trish!
The wound on her arm is my wound!
Narancia... Not you, too...
You fool... You're going to be killed...
I can't condone
such a foolish betrayal.
I won't be a righteous idiot...
Took you long enough
to make up your mind!
You better not hold this
against us later on.
Narancia, I highly respect your courage.
I guess Fugo really isn't coming...
Well, that was his choice to make.
Buccellati!
I... I want to protect Trish!
I'll defeat the boss with you!
I know.
Squalo?
We have some traitors that need dealing with... in Venice.
The traitors' names are Bruno Buccellati and Giorno Giovanna.
The boss's identity: Unknown
Stand name: King Crimson
Has the ability to erase a certain amount of time.
Because of this, he can predict the future. Invincible.
They can be taken dead or alive.
Boss's orders!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind
Determinazione