So that's where... you were... Boss...
You... were there...
In that body...
The moment I started feeling tired
and my soul began leaving my body...
...you said you had to go
since things weren't going well...
You were right...
If you're there, Boss...
...I know for sure that we'll win.
But...
...I feel so alone...
Will you... call me again...
...like you always have?
Boss...
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
None can escape their chosen fate
Only the result in which you are destroyed remains
This enduring dominance is mine alone to relish in
Sing your sorrowful tune in this world bereft of time
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 36  Diavolo Rises
Mista!
Hurry up and pierce your Stand with this arrow!
What?
Requiem just started charging at us!
Giorno!
Stop Requiem!
I can't!
It's too far away!
Wha-
My gun...
What's going on, Mista?!
It's because he's touching the arrow!
No way!
Why did it...?
Let go of it, Mr. Polnareff!
Let go of the arrow!
Glad I took that cop's Beretta, just in case.
But what the hell, Pistols?
Why did my revolver break out of nowhere?
M-Maybe the boss got close?
Idiot!
Think before ya run yer mouth, Number Five!
You sayin' you saw someone get close to us
in this big open space?
None of us saw anyone when the revolver broke!
The metal's worn down!
He's been using it too much recently!
The cylinder axis broke!
We haven't had time to do any
maintenance or inspections!
H-Hey!
What the hell is this thing's problem?
It's going right for m-me!
No, Mista.
It's coming for me.
Even though it has the arrow back...
Gold Experience!
Requiem plans to end me
since I touched the arrow...
Run, Mista!
Reload, Pistols!
Reload the gun!
This isn't a revolver!
We need another cartridge!
It's gonna take time!
I-It's no use...
I'm done for...
I'm throwing him!
Giorno, catch!
I'm gonna toss you the tortoise!
Mr. Polnareff!
You okay, Mr. Polnareff?
He's okay. B-But... how?
Mista, do you remember what
I said back at the Colosseum?
I said that Requiem's ability
had potential even I wasn't aware of.
But I'm beginning to understand it.
Requiem stopped because the time has come.
The time?
Yes...
I can tell because...
...my body has started to change!
That's why it stopped trying to kill me!
This is the true reason Requiem went berserk!
The ability to force living beings to swap souls;
ergo, the ability to turn them into something else!
The prelude has ended,
now the main piece is beginning to play...
...which is why it gave up on killing me!
4.5 billion years' worth of history
of the creatures of the world...
...is about to be overwritten in just a few short hours!
All of it!
I see...
So this is the true terror of Requiem.
But even so...
Thanks to them, I see it now.
I've begun to understand the answer.
I'm on the verge of figuring out
how to steal the arrow from Requiem!
I know what I must do!
Wh-What the hell is going on?
What's up with this ability?
How far has this damn thing spread?
They don't look as if they're dying or in pain...
They just have blank stares on their faces.
But... I'm afraid of my mind
transforming into something else...
Afraid that little by little,
my body and mind will disappear without a trace...
Trish!
I-I'm fine! But...
The time is already upon us.
It won't play out the same for everyone,
but soon we'll all be affected.
So we don't have much time, is that right?
Polnareff!
This is happening because you brought the arrow!
This is the exact opposite of
what we needed to defeat the boss!
Way to tighten the noose on us!
Enough!
No one could have predicted this.
We need to focus on
finding a way to defeat Requiem.
Yes! Get closer!
Get closer to Requiem!
I'll be able to see all of Requiem's secrets
if we only get a bit closer!
The arrow's power will become mine,
and the world will bend to my whims!
After it!
Good!
Don't move, Mista!
Trish and Buccellati, stay right there!
Don't move!
Wha-
I just told you not to move, Mista!
We can catch up to Requiem after this.
What the hell?
Shut up, idiot!
My body's already disappearing!
I picked up your revolver.
The one that you said broke a moment ago.
This broken piece doesn't match up
correctly with the rest of it.
If it broke due to the metal becoming worn,
the pieces should still fit.
Giorno, what are you getting at?
You can't move either, Buccellati!
We need to keep our distance from each other!
Come on!
Requiem is getting away!
If the Pistols said the metal was worn out,
then the metal was worn out!
I have this new Beretta now, too!
The pieces don't match up since part of it flew off!
Perhaps...
But perhaps there's more to it.
We'll know once we see this lost piece.
Gold Experience.
I imbued part of the gun with life and set it loose.
Moles are essentially blind,
but their sense of smell is unparalleled.
It seems to have returned with the lost piece.
H-Hey, hold on a second!
Are you saying someone broke my gun apart by force?
Listen to me!
The Pistols and I are sure about this!
There's nobody in this square who got anywhere close to-
Precisely. No one did.
We need to keep our distance from each other...
...since his range is only a few meters!
Giorno, you...
No one was near Narancia when he was attacked, either.
No one... other than us.
Mr. Polnareff, if your hypothesis is correct
and the boss does indeed have two personalities...
...then his mind should be capable
of freely moving in and out.
Diavolo has latched on to one of us.
Wha-
While he's hidden, Trish can't sense his presence.
He intends to remain in hiding
until we've secured the arrow.
It's why he only appeared for
a brief moment to destroy the gun.
H-Hold on!
I know I'm repeating myself,
but stay away, Mista!
Stay out of his range!
My gun was destroyed!
You're the closest person to your gun.
I-It...
It's not me!
O-Oh, yeah!
When Narancia was attacked...
...the closest person to him was...
Damn. I need to act...
Requiem is getting away.
This newcomer, Giorno Giovanna...
He's hiding within one of us.
But even so, we possess one advantage.
Diavolo can make King Crimson appear...
...but he doesn't have complete control
over the body he's currently inhabiting.
If he had total control,
he wouldn't be hiding from us.
The only reason we're still alive is because he can't manifest and freely move around.
We essentially have him cornered.
It's the tortoise!
It was the closest one to my revolver!
Polnareff is the one who's possessed!
It isn't him.
Requiem nearly killed Mr. Polnareff earlier...
...since the boss destroyed the revolver.
The boss wouldn't allow the body
he's inhabiting to be put in danger.
Besides...
I only sense one being's life energy.
A single soul lies within this tortoise.
You can tell that, Giorno?
Only if I get close enough to touch their body.
How can you be sure?
Life energy exists in clusters.
If I can touch someone, I can tell how many there are.
There's no other way.
I have to touch each one of you to find out.
But how will you get closer?
You'll enter King Crimson's range.
Mr. Polnareff taught me
how to detect King Crimson.
The number of droplets increasing
indicates the moment time has been skipped!
Yes.
But whether or not you can
avoid his attack is a matter of luck...
...as is whether you'll be able
to dodge it in time.
It's definitely not me.
I was the farthest away when he got Narancia...
Then I'll check you first
so we can be at ease.
Hey!
Don't move!
Stay away from me!
B-Back off!
What'll happen to me if Diavolo is inside you?
When Narancia died,
this body was an empty husk.
My soul was able to travel from
Narancia's body into my own, but it was empty.
There's no chance that he's possessing me.
You think so?
That's what you say.
I can't confirm if your ability works.
And anyway, Giorno...
...do you have a way of knowing
for sure that you only have one soul?
You can't check yourself with
your own ability, can you?
Mista, we can't go after the
arrow unless we find out!
Come any closer and I'll blow your limbs off!
Stop!
Check me first, Giorno.
Hurry and do it!
We're losing precious time.
As you said, we have the boss cornered
depending on how you look at our situation.
There's no other way.
Yes...
We need to do this now.
Someone's going to be attacked...
If we get closer to one another...
Giorno!
It's Mista!
He was possessed!
Spice Gi-
No, Trish!
It's you!
He moved your body closer to me in a single moment!
I've been waiting for this moment, my daughter...
The moment you would unleash your Stand!
Who Swapped With Who
Mista
Trish
Giorno
Buccellati
Tortoise
Polnareff
His body has died,
which means Doppio
has also died.
Diavolo
(King Crimson
had possessed him)
My daughter...
If you hadn't revealed your Stand,
I might still be in a bind...
Sticky Fingers!
By grabbing your Stand,
I can manipulate your body.
Now at least I can make this body flee.
He's going to attack!
Brace yourselves!
Time is going to be er-
Wha-
D-Don't tell me...!
Why did he run away without attacking us?
Through observation, he's already found
a way to get the arrow away from Requiem!
We have no time!
This takes priority!
Mista, fire!
Don't let him beat us to it!
Quit wasting time!
You can't hesitate just because it's your own body!
It's not that...
I already fired, Buccellati...
I already... fired six shots...
He's making time leaps as he runs!
He predicted the trajectory of the bullets!
After him!
If he gets the arrow, it's all over!
Its shadow.
That is what prevents anyone from touching the arrow.
If I'm understanding this correctly...
...when I move, Requiem's shadow moves in
the opposite direction from me, independent of the sun.
Which means...
...to that man, it should appear as though the shadow is stretching toward me.
In Buccellati's eyes, the shadow is
stretching in front of Requiem.
So logically...
...every person perceives the shadow differently!
That is Requiem's secret!
This is how it controls people's souls!
It's the very shadow of one's soul.
Requiem itself is the shadow of my soul!
That's why attacking it is to attack yourself!
I can retrieve the arrow if I eliminate the shadow!
Furthermore...
If my soul has a shadow,
then my light must exist somewhere, as well!
He still doesn't have the arrow!
Let's rush him, Mista!
The light source is behind my mind!
He just destroyed something behind his head!
What did he do?
I have it...
I, Diavolo, now have the arrow!
If Diavolo found a way to retrieve the arrow, then we should take advantage of it.
The droplets of blood from him
tearing off my arm are now a simple material...
Gold Experience shall now...
...manifest!
These ants!
What have they done to the arrow?
So far it's working...
I need to go...
I can't waste time!
Blast the arrow away from him!
Don't let him grab it, Mista!
I'm already shooting!
All right!
Even if he can predict them,
look at the distance between us!
He can only knock the ones
coming at him out of their trajectory!
The rest of you knock that arrow back
and bring it to me, Pistols!
H-He'd already thrown...
...someone into the air!
He knew where the bullets would land
and made 'em push the arrow back!
The trash ability of a trash underling...
It is utterly impossible for your feeble intellect
to surpass King Crimson's predictions.
You will never break through!
You're nothing but trash.
I will admit though, Buccellati...
Your team has made me sweat.
I never dreamed you would be
foolish enough to betray the organization...
...nor did I ever imagine you would
uncover my true identity.
However!
The fact that I've learned of this arrow's true power is a gift!
A gift granted to me by fate
for overcoming my past!
I need more ammo, Pistols!
We already told you, Mista!
Reloading the cartridge takes time!
W-We're done for!
Wh-What's going on?
Spice... Girl...
You didn't deflect Mista's bullets.
I just softened them.
The bullets stuck to your hand
like chewing gum and stretched out...
...and the elastic force
made them snap back through your hand.
Trish... You're still conscious!
I'm going to rise above this.
I refuse to live in fear and run away
from the fate you've passed on to me!
If it's in my way, I'll rise above it!
The arrow's flying right at me!
I'm the closest!
He can't get past me!
Even if he predicts where
it'll fall and erases time...
...I'll still be closer!
If only... my daughter...
...if only you had never been born...
Fear truly does stem from the past.
You have angered me greatly!
What?
You said you would rise above, did you not?
You were right, Trish.
Now you can rise above not only your past...
...but above their heads as well.
Trish!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
King of Kings