None of his friends realize
that there's another Stand.
Yes, they don't realize that my Stand...
...Talking Head, is attached to his tongue
and making him say the exact opposite of what he means.
Narancia...
...there must be a reason why you can't tell us the truth.
Giorno!
Giorno's being pulled under!
He's being sucked into the puddle!
Aerosmith!
That bastard is teleporting from puddle to puddle
and dragging Giorno along with it...
...even though there's barely any water!
Yes! I got him.
If we first take care of Giorno Giovanna
with his ability to control life and heal injuries...
...it will be a simple matter of
eliminating the rest of them one by one.
Yeah, all according to plan.
But we shouldn't waste time
finishing off Giorno, Squalo.
Huh?
According to my intel,
Narancia's Aerosmith can track carbon dioxide.
Even though Giorno's unconscious right now...
...his breathing will give away
your Clash's location since it's still biting down on him.
Even if it jumps from puddle to puddle...
...this could get dicey if Aerosmith
tracks your location and gets ahead of us.
It could find us.
I understand, Tiziano...
I'll stop Giorno's breathing.
Right now!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
wasure to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
A rage that erases all sense of forgetfulness
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has followed us from the day we swore to defy the devil
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Cast away the life in which you ask for a future
idomu mono stay gold
Challengers stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for traitors
zetsubou ga tamaneku
We will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care! jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru
So too would my prayers fade away?
Hell no! hajimari no Golden Wind
Hell no! It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 23  Clash and Talking Head
This is really bad!
I can't let them take Giorno away!
This enemy...
So there were already... two Stands... here?
Dammit!
The more I fire and miss...
...the more I'm spreading the water around and making things easier for the enemy!
I have to get ahead of them!
Where are they?
Where'd they go?!
There!
It may be able to teleport,
but if I can track it, I'll pump it full of bullets!
He's using his radar now.
I knew he was going to try to
track us down and shoot us.
We need to stop Giorno's breathing immediately.
I heard you.
I know what to do, Tiz.
But it's not exactly easy to
attack Giorno while I'm moving around!
I got the timing down! Now!
I-Into his throat?!
Giorno!
I-I didn't mean to shoot you!
Wh-What?
His breathing...
The symbol indicating Giorno's breathing...
It isn't showing up on the radar anymore!
Fuck! They got away!
It's over.
Clash went into the sewers.
I'm going to continue down the canal
and dispose of Giorno's body there.
Wait, Squalo!
What was that?
I said I'm taking his body down the canal and...
No, I'm talking about Narancia!
I almost didn't catch it,
but Narancia just said...
..."They got away!" Out loud!
While my Talking Head is attached to his tongue...
...he should only be able to say
the opposite of what he means.
But he said "They got away!"
He even said the symbol on his radar wasn't showing up!
Squalo!
Change your position now!
What are you talking about, Tiziano?
Giorno completely stopped breathing!
None of them are capable of tracking down my Clash!
He said "They got away" on purpose!
To lower your guard!
He only needs your Clash
to stop teleporting for a moment!
I don't know how,
but I'm certain he's tracking you!
Giorno got in the way of my bullets on purpose back there.
That way I could use the nitrate
from the smoke to track him down!
I got this!
I know right where the enemy is!
Here I go! Eat lead!
Here I come, fucker!
This must mean Giorno isn't dead!
If I can rescue him within a few minutes, he won't die!
This is serious, Squalo!
Now that he's hit you twice,
he can track the nitrate smoke coming off your bullet wounds!
I did it!
I got him out of the sewers!
This is it, Buccellati.
The enemy's replay won't go back any further.
I know for a fact that the enemy
was in this cup on this table.
But not for very long.
Moody Blues can't transform or keep going from this point.
What do you mean, Abbacchio?
I don't know.
Maybe they can teleport.
I won't get an answer here.
This enemy's replay...
It's like a torn video tape
that can't go any further.
I can't believe Narancia would go to these lengths...
No, it's Giorno.
This happened because Giorno
intentionally put himself in Aerosmith's line of fire!
Dammit!
I can't get rid of the nitrate smoke!
Even underwater!
It must be because they're bullets
from a Stand ability...
Somehow I need to disappear...
...to somewhere he can't find me!
I've been watching...
This shark motherfucker is pretty damn fast
for a remote-controlled Stand...
...but it doesn't look like it can
get very far with a single leap.
Can't be more than two or three meters!
No!
H-His attacks are becoming more precise!
It's probably because of their injuries,
but I can tell they're getting slower!
Squalo!
Yes!
Now I just need to end this with a finishing blow!
Take this, fish fucker!
Th-This smell...
There's a gas leak!
All according to plan, Narancia!
Since you shot up the pot,
hot water spilled out and extinguished the burner.
Now Aerosmith won't be able to shoot its gun!
You can't track me down anymore!
If one of the sparks from your gun
happens to ignite the gas...
...you may survive,
but everything around you will burn...
...which will fill the room with carbon dioxide and make me impossible to find!
Narancia, if you think you can get
a good shot off with your gun...
...then go ahead and try!
We've won!
You know, if I can't shoot...
...I still have other ways of killing you!
Yes! I got 'em!
Buccellati! Mista!
The enemy's here!
Abbacchio, the enemy's a guy
who can move from liquid to liquid!
Giorno's breathing again, too!
Huh?
Wait. What did I just say?
Why was I able to say the truth?
Squalo, I released my Talking Head
from Narancia's tongue, just like you planned.
Your injuries are severe,
but I'm sure the boss will be pleased.
Did you just yell something, Narancia?
Did you say the enemy's over here?
But I only released Talking Head temporarily.
Giorno's...!
That must be the enemy!
Wh-What?!
W-Wai-
We win, Squalo!
Yes... Everything went according to plan!
Here we go, Pistols!
Shoot, Mista!
Wh-What?!
Sh-Shit! My radar!
I can't track them!
They're going to attack!
Giorno's gonna be taken because of my lie!
N-Narancia!
S-Search for them!
G-Giorno!
Don't... pursue the Stand...
Get the user!
Giorno!
Hey, Narancia!
You idiot!
Why'd you tell me to shoot?!
The room was filled with gas!
Look out! It's the enemy!
The enemy's above you!
No! Below!
The enemy's below!
What?!
Guys!
It's no use!
I can't stop myself from talking!
I need to stop talking!
It disappeared!
They plan on getting rid of Giorno before anyone else!
Don't... pursue the Stand...
Get the user!
Giorno!
Giorno told me to find the user.
That's right... they're still hurt.
They're probably breathing hard because of their injuries.
So that's what he meant.
He wants me to use my radar to find them.
I'm on my own here.
I have to fly solo.
Someone who's breathing hard...
They're a remote-controlled Stand user,
but they have to be around here somewhere.
I'm running out of time!
I need to find them now!
Talking Head
Tiziano
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Good, everything is going as planned.
With Giorno out of the picture,
no one can heal their injuries.
Now please finish off Giorno, if you will.
For good!
Yeah, I'm on it.
Even though I'm injured...
...I have enough strength left to attack him.
Hey, look.
It's Narancia!
What is he doing here?
Where is Clash right now?
Over there.
It exited the restaurant's sewer system
and is headed down the canal.
He shouldn't be able to track it anymore...
Don't tell me he's trying to find me instead!
My breathing...
Calm down, Squalo.
That's impossible.
He's acting out of desperation
since he's out of options.
How many people do you think
are within a hundred meters of here?
Fifty? One hundred?
He won't be able to tell you apart from the others.
But I'm injured...
If his plan is to single out injured people
with labored breathing, then...
Don't panic, Squalo.
Look at the bottom of the stairs.
There are dozens of people with breathing
more labored than yours in this square.
Calm yourself and slow your breathing.
If we hide your injuries and head into the square
like nothing is wrong, we'll be safe.
We've still won!
Yeah, you're right...
I know you're right.
There's no way he'll find us.
I found you!
You're right there!
Wh-What?!
Dammit!
I need to call back Clash!
Calm down, Squalo!
Think this through!
He can only say the opposite
of what he's thinking right now.
He said he found us,
which means he hasn't!
Don't forget that!
So then why did he bother saying that?
He wants you to panic and make
your breathing even more labored!
Please calm down.
You panicking is exactly what he wants.
Narancia won't be able to single you out.
This is a futile, last-ditch effort.
Slow your breathing.
I... found you...
There you are!
I... finally... found you!
He said it again!
Please, calm down!
He hasn't found us. That's a fact!
He's definitely lying!
My Talking Head is still definitely on his tongue...
H-Hey, look!
Wh-What?!
He cut out his own tongue!
With his own knife!
That's impossible!
No one could survive cutting off their own tongue...
...let alone speak!
I found... you!
H-He has another tongue!
The ladybug became a tongue!
It can't be!
It's Giorno!
Giorno Giovanna!
It's just like the boss warned us!
He's the biggest problem!
That Giorno bastard must have created
a tongue for Narancia while they were in the kitchen!
He's coming!
He's headed this way!
So he was tracking my breathing!
It's obviously a bluff!
If he were actually tracking you,
he would have attacked already!
With all the different people around here, there's a lot of breathing going on.
Labored breathing, slow breathing...
Enough that I can't single anyone out.
But I've been waiting...
I was waiting for this...
For someone's breathing to suddenly go way out of whack!
For someone to rapidly change their breathing
after seeing me cut my own tongue out with a knife!
For someone to see a Stand hanging off
my severed tongue and freak the hell out!
That's what I've been waiting for!
I had almost lost all hope and was about to give up!
You, over there!
Your breathing just changed, didn't it?!
Yeah, you! I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to you, long hair!
How could this happen?
He actually cut off his own tongue to find us!
This must mean the shark user
is the guy right next to you!
He's lookin' pretty pale!
Squalo, call Clash back!
I'm already on it!
It's traveling through the sewers
and heading toward that well.
But... there's no water here!
There isn't a source of water near here
that it can use to jump to Narancia!
You must be him!
The guy who dragged Giorno away!
Tiziano!
Now you have liquid to work with... Squalo.
This didn't... go exactly according to plan...
But it won't take away from our victory.
We're still going... to win...
I don't give a shit about
the boss's orders anymore!
I'm not going to kill you because
I was ordered to as a member of his elite guard!
Tiziano...
I'm going to eliminate him to avenge you!
I'll kill every last one of Narancia's friends, too!
I'll make them pay by tearing them to shreds!
They will pay!
Clash!
Rip his throat out!
You think that's enough... to throw me off?
Because of... Because of something like this?
We're gonna get the hell out of Venice safe and sound!
Get fucked.
Vola Vola Vola Vola!
Vola!
Volare via.
"Go Flying"
They're nothing but traitors...
Fated to be eliminated by the boss...
The only future they have
should be filled with despair...
What the hell is keeping them going?
This kind of mental strength
makes me think they have hope...
Wh-What could it...?
Someone just collapsed!
Giorno!
Y-Yes!
He's breathing again, faintly!
Giorno, wake up! Giorno! Giorno!
Narancia...
Abbacchio doesn't think too highly of you,
but before we knew it, we started acting on your judgment calls...
...as if you were leading us...
With you around,
this trip might not be hopeless after all!
Giorno, let's go back to the others.
How long has it been since the attack began?
Four to five minutes?
Either way, I can't imagine another pursuer
from the organization made it to Venice yet.
We should be in the clear.
Let's head toward the airport!
We'll take a plane!
We have to get a plane and head to Sardinia, no matter what!
We need to uncover the boss's past
in Sardinia as soon as possible...
...or we lose.
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Notorious B.I.G.