Can you track them down, Melone?
Yeah.
I just procured a blood sample.
Buccellati's, as it were.
Hey, when's this train gonna start moving?!
Please, it will be just a bit longer.
Another driver is on the way as we speak!
What? What happened to the first one?
Ugh, talk about annoying.
Especially the crying brat over there.
I should have known better than to
take a train full of disgusting plebeians.
Miss...
How would you describe your health?
H-Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
You're in my compartment!
You can read the sign posted on my door, can't you?
Do you happen to possess an object
with your birthdate written on it?
Wh-What do you think you're doing?!
Born March 10, 1977.
Twenty-four years old.
This is... bellissimo.
The perfect age.
Keep your hands off my things!
Get out!
So good...
Such a brisk slap!
If you have the energy to produce such a brisk slap,
then there's no doubt in my mind!
You are...
...in excellent health!
"Health: excellent."
And judging by the taste of your fingers,
your blood type is O.
Correct?
What's wrong with you?
Are you a thief?
Who do you think I am?
My family-
Ah, your name won't be necessary.
Your birthplace and upbringing are irrelevant, as well.
The only pertinent information is your current health, your date of birth, and your blood type.
A Pisces with type O!
Buccellati is blood type A and an Aries, which is a horrific horoscope mismatch.
And that couldn't make me happier!
It appears you drink and smoke, as well.
Do you also use drugs?
If you do...
You're the di molto best person I could ask for!
I-If you want money, I can give you some...
And if you need more, I have a credit card...
Listen.
Could you be quiet and listen?
This next question is the most important one.
Your preference is of the utmost importance.
Which do you prefer?
Apparently the Indian Kama Sutra, a manuscript written
1,500 years ago, outlines more than forty-eight positions.
But I think it's still an incredibly relevant resource..
...as the beginning of the process leading
to the birth of an outstanding child.
Now, choose.
Babyface!
S-S-Someone help me!
Help me!
Conception complete
3 minutes until birth
Analyzing DNA from Bruno Buccellati's blood sample.
Would you like to incorporate the DNA into a body and nurture it so that it can be traced?
Oh, yes. We're going to nurture it...
①Yes ②No
...into something absolutely vile.
Di molto...
yume o shibaritsukeru
A heavy stone of fate
omotai sadame no ishi ni
which has chained up my dreams
marude oshitsubusarete
is threatening to crush me
doko ni mo nigerarenai
Struggle as I may,
hitasura agaki nagara
there's nowhere left to run
dakedo akiramenai
But I'll never give in
gareki no soko ni umoreta kibou no kakera tachi
Though fragments of hope lie buried beneath the rubble
kitto kono te de mitsukedasu sa
I swear I'll dig them up with my own two hands
sekai o kaeru tame ni
in order to make a difference in this world
Fighting gold
jibun no michi o shinjita mono dake ga
Only those who believe in the path they take
itsuka kagayakeru
will one day shine brightly
inochi no kagiri
As long as they live,
kami ni mo sakarai
even if opposed by God,
tatakaitsuzukeru
they will battle on
fukutsu no tamashii tachi yo
with their indomitable souls
Fighting gold
Episodio 17  Babyface
Assuming nobody finds us,
we should make it to Venice by tomorrow or the day after.
Y'know... Everyone seems really bummed out right now...
Makes me wonder if Buccellati said something harsh to Trish.
No, I believe her unease comes from
Buccellati's lack of communication.
Trish is most likely a Stand user without realizing it.
Not to mention her mysterious father...
She must have so many questions...
But Buccellati is forbidden to
speak with her about any of it.
I would like to learn more about her ability.
It could offer me a hint about the mysterious boss.
She's very resolute.
She never cries or complains.
Mista!
Tell Number Two and Number Three
to share the hamburger with us!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
We don't have anything to eat here right now...
Where did you guys get that?!
D-Don't tell me...
Where'd my hamburger go?
Is that it under the seat?
D-Dammit!
A tortoise?
It's got something on its back...
Looks like some kinda jewel... Is it a key?
What're we gonna do, Mista?
This ain't good.
What just happened?
Mista, weren't you keeping watch on the ceiling?
What happened?
Huh? Me?
I-I haven't a clue!
I wasn't watching at that moment...
Huh? Perhaps the truck stopped...
Gestation Complete
Oww!
What happened?
Th-This...
D-Don't tell me I...!
Thank goodness. Nothing happened...
That fucking jerk!
What the hell was wrong with that disgusting pervert?
How dare he scare me half to death!
I wanna kill him, dammit!
That piece of shit!
Hello? Are you the conductor of this train?
Come to my compartment this instant!
What does "kill" mean?
He appears to have been born.
He's begun to learn from his mother.
Babyface's child, that is...
And he's already doing well!
He's responding to his mother's desire to kill someone!
Grow up into something great!
I'm telling you, some creepy pervert attacked me in my compartment!
He attacked me!
And all because you cheaped out
on the lock for my private compartment!
I was even bumped on the head!
Ugh, this is pissing me off!
That scumbag!
I hope you guys are prepared!
What does... "kill" mean?
I'm going to sue the hell out of you guys!
This is unbelievable!
What does... "scumbag" mean?
Would you like to learn a bit more?
Okay, pay attention, now.
This is Mr. Lion.
He's the king of beasts!
The one with the long nose is Mr. Elephant,
and the one with the long neck is Mr. Giraffe.
The one eating the grass is Mr. Zebra.
And...
Oh, what's this?
This is what "kill" means.
Do you understand?
It means to make them die, or to eliminate them.
Next... We have some examples of children's playthings.
A spinning top and baseball.
This is a bowling set, and these are ice skates.
Oh, my!
Look at how handy they are when used like this!
The ones being killed here are "scumbags".
You say "scumbag" when there's only one,
and "scumbags" when there's many of them.
Do you understand?
As for which method you should use to kill them,
just use your instincts.
However, you are forbidden to attack this girl named Trish.
She must be captured alive.
There's also a new guy whose face we haven't seen yet.
He's also with Buccellati,
so make sure you find and eliminate all of them.
I have to pee.
What should I do?
What should you do?
I mean, just do it?
Babies pee all the time.
It doesn't look like anyone forced the lock...
H-Hey, what is this?!
There's something leaking from
the ceiling of this stupid train!
I don't see a leak...
I-It stinks!
What is this?!
It's so smelly and gross!
Miss...
Mommy said that I stink.
She's also screaming that I'm "dirty and gross".
So she did.
And how does that make you feel about her?
Mommy is great!
Yes!
Di molto! This is outstanding!
You're learning so well!
I'm hungry...
What should I do?
Not yet.
You have much more to learn.
It's too soon.
Let me drink! Hurry and let me drink!
Hey, not yet!
I told you, not yet!
I've had enough!
I can't spend another second on this train!
I'll sue the train company and make sure
they take responsibility for everything!
I'll even say the bump on my head
gave me a concussion.
Huh? Did she hang up?
She was too good of a mother!
I'm glad she instilled her desire to kill so quickly,
but it's too soon!
H-Hey!
Buccellati's DNA isn't moving...
It's idle somewhere to the north.
You're really something else...
I can't deny your obvious talent, though.
It seems the automatic tracking of
Buccellati's DNA just kicked in.
It's a handful, but Babyface's son is an
invincible remote-controlled Stand!
It's unbeatable!
Melone
Babyface
Dependent
on Education
Let's just steal one, already!
Are you stupid?
The news would spread like wildfire
and make it to our enemies.
We could get ambushed!
Good point...
Fugo's right on the money.
Then let's hear what Buccellati thinks!
Wh-What are you doing, Giorno?
We'll be caught immediately if we steal just one...
But if we steal a hundred...
If more than one car disappears,
and pieces of them are found scattered in different locations...
...searching for us will be far more difficult.
It should give us plenty of time to reach Venice.
I dig it!
Sure as hell beats hitchhiking.
Yeah, whatever.
Giorno, go tell Buccellati.
Here.
The rest of us will grab a car.
Please get down from the chair.
It's incredibly dangerous outside right now.
I have to ask, Mr. Buccellati...
If I ask a stupid question, can you answer it?
Depends on the question.
What am I supposed to do if I need to use the bathroom?
You don't expect me to use a diaper, do you?
I see... That is a good question.
Great. I'm happy you understand.
Let's convert the closet into a bathroom.
Go ahead.
"Go ahead"?
You said you had to use the bathroom.
I'm not sure where this leads,
but it shouldn't harm the tortoise.
It may actually nourish it.
I have no idea what you're getting at...
Buccellati, we've procured a car.
Good.
Once you've confirmed it's safe, we'll head out.
Understood.
That bike... Where did it come from?
Where's the rider?
Giorno, is something wrong?
Trish?
What the hell?!
Trish!
I-Impossible!
Sticky-
Damn! It's a Stand!
And it's remote-controlled!
But it shouldn't have this much power!
What's...?
Buccellati, please stay alert!
A strange bike suddenly appeared here.
Buccellati?
It can't be! Buccellati!
Where's Trish? Trish!
I was holding the tortoise the entire time...
I would know if they came outside.
Could the enemy have already begun its attack?
Gold Experience!
Di molto!
I got the boss's daughter, Trish.
Captured Buccellati, too.
What should I do now?
Di molto!
Well done, Babyface!
Now get away from there, obviously!
I'm inside a tortoise right now...
There's a human waiting outside the exit.
I've never seen him before.
He's going to find me on my way back. What should I do?
You've never seen him before?
Must be the new guy.
If he finds you, your only option is to eliminate him!
Roger.
I will dispose of the new guy waiting near the tortoise's exit.
Just make sure you do it quietly
so you aren't discovered by the others.
Trish's capture is our top priority.
I'll have them head over there as well, just in case.
I thought I felt a presence there, but...
No, you were right.
Everyone! There's an enemy here!
We're being atta-
D-Did it just... take my throat?!
Are you almost done, Mista?
Don't rush me!
What's up?
Nothing.
Giorno's waving at us.
Probably just trying to remind us that
Buccellati wants the car already.
Quit making me try to rush!
The attack was successful.
It's quiet here now that I stole his throat.
Di molto! Well done!
Impossible!
I destroyed the cabinet,
but it still hasn't shown itself?
And why can't I see it while it's attacking me?
How can it hide while taking out pieces of me?
Taking out pieces... That can only mean...
So you took out his eye and leg, too?
Di molto! Well done!
Now head back here, Babyface!
The attack was unsuccessful.
He figured out what I am. What should I do?
He did what?
The new guy removed the key from the tortoise's back.
Apparently only living things can leave while the key is removed.
My body is floating upward.
What should I do?
I'm not sure what you're saying... Living things?
You're a Stand!
That doesn't even apply to you!
That's true, but right now
I have the eye that I stole from him.
His eye is living.
I knew it... It was that cabinet.
I see now...
It's not that I couldn't see the enemy...
I could see it all along!
It has the ability to dice people up
and reconstruct them into objects!
Melone.
What should I do?
Don't panic!
So what if he figured out your ability?
The new guy hasn't been able to breathe for a while,
and he's missing a leg, right?
Just defeat him and make off with Trish and the tortoise!
Roger.
Gold Experience!
It's dodging by splitting itself apart!
Which means...
E-Everyone...
Somehow... I have to tell them...
That had an effect!
No, that was a regular rock.
N-No...
It's going to take Trish...
At this rate, Buccellati will be eliminated!
I-It's strong...
Is it... invincible?
I'll leave the new guy's corpse here.
As planned, I quietly captured Trish.
Di molto! Good!
I'm heading back to the train, Melone.
The one you're on.
Reconstructing people into objects...
Your ability gave me an invaluable hint.
I realized how similar it is to Gold Experience's.
They both possess the power to recreate things.
By pushing me to the brink of death and providing me with such a hint, it would seem...
...you've helped me grow a bit.
M-Melone, are you getting this?
I wasn't thinking about it earlier,
but now I know the new guy's Stand ability.
What about the new guy?
He turned his brooch into an eye right in his hand!
It became an eyeball!
Hey, Babyface, what are you talking about?
What's this about the dead new guy?
He put a new eye into his face!
He replaced his leg and throat, too!
He has the ability to create life!
He created new parts!
His ability is the opposite of mine!
Hey, who are you talking about?
You're not getting away!
Gold Experience!
The new guy! He...
He's been revived!
A-Are you getting any of this, Melone?
He turned parts of the motorcycle into roots!
I can't shake 'em!
I have to ditch the stuck parts!
I gotta get away from the motorcycle!
Did it turn into a rock again?
This is bad!
He's gonna grab the tortoise!
I'll kill him before he picks it up!
Calm down, Babyface!
Let him pick it up.
What do you mean?
The moment he picks up the tortoise,
finish him off for good.
It's leaking oil. Not good!
Tear him apart until he can't put himself back together!
I got him!
You only freaked me out a little bit,
but how dare you, asshole!
Now I'm gonna rip your head right off your-
I've learned a lot from your
ability to turn people into objects.
I'm not sure if our meeting was fate,
or if our Stands were drawn to each other due to their similarities...
...but because of you, my Gold Experience has grown.
Wh-Where did it go?
I just tore off your hand.
Where did it go?
You did?
That's incorrect.
I severed it myself.
As a small favor, I'll give you a warning...
You would be wise to use your hand
to defend yourself rather than attack me.
D-Don't you dare underestimate me!
Take this!
Wh-What?!
The hand I severed became
a living creature and invaded your body!
Indeed...
As you can see, it became a piranha!
Every time I close my eyes
I wake up feeling so horny
I can't get you outta my mind
Cause sexin' you be all I see
I would give anything
Just to make you understand me
I don't give a damn about nothing else
Freek'n you is all I need
Tonight, I need your body (I need your body)
Tonight, you got my time (oh get it baby)
Tonight you won't be sorry (yeah)
Tonight, you got my mind
You got my mind, all I wanna do is freak you
What must I say (oh tell me)
What must I do (what must I do?)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you (feel it)
What must I say
What must I do (yeah, yeah)
To show how much
I think about freek'n you
Onward to Venice!