Is that Giorno's brooch?
C-Could his brooch be...
C-Could it be growing into a left hand?
Giorno can still make a recovery!
If I can protect that left hand,
Narancia and Mista's wounds can be healed, too!
B-But in this situation... How can I...?
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
wasure to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
A rage that erases all sense of forgetfulness
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has followed us from the day we swore to defy the devil
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Cast away the life in which you ask for a future
idomu mono stay gold
Challengers stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for traitors
zetsubou ga tamaneku
We will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care! jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru
So too would my prayers fade away?
Hell no! hajimari no Golden Wind
Hell no! It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 25  Spice Girl
B-But... If I scream...
...or move more quickly than the brooch, it will kill me.
I feel sorry for Giorno and the others,
but there's nothing I can do.
I'll be its next target after it attacks the brooch...
I have to hide.
This is my only chance to hide in the closet...
This is...
...the seat reclining button.
If I can press it,
the seat's backrest should roll backwards.
It will probably attack the moving seat before the brooch.
I-I'll pick up the brooch
and head for the cockpit while it's distracted.
I-I can't do it!
I can't bet my life on something like that!
It's way too dangerous...
I should just go hide in the closet...
Am I insane?!
What am I even doing right now?!
I can't believe it...
I didn't want to take the risk, but I did it anyway!
Well, I guess I have no choice!
The path to the cockpit is wide open!
Move... slowly...
It's just like the tai chi that Chinese people practice...
I'm only two meters away from the brooch...
I can't rush this...
If I rush, I'll die!
It-It's coming back this way!
It must be because it destroyed the seat
and stopped it from reclining...
Good thing there are more seats to recline.
Wh-Why did it grab onto my leg and not the seat?
L-Liquid?
It reacted to the speed of dripping liquid?
B-But how did my boots get wet?
I only pressed the reclining button!
How could they have gotten wet?
I... I knew it...
I should have left the ladybug alone...
I shouldn't have gotten involved in this!
S-Save me, Buccellati!
M-My boot just fell off next to my foot...
Like it went right through it...
Wait, what?
What just happened?
Quick, pick up that brooch, Trish.
Wh-Who's there?
Is someone there?
I've always been by your side.
Ever since you were little...
...I've always been by your side.
Trish, please pick up that brooch.
You decided this for yourself.
You've already made up your mind
to protect Giorno's left hand.
Hesitation begets weakness.
Also, please give me your orders.
Wh-Who are you?
I am you.
I'm the one responsible for removing
the thing that was clinging to your boot.
I am your ability.
Now, since your decision has been made, please pick it up.
The two of us together...
...will protect Giorno's left hand!
Trish, if we succeed at protecting it,
the future of Giorno and his friends will continue.
Your future, as well!
What's going on?!
Pick it up, Trish!
I'm gonna die!
How on earth am I supposed to protect this thing?!
This is your ability.
You softened the seat.
Wh-What just...?
Softened the seat?
I slipped through it almost as if I cut it open...
And somehow it hurt that thing.
That fleshy part was torn off!
It's fast enough to stop Mista's bullets
and catch up to a moving plane...
...and strong enough to destroy
tough moving objects like it's nothing, and yet...
Colliding with static objects hurts it!
Are you really me?
Am I the one who did this?
And that thing with the boot...?
Our goal right now, Trish...
...is to pick up that brooch.
Your determination has
helped you cast all doubts aside!
You're becoming stronger,
both physically and mentally.
You're capable of softening anything
that exists in this world.
Softening things...
...makes them more unbreakable than diamond!
I-It's coming back!
This time, be still.
I understand that you're me,
but I have to hide!
Soften the closet door!
Please make it in time!
Dammit!
Stay the hell away from me until I close the door!
E-Even though I'm hiding,
it can sense me through the door!
I-It's going to kill me!
I'm beginning to understand that
I'm a Stand user with a Stand ability...
B-But...
...this thing is invincible!
The user is already dead, too!
Nothing can beat this thing!
Trish, I asked you not to move.
We need to reach the cockpit where Buccellati is,
but we went in the opposite direction.
Are you kidding me?
Giorno's brooch won't stop moving
while it's turning into his left hand.
I had to run away!
And anyway...
...all you can do is soften things!
It's taking everything I have to avoid these attacks!
I-It's going to get me!
I-It attacked the clock again?
What?
I softened that table clock.
So long as you move no faster than
the second hand on that clock, it will continue to attack it...
...and prioritize attacking it instead of you.
When I told you not to move,
I meant move slowly.
Move slowly.
Slower than the second hand.
Moving at such a slow speed...
...but with the strength of a vise...
...you and I will tear this thing apart...
...and kill it!
Damn you!
Go to hell already!
You piece of shit!
Quit clinging to this world like a parasite, dammit!
It's crumbling into tiny pieces and disintegrating!
This Stand that pursues its targets like an angry,
vengeful spirit is shrinking and fading away...
Y-Your name...
Do you have a name?
What should I call you?
Spice Girl.
I see...
You're really something else...
Trish Una
Spice Girl
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: C
Now Mista and Narancia's
wounds can be healed.
But Giorno Giovanna...
He's a very strange man.
Not only is he capable of imbuing things with life,
but his actions directly led to your spirit maturing.
I'm going to make sure the engines are okay.
Buccellati, I have some good news for you...
We don't have to worry anymore.
Giorno has actually already...
Don't say another word!
I-I mean... Slowly...
Trish, come here very slowly...
Our altitude is 7,000 meters!
6,800...
6,600!
It won't stop...
It keeps falling, and I can't figure out why!
I can tell you why we're falling, Abbacchio.
But what can we do?
How are we going to handle this?
Buccellati, what are you-
I said don't move!
D-Don't tell me...
Th-Th-That's... That's impossible!
Giorno said that thing has the ability
to catch up to and drain any target.
The jet engine...
Just now, that thing...
Trish, don't turn around.
Don't panic under any circumstances.
Slowly walk this way.
Th-That's...!
No! Th-That's impossible!
Nothing's working!
We keep falling!
Soon we're gonna crash!
O-Or more likely, the engines are gonna blow!
Th-That thing should have been
torn to pieces and disintegrated...
W-Wait...
The engines are just behind the closet...
Oh, no...
If even a tiny bit of this thing was able to get through a crack in the closet wall...
...it may have drained all the energy from the engine.
And now it's...!
We need to make an emergency landing, Abbacchio.
The Tyrrhenian Sea is right in front of us.
We'll have to land on the water!
It's our only hope!
An emergency landing?
Even if we survive the landing,
what options will we have?
That thing will still pursue us!
It's invincible.
It's way too powerful.
It's an invincible ability!
Now, walk slowly, Trish...
Nice and slow, like a slug.
Don't panic.
Whatever you do, don't run!
It will attack if you rush!
Y-You're kidding me!
What are you doing?!
It's going to get you!
Yes, it certainly will!
If I do something as stupid as moving slowly,
it will catch up to me, anyway!
Get in the cockpit, Buccellati!
Have you lost your mind, Trish?!
It can destroy the door!
Th-The door...
Is this...?
What the...?
Are you really a...?
An emergency landing?
Buccellati, that's exactly what we shouldn't do!
If you want us all to safely arrive in Sardinia...
...we need to destroy this plane!
Wannabe!
Spice Girl!
T-Trish... This is...
When did your Stand ability...?
Th-The glass and walls feel like
they're made of rubber!
Since this thing prioritizes fast moving targets,
crashing is our best option!
A crashing plane is way faster...
...than this parachute!
Yes! Screw you!
We took some serious damage,
but since our plane just crashed into the sea near Sardinia...
...the boss's men won't be able to
confirm whether we're dead or alive.
Right?
The organization's lost track of us!
This bought us some time!
Time we can use to uncover
the boss's identity and find him!
No, Abbacchio.
It looks like we're going to sustain
just a bit more damage...
I'll eliminate this thing myself.
Nothing but my zipper can do it.
Wh-What?!
Don't tell me...!
It's completely invincible.
It's impossible to kill it.
We can only outspeed it,
just like Giorno did.
Y-You can't be serious, Buccellati!
D-Don't do it!
You're gonna attach it to your arm?
Arri Arri Arri Arri!
Don't!
Are you trying to maim yourself, too?!
No, Abbacchio...
None of us will be permanently maimed.
Giorno's Gold Experience ability...
...is safe right here.
Wh-When did you...?
Arrivederci.
"So Long"
Stand name: Notorious B.I.G.
Complete annihilation: Impossible.
It is forever cursed to chase
the crashing waves of the sea.
Every now and then, it will attack and sink
passing ships that happen to move faster than the waves.
These waters eventually came to be known as
the Tyrrhenian Belly by local fisherman, and are thought to be cursed.
Now we just need to lay low
and find out who the boss really is.
We're going to uncover my father's past!
The private jet hijacked by unknown thieves
from the Marco Polo International Airport...
...crash-landed in the Tyrrhenian Sea,
fifty kilometers northeast of Sardinia.
It remains shrouded in mystery.
No passengers were found on board.
I believed I could make it disappear,
but one's past never allows for true peace.
I can't believe it.
This is why blood relations are so troubling.
I wouldn't be concerned if it were a stranger, but blood relations make this difficult.
But it's nothing more than that.
Blood relations.
Rid myself of that,
and my enduring dominance will remain eternal.
Several days ago, after Pericolo secured Trish...
...the traitors who were after her scoured this apartment
Trish and her mother lived in, but they all failed to notice something.
Trish awoke every morning of her life in this place...
...and...
She grew up seeing this photograph that her mother had lovingly put up on a near-daily basis.
But this date...
There's not a doubt in my mind...
It was fifteen years ago.
This portrait...
Even I almost missed it.
To think that such a thing existed...
Their plane crashed... but they're alive.
I can feel it...
My daughter's Stand ability has awakened.
I know she's alive and headed toward Sardinia.
And if it was Abbacchio's Moody Blues
that was flying the plane...
...that means at the very least he also survived!
I can't allow Moody Blues
to reach the place in this photo.
Trish may not realize it now,
but she'll surely remember...
...the existence of this picture.
And if she goes to Sardinia...
...she'll discover that the person who took this portrait of her mother fifteen years ago... was me!
I won't allow Moody Blues to replay that!
I have no choice but to go there personally.
This is too important to leave up to my subordinates.
Oh, y-you were home!
I did knock, but...
I'm here to clean your room.
P-Pardon me, I'll be back la-
Huh?
Why was I here again?
O-Oh, right! To clean!
I'm supposed to be cleaning!
Well now, I should get to work.
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
A Little Story From the Past ~My Name Is Doppio~