Guys, guys!
Just listen to me!
What the hell is it?
Can you just be quiet already?
I was thinking about it last night...
So, if you ate human meat,
do you think it would taste good or bad?
No, Mista.
Let's not talk about that.
Why would you bring up
that kind of shit now?
Fuck off!
Go eat by yourself!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
You'll never arrive at your destination.
More precisely,
you'll never arrive at the truth.
You impertinent brat!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Muda!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
None can escape their chosen fate
Only the result in which you are destroyed remains
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 38  Gold Experience Requiem
Y-You did it! Finally!
Your Gold Experience evolved with the arrow!
I didn't get a good look,
so I'm not sure how you did it...
...but he's finally defeated!
Wait... Hold on a second...
Did he float up yet?
Hey, where is he?
Where is his body?
Shit!
Where is he?
Find him, Giorno!
Where is he?!
Somehow... I'm...
...just barely... still alive...
I don't know how...
But... What was that?
My victory was assured
in the vision I witnessed, and yet...
Just what in the world...
was that Requiem?
For now...
I'll escape into the sewers...
I still... have enough strength left for that...
I... I did it...
Was this just good fortune?
You bastard!
If you're tryna...
s-s-sneak up an' snatch my coat...
You got another thing comin'!
You ready to go?
Are ya?!
I'm no weakling!
I'll fuck you up!
Come get some, ya limp-dick bastard!
What?!
Come on! Come get some!
I-Impossible!
This can't be...
You ain't never gonna get my coat!
I can't get up!
S-Someone...
You'll never get it...
N-Not here...
I-I'm Diavolo!
I can't... to a man like this...
I'm fading...
Where am I?
Why was I sleeping on this bed?
I fell into the river,
and then I went into that sewer...
Let's see... Today's date is the 25th.
11:20 AM.
File number 68.
I, Dr. Monica Ultello,
will be carrying out this procedure.
Subject is an adult male,
estimated between thirty and forty years old.
Identity unknown.
Judging by the state of his skin,
about 48 to 54 hours since time of death.
I will now begin the autopsy
to determine the cause of death.
Hey, woman... What are you talking about?
Though his body was found by the river...
Where am I?
What am I doing here?
...there doesn't appear to be any water in his lungs,
indicating that he didn't drown.
Hey, woman!
I can't move...
M-My fingers...
My body...
What is happening?
Hey, woman!
Can you hear me?
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing?!
Why won't my body move?!
A-And this pain...
I-It's agony!
Cause of death was a
stab wound sustained to the liver.
No signs of hesitation visible,
so suicide can be ruled out.
Next, I'm going to make a small incision in the abdomen to check for abnormalities.
Liver appears healthy.
Good color.
W-Was that a dream?
Am I dreaming right now?
But...
I-It's happening again. Where...?
What time is it?
Where am I?
I was in the Tiber River in Rome...
And that feeling...
That unimaginable pain
I experienced in the autopsy room...
I-It felt so real...
Hello, sir?
Are you all right?
I just noticed you hunched over in the street...
Are you feeling unwell?
Hey, stop that!
What is going on?!
This isn't right!
S-Something so mundane couldn't possibly...
Could this be...
...Gold Experience Requiem's...!
We have to go find him!
I can sense that he's still alive!
We can't rest easy until we know for sure!
No, there's no need to look for him.
What?
It's all over.
I couldn't quite see Requiem's ability for myself...
...yet for some reason,
I know deep in my heart...
...that he will never arrive at his destination.
More precisely,
he will never arrive at the truth.
The truth of his death will never come to pass...
What's wrong, mister?
Does your tummy hurt?
Forever more.
B-But he's still alive...
His is an end with no end.
That... is Gold Experience Requiem!
H-How many times am I going to die?!
Wh-When and where will it happen next?!
S-Stay away!
Stay away!
S-Stay...
Stay the hell away from me!
So we really did it?
We're the ones who won?
Hey, come on!
Let's get back to the Colosseum!
Even though Buccellati got his soul back,
he's gotta be hurting!
I bet he's waiting for us at the Colosseum wondering what the hell happened!
Yeah!
Giorno, come on!
We gotta go to the Colosseum!
You'll heal Buccellati's wounds
so we can all go home!
Yeah... Let's go.
I'll be there in a moment.
Giorno, this is how it should be.
Don't let it trouble you.
Everything we've done until this moment led us to victory.
Fate is a sleeping slave.
A slave we were able to set free.
That is our victory.
Giorno Giovanna
Gold Experience Requiem
Power: ?
Speed: ?
Range: ?
Durability: ?
Precision: ?
Growth Potential: ?
Just hear me out!
Taking time to really think about what you're eating...
...is connected to whether or not
you're living a happy life.
That's why I think it's so important.
Think about it!
There are animals who mostly eat meat, right?
Like lions, cats, vultures, and all that.
You won't find meat from
carnivores like that at any restaurant.
But why?
It's because it smells
and you can barely eat it!
It's nasty!
So, let's recap.
Cats are too nasty to eat.
We still on the same page?
Even if some master chef
said it was delicious, I'd never eat cat!
On the other hand,
have you heard of sweetfish before?
Sweetfish don't eat bugs, just algae.
They're herbivores.
Fish guts are usually way too bitter to eat,
but sweetfish guts taste delicious.
It's because they're not carnivores!
So putting what we know together...
...we can deduce that the meat
we consider delicious comes from herbivores!
Cows! Pigs! Chickens!
The better their feed, the better they taste!
And from this we can conclude...
...that human meat
would taste nasty since we eat meat!
Well?
What do you think of my answer?
I get it.
I'm convinced.
That whole thing in a bunch of books
about human meat tasting delicious...
...is a complete lie!
I, uh... I actually eat way more
fruits and vegetables than meat, though...
Then you're probably pretty tasty!
Narancia, don't humor him!
Buccellati, about time you showed up.
You all know "Leaky-eye" Luca
who controls the airport, right?
He was just found dead and disfigured.
The capo Polpo ordered
one of us to investigate.
That guy was a dick.
He had it coming.
He liked picking on the weak...
...and he sold drugs to kids.
He probably took too many drugs
and knocked himself upside the head or something.
Narancia, you may feel that way on the inside,
but don't say it out loud.
Remember the world we live in.
Would you like me to investigate?
You're going to be a capo someday.
There's no need for you to
trouble yourself with something so trivial.
It's fine, I'll do it myself.
By the way, Fugo...
Oh, your guest.
He's been waiting for you all morning.
He's a civilian who runs
a flower shop in Monsanto Plaza.
I already looked into him.
He's an ordinary, responsible gentleman,
but he lost his only daughter six months ago.
Mr. Buccellati...
As you can see, my legs have seen better days.
Normally my wife would be able to assist me...
...but today I came alone, and for that I apologize.
Do you pay your taxes?
I beg your pardon?
Do you always make sure to pay
the taxes you owe to this country on time?
Of course I do...
I don't know what you came here to talk to me about...
...but a civilian like you shouldn't be here.
If you properly pay your taxes...
...then you should go talk to the police
or another law enforcement agency.
The moment we begin discussing this for real...
...you'll owe the organization
a greater debt than you can even imagine.
I, like everyone else in this country...
...worked hard to support my family...
...believed in the law...
...and raised my child to be a law-abiding citizen.
She was my only daughter.
Last September she turned seventeen.
I apologize if I'm asking too much...
...but I'd like to continue this
conversation with you in private.
If you're intent on continuing this conversation...
...know that they have
complete trust in me, and I in them.
You're asking me to interrupt their meal
and tell them to go outside?
I can't do that.
This happened a few months ago...
My wife told me that
our daughter had a boyfriend.
I heard that he was
a young sculptor just starting out.
I didn't have a problem with that,
but even though he was older than my daughter...
...he never came to
introduce himself to us, her parents.
Admittedly, it bothered me.
Shortly after that...
...my daughter jumped from
the roof of his apartment building...
...while clutching a strange stone sculpture
he had made, and landed in the courtyard...
I'm so sorry for losing my composure...
Why does it still hurt so much to cry?
I put my hopes in my daughter...
My daughter was a shining,
beautiful young woman...
I want you to avenge her!
Make that man pay for what he's done!
Slow down, mister...
Are you saying she was murdered?
You think her boyfriend
pushed her off the roof?
Whenever someone is murdered in this town,
I hear about it.
The police refused to continue
their investigation and ruled it a suicide...
Even my lawyer abandoned me!
But I know something
only a member of her family would...
My daughter would never commit suicide!
Both my wife and I
can say that with confidence!
Please!
I want you to settle this once and for all!
Please make that bastard, whose life went uninterrupted, cry these painful tears instead of me!
Life is full of hardships.
You have my sympathies,
but I can't agree to this.
Do you think we're assassins
who would lynch just anyone for pay?
Everyone in this town relies on you!
I just want proper judgment to be passed!
Proper judgment?
Mr. florist, earlier you asked if we could speak in private.
You asked this because you knew how dangerous of a conversation it would be, didn't you?
But what you said about knowing something only a member of her family would know...
I can't take that lightly.
It's hard to believe that no one in law enforcement was moved by those words these past six months.
I truly can't believe it.
The least I can do
is get this boyfriend to talk.
I won't ask for your payment
unless we can confirm beyond a doubt that he's guilty.
Is that acceptable?
Mr. Buccellati!
Mista...
I'd like you to handle this.
Sure thing.
Note: Bad luck
What the hell...
...is this stone?
Note: Please kill me
Mista, make sure you put that
back on its pedestal.
Uh... Did I knock this stone...
...off its pedestal?
Was it here this whole time?
Be careful when you stand up.
You don't want to knock it to the ground.
Mista, Buccellati says we can drive you partway.
Right...
Mista, here's the address of his apartment building.
And here's a picture of the boyfriend.
Find him and make him talk.
Rough him up a bit if need be.
Make sure you get a confession.
You have a tape recorder, right?
Yeah... But how far should I go?
I mean, if it turns out he's a murderer
and really did kill that girl...
We aren't assassins.
Go as far as making sure he can't walk for a few years,
then leave the rest to the police.
I'm sure that will satisfy
the florist's need for revenge.
Hey, where are you going?
Hurry up and get in the car.
I'll leave you behind.
Mista! Do you want a ride or not?
Are you taking a leak?
I'm not! Yes, I want a ride!
I'll be right there!
What's been bothering you, Mista?
Well, something about
that guy's story just seems off to me...
When he said his daughter
jumped off the roof...
...he mentioned she was
holding some kind of stone, right?
Did he say what kind of stone it was?
Stone?
Like, the shape of it...
How big was it?
The boyfriend is a sculptor, right?
He said it looked strange.
But what exactly about it
made it look strange?
He just said it looked strange.
What are you getting at, Mista?
Wait, that stone back there...
S-Stop the car for a second, Fugo!
Stop the car!
Why?
Just stop the damn ca-
Why do you want me
to stop the car?
E-Err, never mind...
I'm just seeing things...
It's nothing.
Are you okay?
How much wine did you drink earlier?
Hey! I'm not drunk!
Excuse me for saying something dumb!
I'm so sorry for raising a fuss!
That's his apartment building, right?
You can let me out here.
Oh, for crying out loud...
Is it really a good idea
for Mista to go at this alone?
Should I accompany him?
No, I'll accompany Mista.
I just remembered that rumor about Stand
users gathering in this town for some reason.
You can take care of the
"Leaky-eye" Luca investigation.
Understood.
So the guy's apartment is
on the seventh floor...
...and above that is the roof.
His name is Scolippi...
The courtyard...
So this is where the florist's daughter...
That's a Stand!
This incident involves a Stand user!
And just what the hell is this stone?!
Buccellati!
Sleeping Slaves