Oasis!
Take this!
I don't have time!
I knew it...
The mold won't grow on you even though you fell...
Cioccolata's Green Day kills anything that's alive.
What's up with your body?
Since it doesn't work on you for some reason,
I'll just have to beat you to a lifeless pulp...
...w-w-with my Oasis!
It's going to take time to defeat him.
With that in mind, the least I can do...
...is lead him away!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 32  Green Day and Oasis Part 3
Now that I've made it this far,
surely the underground man...
There are accidents everywhere!
What's going on?
Look! There's another unconscious person over there!
Hurry and get them help! Over here!
Ambulance! Under the stairs!
Wh-What's...?
Wh-What happened to the mold?!
C-Cioccolata?!
The mold disappeared...
Giorno, Mista...
You beat the man in the helicopter, didn't you?
Secco, it's me.
Did you take care of Buccellati?
Something unexpected has happened on my end.
I'm just about to finish off Giorno,
but I've taken some damage to the head...
So just in case something happens,
I need to tell you this now.
Listen carefully, Secco.
They're headed to the Colosseum.
I overheard the Pistols talking about it.
Apparently someone is waiting there for them...
...and they know the secret to defeating the boss.
That's why Giorno and the others are trying to reach them, and why the boss is trying to stop that from happening.
Heed my words.
You must obtain this secret before anyone else does.
You're the only one I can count on.
What's with him?
Wait, that phone call... Was that...?
Screw you, Cioccolata!
Did you really think I'd feel sad over you?
After you lost?!
You were super smart...
...and you'd play with me and throw me sugar cubes,
not to mention you were loaded.
And you were super strong on top of that...
Or so I thought.
I figured I'd never have to worry about anything
as long as I listened to you.
But you were a total wimp!
You lost like a little bitch!
I'm already over you, scumbag!
I hate your guts!
He knows!
He knows that we're trying to reach the Colosseum!
He wants to find out the secret!
I won't let you!
Half...?
Take this!
Sticky Fingers!
What?!
Oh yeah, doesn't "Colosseum"
kinda sound like "Kill as ya see 'em"?
Don't you think so, Mr. Language Teacher?
Figured I should ask before I kill you.
Until now, I thought the worst would be over
once we stopped the mold coming from the man in the helicopter.
But this situation keeps getting worse...
The real threat is this man who can move underground!
If I let him get away and reach the Colosseum first...
...he'll go on a rampage!
You're... kind of a pain... Buccellati...
But you knew that, didn't you?
I'm faster and stronger than you at close range!
What a pain!
You're finished!
You sure can think fast.
You got away again...
Just barely, though.
But your body is really weird.
The heck is your deal?
You're covered in broken glass,
but you're barely bleeding.
Did you... also just see that?
Hey... What do you think that is?
It came from the middle set of arches, right?
Something was shining.
It happened earlier, too.
Oh? There's something there in the dark!
Was that...?
I saw it... I got a good look!
It was a reflection!
Someone was looking at us with binoculars!
The guy you wanna see is definitely there!
He was in a wheelchair, wasn't he?
I think I saw some prosthetics, too!
Is he a cripple?
His secret is all mine!
I don't care what's up with your body...
I'm gonna end you, Buccellati!
Are you mocking me?
You went into the ground with your zipper?
Are you copying me?!
Do you think you stand a chance against me...
...by going underground?!
Take this! Oas-
He's not hiding... He's moving...
These vibrations...
He's trying to go somewhere...
Y-Y-You lousy knockoff!
Are you seriously pulling a trick like this against me?!
You and your piss-stained zipper guy!
H-How dare you rip off my technique?!
The only good copying me is gonna do...
...is show just how screwed you really are!
You'll never reach the Colosseum!
Everything around me is turning soft...
He decided to pursue me!
But this noise...
It's barreling toward me with no sign of slowing down...
Apparently sound reverberates
better through liquids than solids.
Like water, for example...
Does that mean he can hear me moving, too?
You got further away than I thought,
but you can't run forever!
I can feel it...
I can feel how far away you are!
You're to my left, twenty meters ahead...
Now you went left.
Just ten more meters.
Seven more meters...
Five meters...
I'm not gonna strangle you.
I'll bury you alive!
You dug your own grave
and buried yourself inside, Buccellati!
You think you can escape my punches...
...when you're surrounded by walls of dirt?
Just two more meters!
A water pipe?
Did you think you could trick me by cutting it?
For real?
The fact that you're pulling dumb shit like this
tells me you're starting to feel cornered!
You basically just admitted that with your abilities...
...you'll lose once my Oasis catches up to you!
I don't know where you are,
but I can tell you're within twenty meters of me.
You're intentionally staying still so I won't find you.
What else could it be?
Are you trying to come up with a last minute plan?
I guess you are pretty quick-witted.
But...
You're not gonna feel safe much longer...
...as quick-witted as you are...
That's not the same noise as earlier.
What could it be?
It's coming from all directions.
The stone pavement on the ground...
...turns to mud when my Oasis touches it.
But once it moves away from my body...
...it hardens again.
Hey, Buccellati!
You may stand a chance here!
If you stay totally still, maybe you'll survive...
I mean, I heard a story about how a death row inmate
miraculously survived three hangings...
...since either the rope broke
or the gallows malfunctioned!
I can't take this.
I need to go back up!
But I can't just run along the ground, either!
I knew this might happen,
but if he doesn't make it here...
...I'll have to destroy the arrow.
I've put my hope in them and this arrow.
The only ones who can surpass King Crimson
and its ability to control time...
...are those who know the true power of the arrow.
I'm not capable of wielding it.
They are.
Twelve years ago,
I acquired this arrow after fighting a battle in Egypt.
The fear this arrow has brought forth...
...will never come to an end if they don't make it here!
Jean Pierre Polnareff
(36 years old, Frenchman)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world."
(A quote from a certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
This profile on them is a bit ironic.
They became gangsters
after being rejected by society...
...yet they're the only ones trying to save the world
from falling into the hands of evil.
But in the end...
...will this Buccellati be able to make it here?
This was all for nothing if he doesn't win.
I'll be forced to destroy the arrow
and its secret if he fails.
Right now, the only thing I can do is sit here and wait.
Soon this will begin.
I've been waiting for such a long time...
...doing my best to protect the arrow's true power.
I-It's too much!
I'm at my limit!
He moved!
He couldn't take it anymore and moved!
Twelve meters to the right. Buccellati...
He's planning to hide below the Colosseum...
...so he can avoid all my stone spears!
That's not happening!
H-He's coming!
I can hear him catching up to me!
I feel your reverberations!
You're just ten meters straight ahead!
Eight meters...
He's moving faster than me!
Sticky Fingers!
You know...
...I thought you were planning something.
Buccellati, is this all you have up your sleeve?
Though I gotta hand it to you for being the only person to ever hide from my Oasis for even a second.
But you're finished, now!
I'm closer than before. I'll find you soon.
The longer you hide...
...the closer you come to defeat!
Wh-What...?
M-My skin...
Don't tell me...
Even the stone pavement is turning into mud!
So it only makes sense that your body...
...would start turning to mud once I got closer to you!
I can hear you!
I know where you are!
I have you for sure this time, I know it!
I'm just a meter and a half away.
So you've already made it to the Colosseum...
You were so close.
Take this!
The secret will be mine!
Sticky Fingers!
To be honest with you,
I don't know how I ended up like this...
...but I can barely feel pain anymore,
even with several fractured bones.
My heart has stopped,
so I'm not bleeding very much, either.
I've become numb to pain.
That's why I was waiting for this...
I'm sure my eardrums will be able to handle
the pain I'm about to put them through.
The thing I was waiting for...
...was for you to drag anything
and everything into this muddied ground.
Street lamps, street signs, parked cars...
...and most importantly, their tires.
Whoops.
I guess you can't hear me anymore.
You cheater...
Y-You really did it now...
But... this isn't a big deal!
I can still hear!
I heard the tire popping!
I know where you are!
You're right there, Buccellati!
M-My leg!
Wh-Where am...?
Wh-Why?
Wh-Where is he?!
What did he do to me?!
How did I think that car was him?!
Your eardrums were ruptured.
Your Stand that allows you to travel
through the ground... Oasis, was it?
Now that you can't use your ears as a radar,
your ability is useless.
I know what you're doing, asshole!
You're gonna try to destroy my eardrums, aren't you?!
You think I won't be able to move underground if you destroy my ears, don't you?!
What a dumb idea!
Get back!
Stay away from me!
I don't intend to take your life.
But now that you're aware of
the man waiting for us at the Colosseum...
...I can't just let you go free.
I'm going to have to knock you out.
Damn you!
You're gonna try to knock me out, aren't you?!
S-Stay away from me!
Stop talking.
This isn't even a conversation.
S-Stay away!
Score!
Th-The instant you attack me,
I'm gonna turn this kid to mud!
Then I'll throw him at you and run!
You don't wanna kill a kid, do you, idiot?!
Change of plans!
I was planning on beating the boss earlier...
...but now I'm just gonna report this
to the organization and get a nice reward instead!
Working for the organization will be a lot easier!
Hey, brat!
Get me a taxi!
Raise your hand and flag down a taxi for me!
You better listen to me!
Hey!
Do you hear me?!
You dumb brat!
Hurry up... and get me... a taxi!
Buccellati!
Why are you walking over to me?!
Can't you hear me?!
Your max range is just two meters!
I'm sure of it!
You probably think I can't get away
since I screwed up and hurt my leg!
Don't underestimate me!
I'm gonna kill him!
You couldn't reach me!
I'm out of your range!
You dense motherfucker!
You just grazed my ha...
Wh-What the...?!
A-A zipper!
Dammit, my throat!
It was barely even worth prediction,
but my vision showed...
...that there was no way
Buccellati would sacrifice a kid like me.
Dammit!
I need to get rid of this!
Burnable Waste Pickup
Mon, Wed, Fri
Ah, Cioccolata!
Cioccolata!
I came here after tracing
the signal from Secco's cellphone.
But the situation here is different
from what the boss described to me.
To think that Secco had already lost...
Since they work as a pair,
Cioccolata is also probably...
It seems Buccellati is here alone.
Where are Giorno Giovanna, Narancia, and the others?
Wh-What? My body suddenly...
All my strength is...
It can't be...
My vision is blurring, too...
Am I finally out of time?
I knew this moment would come...
But now?
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
His Name is Diavolo