Doppio...
Have you already forgotten that I gave you a portion of my King Crimson's ability?
Now is the time to use it!
You have King Crimson's arms and Epitaph at your disposal!
Calm yourself and watch for any movements.
Then try your best to predict
anything that could happen around you.
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Look carefully and predict anything that could happen...
Episodio 27  King Crimson vs. Metallica
Look ten seconds forward!
B-Birds!
The birds flew away like in my vision!
B-Boss!
I just saw him!
In the vision Epitaph showed me,
he conceals himself ten seconds from now!
I saw something in the shape of a human
blending into the rocks in the background!
B-But right now I can't see him!
I can't see him with my own eyes!
That's Risotto.
He's concealing himself through unknown means.
Could it be...?
You may not be able to see him with your eyes,
but you can with your visions.
Look a few seconds into the future
to see how he's going to attack you, Doppio!
Th-There he is!
H-He moved!
Wh-What?!
I-I have a situation, Boss!
In ten seconds, s-scissors are
going to b-burst out of my throat!
Calm yourself, Doppio.
What you witnessed was not your death.
Risotto was a hitman in my organization
whom no one could find.
Brace yourself for the pain
you are about to endure.
Watch carefully for how he's going to attack you...
...just a few seconds in the future!
The fact that he's drawing near me, Boss...
...tells me he definitely doesn't have
a remote-controlled Stand.
Th-The vision showed scissors stuck inside my throat...
Are you telling me the future can't be changed, Boss?
Correct.
Now that you've seen the vision,
you must brace yourself.
It is an inevitability that you will have
a pair of scissors stuck in your throat.
But see through it!
See through his attack and act accordingly!
If you see through his methods,
you can exploit his weakness!
Then once you are within two meters of him, strike him with King Crimson's arms, Doppio!
Dammit!
There you are!
Take this!
You're sloppy.
But then again,
in all my years of being a hitman...
...you're the first to land a blow this close to me.
How intriguing.
How did you know?
Your ability interests me.
Even so, you'll meet your end!
I-Impossible!
How did he get them under my skin?
I'm sure he didn't lay even a single finger on me,
and my mouth has been shut this whole time!
A-And his Stand never even touched me...
But somehow the scissors
are coming out on their own!
I-If I don't do something,
they're going to tear my throat apart!
I need to get them out!
His actions just now...
I thought I would be able to
slice open his throat just now...
...but it's like he knew I was
going to put those scissors there.
He put his hand to his throat and defended himself.
Something is happening here.
I need to be more careful...
...so that my next attack will end this.
Damn you!
Dammit... I still don't know...
The boss is gonna yell at me...
It's still a mystery how he's
making himself disappear, too.
B-But this damage...
T-The strength in my legs is...
Th-That's...!
What's wrong, Doppio?
Did you see his attack?
B-Boss!
You weren't able to see it?
Then move away from there immediately.
Figure out where he is by
forcing him to pursue you!
Y-You asshole...
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to see through him for sure this time!
Damn...
I'll get within two meters of him no matter what!
You just witnessed King Crimson's next vision, did you not?
What did you see?
I asked you a question, Doppio!
A right foot, Boss.
In just a few seconds,
he's gonna come at me with scissors again.
I saw it flying off.
A foot is definitely about to go flying.
What did you just say, Doppio?!
H-He's coming!
I saw him!
Flee immediately!
Why didn't you run the moment
you saw that vision, Doppio?
Risotto Nero, the hitman.
While his movements are careful,
he's already made preparations to kill me.
I already can't put any strength into my legs.
I don't think I can run.
Razor blades, scissors...
He's been waiting for me to lose all my strength!
This is bad.
Doppio won't be able to win.
Even if I were to come out now,
it would take at least ten seconds.
This could be dire...
The damage he would sustain from
losing a foot would be severe.
Somehow, I need to minimize the damage.
I told you to flee from there immediately!
He's going to kill you!
But Boss, if I may interject...
That's exactly why I shouldn't move.
I've used up all my strength.
It'll be easier to figure this out if I don't move.
I've been trying to figure out where he's been
attacking me from with the razor blades and scissors.
But that's not going to help me!
There you are!
His ability...
...allows him to create and control razor blades made from natural iron inside living creatures!
This frog and I being so worn out
is what tipped me off!
You use your Stand ability to manipulate the iron within living creatures to create razor blades!
And since the razor blades
came out of the frog before me...
...you must be approaching from that direction!
Th-This man!
Looks like the prediction was right.
A foot did go flying off.
Now the mystery behind the enemy's form is starting to unravel itself, Boss.
Huh? Boss?
That's strange.
I could have sworn I had a phone on me...
Where did I drop it?
I mean, that's a frog...
Oh, there it is!
How the heck did I drop it down there?
It's underneath these rocks and covered in sand!
This is awful!
I need to report this to the boss as soon as possible...
D-Did it break?
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Yes!
Even though electronics are so
light and small these days, they're really sturdy!
Hello? Congratulate me, Boss.
He can't move anymore.
Impossible...
Well done, Doppio.
My Doppio...
Should I be the one to finish him off?
Or should I wait until you get here, Boss?
I want to personally ensure that
Risotto Nero is finished off for good.
Leave him to me.
Get closer, Doppio.
Get within two meters of him...
I will take it from there.
Until then, get closer to him.
Got it!
I'll get closer, Boss!
Inside the wound where his foot was severed...
They're wriggling...
Risotto's Stand is inside his body!
You have the power of precognition
or something to that effect, don't you?
You had a good idea of
what would happen and how I would react.
There's no other way you could have
seen through my position or means of attack.
I'm certain you were an incapable,
inexperienced runt when this fight began.
But... just who are you at this moment?
You suddenly became filled with confidence.
And what's with that look?
Those aren't the eyes of a young man.
It's as if you're two people at once.
Could that be what's going on?
No, I misspoke.
It's not even that it "could" be...
I'm much closer than I thought...
...to the person I've been looking for!
Two years.
It's been two years since we were turned into leashed pups, quivering with fear.
You're definitely something more
than what we've been looking for.
I'm sure of it.
I want to know what you are.
I want to see your true form!
I want to know what you are when I kill you... no matter what!
Risotto Nero
Metallica
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Solido Naso...
That must be one of the boss's aliases.
He wouldn't hide his daughter so quick if it weren't.
We came all the way out here
just to waste our fucking time, dammit.
But if we can get his daughter,
maybe we can figure out who the boss is!
Right, Bro?
We haven't been able to do shit
since what happened to Sorbet and Gelato.
I wonder who's guarding his daughter.
Pericolo isn't a Stand user,
so maybe Polpo or someone close to him?
Maybe we should just go to Naples
and ask him in person.
Don't get yourselves worked up.
It's times like these where we
need to stay calm before taking action.
I understand how you all feel,
but we need to bury what happened to Sorbet and Gelato.
Failure means death.
I'm riled up, but...
Whichever one of us gets too worked up
is the one who will die.
The foot I chopped off!
I was right... Risotto Nero...
I see what your power is now!
Magnetism!
You're maintaining control from that distance
with your Stand's ability to control magnetism!
You took control of the iron inside me...
...and made me throw up razor blades
and scissors by creating them inside my body!
You can make yourself disappear by
covering yourself in iron powder...
...and painting the scenery around you
to camouflage yourself!
Correct.
You may have figured out how
Metallica works, but it's too late.
Because you're already finished...
Iron.
It's an element that exists everywhere in this world.
Of course, it's in things such as
sand, spring water, and plants.
Iron also happens to be a
naturally occurring material found in humans.
What are you doing, Doppio?
You predicted his movements!
I will not allow you to sustain further damage!
Th-This is...
B-Boss!
Because you saw through my ability,
my foot was severed.
But you're already finished.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Large amounts of iron can be found in
vegetables like spinach and meats like liver.
It's an important substance that
runs through your bloodstream.
What do you think happens when
all iron in your body is expelled at once?
Simply put, your blood turns
a horrible shade of yellow and you die.
The iron in your blood captures the oxygen
that enters your body when you breathe...
...and carries it throughout your body.
Without it, precious oxygen doesn't
reach your fingertips or your brain.
Essentially, now that you've
been robbed of so much iron...
...in spite of how hard you're breathing,
your body isn't taking in any oxygen.
You'll be a walking corpse before you actually die.
Now, then...
I wonder what I should do next.
Should I wait until you croak, or...
Since we seem to be short on time...
...should I go over there and finish you off?
B-Boss...
That's...
They're near the mansion!
It's Buccellati!
He finally showed himself!
Narancia's there too, and...
So is Abbacchio!
What? Abbacchio's there?
We're running out of time...
Doppio, finish him off with your next attack!
Predict Risotto's actions with your vision!
I'm already looking!
Risotto will come around my right side, then...
He disappears!
I can't see him!
It can't be...
What do you see, Doppio?
What do you see?
I... I'm gonna turn the tables, dammit!
I'm gonna finish him off, Boss!
In the few seconds I have before
my vision becomes a reality...
...I'll blow his head off instead!
Just like I severed his foot earlier!
H-Here he comes!
Don't do anything else, Doppio!
There's nothing more you can do.
Listen well, Doppio.
This is important.
Don't waste any more energy.
I'm heading there as we speak.
It will be a few more seconds,
but I will deal with Risotto.
A few seconds?!
That's too late!
He'll attack me at any moment!
Handle it!
If my full ability can reach you,
I can erase the time you witnessed in your vision!
But I'm the one who's about to die!
I'll kill him first!
Doppio!
This is the only way!
This is the only way to ensure your survival!
Your body has reached its limit.
I won't allow you to waste
any more energy on my behalf!
You're going to kill him?
You of all people could never
locate him a second time!
...But what if I can, Boss?
If I know where he is...
If he's going to use his ability to try to steal even more iron from my body...
H-Here he comes!
He's attacking!
The strength to pull...
He should have the strength
to pull the iron from my body!
The scalpel is pointing in the
direction of the magnetic force!
There you are, Risotto!
I figured you would try that.
Magnetism pulls at iron.
You thought you could determine my location
by the direction of the iron being pulled.
Unfortunately for you, however...
...what you sensed was Metallica
producing magnetism in my severed foot.
I left it there.
I learned from my mistake
after you chopped off my foot.
I need to make the best of what happened.
There's hardly any oxygen left in your body.
You are completely finished.
You shouldn't even be able to move an inch.
You're different from before.
You're brimming with confidence, now.
The excessive physical changes to your body...
...and the way you talk to yourself...
I get it now.
I finally figured out who you really are!
Yes, I seem to recall something like this happening in 16th century Germany.
There exist people in this world
with multiple personalities.
In some cases, the effects aren't just mental.
There have reported cases of people's bodies,
physiques, and even the language they speak changing!
Originally, I thought you were
the boss's most trusted subordinate.
But you...
To think that you...
I can't wait!
Once you die,
I'll be able to see what your face truly looks like!
There's nothing you can do!
I'm keeping my distance.
You have no strength to resist.
You're out of options!
I've won!
I'm going to chop off your head!
This is the end!
Take this!
Metallica!
Wh-What?
Risotto...
I told Doppio...
...that you were no longer an enemy he could handle.
D-Don't tell me...
I knew it.
The enemy was already here.
But I shot right through him!
I got him good, too!
Y-You...
Since my blood has been robbed of iron
and is no longer carrying oxygen through my body...
...it's as if I weren't breathing at all.
Which means the only signal
Aerosmith is tracking right now...
How many enemies are there, Narancia?
Just one!
Only one person is breathing on that cliff!
...is your breathing, Risotto.
I see.
This matches what Doppio
witnessed in his vision, but...
I would have won...
I would have won for sure, but...
But you had already thrown the scalpels at them...
Boss...
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Beneath a Looming Sky