kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
None can escape their chosen fate
Only the result in which you are destroyed remains
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 39  Sleeping Slaves
Buccellati?
This stone is shaped just like...
You!
Are you the sculptor?
Who the hell are you?
Don't even think of trying anything!
I didn't kill you since I was ordered not to,
but now that I know you're a Stand user...
...there's no guarantee that
I won't blow another hole between your eye sockets!
Who are you?
How do you know Buccellati?
I'm curious about the florist's
daughter's death by falling, too, but...
Why did you follow me
from the restaurant?
Daughter?
Are you a police officer?
No, the police wouldn't-
Listen, you sick fuck!
I'm the one asking questions here!
Just answer me truthfully!
Focus on that.
Got it?
Don't make any unnecessary moves.
I consider lying
an unnecessary move, too, capisce?
Good.
I'll ask you one question at a time.
First off, are you a gangster?
Are you affiliated with an organization?
I can always find out for sure later if I want.
N-No...
I'm just a sculptor...
I'm not famous,
but I make a living off of it.
Then how did you become a Stand user?
I don't even know what a Stand is.
If you mean this ability...
...it started happening to me
when I was a kid.
Was it the same for you?
Hey!
Next question.
Why did you follow me from the restaurant?
And how do you know Buccellati?
Buccellati...
That name, Buccellati...
Is it his?
Please, let me see him!
He came here with you, right?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You didn't answer my question, dipshit!
I-I don't think you'll like my answer...
...but the stone moves on its own,
regardless of how I feel.
It's been that way since I was a kid.
Its power is beyond my control.
The stone didn't follow you.
It was following him...
Buccellati.
Oh, is that right?
Are you really that set on never
being able to hold a chisel ever again?
I hate to break it to you,
but Buccellati isn't anywhere near here, idiot!
You're the one who's lying here.
Buccellati is in this building with us.
Let me see him!
His life depends on-
Don't fuck with me!
Why did you kill the florist's daughter?
What are you aft-
What do you think you're doing?!
I told you not to try anything!
The stone just left...
What?!
One of the greatest sculptors to ever live,
Michelangelo, once said...
"I don't have any thoughts
when I take hold of a marble slab.
Every block of stone
already has a statue inside it...
...and it is the task of the sculptor to discover it."
What are you rambling about, asshole?
I'll kill you if you don't hurry up
and bring that stone back here!
Michelangelo's point was that
the ultimate form isn't something you can carve out consciously.
Its destined form
lies within the stone itself.
He could see a sculpture's
destined form as he worked.
The truth is that
I didn't sculpt the stone into the shape of Buccellati...
...nor did your bullets.
It took on its destined form.
The statue had a hole in its chest
that was gushing out blood.
I don't know if it will happen
in a few days or a few months...
...but Buccellati will soon meet this end.
We're all slaves to fate.
That's the meaning of my ability, Rolling Stones.
This is your last chance!
Bring the stone back here right now!
If you die, so will your Stand!
You get me?
If he touches my Rolling Stones,
he can die without suffering.
I wanted to see him so I could
hear his final words.
Wh-What's with this guy?
Is he making fun of me?
How the hell can he be so calm, dammit?!
Have it your way!
You really want your brains plastered all over the wall?
Look!
I have three shots left!
This is how you control destiny!
I can tell that you're trying to do something to Buccellati,
so bring that stone back here right now!
You're out of time,
and you're out of chances!
I told you.
There's nothing more I can do.
Bring it back right now, motherfucker!
The florist had weak legs, right?
He doesn't know it yet...
...but it's an early symptom of
a disease affecting his internal organs.
He'll most likely survive, though.
When his daughter died,
her organs were preserved in an organ bank.
He'll receive them as transplants.
The girl found out from the stone that
she'd contract the same disease in a few months.
She understood and believed it.
Rather than dying in pain,
she decided to die while she was still healthy for her father's sake.
She wholly accepted the stone, and...
The stone allowed her to die without suffering,
and in such a way that her organs weren't damaged.
You have some balls to say that,
considering you killed her!
Wh-What?!
It's a misfire, Mista!
That bullet was a dud!
No way!
That bullet is Number 5's responsibility!
Aww, why me?
I can't die yet.
The stone hasn't yet carved out my demise.
Y-You really think I'm gonna get
two misfires in a row, asshole?
You've begun to understand
the shape of destiny.
You've lost the will to kill me.
Am I wrong?
Wh-What's with this guy? Shit!
What the hell is he talking about?
Is he still messing with me?
Hey, Fugo, you there?
Tell Buccellati that
the sculptor is a Stand user!
What?
The scumbag keeps bringing up Buccellati...
...but I can't tell what's going on anymore!
What are you talking about, Mista?
You two didn't meet up yet?
Huh?
Buccellati followed you
into the apartment building a while ago.
He went in right after
you got out of the car.
Hello? Mista? What's wrong?
What?!
Rolling Stones
Scolippi
Power: ?
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: ?
Wh-What's his number, Fugo?
I have to find him!
What's the number on the phone
Buccellati has with him right now?
Are you okay?
The phone you're calling right now is Buccellati's.
Hey, Mista? Hello?
Hurry, Pistols!
Find Buccellati!
Mista? Hello?
Hey, wake up, you sculpting scumbag!
How can I stop the stone?
Hey, wake the fuck up!
Answer me, asshole!
What do I gotta do to stop the stone
from reaching Buccellati?
P-Please... Tell me...
I think I kinda get
what you were saying earlier.
But what the hell am I
supposed to do about it?
There's no way I can let Buccellati touch the stone...
I just can't...
Please, tell me...
It will be easier for you...
...if you don't defy the stone.
No one has managed it before,
but if you somehow destroyed the stone...
...or somehow change its shape, then perhaps...
Found him, Mista!
We found Buccellati!
Number One said that he found him!
Buccellati's on the seventh floor!
The stairs!
Buccellati's climbing the stairs!
What?!
Th-This is bad!
The stone!
The stone's on the stairs, too!
It's right in front of Buccellati!
Stop him, Number One!
Tell him not to touch that stone!
It's no use, Mista!
Number One's bullet doesn't
have enough power left to make it!
Buccellati!
Yee-haw!
P-Pistols?
We did it!
That was a close one!
It's falling apart and changing shape!
It's good that we changed its shape and all, but...
...b-but I get the feeling
we made things worse...
Pistols, what is going on here?
Is that a Stand?
And its shape...
Run, Buccellati!
Sticky Fingers!
Don't attack it!
You're screwed if you touch it!
Run over this way, Buccellati!
Mista!
You can't touch the stone!
If you lay even a finger on it, you'll die!
What do you mean?
I'll give you the details later!
Is the stone a Stand?
Hurry and get downstairs!
Get out of this building and
run as far away as you can!
What?
This is how it got out of the elevator earlier...
Sh-Shit!
These stairs are dangerous!
We need to find another way down!
Taking the stairs isn't gonna work!
Go up, Buccellati!
Wh-Where is it?
It's not here! Dammit!
Where did it go?!
Mista, what's going on?
Sh-Shit!
Above you, Buccellati!
Buccellati!
Wh-What's with the face on this stone?
If we can somehow destroy the stone
or change its shape...
Mista!
If I smash it into the pavement from this height,
it should shatter to pieces!
Goddammit!
You're not getting away!
That's impossible! Mista!
Shit...
What that sculpting asshole said earlier...
...turned out to be true...
If you don't appear in the stone,
it's not your time to die...
What on earth have you been doing, Mista?
You left the tape recorder
on the car seat, idiot.
Hey... Nice seeing you, Fugo...
What was that stone?
Mista, what chain of
coincidences led to this?
Uh... You should be fine now.
I, uh... don't even know where to begin...
Anyway,
as for the florist's daughter's death...
The sculptor was kinda the culprit...
...but also kinda not the culprit...
I roughed him up enough to land him
in the hospital for a few months, though...
You seriously defy all logic.
Was he an enemy or an ally?
Was it suicide or murder?
Explain it so it makes sense!
That's the thing, though...
It's kind of hard, uh...
to sort it out in my head.
Long story short,
we destroyed the stone and it's all over now.
Hey, Buccellati,
I'll look into the incident with "Leaky-eye" Luca.
No, the investigation will be over sooner if I do it myself
rather than listen to your summary of it.
I can handle it alone.
Fugo, try to get a decent explanation out of Mista
so we can explain what happened here to the florist.
Buccellati, I'm willing to do anything for you...
I'm not sure how I should say this...
...but do you really think I can
make sense of this guy?
You can stop thinking now.
We'll just have Abbacchio's Moody Blues help us.
"It's all over..."
It's all over, you say?
If you had just accepted Rolling Stones,
this would have ended peacefully...
We're all slaves to fate.
We can't ever change
what has already taken shape.
I don't know these people,
but a difficult path lies before them...
A path along which many of them will perish.
But...
...are they all like this?
He jumped from up there to destroy the stone
for his friend, Buccellati.
Perhaps the path they're about to take
holds some deeper meaning.
Their hardships may end up
being someone else's hope...
...and be revealed to serve a higher purpose.
I can't wish for their safety,
but I pray that they are sleeping slaves.
Sleeping slaves
who will find meaning once they awaken.
Hey, hurry up!
Who's gonna heal Buccellati's injuries
if you don't hurry up?
Hey, Giorno!
Whoa!
Be careful, Trish!
Thanks.
Something suddenly appeared at my feet...
Trish?
Hey, Trish!
Wh-Where'd you go, Trish?
Trish!
Hey, Giorno!
Where the hell did Trish go?!
Unbelievable...
Trish is right there, Mista.
Mista, Giorno, I'm right here.
I didn't trip on that stone.
It's what was in its shadow.
Don't leave me behind.
If you leave me here...
...I have no idea how many days it would take
to reach the Colosseum.
P-Polnareff?!
Mr. Polnareff.
You're still alive.
But if all our souls were switched back...
...then your soul... and the tortoise's...
My body is dead.
But the moment my soul was sucked out...
...I was able to cling to this tortoise's Stand.
I can't leave this key,
but I decided to live here as a ghost for a while.
Well, it's great that you're okay and all...
...but this isn't over yet!
We're headed to the Colosseum
to heal Buccellati's wounds!
Buccellati? But his soul...
Hey, what are you doing?!
Oh, uh, sorry!
I'm starting to think you were right...
I do smell kinda weird...
So this is what I smell like?
Maybe I'll start using cologne...
Really?
Maybe I said some weird things earlier,
but only because I was freaked out...
It doesn't really bother me anymore.
It almost smells a bit nostalgic.
Really? Really?!
Yeah.
But your fingers are still weird.
What are you going to do with it?
Those who carry the will of the deceased
must continue onward.
I won't destroy this arrow.
Keep the arrow inside the tortoise.
That will do, Giorno.
That is the duty of those who have survived.
Let's go...
...to the Colosseum.
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights