That's perfect!
That's the perfect spot!
Yee-haw!
Good thinking, Mista!
The attack can't affect us
as long as we keep moving upward.
I see now...
I'm starting to understand how they've
lived this long despite betraying the boss.
Secco, did you get the footage?
Did you capture the desperation
on their faces as they clung for dear life?
Good!
Good, good, good, good...
You captured it perfectly, Secco!
The more a person's curiosity is aroused, the more mental strength they exhibit.
Humans evolved due to being
far more curious than any other creature.
I want to see it already...
I just want to see people like him die already!
Oh, right.
Sorry, I almost forgot.
You get a treat for taking such a great picture.
Does two sound good?
You want three?
Three whole treats?
You little glutton!
Well, fine, you can have three.
Get ready, Secco!
Here's three of them!
Oh, sorry.
Good!
Good, good, good, good...
You really blow me away, Secco!
Now go!
Go after Buccellati and the others, Secco!
You and your Stand, Oasis!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 30  Green Day and Oasis Part 1
So what's the plan, Buccellati?
We can't go back out to sea.
If Giorno is right and the mold's range
is extended by the corpses...
...then instead of tracking down the user,
we'd be better off finding a car and leaving the village.
Reaching Rome is our top priority right now.
Giorno, how is Narancia's treatment going?
Treating him here is difficult.
His wounds are filled with living mold.
All right, Mista.
Climbing up should be safe.
We'll climb up those stairs and find a car.
Buccellati has been acting coldly.
He didn't even ask Narancia
whether he was okay or not.
And earlier,
when you were struggling to get out of the boat...
...what did he say?
He coldly ordered you to throw the tortoise.
Why are you so upset?
Of course he did.
I'm the one who got in the boat.
It's good we made it out alive,
but what I did could have gotten us all killed.
And if Buccellati didn't
yell at me to throw the tortoise...
...I could have dropped it in the sea.
I know that!
I'm just saying that he's been
acting cold toward everyone.
You know...
I don't really get how girls think, but...
...were you hoping he'd ask if we're okay?
I know Buccellati pretty well,
but it's gonna take time for you to understand him.
Who says I want to?
Well, right now we need to
focus on getting to Rome.
You can figure out how you feel later.
I'm not feeling so good right now...
I need to rest...
Right now we can only go up...
...but if we get into a situation
that makes us have to go lower...
We'll be fine.
This village is built on the side of a mountain.
All the roads go uphill.
And outside the village, cars are still running.
Its range hasn't extended that far yet.
We need to find a car
and leave here as soon as possible.
Reaching Rome is our top priority.
Which car should we take?
One with a corpse next to it.
Ideally, the corpse will be holding the key.
It was just the mold
breaking the corpse's hand.
I'll watch the rear.
You hurry toward the parking lot.
Got it.
Mista, it wasn't just that...
Something... Something is wrong...
Hurry and go up!
R-Right!
What are you doing, Mista?!
I told you to go up!
I already am, Buccellati!
But...
...we're sinking!
We're moving away from the wall!
What's going on?
The whole staircase is being pulled underground!
This isn't the Stand user
who's been making the mold!
They have an ally!
This is bad!
We need to get up there!
The mold's gonna get us
if we go any lower!
Jump onto the wall!
My gun!
We're not the ones sinking...
The whole staircase is sinking,
almost like it's melting!
What is that?
The enemy!
The enemy is coming for us from below!
Mista!
Climb up the wall!
Sticky Fingers!
He's fast... This guy is fast...
And this is bizarre, but...
...the ground feels solid when I
touch it with Sticky Fingers' hands.
This is a solid stone staircase,
but I'm sinking into it...
And that thing is somehow
freely moving around under solid ground...
This is bad!
I can't tell where it is!
Where are they coming from?
Can you hear me, Sex Pistols?
Yee-haw!
Get back here!
One coming at us from beneath the ground,
and the other with a flesh-eating mold Stand...
Both of their Stand abilities
compliment each other.
The two of them are more compatible
than any team we've encountered so far.
Are their damn pinkies tied together
by the red thread of fate or what?
I found one, Buccellati.
The corpse of a driver still clinging to their key.
You bastard!
I just got a look at the enemy!
He jumped from the stairs
and dove into the wall!
Th-This is...!
Run, Mista!
It's too fast!
Even if we make it to the car,
we won't have enough time to start the engine!
I'll hold him off!
Keep going!
Don't stop, Mista!
The ground is still hard!
Your bullets will bounce off!
If the sinking ground is somehow still hard...
...then my best chance is
when I get pulled under!
This guy's a close-range power type.
His range is short.
I'll be able to see him
once he tries to pull me in again.
That's when I'll get him!
There!
He showed himself!
Now!
Eat lead!
Mista!
This figures...
I guess I'm not surprised a
close-range power type can deflect bullets...
Then again...
If you wanna deflect my bullets,
I can have Pistols do the same!
The first three shots I fired should...
What?!
He's not gonna finish me off?
So he thinks he can kill me
whenever he wants now that I'm hurt?
Hurry and grab the key, Buccellati!
Start the engine!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and get in the car!
As long as we manage to leave
this village by car, I'll be satisfied.
All I want is for us to reach Rome.
Where are you going, Buccellati?!
Wh-What?!
So you can track us from
underground no matter where we go?
What a terrifying ability.
But can you tell where I'm headed right now?
I guess you couldn't.
You had no idea!
Arri Arri Arri Arri!
Arrivederci!
Green Day
Cioccolata
Power: A
Speed: C
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Arri Arri Arri Arri!
Arrivederci!
My...
My face!
What?
Hey, Cioccolata...
Three days ago... You heard, right?
The boss sent a Stand to the airplane... Notorious B.I.G...
Hey, Secco...
Shouldn't you be tracking them down right now?
Why did you call me?
Hey, Cioccolata...
This is important! I mean it!
Notorious... Is that thing...
Is it alive?
Or is it a dead Stand?
Where is this coming from?
It's an easy question!
Tell me!
If Notorious was here,
would Green Day's mold grow on it?
On the dead Stand?
Notorious B.I.G...
Are you talking about the one whose user died,
but the energy from his grudge let his Stand survive?
I have no idea.
I'd be curious to know, but I couldn't tell you.
But what I can tell you is that Green Day will rot absolutely anything that is alive.
Its mold doesn't grow on things
that aren't alive like rocks and stuff, right?
Enough with this!
Quit wasting time and get footage of those guys dying already!
But that's the thing, Cioccolata!
Look up the hill!
Look at the road!
Hey, Secco...
Why is there a car leaving the village?
Don't tell me they're the ones in that car!
Why are you just watching them?
Hey, Cioccolata...
I can't believe this...
He hit me in the face!
That Buccellati guy...
There wasn't any mold growing on him...
...even though he jumped down!
I can't believe he got me after doing that!
That shouldn't have worked!
His body won't grow mold!
What the hell is going on?!
I haven't the slightest.
Back there, I was almost sure...
...that you had jumped straight down.
You really scared me, Buccellati.
Did you hang onto the wall with a zipper?
Must have been a close one.
It doesn't look like the mold got you at all.
Mista, you should rest.
I closed up your wounds,
but they'll bleed if you keep moving.
I'll keep watch for any cars following us.
Sure...
Buccellati, your wrist...
Did you hurt it?
Please let me see it.
Can you hear me, Buccellati?
We're in danger if you're incubating mold.
Please let me see it.
That's...!
Th-That's impossible...
His skin is ice cold...
A-And his pulse...
Giorno, did you just ask me something?
I didn't quite catch that.
What's... going on?
Impossible...
It can't be true!
Th-That's right...
This isn't the first time this happened...
I thought I had just imagined it back then,
but when we left Venice...
I guess I hurt myself.
Looks like I'm running out of time.
The feeling in my skin is slowly...
Actually...
...maybe there was no feeling in it from the beginning.
That's impossible!
Don't tell me back there...
...when you saved Trish from the boss in Venice...
Buccellati, don't tell me back there...
It's strange.
I've come to terms with my fate.
This small, fortuitous bit of fate
granted to me by the heavens...
When you healed my wounds back in Venice...
...somehow you granted me enough life energy to keep going for just a bit longer.
Why?
Why didn't you say anything?
My Gold Experience completely
healed your wounds back then!
It can heal whatever is wrong with you now, too!
Giorno, I'm sure your Gold Experience
knows about this better than any of us.
Nothing can be done for a life that's ended.
By the time you healed me, my life...
...had already ended.
Will you promise not to tell the others?
Impossible...
That's impossible, Buccellati!
Y-You're...!
Quiet, Giorno!
Listen! What's that sound?
Is it just my ears ringing?
We're not being followed by a car!
I hear something.
It's approaching!
It's closing in quickly!
What?!
Above us!
It's a helicopter!
They're dropping mold onto us!
Wh-What the hell just happened?!
Buccellati, we're descending!
This road goes downhill!
The mold is going to get us!
Giorno! Mista!
We have to bail!
Grab hold of me!
Climb up!
Even if it's just a little, climb up!
Subconscious...
In a way, Stand abilities
represent the user's subconscious capabilities...
If they feel guilt in their heart,
their ability may subconsciously hinder their actions...
But this person revels in cruelty.
They live for it!
That's why their ability is like this.
Nothing is holding them back!
Their depravity has no limits!
Hey, wake up! What's wrong?!
I-I'll go get you a doctor!
Hey, don't!
Don't go down that way!
I'll get you a doctor in no time!
Hey, what's going on?
What's the fuss about?
The mold...
It's spreading at a rapid pace!
Impossible!
There are three million people living in Rome!
This is nothing like that fishing village!
There are members of the organization who live in Rome.
The boss is going to be hurt by this, too!
This man doesn't care.
He's enjoying this!
At this rate, everyone in Rome will die!
No, he won't stop even if it spreads further!
There's another problem!
If we don't stop it, the mold's killing range will spread to
the man waiting for us in the Colosseum before we ever reach him!
Mista!
Is that helicopter within range of your gun?
Though, even if it's not, we have no choice!
Make sure you take it down!
Got it!
He won't get away!
Go, Sex Pistols!
Yee-haw!
The guy in the helicopter wanted me to fire at him...
He wanted to make sure the guy who can
dive into the ground could safely reach us!
Good, Secco dove down safely.
Or rather, he landed down safely?
They're trapped now.
Now whoever Buccellati and his team
had intended to meet in Rome...
...will be eliminated by Green Day.
Th-The asshole's coming at us
from the top of the hill!
We can't turn back!
Mista, concentrate on the helicopter!
We can't let it escape!
I'll deal with this guy.
I-It's no use, Buccellati!
It's already too far away!
I can't hit the gas tank or the propeller from here!
You're wrong, Mista.
You never know until you try!
It's no use!
They won't reach!
I know my Pistols' range better than anyone.
The helicopter got away...
The underground guy is coming for us!
Your bullets hit their target, Mista.
Now the two of us can
eliminate the man in the helicopter.
We're going up!
We're going up?
To the helicopter?
What?!
What is this?
We need to take care of him
before the mold reaches the Colosseum!
Buccellati...
...we can leave the man
beneath the ground to you, right?
Go, Giorno!
Hurry, Mista!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Green Day and Oasis Part 2