Wh-What?
My body suddenly... All my strength is...
It can't be...
My vision is blurring, too...
Am I finally out of time?
I knew this moment would come...
But now?
I have to go...
Go?
Wait... Buccellati and his team
must have a goal in mind.
Where is he trying to go?
I'm sure the boss wants to know.
Excuse me...
Would you like me to lend you a hand?
It's fine if you don't, but...
What? You're still here?
I'm fine...
Leave me alone...
But... And I apologize if I'm being presumptuous...
It may be difficult for you
to cross the street in this state.
I really don't mind lending you a hand.
If it's not a bother, that is.
Well...
I suppose it couldn't hurt.
Where are you headed?
Just to... the entrance of the Colosseum.
The entrance of the Colosseum, is it?
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 33  His Name is Diavolo
I'm running out of time.
Just take me to the other side of the road, please...
Look out!
You stupid-ass drunk!
Are you okay?
Were you even look-
Wh-What?
Why is Buccellati's hand so cold?
Sorry about that...
Is this a guardrail?
Did I run into it?
Could Buccellati... have gone blind?
He also ignored the car horn
and tried to cross the road...
Could he have gone deaf, too?
That cut on your throat...
You weren't injured back there, were you?
No. Now that I'm taking a closer look,
it seems you got it sometime this morning or last night.
It isn't bleeding.
That's a strange place to be wounded.
Even though it's under my collar,
he can see it clearly...
He's looking right at it!
At the wound given to me by Risotto!
Oh, you picked that up for me.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
So, are you ready to go?
All right, I'm ready.
He can hear me, too...
But it feels like there's more to this
than the injuries he's sustained.
What's going on with him?
That's Guido Mista!
Damn! I wasted too much time.
I should have known he'd come here.
What's wrong?
We didn't finish crossing yet.
No, uh...
Sorry, the cut on my throat
started to bleed again...
He's headed this way!
I'm sorry to push you, but I'm in a hurry.
I need to cross as quickly as-
No!
Don't stand up!
I mean... There's another car coming.
We'll cross once it passes.
No, it's on the other side of the road.
We can cross.
Come on.
Let's cross.
N-No... Mista's coming!
I'll just have to eliminate him right here!
Right now!
Brrring ring ring ring ring! Ring-a-ling!
I-I wonder what that sound was just now!
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Ring-a-ling! Ring-a-ling!
What are you doing?
What did you just say?
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Ring-a-ling! Ring-a-ling!
Why am I getting a call right now?!
My cover is about to be blown!
You're...
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
You gotta be kidding me!
Why are you calling me right now of all times?!
Do you want him to find out or what?!
Trish!
You shouldn't be out here yet!
We may still be in danger.
Go back inside the tortoise!
You don't understand. He's here!
I'm getting the same feeling as before...
It's just like when we were in Sardinia...
You're... who again?
You, in front of me...
You're...
...Trish!
I can feel him!
He's nearby!
The boss is close to us!
He's nearby?
Do you know exactly where he is?
He appeared out of nowhere...
...but I'm not sure where!
Thank goodness... You're safe...
Well done.
You've done an outstanding job.
This is why you're my highest ranked
and most trusted subordinate.
Don't worry.
Buccellati may be looking your way,
but he doesn't see you for who you are.
What do you mean?
I am unsure of how it happened,
but Buccellati is already a living corpse.
His heart has stopped, and his breathing has ceased.
His vision is gone,
and his eardrums were ruptured during his battle with Secco.
All he can see right now, Doppio,
is the shape of your soul.
All he can hear is the energy of your soul.
He is unable to see inanimate objects like guardrails,
but he can see the souls of people driving their cars.
What's wrong, Trish?
Did something happen?
My daughter's soul and mine
have a similar scent due to their similar shape.
That is what I just granted you.
The only thing Buccellati sees
is the form of my daughter!
Let Buccellati lead you to whatever he's looking for.
Have him take you there!
Trish...
I'm sorry. I'm tired and wasn't thinking.
But thank goodness you're safe, Buccellati.
Y-Yeah... But more importantly,
wasn't there a young man here just now?
I just saw him run off in a hurry.
But we need to get going, Buccellati,
and reach our destination.
You're right.
I hate to ask this of you, but could you lend me a hand?
I just don't have enough strength anymore...
Yes...
Of course.
King Crimson
Diavolo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: E
Durability: E
Precision: ?
Growth Potential: ?
In the suburbs of Naples...
Trish, it's small, but I have a house there.
When this is all over...
If you have nowhere else to go... you can live there.
My neighborhood has a school
and a nice restaurant.
It's close to the beach, too.
Life has been treating you so cruelly...
...but you should be able to begin anew there.
Thank you.
But more importantly, where should we go next?
Climb up those stairs...
Upstairs?
Don't turn your head, Doppio!
Keep going...
Act as though you haven't noticed anything!
Someone is there.
In the shadow of the stone pillar above you!
You're being watched!
Their goal was to meet someone here.
But who could it be?
I'm at a complete loss.
Boss, how do you know they're here?
And if someone is watching me here,
I'll need to turn around to see who they are.
Look into Buccellati's eyes.
The answer lies there.
The man's reflection is in his eyes.
Don't move!
Stay where you are.
Take even one step
up the stairs and the deal is off.
You're right!
There's someone in the shadow of the pillars!
My name is Bruno Buccellati!
I came all this way because
I trusted you held the secret to defeating the boss!
I know.
But before we proceed, who's there with you?
I don't have any data on them!
As you shouldn't!
Trish isn't a member of the organization,
and I only met her a few days ago.
But as you can clearly see, she's one of us.
Trish?
That sounds like a woman's name.
Sounds like?
This is bad...
I'm about to be found out, Boss!
Calm yourself. Listen to me.
This is what you have to say.
"Does the fact that I'm a woman bother you?"
Say it now, Doppio!
Does the fact that I'm a woman bother you?!
I guess I should watch my mouth.
I couldn't see you well in the darkness.
Is she a Stand user?
Of course she is! But enough questions!
Now it's your turn to say who you are!
Let's cut to the chase!
No, not yet.
I need to see her Stand.
Trish! Move slowly.
I have no data on you,
but you'll earn my trust by showing me your Stand.
B-Boss...
Who is this man?
He's clearly experienced in combat...
...and he's taking any potential
Stand range into account.
Who could he be? If only I knew...
Well?
Hurry and show me from where you're standing!
Move as delicately as if you were lifting up your skirt!
That's... It can't be!
Why does he have that?
That arrow... There's no mistaking it.
That's the arrow from back then!
What's this menacing, murderous intent I feel?
It's like someone is holding a knife over my heart...
I remember this feeling...
It can't be!
No, I remember now...
There is one person it could be.
Someone who could have
tracked me down by following the arrow...
He's...
Long ago while I was in Egypt,
I found arrows capable of awakening Stand abilities.
From the moment I laid my eyes upon them
I could tell they held a mysterious power.
An old woman with two right hands named Enya...
...offered to reveal how to use the arrows
if I agreed to shoot them for her.
I saw no reason to keep more than one,
so I sold the other five for a handsome sum of money.
Come to think of it,
that old woman said something rather bizarre...
She claimed that the arrow chooses people,
and that the chosen are drawn together like magnets.
In the 90's, after our battle with Dio,
my old friend Kujo Jotaro and I began an investigation...
...into these arrows that supposedly
drew out Stand abilities.
We heard reports of a young man who had dug up other arrows,
so we split up in an effort to find him faster.
Jotaro went to the Americas and Asia...
...and I went to Europe and Africa.
I soon learned that one of the arrows ended up in a region of Italy
that had recently become a hotbed for drug-related crimes.
I investigated an area there where drug crimes involving young people had shot up more than twenty times...
...and that was when I knew I was close.
But...
My organization was nearing complete domination
after just a few years.
Subordinates were swearing undying loyalty to me...
My men were planted in every branch of society...
I correctly assumed that someone was
attempting to track me down.
In the end, I finished him off myself.
It was the only sure way to end it.
I knew it must be done.
I ended up making two grave mistakes.
My first mistake was not realizing that
the organization had already fully formed.
Communications, the government, the press...
Society itself had isolated me.
And my second grave mistake...
Silver Chariot!
I suppose I'll tell you since you're about to die.
...was not realizing that the man
who had dug up those arrows...
...had powers far more sinister
than I could have imagined!
The moment that anyone sees King Crimson...
This ability...
Time... It...
...is the moment they will depart from this world.
Is there really... no hope...?
I was certain I had killed him!
To think a past I had long thought buried
would appear again before me with an arrow!
Buccellati!
The person next to you is...!
Wh-What? Buccellati!
Where did the person next to you go?!
They disappeared!
Don't tell me...
Where did they go?!
Where did the person you brought here go?!
T-Trish...
Tell me who the hell was with you just now!
I didn't see or hear anything fall,
but a piece of the binoculars is already behind me...
It can't be... These movements...
Time just skipped!
Just like when we were in Venice!
We unwittingly climbed up the stairs!
We're out of time...
The man waiting for us at the Colosseum
just entered the boss's range!
This is a trial.
A trial in which I must defeat my past...
One can only grow stronger
by conquering their past follies.
Wouldn't you agree, Jean Pierre Polnareff?
You're...!
Diavolo!
It seems that no matter how hard
I try to tear apart my past...
...it manages to wriggle up
between the rocks like a worm.
I'm surprised.
It's no wonder I couldn't figure out who would oppose me.
How did you get here?
But in the end...
...it doesn't matter how you managed to survive after I scattered your remains to the ocean.
All that matters here, Polnareff...
...is what you were attempting to tell
Buccellati and his men!
Don't even think about walking up these stairs!
I stay above you, you stay beneath me!
Why won't you fight for yourself, Polnareff?
Do you no longer have the mettle for it?
Or is it that you can no longer physically fight?
How do you intend to use that arrow?
This can't be happening...
I was sure it was a kid down there!
Diavolo... When did you get so close to me?
You're the one who's beneath me, Polnareff!
So long as you're beneath me in Hell...
...it doesn't matter what you
intend to do with that arrow!
There! Silver Chariot!
I see your Stand ability
hasn't lost any of its strength.
You've learned from your mistakes.
You countered my time skip by counting your dripping blood.
I see. All it took was that single moment
when the blood stains changed...
Your timing was impeccable, too.
Had I come closer,
I would have been gravely injured.
This is bad...
I can't believe Diavolo was
the first person to make it here...
This is my only chance... I have to try...
I must protect this hope at all costs!
You're already within my range!
You won't escape this time!
King Crimson!
Once time begins anew...
...you'll be unable to see
how many drops of blood you've spilled.
As of this moment, I've conquered my past folly!
Take this!
The passage of time will begin anew!
Wh-What is this?
The arrow... His Stand...
I don't know what it's doing, but...
Take this!
Th-This arrow...
What is it doing to Chariot?
There's some kind of power behind this glow!
Time, begin anew!
Impossible!
What did he do?
The arrow has other uses
besides drawing out Stand abilities?!
This is my gamble to keep
the arrow away from Diavolo...
I didn't want to show him that...
...but I don't have the power
to fully control the arrow any longer...
You won't get away!
That arrow is our hope...
Whoever can fully control the arrow
will be the one to control the world...
I-It happened again!
It skipped! Time skipped again!
Trish! Where's the boss?
You spent years uncovering some
incredible secret about the arrow.
I suppose you held out for quite a while, Polnareff.
Unfortunately for you, the arrow is now mine!
Your heart seems to have stopped.
But the life you lived wasn't meaningless...
...Jean Pierre Polnareff.
You've proven to be quite useful to me.
Giorno!
L-Look over there!
It's Buccellati!
Hey, he looks really hurt!
Buccellati!
Be careful!
The boss is somewhere nearby!
They're here...
What?
Who are you?!
How long have you been standing there?!
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
A Softly Playing Requiem
Part 1