Still nothing?
Check the Interpol database and
Sardinian police records if necessary.
Are there any records matching these fingerprints?
Nothing. No hits.
This is the boss we're dealing with.
He likely erased all records of himself.
But they must be somewhere...
That's why he tried eliminating his own daughter
and fears anyone determining his appearance.
Should we try the records of the dead?
Perhaps the boss faked his own death.
Do it.
He can't get away with this...
Just now for a brief moment,
I felt the same as I did back in Venice.
The person who came close to Abbacchio...
...was my father.
This man laid his hands on Abbacchio.
Are you saying that the boss is here, Trish?
Yes.
I'm not sure where he is, but he's close.
Buccellati!
Not right now!
We need to make sure we know
who the boss is and assassinate him, or we'll lose.
Uncovering his identity is paramount!
No hits.
It's hopeless...
The boss is too careful...
We can't pursue him any further...
That's not true!
You've got him right where you want him.
What?
Now it's just a matter of finding a way to defeat him!
kami no sadame ni sae
Even opposing the fate willed to us by God
hanki o hirugaesu... Gangster
We gangsters will raise a flag of rebellion
osore to iu kanjou o kakikesu rage
The rage in our souls that erases any sense of fear
akuma ni somuku to chikatta hi kara
Has been with us since we swore to defy God's diabolical plan
houfuku to wa shuumatsu ka
Will retaliation mean curtains for us?
mirai o kou ikikata o sutete
Casting aside a life in which our futures remained certain
idomu mono Stay Gold
We challengers will stay gold
sou sa me ni wa me o
Indeed, it's eye for an eye
uragirimono ni wa requiem o
And a requiem for the traitor
zetsubou ga tamaneku
Together we will stand up against this world
sekai ni tachimukau
In which despair breeds despair
Don't care jihi nado iranai sa
Don't care! I have no need for mercy
karada horobiru toki
If my body were to crumble to nothing
inori mo kiehateru? Hell No
So too would my prayers fade away? Hell no!
hajimari no Golden Wind
It begins with a Golden Wind
Episodio 29  Reach the Roman Colosseum!
I've been waiting for this!
For people like you who were
willing to tirelessly investigate this man.
Someone hijacked our connection!
Giorno, disconnect the line!
Wait! Hear me out!
I'm on your side!
You want to defeat Diavolo, don't you?
Diavolo?
I want you to believe me.
Clinging to the hope that someday I would find someone attempting to beat Diavolo...
...I've kept this line open.
I've been waiting for so long...
Years and years, desperately hoping...
I'm on your side!
I'm not convinced.
Diavolo?
Giving us a name doesn't prove
that you're on our side.
Giorno, disconnect the line.
His Stand can skip over time!
Did you know that?
Though I'm sure you did...
since you're in such a hurry to figure out who he is.
He's on our side...
This man is on our side.
My father wouldn't leave anyone alive
who knew what his Stand ability is.
Stay silent, Trish.
We can't reveal our hand just yet.
All right, tell us what you know.
Start by telling us your name.
My name isn't important.
My body isn't in fighting shape anymore.
What's most important right now is
whether or not you guys are capable of defeating him.
His ability to erase time has no weaknesses.
I'm sure you've been planning out his assassination...
...but you're doomed to fail!
Are you saying you know how to defeat the boss?
His King Crimson is invincible!
But there's a possibility you could defeat him.
Only a slight possibility.
A possibility you must obtain.
Obtain?
Come to me.
Come to Rome!
If you make it here,
I can give you this possibility!
What makes you think we'll go?
How can we trust you?
I'm sure at least some of you will have seen this.
That's...
...the arrow!
Rather, it looks just like it!
Why do you have that?
I'll tell you later.
You'll need to come to me to retrieve it.
He doesn't know the true way to use this arrow.
This arrow isn't just for awakening
Stand abilities in living creatures!
A hidden meaning lies within it!
I'll tell it to you.
Come to Rome.
This arrow can beat him.
It's the one and only way to end this!
Brrring ring ring ring ring...
Brrring ring ring ring ring!
Hey, you there!
What are you doing with my phone?
That call is meant for me!
Hand it over, you selfish brat!
Hello?
Yes, this is Doppio!
It's strange, Doppio...
What is, Boss?
Buccellati and his team...
Abbacchio's death should have
made them feel lost and hopeless.
But they don't.
They fled without hesitation.
They left on that boat with an objective in mind.
Look into it.
Return to the place Abbacchio died and look around.
Something here feels amiss.
Look around?
What am I looking for?
Fear is born...
...from troubles of the past.
This is what I feared most
since I learned of my daughter's existence.
There's nothing out of the ordinary here, Boss.
Only a broken statue.
I feel it.
It's undeniable.
Those traitors...
I'm sure of it now.
There's something they know that I don't.
They know something?
Like what?
They barely had any time.
Something I would never suspect!
You've done enough, Doppio.
Go after them immediately.
You'll have to track them down on your own.
Yes, sir!
Also...
Cioccolata and Secco...
Have those two intercept Buccellati
before he reaches his destination.
I'd rather not have to rely on those lowlifes,
but I have no choice.
This is where it ends.
Listen well, Doppio.
We all must vanquish our fear eventually.
The time is now.
We must get through this at any cost.
This is what it means to live.
Who the hell is this guy
waiting for us in Rome?
Can we really trust him?
Got me.
But Buccellati made up his mind.
What else can we do?
Let me tell you a little story from the past.
There's a place in Greenland called
Cape York where only the Inuit people live.
It's famous for having a large crater
created by a meteorite landing.
It's said to have fallen
tens of thousands of years ago.
In 1978...
...two men from a team that were
surveying the crater for any natural resources...
...contracted an unknown illness.
Their bodies became covered in
blisters that grew until they burst...
...leaving them dead and
seemingly drowning in tomato sauce.
Furthermore, one of them had somehow
shot a jolt like a stun gun from his finger...
...and burned off a few fingers
of the doctor treating him.
In later investigations,
it was discovered that a virus...
...which was tens of thousands of years old,
had been trapped within the meteorite inside the crater.
The virus may have traveled here on the meteorite.
A virus?
What about it?
I discovered something...
This arrow is made from the same material as the meteorite found in Cape York!
Centuries ago,
a human who craved absolute godlike power...
...learned of the meteorite and
turned it into several arrows, including this one.
This lethal virus culls most lifeforms.
It's from a theory called "viral evolution."
Most people who contract the virus die,
but a select few possess something that allows them to live.
And as if to reward their tenacity,
the virus grants them a new ability.
Your own bodies are living proof of this.
So that's what Stands are...
That's the origin and principle governing the arrow.
I understand.
What you've said makes sense.
But what's this so-called secret way of
using the arrow that we need to retrieve?
I can only tell you that face-to-face in Rome.
On top of that,
I can only tell one of you what it is.
I can't let anyone else
ever find out about this secret power.
But once you know the method,
it will give the one who uses it power beyond comprehension.
It's the only way you'll stand a chance
of beating King Crimson.
We have no way of
telling if your story is true.
But I'm sure the boss would
eliminate you if he caught word of this.
I'll trust you.
How do you want to meet?
Come to the Colosseum in Rome.
You'll know what to do.
I'll be waiting whenever you get here.
I'll tell you everything.
Let go!
Ya can't do this!
Fuck off!
I gotta take a piss!
I gotta go!
For fuck's sake!
That ain't the toilet!
There ain't no toilet there!
It's over here!
Look!
Damn, this feels good!
I'm gonna do it!
We'll get off the boat once those drunks leave.
We need to get a car as soon as possible.
Rome is just fourty-five minutes from here.
Yeah, got it.
This is good timing, too.
The moon's hidden behind the clouds.
Hey, Mista...
There's some drunks sleeping over there, too.
Dammit!
Was there a party here tonight or what?
Get off it!
Yer gonna get yelled at!
Come on!
Leggo of me!
I said I gotta go,
and you fuckin' bet I'm gonna go, goddammit!
You can't!
It's not a toilet!
See?
It's right here.
Hey.
How am I gonna reach it like this?
You expect me to open my fly like this?
Wh-What the hell happened?!
Don't touch me!
What's going on?!
It's a Stand attack!
What?!
It's an ambush!
The enemy is here!
Listen closely, Secco.
Nothing is more important right now than
making sure you don't run out of batteries.
Nothing angers me more than
realizing you didn't record anything.
Are you sure it's recording?
Excellent.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Epitaph
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
Allows the user to see the future as though viewing it
on a TV. Also allows for seeing beyond time that's been
erased. Its visions of the future are never wrong.
Cioccolata: Thirty-four years old. Formerly a doctor.
Around two years ago,
a patient in his care died due to a simple mistake.
Once he was laid off from the hospital,
Passione took him in.
Though he appeared to be
an elite who fell from grace...
...the boss discovered his true nature
once he became a Stand user.
That patient's death was not accidental.
He had been killed on purpose.
He intentionally misdiagnosed countless
healthy people so that he could operate on them.
During these surgeries, he reduced the anesthetic
so that his victims would wake up part way through.
Ever since he was a boy,
he had always been at the top of his class.
When he turned fourteen,
he volunteered to take care of the elderly.
However, in actuality, he was administering
mysterious drugs to the elderly patients put under his care.
Also...
Your family despises you.
No one will ever visit you.
He told them horrible things every single day...
...driving many of them to suicide.
On his book shelf at home, he had twenty-five video tapes
capturing the expressions the elderly made when he told them his lies.
After driving nine elders to suicide,
he decided to become a doctor.
What Cioccolata loved most was
watching people as they died.
He became a doctor so he could experience more people's suffering and death firsthand.
While watching others die,
he felt above the rest of humanity...
...and believed he truly
understood the human psyche.
Cioccolata's one and only partner was Secco.
The only notable fact about him is that
he was Cioccolata's former patient.
Somehow the two got along,
and Secco followed all of Cioccolata's orders.
Even among the many Stand users who operate within Passione, these two stand out as notoriously monstrous.
That's who Cioccolata and Secco are.
I figured out that they're
headed toward Rome, Boss.
I just received word that they
arrived at a local fishing village.
Listen well, Doppio.
Leave it to Cioccolata to intercept
and eliminate Buccellati and his team.
However, you must catch up to
the two of them at any cost.
Those two... yes.
I rarely ever feel repulsed by others...
...but Cioccolata is the most
vile person to walk this earth.
Rome will likely be in shambles once he's through.
So you think he'll go berserk?
That is why you must catch up with them, Doppio.
You must take control in the end.
The two of them cannot
be allowed to interrogate Trish...
...nor learn what Buccellati and his team
are looking for in Rome.
You're the only one I can trust.
Do you understand?
You're my number one operative.
I understand, Boss.
This is what I live for.
Sorry, was that call too long?
Thank you very much, young lady.
Uh, hewwo?
What the fuck is that, Mista?!
When did that get on you?
I don't know!
Just hurry and find the user, Narancia!
Find out where the enemy is!
Aerosmith!
This is bad!
It already took out a bunch of civilians!
The enemy's range is covering the whole village!
They actually involved
innocent people in this?
This is gonna make finding the user...
Dammit, I can't tell them apart!
What's the situation, Mista?
My hand suddenly started bubbling up...
I have no idea when this shit got on me!
It's almost like mold...
It's ripping my skin open...
It looks like it's coming from under my skin!
The same stuff came out of the villagers,
and their bodies are in pieces!
Th-This looks really bad, Buccellati!
We can't go ashore!
We'll never make it up to the parking lot!
We're better off getting
back on the boat and leaving the shore.
Do you see any signs of breathing?
None nearby!
Wait, Buccellati!
Until we know what attacked us,
it's too dangerous to move!
What I know is that if we go ashore,
we're gonna get attacked by whatever that stuff is!
Giorno!
It got on me?!
This is...!
Wh-Where the hell is it attacking from?!
M-Mista!
Grab my hand!
Mista!
Don't extend your hand!
The Stand is using some kind of
switch to trigger its attack!
Trigger its attack?
What does that mean?
It attacked me the second I lowered my hand!
Come to think of it, it first bubbled up on my hand after I reached into my boot for my gun.
And the drunk guy was attacked
when he jumped down the stairs.
The other one had already gone downstairs...
And Narancia had jumped down into the boat!
Does that mean it attacks when
your body goes below a certain point?
B-But...
At this rate all of you...
He's not descending.
He isn't boarding the boat
to save the other one.
He figured it out quickly.
Exactly how...
...my Green Day works.
Mold...
I've read about this before...
There's a certain kind of mold
that can grow inside of insects.
If the insect moves below a certain point,
the mold will propagate and kill it.
Entomopathogenic fungus
and caterpillar fungus.
This is just like that!
If you move below a certain point within its range,
it reacts and attacks you!
This is a Stand!
Why would it operate like that?
To give the Stand an even larger range!
Just like how the mold spreads from with the dead insect,
the corpses produce more corpses.
If its victims move a bit further before dying,
it extends the mold's range.
This is just what they want.
This Stand ability acts on the user's unconscious will.
Climb up, Narancia!
Get off the boat and come ashore!
Mista!
Hurry up!
You're still too far away!
My foot!
Throw the tortoise, Narancia!
Throw it toward Mista!
Okay, Narancia!
That's perfect!
That's the perfect spot!
You and the tortoise are
in the absolute perfect spot!
Yee-haw!
Good thinking, Mista!
The attack can't affect us
as long as we keep moving upward.
They made it up.
Somehow they made it onto the shore without a single one of them dying.
Interesting.
Good. Excellent.
They're accusing, like always without knowing
What is just fiction or what is the truth
They have no mission, they have no passion
But they dare to tell us what's bad and what's good
Stand up
Join us
Modern crusaders alive
We have the power who'll face the future
Cause we are the fighters, just fighting for our rights
Green Day and Oasis Part 1