Amidst the mountains, surrounded by a series of cliffs, there lies a town...
Wind Knights' Lot!
It was founded in the Middle Ages as a training ground for knights.
Now that it's the 19th Century, this castle fortress has been converted into a prison where the prisoners are tasked to mine for coal.
The townspeople have built their livelihoods around mining and the local harbor.
Their current population, including prisoners, is only 517 people.
And soon... the entire town will be wiped out!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 5: "The Black Knights"
These people are working like any other day...
This town will be all right, for now.
Moreover, I know Dio must be hiding near here!
What's the matter?
N-Nothing...
The good Mr. Speedwagon here was being ever so persistent...
So I struck him with the intention to unlock a temporary use of the Ripple with his breathing...
...but I made a slight miscalculation, and my finger slipped.
Sorry... do excuse my clumsiness, Speedwagon.
You old coot...
Mr. Zeppeli, it was just a little boy!
A thieving little urchin, but that was quite the display of athleticism.
Would you two stop standing around and do something?!
All of our money's in that bag!
Oh, damn it all!
His theft and escape were flawless...
See here...
Let's have that boy show us around town.
He's... walking on water?!
Jojo! If the water reaches up to your knees, you aren't using the Ripple energy to its full potential!
That sounded good, Jojo. I can tell the Overdrive went through the entire cliff side.
Do you think this is a good place to stand?
No, I believe another few feet to the left would be best.
I'd bet two quid on it!
It broke loose!
Nice catch!
Huh... what the...
Wait... who are you guys?
There's something strange about this boy...
Was my Ripple too strong?
No... and this boy isn't the strangest thing around here...
Take a look around you.
This place...
...is a graveyard!
It seems we weren't the only ones to foresee our target's movements and head in for a nice catch...
That young lad was most likely under some kind of hypnosis...
Mr. Joestar, look above you!
The sun has set...
...just as your lives will soon fade into darkness!
Dio!
They're crawling out of the ground!
I... I've been preparing for this moment...
...and it's more horrifying than I ever imagined!
Just knowing that a cocky bastard like him is still alive and kicking... it makes me break out in a cold sweat!
The wretch who repaid Lord Joestar's compassion with blood-soaked betrayal!
That... that bastard will pay!
So, that's Dio... I see...
Neither he nor his zombies could make a move while the sun was out.
So he used that hypnotized child to lure us into a battle,
assuring that the time and place would suit them.
If someone this cunning has been granted the power of the mask...
Then he must be eliminated, no matter the cost!
Zombies created from the corpses of knights?!
What's your name, young man?
P-Poco...
All right, Poco...
Get on my back, and hold on tight!
Let's go, Jojo!
Okay!
Zoom Punch!
Amazing!
Dio Brando...
I don't know you personally...
...but allow me to speak directly to the power of the stone mask that dwells within you.
At last, we meet again!
Hey baby, do you really want to fight on such shaky ground?!
Come down here!
Watch your tone, insect!
I alone sit atop the food chain...
I have become the next dominant species, ushering in a new era!
What makes you think a mere mortal could stand on equal footing with one such as myself?
The malevolent aura surrounding him is overwhelming!
He's able to intimidate all who stand in his way!
Once the burn on my stomach has healed,
the memory of Jojo defeating me will be completely gone...
Come at me, magician! Let your blood help wash away my scars!
You monster... how many lives have you taken away in order to mend your wounds?!
Be honest... do you remember every crumb of bread you've ever eaten?
Dio!
Mr. Zeppeli?!
I'll take care of him...
It's time to end this!
Ripple of the sun, flow through him...
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
It's working! The Ripple is flowing into Dio's arm!
Weakling, weakling!
He... he froze my arm?!
W-What is this?!
Zeppeli, was it?
This energy you use seems to radiate from the flow of blood...
If I freeze your blood vessels, there's no path for that energy to flow through!
I should have let you know that I have total control over my body.
I sapped the fluids from my arm after I caught your punch...
Without that fluid, my body was flash frozen, taking yours with it!
And now...!
Imbecile! Crushing your arm and skull will be as easy as smashing a cheap vase!
Dio! I'm putting an end to your twisted schemes!
Dio's hand... I can feel pure evil flowing through his veins...
You flatter me...
And I must say, I'm impressed you managed to stop my fist.
I applaud your skill.
Jojo!
Jojo...
If I were you, I would hurry up and let go of that hand.
Take this, Dio!
Wrrryyyyyy!
With your arms frozen from me sapping my fluids, your blood cannot flow.
Which means that you have no way of channeling the energy of the Ripple!
H-He's too powerful!
The energy he wields is five times more powerful than ours combined!
This is bad... I cannot allow Jojo's arm to end up like mine!
I will not allow him to injure Jojo!
Mr. Zeppeli!
W-What just happened?!
It's so cold...
It's so cold, but it feels like it's burning!
My skin ripped off like I pulled my hand away from a piece of frozen metal!
Old man Zeppelli's arm!
If we can't get the blood flowing, he'll lose his arm to frostbite!
He's unstoppable...
If there's no way to channel the Ripple of the sun, then how can we ever beat Dio?!
Ripple?
A breathing technique?
If you're going to huff and puff...
Th-The rocks...
...then you'd be better off using that breath to blow the trumpets for my fanfare!
Tarkus! Black Knight Bruford!
This matter isn't even worth dirtying my hands over!
Come forth, and play me the fanfare I deserve with their screams of agony!
W-what the hell are they?!
Poco! Hide somewhere safe!
These fearsome knights served the most unfortunate Mary Stuart.
They were executed with Mary at the hands of Elizabeth I!
Clean up this mess.
The two of you, do whatever is necessary to stamp out these insects.
He didn't just hold up that rock with one finger... he shattered it, too!
Those zombies...
They're headed towards Jojo!
It's no good... he can't win when he's outnumbered!
If only the blood were still flowing in my arm...
If it were, what could you do?
I could use a breathing technique to heal my wounds...
There must be some way for me to thaw my arm!
Old man Zeppeli, you just need to thaw out your arm, right?!
D-Do you have something in mind?!
Something... like this!
Speedwagon!
The men of the arctic recovered from frostbite by warming their limbs with the flesh from a freshly killed seal!
Zoom Punch!
Your blood belongs to me now!
H-He's draining my blood?!
S-Speedwagon... what are you...
I didn't come all this way just to be a bother for you and Mr. Joestar!
If he can drain blood through his hair,
then that means I can send a Ripple through it!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
I-I can't generate a Ripple?!
Or is the Ripple weak because of all the blood I've lost?!
I underestimated you...
I expected you to run when things started to get out of hand...
I'm sorry I doubted you...
You can thank me after we make it through this fight, old man!
I-I have to heal as fast as I can to rejoin the battle!
I'm too terrified to even feel the pain from the frostbite forming on my chest...
That sword is so big, it dwarfs Mr. Joestar's 6'4" body!
That mysterious black hair... and the expressions on their faces!
There's something about those two...
With all that I've seen in my life, I can tell there's something overwhelming about these two!
Every true Englishman knows the names of these legendary knights...
Tarkus and Bruford!
I can make history itself serve me!
Long ago, in the year 1565...
Two queens were at odds for the throne of England.
One of them was Queen Elizabeth I...
The other was the beautiful 23 year-old Mary Stewart.
The hero, Tarkus, and the Black Knight, Bruford, were both loyal to Mary.
These men, orphaned and homeless as a result of the war,
were taken in by Mary's warm hospitality.
Even the most powerful of men will seek comfort for their soul.
In Mary's presence, they felt something far more profound than love.
The two were prepared to sacrifice their lives for Mary's sake.
Mary's husband, Lord Darnley, met an untimely demise!
Elizabeth saw this an opportunity, casting suspicion on Mary for the death of her husband!
The people turned against Mary, and as a result she was captured and imprisoned.
Tarkus and Bruford battled endlessly to rescue Mary...
With few other options to choose from,
Elizabeth approached the knights with an offer.
"If the two of you surrender at once, I shall spare Mary's life."
We cannot refuse such an offer...
We accept with no regret.
The two knights were captured... and then executed...
Let me tell you one last thing before you die...
Mary is already dead!
You idiots were tricked!
Look... see that heap of trash over there?
That's your precious Mary!
Damn you, Elizabeth!
How... How dare you betray our agreement!
You've brought a curse upon yourself! Upon you and all your kin!
Beyond death itself, we curse you!
Thus, they were executed.
It was said that Tarkus' neck, wrought tense from rage,
broke many an executioner's axe before fully giving way.
Bruford supposedly sunk his teeth into the leg of his executioner,
tearing off a chunk of his flesh before finally submitting to death.
I found myself quite enchanted by their savagery!
I dug up the graves of those two heroes who died cursing humanity, and I chose to give them new life! It was all thanks to me, Dio!
I turned them into machines of vengeance that the devil himself would fear!
Wrryyy... We have sworn loyalty to Master Dio!
We will spread destruction across the earth!
Every last one of you will die!
Th-That thirst for revenge... It made their bodies grow with their hate!
Dio has turned these heroes into monsters!
Is there any way we can defeat these beasts?!
In my left hand... I channel the Ripple of fire!
Scarlet Overdrive!
A-Amazing!
I forgot... there's something that drives Mr. Joestar to grow as well!
It's his love for his late father, his hope for a bright future...
And for the hopes of us all!
This boy seems like he has some potential...
He'll make a passable warm-up after 300 years of slumber!
I'm gonna swallow you whole!
I bet your cartilage is scrumptious!
Another zombie?!
Underlings like you... should know your place!
W-What speed!
Master Dio!
I am impressed with the boldness that this young man displays!
I, Bruford, ask you to grant me the honor of bringing death upon him!
Do as you like.
Tarkus! Leave us be.
The Black Knight, Bruford... what savage power!
And such ruthlessness, as well!
His confidence and strength radiate from him like an aura!
It's surreal... The very same Bruford the Black Knight that we learned about in school...
Now he stands before me, ready to unleash his vengeful rage!
I have to steady my breath!
Relax my muscles!
W-What?!
He has both arms behind his back! How will I know which one he's attacking with?!
Or will he use his legs?!
In a shocking twist, he used his hair!
D-Damn--!
You have impressive reflexes...
Few would be able to dodge my Dance Macabre Hair in time...
Intriguing!
Mr. Joestar!
This is bad... He won't be able to breathe underwater!
Which means he won't be able to use the Ripple!
We have to do something!
T-Tarkus!
Damn it... we can't get to Mr. Joestar with him in the way!
The battle is already won. Bruford has an overwhelming advantage in water.
There is no need for the mighty Dio to remain here!
The time has come for me to transform the people of Wind Knights' Lot into an army of zombies!
In one more night, the zombies will spread,
and then... they will consume all of England!
One breath...
Just one breath, and I can use the Ripple!
Now, our battle will commence underwater!
Your lack of breath is your handicap,
while mine is the heavy armor weighing me down.
I will not use my sword...
This shall be a battle between true warriors!
Now, try and defeat me before you drown!
Can I reach the surface before he closes the gap between us?!
Do I stand a chance to win?!
On the brink of defeat, the explosive power within Jojo brought forth a risky last-ditch idea!
The average person would only think to swim to the surface as they struggle for breath.
However, Jojo did not!
He did the exact opposite... He dove even deeper!
W-What is he doing?!
What? Danny took hold of your toy gun and won't let go?
That's because you're trying to force him to give it back.
Instead, try letting him think that you're giving it to him.
Wind Knights' Lot is a coal mining town!
That means that the earth around here has been excavated and filled in countless times!
There!
There should be pockets of air trapped beneath these rocks!
That's it!
All I need is a single breath!
I can feel it... The beat of my pulse pounding!
H-He's...
It seems you're the one at a disadvantage fighting underwater!
Because, you see... the Ripple is naturally channeled through water!
This is it! Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
We spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley... hey!
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
there with you
Next Episode
You're pathetic, Bruford!
I am an elite slaughterer!
This pain is nothing!
Yours is a destiny of bloodshed.
Life force Magnetism Overdrive!
Episode 6:
"Courage of Tomorrow"