I found what I was searching for, Dio!
And now I have proof of your devilish conspiracy!
He's got me backed into a corner...
But I will not submit!
I returned to make sure that Jojo was dealt with once and for all!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Quality Check:
Tonitonichopchop
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 3: "My Youth With Dio"
I was able to find the antidote...
I've already given it to my father.
Dio... this pains me.
I never expected to have to deliver the man who was raised to be my brother over to the police.
It's a shame... Dio...
You probably don't believe me, but that is how I honestly feel.
This is the kindness I've come to expect from you.
Jojo... I realize it's selfish, but I have one last request...
Please, let me have some time...
Just enough so I can surrender myself to the police!
Unbelievable!
I was certain that he would struggle, attacking like a cornered beast!
Jojo...
How in the bloody hell did you escape from the slums alive?
I have no other choice...
I'll have to wait until he lowers his guard, then gut him with my knife!
Please, I regret the wicked life I've led up until now!
I was born into poverty, and it led me to pursue such foolish ambitions!
I've been such an idiot!
The fact that I would harm my benefactor over his fortune...  after all the kindness he's shown me...
I returned here because I wanted to turn myself in!
Why else would I return when I could have fled anywhere in the world?!
Th-that's true...
I want to pay for my crimes...
Dio...
I'd be careful, Mr. Joestar.
You can't trust a word this scoundrel says!
You must be wondering who I am...
Allow me to introduce myself...
Speedwagon's the name, and meddling's my game!
I met the good Mr. Joestar here in the slums of London, so I accompanied him to help keep an eye out.
Mr. Joestar, I've grown fond of you and your naiveté, so let me tell you something...
I've lived in the underworld my entire life,
and I've met scoundrels of every sort.
I can tell a good man from a rotten one just by their scent...
This bastard stinks!
He reeks worse than the lowest gutter trash I've ever met!
I've never met a scoundrel of his caliber in my entire life!
So you say your upbringing turned you into a bastard?
A likely story!
You've been evil since the day you were born!
Perhaps, you recall... this face?!
This easterner confessed to selling you the poison.
I heard everything...
I am truly sorry...
I tried to raise you with the same
hope and affection as I have for my own son...
Father, you shouldn't be out of bed!
Very well... I shall return to my room.
I have no desire to see my son taken away in chains.
Jojo, please see to the rest.
Yes, father.
I suppose this is the end, then...
That boy will not be detained.
I can see it written on his face, evident by the three birthmarks on his ear...
He was born under the star of great fortune.
Jojo... the least you could do is be the one to put the cuffs on me.
For everything we've been through these seven years...
Okay...
Watch yourself, Mr. Joestar!
Jojo... I suppose there are limits to the abilities of humankind...
If there is one thing I have learned in my short life...
The more you plot and scheme, the less likely it becomes things will go according to plan...
One would have to be more than human to overcome that...
What are you saying? What do you mean?!
I'm through with being a mere mortal, Jojo!
I will transcend humanity!
The stone mask?! Why do you have it?!
Watch out!
Shoot him!
And I'll use your blood to do it, Jojo!
That's...
Father!
Fire!
Jojo...
F-Father...
I could have dodged that knife...
But I was so distracted by the stone mask...
And in my stead, you...
Take this...
This ring belonged to your late mother...
Father!
That knife wound is most certainly fatal...
Damn it, I was supposed to keep this from happening!
Lord Joestar! This is what I was talking about!
This is my fault! If only I had thrown Dio Brando's father behind bars!
His father...?
It wasn't long after I joined the police force that we caught a man who was trying to sell a stolen ring...
That man was Dio's father... Dario Brando!
Indeed, this matches my ring...
My wife and I had a matching pair made especially for us.
We caught a thief by the name of Brando trying to sell it.
Brando?!
Lord Joestar thought Brando had saved his life...
But it was all a ruse!
He was just a sneaky rat who tried to loot the wreckage of an accident!
Bloody hell!
Tell me... Did he say that I had willingly given him that ring?
Yes sir, that he did!
What a load of rubbish!
That was no lie...
I sent him that ring.
W-What are you saying?!
He's innocent.
There is no reason to detain him.
Why?! Why would you let him get away with this?!
I might have done the same thing, had I been born into poverty...
Please take this... Sell it, and buy something for your family.
And please... Turn your life around, do not stray from the path of good.
Lord Joestar knew the truth, and he still agreed to take Dio in!
Father, please stay strong... The doctors can save you!
Jojo, please don't hold this against Dio...
This was all my fault...
I was far too strict, even with you...
I can only imagine how that must have made Dio feel...
It must have pushed him to do this...
Please... bury Dio alongside his father.
Father...
It's not so bad, Jojo... Being able to die...
In the arms of... my son...
Lord Joestar!
It was his kindness that led to all of this! It was all for nothing!
You're wrong!
That man's kind-hearted spirit has been
passed down to his son, Jonathan Joestar!
It will become the flame that drives him, his source of strength, lighting the path to his future!
Normally, I can't stand naïve fools who cry whenever life sends hardship their way...
But this family is an exception...
They have absolute faith in their course of action! They're true men, through and through!
The... the body!
Where is Dio Brando's body?!
Constable, get away from that window!
Wrrryyyyyy...
The constable's head!
W-What's the meaning of this?! How is he still alive?!
How could he survive those gunshots?!
Be careful! He must have a weapon on him!
I-Impossible!
H-He's heading this way...
What are you doing? Shoot him!
Dio, stop!
D-Dio!
Don't be reckless, Jojo! Just shoot him! You have to!
He... He's still alive... He was shot in the head, and he's still...
What is this...
What's going on?! Because I haven't the foggiest idea!
How is this possible?!
Jojo!
Witness the incredible power I now possess... I owe it to the stone mask!
Not to mention your father's blood!
Wrrrryyy!
He's draining his blood... and drawing energy from it?!
What happened that you turned into this, Dio?!
My head is spinning...
The knife... my father's death... his blood...
Dio... the stone mask... my research...
The brain... strange abilities... untold power!
Is Dio no longer human?
Wrryyyy!
Father...
D-Don't!
He's unstoppable!
I've never seen a monster like that before!
I've never seen a beast with that kind of otherworldly power!
I know...
To be quite honest, I'm terrified.
But Dio...
I cannot allow you to remain in this world!
I've inherited this responsibility, and I will put an end to it!
Mr. Joestar, don't! He'll kill you!
The brain!
Those spines in the stone mask must unlock some kind of hidden potential in the human brain!
Which means there might still be a chance to defeat him...
A corpse!
Blood... I want to lap it up!
Blood... just let me drink some of it!
Monster or not... it still pains me.
Father... please give me the strength!
I have to be strong...
Because Dio isn't human anymore!
He's a demon!
Watch out!
I won't let you slaughter another innocent person!
H-He stopped it...
It went through his hand and he still stopped it!
And the wound on his head is gone... it's already healed!
Immortal... He really is immortal, now!
Weak! You're still a weakling!
Jojo...
A little more...
I'd like to have a little more fun with this magnificent power...
I still haven't tested the extent of my abilities, after all...
Hiding, eh?
Remember what I said, Jojo?
Plot and scheme all you want, humans will always be slaves to their limitations.
I would stop struggling if I were you...
Come out from behind that curtain!
This isn't some scheme... This is courage!
His wounds are healing, even though he's on fire!
That's the reason behind his immortality!
This fire won't be enough to stop him!
What are you doing?!
Get to safety, Speedwagon! This isn't your fight!
There's no chance to escape if you go up there!
The fire is spreading to the entire mansion!
Mr. Joestar... what are you thinking?!
Come up here, Dio!
Dio! I won't let you and that unearthly power escape into the world!
Mr. Joestar, don't do it!
You're trying to keep me distracted...
So that your friend can escape...
Very well.
I'll heal these burns by draining the life from you...
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
I can fall from this height and not even feel a thing!
And you've just backed yourself into a dead end!
Father...
Father, I'll miss you...
Rise up to heaven, along with these burning embers...
And...
Please lend these flames the strength to do what must be done!
Mr. Joestar... what are you...
No... you can't be planning to...
No... you mustn't do what I think you are!
He's coming!
Wrryyyyyyy!
Weak! Weak as always!
At that moment, Jojo's entire youth flashed before his eyes!
My youth... the youth I spent with Dio!
That youth... ends here, once and for all!
Mr. Joestar wants the fire to burn hotter!
Hot enough to burn that monster to cinders before he can heal!
Just to defeat Dio!
That's why he's gone to the roof, he's waiting for the fire to grow stronger!
Don't!!
You worm! How dare you!
Joestar Manor... the home I grew up in is burning.
My father is dead... I've lost everything... Everything but my life!
But I'm willing to see that burn, too!
Whatever it takes, Dio... As long as I can put an end to that twisted power you wield!
Goodbye, Jojo!
It was only for a moment, but your resolve managed to impress me.
Now cry tears of joy, for you will be able to die alongside your father!
You buffoon!
I have surpassed humanity! I am immortal, invincible! I can rule the world!
This is the power you have given me, Jojo!
Too high!
Dio!
I'm not finished with you!
W-What?! You-
I'm not letting go this time!
Dio, I'm going to make you face your fate!
With the knife--
With the knife that you used to kill my father!
Wrrryyyyyy!
The bones in both of his arms should be shattered!
And his body is in flames, so why won't he loosen his grip?!
Very well! Let us plunge into the inferno together!
But you will be the only one to die!
My body is nigh invulnerable, I have the power to escape the flames no matter how hot they burn!
Father!
Give me the last of your strength!
He cries out... A cry that could no longer be heard!
Perhaps his words were able to reach his father's soul...
Or perhaps he instinctively used the home he grew up in to his advantage.
He kicked!
And after kicking that wall...
W-What?!
The guardian of the Joestar estate:
A statue of the Goddess of Love!
How dare you?! You think you can do this to-
I... I forgot...
My fatal error... was forgetting the way his anger can explode...
Jojo!
It can't end... not like this...
My... life...
Mr. Joestar!
Father...
You're alive!
He's alive!
He beat Dio...
He won!
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
There it is.
Next Episode
Courage comes from knowing true fear!
This guy's more of a freak than Dio!
Let's go, you maggots!
Where have I seen him before?
Please... teach me how to use the Ripple!
Episode 4:
"Overdrive"