Seven years have passed, it is now 1888.
-1888, London East End-
It is a time when women were being victimized by the mysterious serial killer known as Jack the Ripper.
He would come to be known as "The Terror of our Times."
But another "Terror of our Times" was born that year as well...
Born from the battle between Jojo and Dio!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Quality Check:
Tonitonichopchop
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 2: "A Letter from The Past"
He's got the ball!
The ball has been stolen by the hero of Hugh Hudson Academy!
Jonathan Joestar!
Jonathan Joestar, normally a mild-mannered gentleman, towers over his opponents at 6'4"!
At this moment however, he's roaring as he charges towards the goal!
Will he be able to win the championship for his team as the match draws to a close?!
He's been tackled!
But... but he's still standing!
Two more opponents are closing in!
They're on him! He's pinned down!
This is incredible!
The three men that attempted to tackle him are now being dragged along towards the goal line!
What power! What determination! My god, he's like a locomotive!
And now there's four!
This is too much, even for Joestar!
There's a pass!
It's received...
And it was caught by...
Dio! The pass was caught by Dio Brando!
Can he make it past them?!
He does! And again...!
And he's through!
He's on a solo run to victory! Once again, his speed is unmatched!
It's a try!
They pulled it off!
This final match of the season secures the championship!
It was all thanks to the excellent teamwork between Jojo and Dio!
We did it, Jojo!
Dio, your running was even more amazing than usual!
Thank you.
But I couldn't have done it without you, Jojo.
Dio Brando is on track to graduate at the very top of his class.
Meanwhile, his partner Jonathan Joestar has been making waves in the field of Archeology!
Victory wouldn't have been possible without these two young men! They are the pride of the entire university!
Jojo, we should tell father about our victory as soon as we get home.
Even after being adopted into our family, since when has Dio referred to my father as his own?
In spite of the conversation we just had, I feel no friendliness between the two of us...
Why? He's so charismatic, so affable...
Those events from seven years ago are still causing me doubt and confusion!
Dio! The school paper wants to do a story on your friendship. Could you give a us statement, please?
Our friendship? How embarrassing...
Come on! We'd love to hear it.
Well in that case...
Friendship?! Spare me your idyllic drivel, you undignified pieces of filth!
Soon, I will graduate... and then I will no longer require Lord Joestar's support!
I've spent the last seven years fabricating a rapport with Jojo, all for this moment...
My plan is to become the sole heir to the Joestar fortune!
And I am finally of age to rightfully claim that fortune and use it as I see fit!
Father, how are you feeling?
A little better... aside from the cough.
The doctors recommended I be admitted to the hospital today.
The hospital? That's a terrible idea!
The level of care at a hospital is atrocious, their only concern is how much money they make!
I turned them down, I feel more at ease in my own home.
And besides, the pain in my chest is gone, and the swelling in my hands seems to have gone away...
I'm already feeling better.
All he did was catch a cold...
But he's in such horrible condition...
Now then, Dio, Jojo... congratulations on the championship!
You already heard about it?!
A friend of mine from the university informed me about it.
That's an awful friend you have there!
We came home as soon as we could to surprise you with the good news!
Ah. Regardless, I am quite pleased!
I'm so proud of both of you. I have such wonderful sons.
I'm particularly proud of all you've accomplished, Dio.
Once you graduate, I want you to pursue whatever path you'd like.
You will have my full financial support.  You are family, after all.
You have my deepest gratitude for giving me the chance to rise above my meager upbringing...
I will do my best to live up to your expectations.
This is a secret that only I know...
I can only wonder what purpose this mask was created for...
Part of my interest in it is rooted in the fact that my late mother was the one who acquired it...
Perhaps one day I can publish my studies on the secret behind the mask...
Wouldn't it be amazing if I became renowned for my work?
Oh, drat!
I appreciate the help as always, Master Dio.
It must be my age... going up the stairs is becoming quite a trial.
I just thought of something... truly dreadful!
Dio...
He's...
Dio!
Just now...
What did you do with that medicine?!
What ever do you mean?
Do you usually bring my father his medicine?
Yes. What of it?
I found the letter that your father sent, seven years ago...
"I have fallen gravely ill..."
"I'm going to die soon, I can tell..."
"I don't recognize this disease, but my chest aches, my hands are swollen, and I can't stop coughing..."
These symptoms are the same as my father's!
What is the meaning of this, Dio?!
What exactly are you insinuating?
Let me see that medicine!
Jojo, if you doubt the validity of that medicine...
Then you doubt our very friendship...
Is that worth risking our friendship?!
The intensity of Dio's glare made me avert my eyes...
I don't even have any real evidence to base my accusation on, only suspicion.
Jojo... place the medicine back on the tray...
Do that, and I will ignore your preposterous accusation.
Dio! Swear to me...
As a gentleman, swear on the honor of your father and the Brando name!
Then I will trust you!
If you can swear on the honor of your true father, then I will return the medicine and never speak of this again!
If my suspicions are correct, then no matter how prideful he is, he wouldn't swear on such a lie.
Dio, swear this to me!
S-Swear?
You want me to swear on his honor?!
Who do you think he was...
There was nothing honorable at all about that pile of gutter trash!
You've confirmed my suspicions, Dio.
Your lack of composure and your malice are not normal.
I don't know what happened between you and your father...
But whatever it was, it drove you to murder him!
I will protect my father, and the Joestar name!
So, you want to fight?
Dio, I know what you've been after these past seven years!
There was never any friendship between us!
And you will stay away from my father!
I'll have this medicine examined, and I'll see you pay for your crimes!
Damn it...
And I was so close...
Was stumbling upon that letter some kind of divine justice?!
No! I won't let my plans be ruined because of that piece of trash!
Get rid of that dead bint's clothes already!
He put my mother through hell before she died...
Just the thought of that oaf's blood
running through my veins is enough to drive me mad!
Booze, bring me my damn booze!
But now... there is no turning back!
Father, I'm going to London for a few days.
Until I get back, please accept treatment from these doctors, and no one else.
The master has lost faith in our care...
That is not the case, but please do as Jojo asks.
I may not understand his reasons, but I have faith in my son...
F-Father...
His condition is getting worse...
He may need some sort of antidote...
It will take him at least three days for him to track down the source of that poison...
That leaves me three days to take care of Jojo...
And to make sure none of the evidence points to me!
Seven years ago, my blood caused a reaction in this mask.
If I can cause those spines to penetrate Jojo's skull, he'll be dead in an instant!
It will appear to be an accident during his research!
No one will ever suspect foul play!
Jojo... it looks like your curiosity...
-2 days later, London-
Is going to be the death of you!
Whoa there!
The university's laboratory was unable to identify the components of the poison...
Which means it more than likely came from the Orient.
That means...
Young Master!
You're approaching Ogre Street, the most dangerous slum in all of London!
I know... but I must go, nonetheless.
You're free to leave.
Dio lived in London...
This is the most likely place for him to have found such an exotic poison...
Once I track down its source...
I'll have my antidote and my evidence!
Yet another dead end?
How dreadful! That cat was eating a puppy!
Hey, Tattoo! Take him out!
Got it!
We'll carve up that fancy tosser and leave him dead in the alley!
I see... this place really lives up to its name!
Is he stupid?! He caught my bloody knife with his bare hand!
I guess you weren't thinking, because if I twist this knife then you'll be missing four fingers!
Just try it!
And the moment you do, you'll receive a kick in the bollocks from a leg the size of a tree trunk!
I have a cause that's worth losing some fingers over!
I will defend my father... I will defend my family...
I have more at stake in this fight than you do!
You there, you're of Asian descent...
Do you know of a place that sells poisons from the Orient?
You!
You say you don't mind losing your fingers?
Let's hope you're not bluffing, rich boy!
We'll put you to the test!
I won't let anything stand in my way!
What's with this dunce?!
Have you ever been in a real fight?!
You're protecting your head, but the rest of you is wide open!
That's the sound of steel cutting into bone!
You may have spared your head by throwing that knife, but you still took a direct hit!
W-Who the hell is this guy?!
H-He wasn't bluffing!
He's not just willing to lose his fingers, he doesn't even care if he loses his legs!
He's got the determination to cast aside all fear and physical pain!
I should have never tried to pick a fight with a tough guy like this!
What? Jojo went into Ogre Street on his own?
I tried to reason with him, but...
Let's not cause any unnecessary worry. Do not speak of this to Lord Joestar.
Looks like I may not have to use that mask after all...
Has he been murdered already? Perhaps a lynching?
D-Don't...
With my honor as a Speedwagon at stake, I refuse to forgive you if you lay a hand on this gentleman!
Gentleman?
Tell me something...
Why did you hold back when you kicked me?
With those legs, you could have smashed my face in!
I am here for the sake of my father.
The moment before I kicked you, I thought of your own father, your mother, your siblings...
I don't want to bring any pain upon your father, as well...
He's... he's serious!
He's naive to his core!
But...
I see... My friends aren't hurt very badly either...
This chap's a true gentleman, right through to his heart of hearts!
Truly worth of my admiration!
So, what's your name?
Jonathan Joestar.
All right then, Jonathan Joestar...
You said you were looking for a proprietor of Oriental poisons, correct?
I'd be careful! He's a cunning bastard!
It's been three days... and Jojo still isn't back.
He'll accomplish what he set out to do.
He was rambunctious when he was younger, but he's grown into a fine man.
I fear I may have been too strict with him in order to achieve that...
Damn it... Jojo, you had better be dead by now...
Did he discover where the poison came from...?
How could I lower myself to drink this swill...
I'm heading down the same path as that booze-addled piece of trash!
D-Damn it!
Oy, watch where yer' goin'! You clumsy fop!
Oy mate, I think the little shrimp got some piss on me jacket when he nudged me!
You listening, you little son-of-a-bitch?!
Me teef! Me fuckin' teef!
You bastard... what have you done to my friend?!
I'm amazed a disgusting, senile old fool like you has the nerve to speak to me in such a way!
This should be interesting...
I can use this opportunity...
To test this out before I use it on Jojo!
What're you yammerin' about?!
Consider this a live experiment!
W-Where is this light coming from?!
Was it just my imagination?
So he's dead?
How humdrum! It's just a run of the mill torture device.
It can't be...
He's not dead?!
W-What in the hell is he?!
Fangs?!
What... what incredible power!
He's... he's still standing?!
Doesn't he feel the pain from his arm?!
H-He barely grazed me, but my collarbone is broken!
I have to jump into the river...
I thirst...
I don't know why, but I'm so incredibly thirsty...
He's draining my blood?!
What the?!
Now I understand the secret behind the mask... but...
Damn it all! I don't want this sunrise to be the last thing I see!
T-The sunlight...
Where are the servants? Why are all the lights out?!
Jojo...
I found what I was searching for, Dio!
And now I have proof of your devilish conspiracy!
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
Next Episode
Jojo... I realize it's selfish, but I have one last request...
I can tell from his scent! He reeks worse than the lowest gutter trash I've ever met!
I'm through with being a mere mortal, Jojo!
Dio!
Episode 3:
"My Childhood With Dio"