I have to move my arm...
...before the Ripple reaches my head... Before it...
Before it-!
Master Dio...
If only he had a new body...
And so it was written in the London Press,
on December 4th, 1888:
Earlier this month, 73 of the 452 residents went missing
in the small mountain town of Wind Knight's Lot.
"The police are still on the lookout."
"There was only one eyewitness report."
"Four outsiders were sighted at the bottom
of the eastern cliff as they burned a pile of clothing."
"One of the suspects was seen taking a strange mask from the mansion, and later witnessed crushing it to pieces with a hammer."
That settles that!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 9: "The Final Ripple!"
"The head of the Joestar family, Mr. Jonathan Joestar..."
"...and the daughter of the Pendleton family, Miss Erina, have become married!"
"They're expected to honeymoon in America," huh?
Oh no! Look at the time!
Mr. Joestar's gonna be leaving soon!
Hey!
Mr. Speedwagon!
How can you be so late when you're seeing someone off?
My bad, my bad!
So where are they?
They're already on board.
Eh?!
The boat's leaving soon!
What?!
Where?! Where?!
Brother Styx, we hope to hear good news from your mission to Mexico.
I shall do my best.
Mr. Joestar! Where are you?
Outta the way!
This thing weighs a ton! What the hell could be in here?
How should I know?
Some strange oriental guy payed the fee to load it on board last night.
Wrrryyy...
Hey...
D-Did you hear something?
Cut the complaints and get moving!
We don't load this cargo, we don't get paid!
That hurt! What was that all about?
Mr. Speedwagon!
Look, there they are!
Hey, Mr. Joestar!
It's a damn fine thing!
I wish nothing but happiness for the two of you!
I'll always be there for you guys!
If you ever need me, I'll have your back, no matter what!
But knowing me, I'll probably just get in their way.
Mr. Joestar! Enjoy your trip!
- The Atlantic Ocean, En Route To America -
A single bird. It must have gotten separated...
Erina,
what's the matter?
Why were you crying?
They're tears of joy...
The joy of having you here.
When we were children, you took out
your handkerchief in front of those bullies,
even though you knew it would make them go after you instead.
Being together with the noble Jonathan Joestar is what fills me with such joy.
I feel the same.
When my heart was at its coldest,
you were the only warmth it knew...
This is why I'm so happy to have protected the world you live in.
I wish father could have met you...
Erina...
Come now, dinner is being served!
Jonathan-!
I was just about to tell you to watch your head...
Ah, if only this day could last forever.
For Christ's sake, the engine room?
I just had to drop it in the dirtiest place possible.
I don't need it too badly, but it is a tool of the trade.
My Lord...
You certainly enjoy testing the patience of your humble servant.
No thank you... I've never tasted alcohol before.
Just try a bit. One sip won't hurt.
I swear, it isn't very strong.
Just try it.
Go on...
I-It's him!
Jonathan?
It can't be... that's impossible!
Dio... is still-
Erina, go back to the cabin!
And make sure to lock the door behind you!
Huh? What kind of cargo is this?
What's with this lock?
How bizarre... I can see the latch on the other side of the lock.
But that would mean this box...
...was locked from the inside?!
Hold it!
You're-!
My body... I've found it.
D-Dio!
Jonathan was acting strange...
Something must be wrong with him.
Jojo, look at what you've done to me, the mighty Dio.
Behold... Behold, and I will show you the fruits of my labor.
And why am I showing you this?
Because, Jojo, despite the hatred I should have,
I now find myself admiring you instead.
Your courage. Your soul. Your power. I respect it all.
This is what I have come to realize.
Dio...
Jojo...
Were it not for you,
I would have never come into possession of the stone mask.
However, you were also the one that kept me from ruling the world.
If there really were a god controlling our fate, I doubt even he could have made two destinies more perfectly intertwined than our own.
You and I are equal parts of a greater whole.
And so, I will now seize the body of the only man in the world I truly admire...
...and I will live on for an eternity!
That is the fate of the mighty Dio!
Your death will be painless; a final act of courtesy towards my rival!
Those eyes! This is bad!
You shall live on as my new body, Jojo!
Jonathan!
Eri... na...
Jo-Jonathan!
What a shame.
Had you not tried to dodge, I would have pierced your brain and granted you an instant death.
You're so surprised to see your life descend into
utter hell you've been stricken speechless, is that it?
Did Jojo not tell you of my legend? My descent into darkness?
Despite this pitiful state, I'm sure you still recognize me... Erina Pendleton.
Or should I say, Mrs. Erina Joestar?
Dio!
This ship is teeming with monsters!
By your command, I feasted on the blood of a single crewman,
and now the entire ship is filled with our brethren!
And now we shall all make our way to America, won't we, Master Dio?
I-I can't speak...
But more importantly... I can't breathe-!
Erina...
Erina!
I have to... save you-!
I can't channel the Ripple-!
Master Dio, look!
This worthless pile of filth can't breathe!
He can't use that Ripple thing either!
Should I begin shredding you to pieces for reducing Master Dio to this state?
Or should I wait the few minutes that it will take for you to bleed out?
Enough, Wang Chung!
There shall be no disrespect towards Jojo!
He was the only mortal capable of reducing me to this state.
You will honor his accomplishment by
quickly and painlessly slicing off his head!
Y-Yes, Master Dio!
And with that, my friend's body shall become my future!
Johnathan!
Be careful with his strange movements! Stand back!
He's going to take a gamble on a last ditch attack!
There's nothing to fear!
Master Dio overestimates this filthy dog!
I'm going to scoop out your brain with my fingers, you imbecile!
Erina... not her...
I'll release the last of my Ripple energy at once...
...no matter how little I have left!
Th-This is bad! Wang Chung!
It's gone... Something inside of me is gone...
Something vital...
This isn't good!
Th-That... That was the last of my life force...
My life's final Ripple... and it was too weak to destroy that zombie...
But it should be... just enough...
W-What?!
Jojo must have done something to Wang Chung's body!
That Ripple didn't destroy his body,
but it was enough to manipulate his movements!
And now Wang Chung is clinging to that machinery like he's being possessed.
A-And by doing that he's going to stop...
...the ship's guiding screw shaft!
A zombie is more than strong enough to stop that shaft!
And with it stopped, the steam inside the ship's pistons will have nowhere to escape, causing the pressure to rise!
Which means once the pressure reaches a certain point... the ship will explode!
Jonathan...
How did this... How could this have happened... Why?!
Get out of here, Erina...
The ship is... going to explode...
I don't understand why this is happening...
I never imagined this happening...
I don't know if I want to cry, scream, or maybe just faint...
I just don't know.
However, there is one thing I do know.
I, Erina Joestar...
...will die at your side!
I can tell from the warmth of his lips...
Why is this happening? I can feel death enveloping him...
Jonathan Joestar is going to die... but, as long as he's alive...
...I will stay by his side.
Until the ship explodes. Until everything turns to embers... Until everything is gone.
Let the tears flow if you must... but please... survive...
H-How is such nobility even possible?
You're willing to die, and only to save the life of someone else's child!
Your courage can be so cruel!
All that I wish for is to die by your side!
That mother... sacrificed herself... for her child...
The same... as my mother did for me...
Take the child... Take it... and hurry!
So, you plan to blow this ship to pieces?!
Jojo, even with these last breaths, your obstinance is remarkable!
But the mighty Dio can be just as obstinate!
I will survive! No matter what it takes!
And I'll be taking your body along with me!
Zombies!
Devour Wang Chung! Get those pistons moving again!
It's going to begin exploding soon...
Jonathan!
The explosion is starting!
But I, the mighty Dio, must always protect myself from the sun!
I'm more than prepared to withstand a little explosion!
Erina! Take a good look!
With Jojo unable to create a Ripple,
I can take control of his body with ease!
And then, I shall retreat to my bedroom in that box!
It's capable of withstanding an absolutely massive explosion!
Consider it a bomb shelter made for one!
Here I come, Jojo!
And I bid welcome to my new, immortal body!
Jonathan!
Dio...
You could be right...
The two of us may very well be inseparable by fate.
I even feel like I have some kind of bizarre friendship with you...
And now our fates are truly one in the same...
We will both vanish in the explosion of this ship.
Find... happiness... Erina...
Let go of me... Jojo!
Let go of me! Just think about it, Jojo!
I can grant you immortality as well!
I'll heal your wounds. You can spend eternity with Erina!
Jojo!
Jojo?!
H-He...
He's dead...
February 7th, 1889
Jonathan Joestar passes away
Jonathan Joestar's life vanished in the depths of eternity.
He spent his life in the shadows of history
that the world will never truly know.
Society will never know the story of the proud life that he lived.
However, his descendants will.
The new life growing inside me will know the truth.
Erina Joestar was rescued off the coast of the Canary Islands two days later.
And for now, the curtain falls on the legend of the stone mask...
However! This was only the beginning of a new age of adventure!
Part 1: Phantom Blood
The End
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
Next Episode
It was 1938...
It's been a while, Speedwagon.
How'd you know about my brass knuckles, you little punk?!
Deal with him!
Joseph Joestar. But just call me Jojo.
Episode 10:
"New York's Jojo"