Because, you see... the Ripple is naturally channeled through water!
This is it! Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
Jo-!
Jojo!
H-He did it!
This isn't over!
I never expected he would reach the surface at the same speed as the Ripple...
What speed... The Overdrive only grazed Bruford's forehead!
It looks like I'll have to deliver the Ripple of the sun with a full-contact punch after all!
Master Dio! I offer my eternal gratitude for being revived,
as well as the chance to fight this child!
He is worthy to bear the title of a true warrior!
We shall no longer hold ourselves back within the confines of underwater battle!
Let this be a battle of strength versus strength!
Skill versus skill! Cunning versus cunning!
You whelp! Prove that you can stand up in battle against the mighty Bruford!
Wrryyyyyy!
Even under Dio's influence, he still has the same pride he had until the day he died!
And that pride is rooted in his respect for intense battling!
I'll take your blood and make it my own!
He's attacking with his hair again?!
Have at it! This time I'll send my Ripple right through it!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 6: "Courage of Tomorrow"
Overdrive Barrage!
Jojo!
This is bad... A Ripple can only flow outward from the limbs!
If he's tied up and unable to move his arms,
he won't be able to use his Ripple to cut that hair!
E-Even if we try to help him, we've already got our hands full!
Tarkus, you brute!
H-His hair is piercing through my clothes and eating into my skin...
...and the more I struggle, the stronger it gets!
He's draining my blood through his hair!
This is the end, young warrior!
I'll slice off your head and drink from the fountain of blood!
That's it!
The Ripple that flows through steel...
Metal Silver Overdrive!
B-Brilliant! He was able to defend himself from the sword and deliver the Ripple with the same technique!
My heart is burning...
...with the heat of a raging fire!
Feel the pounding beat of my pulse!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
He did it! That's the sound of the Ripple when it makes full contact!
Th-This man was nothing like the savages I've fought so far...
Bruford... he still had his wits about him, and a sense of his past...
Regardless, it's better this way... He's a zombie that preys on humankind, giving rise to more monsters!
He must be defeated!
I am... the Black Knight, Bruford!
This pain means nothing to me!
You're pathetic, Bruford!
Even reduced so low, your bloodlust as a zombie forces you to keep attacking!
What?!
Mr. Joestar, what are you doing?!
Move or he'll strike you down! Why won't you move?!
What is this...
What are they doing?!
You said before... the pain was nothing to you.
Pain... You can feel pain again.
F-Flowers...
They're blooming at Bruford's feet!
After being struck by the Ripple, the Black Knight Bruford's body is starting to crumble.
But at the same time, he can feel pain once again...
The same pain that once made him human!
The Ripple has destroyed his zombified body, but it has also resurrected his noble soul!
That's why I stopped fighting...
That's why you didn't follow through with your sword...
His face!
It isn't twisted with anger or resentment anymore!
It's gentle, like the face of a boy as he talks to his mother!
You... thought I was going to halt my strike?
You were really so sure I wouldn't retaliate?
Do you really have such faith in others?
This pain is the burden of the living...
A pain that serves to contrast with the rare moments of pure joy in life.
I suppose that is the meaning of humanity.
I feel a bizarre sense of peace right now...
I no longer feel resentment for this world.
Having met such an astounding man...
Such a warm human-being...
Meeting a person like you before my end will finally allow me to join my queen.
My friend from a world three centuries beyond my own... tell me your name.
Jonathan Joestar.
Jonathan...
I wish upon you the same blessing that is engraved on this sword, bestowed unto me by my Queen...
Good Fortune
Luck!
...and let this guide you towards your destiny...
Courage!
Pluck!
Bruford!
What a tragedy... What a bizarre fate!
To have the only salvation for your soul come when faced with death...
Even as he embraced death while cursing the world,
he had such pride!
That terrible stone mask! It was responsible for changing him into an absolute madman!
No matter what... I'm not going to forgive you for this, Dio!
Jojo! Behind you!
Tarkus!
H-How could you?!
How could you shatter Bruford's armor like that?!
You just hearlessly crushed it into dust!
Bruford was a coward!
I may have respected him,
but he was nothing more than a strategist!
I yearn for the day I can become an elite slaughterer!
My strength... will bring death and destruction to all!
Now let me hear your cries of despair!
Nice catch, Jojo!
The cliff is collapsing!
These leaves...
Jojo!
Right!
Life Force Magnetism Overdrive!
Grab on, Speedwagon, Poco!
Within every human being, there exists a very faint trace of a magnetic field...
By using an Overdrive, this inherent magnetism can be greatly powered up!
By letting that Ripple flow into the leaves, they too become living magnets!
Amazing!
Yay!
How are you doing this?! Are you folks even human?
Or are you some kinda angels sent down from heaven?!
He's got a point!
I've grown so used to this madness, I've quit questioning it.
But there's one mystery I'd still like to see answered!
Old man Zeppeli, where in the world did you learn to do all of this?!
I met a rather curious fellow in a port town in India...
He claimed to be a doctor, but he appeared far too young and ragged for that to be true.
I was shocked!
On that fateful day, he radiated a bright light which healed a leg that would have required amputation with conventional medicine!
The power he used was that of the Ripple!
I realized I could use the Ripple to help defend against the maleficence of the stone mask....
...so I journeyed further along the Salween River into Tibet, seeking the man whom taught that doctor...
His name... was Tompetty.
Wanderer from afar, I can see your future...
You have come seeking knowledge... but be warned, should you move forward, your destiny will forever be changed.
Your fate will only lead to death.
Very well.
I have a cause that I am more than willing to die for.
The prophecy foretold by my teacher, Tompetty...
I can't tell Jojo, or anyone else...
Old man?
W-What's that sound? Is it from the Ripple?
N-No!
It's Tarkus!
Wrryyyyyyy!
H-He's a madman! He threw himself at us from that height?!
This glider is filled with the Life Force Magnetism Ripple!
What did he expect would happen?
Look!
T-That's the knights' old training grounds!
Jump down there, before he makes us crash into the ground!
Tarkus slammed straight into that stone wall!
Zombie or not, that must have destroyed his body!
And unlike Dio, he didn't wear the stone mask!
His body can't regenerate, so there's no way he's still moving.
W-What a monster... His obsession with battle keeps him moving...
...even though his bones should be completely shattered!
He's climbing up!
Our priority is defeating Dio, but if he's going to chase us, we won't have a choice.
We'll deal with Tarkus first!
Jojo! Get that boy to safety inside!
There's something strange about this door... It doesn't feel right.
B-Be careful!
This is where the Knights used to train for their battles!
I've heard this place is full of traps!
Mr. Joestar! Something's coming for you!
Mister!
Jojo!
T-This is...
...Tarkus!
How nostalgic...
...The Chamber of the Two-Headed Dragon's Chain Death Match...
It's been three hundred years since I've been here... I shall Indulge.
This is one of many chambers where the medieval knights would hone their deadly skills!
The Chamber of the Two Headed Dragon, home to the Chained Neck Death Match!
I have taken 48 lives in here... You will find I am quite skilled at it.
G-Give it a rest, old man Zeppeli! It's too thick!
O-Oh no... His knuckles are torn ragged!
Unfortunately, the Ripple was never intended to be used as a tool for destruction...
A small rock can be broken, but this door is far stronger than that.
Even worse, Jojo will run into the same problem...
He won't be able to break those chains!
The only way out of that collar is the key...
The one in my collar!
The door cannot be opened from the outside during a match...
...and the key for each man's shackles is contained in his opponent's collar!
Which means the only one who will leave this room...
...is the one who can rip off the head of his opponent first!
Overdrive!
T-The chain is attached to the ceiling, so the Ripple disperses before it can even reach Tarkus!
He broke my arm!
I could heal it with the Ripple's life-giving energy...
...but first I need to do something about the collar crushing my neck... it's keeping me... from breathing properly!
Jojo!
Damn it! D-did I just wet my pants?!
I-I need to get away from these people...
They're the ones who brought this disaster on our town!
Mr. Zeppeli, that lever...
I think the door only opens from the inside!
Jojo may be willing to fight one on one,
but he's sure to be exhausted after defeating Bruford.
We have to find some way to get in there and help him, no matter what it takes!
I don't see any other way in there!
It's too small...
These guys could never fit through there...
But...
...I can.
Damn it!
If we can't get the door open, then we're out of options!
We'll have to go through the entrance
that Tarkus used further down!
But that will take too long!
We have no other choice!
I'm always watching everyone from the sidelines...
I can never do anything to help!
Hey, Poco... Look at me!
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
The little brat's scared out of his wits!
He's shakin' like a leaf!
Would you look at that!
He's gonna cry!
H-Hey!
That's enough, let's scram!
S-Sis...
They were bullying you again, weren't they?
It's just sad. Why don't you fight back for once?
I... I will... tomorrow!
And yet tomorrow never comes...
I-I mean it!
Poco...
What really scares you the most?
Is the pain what you're really afraid of?
Is that what frightens you so much?
You think that pain is scary...
What about the thought of growing up to be powerless? Doesn't that scare you even more?!
I-I...
There, there, crybaby...
Let's go home and get those clothes cleaned up, okay?
Poco!
A window?!
H-Hey! Are you trying to get in through there?!
Stop, you fool!
Stop him! Even if he manages to get inside,
Tarkus will have no qualms with killing a little boy!
Kid, what are you doing?! It's too dangerous!
T-Think about what happened when
those monsters attacked last time...
If that big man dies, then who's gonna protect the town?
Who's gonna save my sister?!
I'm doing this... to protect my sister!
Sis! Tomorrow comes today!
Get back! It's dangerous!
Wrryyyy!
Don't interfere with our duel!
Poco!
I-I'm not... afraid... of a little pain...
I... did it...
That was incredible, Poco...
Don't worry... Your injuries aren't too severe.
Old man Zeppeli, make this animal pay for what he's done!
Sir?
Your fate will only lead to death.
Well... the time has finally come, as it was foretold...
If this is to be my destiny... then I will embrace it without regrets.
Mr. Zeppeli!
What... did... you just say?
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
Next Episode
This... is just too cruel!
You'll pay for this, Tarkus!
I'll smash you to a pulp!
Jojo...
Inherit my will!
Episode 7:
"Sorrowful Successor"