Poco! Who do you think you are, being out at such a late hour?!
D-Dad...
I'm glad that you're safe, but...
W-Where's my sister?
She got worried and went off looking for you!
She... She went outside?!
Poco, what's gotten into you?
This isn't like you.
Sis...
Sis!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 8: "Jojo & Dio's Bloody Battle!"
Allow me to give you a metaphor.
Much like this exquisite rose,
your beauty has only just begun to bloom.
But consider this, Mademoiselle.
Once a flower has bloomed,
all that remains for it is to wither away and die.
Such a pity, isn't it?
The little lady is sixteen years old!
Truly a prime virgin!
She's absolutely radiating delicious life energy!
Right, Master Dio?
Those without a sense of etiquette have no right to live.
Now then, Mademoiselle. I have a proposition for you.
Wouldn't it be lovely to spend eternity in the prime of your youth?
You see I, the mighty Dio, am not the type to
force someone into companionship, unlike other men...
You will choose your fate, and it will be of your own free will.
Monster...
Eh? I didn't quite get that.
You're doomed to be cursed for all eternity... you m-monster!
Eh... It's quite the pity, having to part ways so soon after we met.
But before you go...
This is Doobie, the Monstrous.
And if the company of the great Dio is not to your liking,
then perhaps he will better entertain you.
Bye, Mademoiselle!
Who did that?!
Who indeed.
I don't see why I should share my name with such a lowly zombie!
Sis!
Poco!
You really fell for it!
What is that, moving inside his head?
W-What...
That zombie... has snakes slithering inside of him!
And not just any snakes, venomous cobras and ones that eat human flesh!
You've been bitten!
Those poisonous snakes bit him... m-more than once!
What a nuisance.
I don't have time to waste on Dio's twisted underlings!
He's strong...
He even managed to squeeze out the venom.
It's amazing he gained such control over
the flow of his blood in such a short time.
It's because old man Zeppeli passed his
life force on to Mr. Joestar before he died!
It only takes a bit of Ripple energy to manipulate these snakes!
Sis!
Poco!
I've returned from hell, Dio!
So, you're still alive, Jojo...
I suppose that means you managed to defeat those knights, correct?
Master Dio! Give us the order and we'll execute him!
Let us bury him in our fangs!
Dio!
No! This one, here...
Leave this one to me, the mighty Dio!
I'll be honest, Jojo.
I did not want to have to be the one to kill you...
I find little amusement at the thought of turning
the man I was raised with, my own brother, into an undead.
That's why I intended for those two knights to handle it.
However, I see now it was naive not to finish you off myself.
Seeing you alive has shown me the error of my ways;
the one fatal flaw of the mighty Dio.
But now, I see it is up to me to tear you limb from limb!
The feeling is mutual! I feel no guilt in putting an end to you!
By the way, Jojo...
Where is that old man with the ridiculous hat and mustache?
Where could he have gone?
Dio... let me tell you how I feel.
Although it is unbecoming of a gentleman...
To be perfectly honest, right now I, Jonathan Joestar...
...would like nothing more than to avenge
the people you've killed, Dio! Prepare to die!
Come, Jojo!
Mr. Dire!
Get back, Jojo!
I, Dire, have greater claim for vengeance against this fiend!
Zeppeli and I shared a 20 year friendship,
forged in the rigor of our harsh training!
Dio, listen!
Let it be known that I, Dire, shall send you into the fiery depths of hell!
Stop! Dio has hidden powers that you've never dealt with!
That is quite the interesting footwork...
I suppose you humans can achieve that level of agility through mere effort.
But in just one night, the mighty Dio has
surpassed even the most extraordinary of mortals!
Wrrryyyyyyy!
You think that pathetic looking kick
will be enough to defeat me, the mighty Dio?!
You fell for it, fool!
Thunder Cross Split Attack!
Amazing!
This technique is allowing him to attack and
keep his opponent from defending with their arms!
It's a perfect offense and defense!
No martial artist has ever successfully defended against it!
That's-
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
I... can't move!
His dehydration freeze!
He withdraws all fluid from his body in an instant,
dropping his temperature to steal body heat from his enemy!
When Dio freezes the body, he halts the flow of blood,
effectively stopping the Ripple along with it!
B-But even I'm shocked at Dio displaying such power!
Now he can freeze an entire body in an instant!
Y-You bastard!
Weakling, weakling!
Did you really think you could stand up to me, you utter fool?!
Coming here has guaranteed that you will die like a dog!
Now, allow me to provide you with the most vicious death I can offer!
D-Dire!
Stop!
Jojo! Let's begin.
You'll be the next I send into oblivion!
Dire!
Thorns from a rose infused with a Ripple are quite poisonous, aren't they?
Mr. Dire!
How... How dare you...
How dare you scratch my face!
Mr. Dire...
Speedwagon!
Yeah!
Dio, the key to defeating your dehydration freeze...
The key to finally piercing you with a Ripple...
Mr. Dire has just shown me the key to defeating you!
I'll charge it with the Ripple, and then strike you down with
the hero Bruford's sword imbued with Luck and Pluck!
Good Fortune
Courage
You're all lower than frog piss...
You and that damned Ripple!
You dare strike me with it?!
Know your god-damned place!
I'm going to feed you all to the undead!
I'll make sure each of you pissants is turned into mincemeat!
There it is! That's the twisted personality I sensed,
more gruesome than any villain I've ever met!
He was simply hiding behind a mask of calm and gallantry!
This is his true nature!
Now he's finally been outed, just from the shame
of having tasted the Ripple for the first time!
I, Straits, will show no mercy!
The name's Page!
Jones!
Plant!
Bonham!
Blood Vessel Skewering!
Since a rose is a living thing, it can carry
the power of the Ripple when it's released from one's hand...
But seeing as metal is not alive...
...I must channel it directly.
They keep coming...
Lad, let us take care of these underlings.
From what I can see, Dio could match the speed of a cheetah!
With the power of Zeppeli's Ripple added
to his own, he should be able to keep up!
However, Dio is so strong, he can destroy
flesh and bone with the lightest touch!
It would end in an instant...
The battle will be decided as soon as they make contact!
I'll drain the life right out of you!
I'll purify your twisted ambition!
W-When did he grab those roses?!
Wrryyyyy!
Now's my chance!
G-Good! He circled around to Dio's right!
He's blind on that side!
D-Damn it! His fighting skills have improved!
H-He's got him!
He finally defeated Dio!
Not quite!
You damned buffoon!
It... can't be...
It's frozen!
Weakling, weakling!
Wrrrryyyy!
Now you will become another one of my children of the night!
I'm caressing your carotid artery as we speak, Jojo!
This warm, throbbing pulse...
...It's quite the sensation.
K-Kick!
My legs are frozen, too!
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
Try to hold still, Jojo!
Otherwise this delicate little vessel might be severed.
And I'll have none of that, not when I plan to knick it
just enough to exchange my vampiric fluids for your blood!
I-I have to help him!
My zombies!
Keep those pissants out of my hair for just a moment!
They aren't relenting!
We don't stand a chance of saving him!
Now then, Jojo.
It's finally time to receive my fluids and become my servant!
Dio, it isn't over yet!
There's just one fatal flaw in your plan!
And what's that?!
You left the rest of my body unfrozen so you could drain my blood!
Freezing my body prevents the Ripple from flowing.
However, it also prevents you from draining my life energy!
This is your one fatal flaw!
He's using the torch to thaw out!
This can't be... The heat from that flame is
more intense than the cold from dehydrating him!
He'll use the sword to channel the Ripple...
Sunlight Yellow...
Overdrive!
Take this!
He got him!
No, look again!
It seems as if the Ripple has failed!
My arm... My arm is frozen again!
He can freeze me just from touch!
Not good enough, Jojo!
I, Dio, must admit that your ingenuity in
times of desperation is quite impressive.
And your plan with the fire was equally impressive.
But come now, Jojo. You have no way of
defeating my freezing technique.
You've seen what I did to your arm.
I can freeze your entire body solid in a mere two seconds!
He expelled the vampiric fluid... Mr. Joestar hasn't given up just yet!
Whatever is that tense looking stance for?
Do you still intend to fight?
Struggle all you like, but remember
you're limited to what you can do as a mortal.
All your training to master this Ripple technique has been...
Useless, useless, useless, useless, useless, useless,
useless, useless, useless, useless, useless, useless!
A monkey cannot surpass a human!
Because when faced with the mighty Dio,
you are nothing more than a mere monkey, Jojo!
You're wrong!
If a man has faith, he can accomplish anything!
Humanity can evolve, and so can I!
I'm afraid that you can't!
Especially not once you've become my zombie!
Wrryyyyyyy!!
His hand! It's on fire!
He lit his glove on fire!
That might be enough to overpower the freezing technique!
You're about to learn which one of us will taste defeat in the end, Dio!
WRRRRRYYY!
H-He blocked it!
No!
It's getting through!
I... I-I'm melting...
T-This pain... This heat!
I was supposed to live on for centuries... For eternity...
I, the mighty Dio!
Begone, Dio...
I am the mighty Dio!
He expelled the rest of his fluids from his eyes?!
If I had been hit just a few centimeters to the right...
my brain would have been pierced!
This is bad!
It's his final act. One final act of defiance
before his evil vanishes from this world.
Dio's falling off the cliff!
Dio...
Hey, mister!
He's just exhausted.
Can't blame him either. He's fought countless
life or death battles in a single night.
But, why was he crying when he beat a bad guy?
It's because he spent his youth alongside Dio.
Still, I can be happy in his place!
Did you see that, old man Zeppeli?
He did it... Mr. Joestar finally did it!
Dio is dead.
I'm not one to exaggerate, but I daresay we saved the world!
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
We spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley... hey!
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
there with you
Next Episode
It's a damn fine thing!
They're tears of joy.
R-Run...
As long as we're together, I wouldn't mind staying like this forever...
My body... I've found it.
Episode 9:
"The Final Ripple!"