- 1863 Tibet -
You've done well to endure the hardships of
your training for the past three years.
If you so desired, you could run
across the land without losing a single breath.
Normally, we would begin to move into the final stage of training, instructing you in the most advanced Ripple techniques...
But I must warn you one last time, Zeppeli...
If you continue along this path, there will be no escaping the fate I have foreseen for you.
This is your last chance to turn back.
Doing so will allow you to take a different path.
Master Tompetty...
Elder, please... tell me the destiny my life force reveals...
...about my fated death.
When will it happen? Where will it take place?
What good will come of knowing this?
I have a task that I must be able to complete...
A duty that I cannot turn my back on...
Knowing will allow me to stay true to that goal.
Once I know the time of my death, I can make peace with the outcome.
Then I will accept my fate.
If you are truly this determined...
...then so be it!
In an ancient chamber, hidden from view, and heavy with the stench of death...
...a child will reveal the way.
In order to set a young lion free, you will incur a mortal injury...
And then, you will be clenched in the cruel grip of death!
Old man Zeppeli...
Be careful, old man!
Here I come, Jojo!
Now I must set that young lion free... Onwards, to his destiny!
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
Editor:
Chonichonitoptop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Chonichonitoptop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Chonichonitoptop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Chonichonitoptop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Chonichonitoptop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Chonichonitoptop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 7: "Sorrowful Successor"
This collar won't even budge...
...and I still haven't seen Tarkus use this room to his full advantage!
It's eerie!
Make your move, worm!
I know you're itching to unleash your Ripple on me!
A wretch like you won't even be able to lay a finger on me!
What's the matter? Lost your nerve?!
Way to go, old man Zeppeli!
Take this, Tarkus!
Tornado Overdrive!
W-What the-?!
From above!
No, Mr. Zeppeli! The chain is coming from below you!
An attack that closes in from above and below!
This is my deathblow; the Hell and Heaven Snake Kill!
Now I'll crush you both to death!
I-If I can't breathe... I can't use... the Ripple...
Jo...
Jojo...
Master Dio...
...I have disposed of them, as you wished.
This was... This was far too cruel!
Mr. Joestar!
So you're still alive, even with a broken neck?
Time to put you out of your misery!
Jo... Jojo!
This one is also still going?!
My ultimate...
...This is my ultimate...
This is my ultimate technique! I'm passing it on to you, Jojo!
Jojo... please... inherit my will!
Ultimate Deep Pass Overdrive!
Jojo... I'm passing down all of my life energy to you...
O-Old man...
Old man Zeppeli!
I'm going to smash the two of you to a pulp beneath my feet!
H-How the hell-?!
M-Mr. Joestar... lifted up Tarkus?!
Old man Zeppeli's Ripple must have healed his broken neck!
You fool! You're really trying to remove that collar by force?!
You're just a mere mortal man!
You're trying to break steel that even I couldn't break,
even with the power granted to me by Master Dio!
You will pay, Tarkus!
Mr. Joestar!
W-What?!
Your twisted mind... that hideous madness of yours...
You willingly surrendered the depths of your mortal soul to Dio, haven't you?
Wrrrrryyyyyy!
He's strong!
He's incredibly strong!
He isn't the same Mr. Joestar he was before!
The Ripple of old man Zeppeli's life force is flowing right through him!
This is the strength of their power combined!
Tarkus... Not a single bone of yours will be left when I'm done with you.
I'm going to exorcise that wicked soul of yours!
Fade back... into the shadows of history!
I've had enough of your insolence, whelp!
So you're resorting to petty tricks?!
He got him!
Mr. Zeppeli!
Mr. Zeppeli...
This... This can't be...
If you're gone...
If you're gone... what are we going to do?!
Jojo, you...
You damned idiot!
Now is not the time to mourn!
You... you still have to...
Now, there's no time to lose...
You must must go and defeat Dio.
Destroy... the stone mask...
Mr. Zeppeli!
I'm... satisfied with the way... my destiny played out.
When I was a young man... I was married...
However... I abandoned my family for the quest to destroy the stone mask...
But now, I can rest in peace being satisfied with the life I led...
I can accept what has become of me...
In the end... at least I was able to pass on all that I had...
Jojo.... you are my living hope.
Mr. Zeppeli...
I think of you as my best friend and son...
...and... I will continue... to live on...
...within you...
Jo...
In the words of 19th century novelist William M. Thackeray...
"To love and win is the best thing."
"To love and lose, the next best."
And so, once again, Jojo finds himself inheriting another man's way of life... and his very spirit.
Goodbye... Mr. Zeppeli.
I-I'm begging you...
Please... Please, just spare my child...
Let me see if I understand your request, Miss...
You do not mind what happens to you, so long as we do not harm your child?
Is that correct?
Just spare my child... I beg of you!
How heartwarming!
Okay... Neither I, nor my men, will bring any harm to that infant.
I, Dio, swear this to you.
But, if I may... The men you see around you have all given in to their fear,
and so they offered their souls to me in my greatness.
You and your child would be much happier if you both joined us, I assure you.
You would be free from from worry and pain...
Your family would be absolved of all hatred!
Please, spare my child!
Spare him...
Okay, okay.
My... My baby!
As I promised, my men and I have done nothing.
Even as his mother, you still devoured him!
A tragedy of your own making...
Mr. Joestar's face has changed...
He has a very brooding look on his face...
The same goes for me...
I'm just barely able to hold back the anger and sadness!
Even so, until Dio has been defeated, we can't afford to mope!
Mr. Joestar! Dio said he was planning to wipe this town out by tomorrow!
Zombies will give rise to more zombies!  They'll breed like rats!
How are they holding up over there?
Are the people of Wind Knights' Lot still alive?!
I hope my sister and the others are okay...
Let's hurry...
Mr. Adams!
Hey, Poco! Where have you been, wandering off at this hour?
Mr. Adams, is my sister all right?!
And what about the town?!
Is she okay?
Kid... she's not all right at all!
She's absolutely livid!
She said she's gonna lock you up with the cows when you get home!
Well, it looks like the town is safe for now...
Then let's hurry!
T-Thank you, Mr. Adams!
A-A child...
The warm blood of a child is such a treat!
He was already a zombie!
You think you can match my speed?!
It looks like the town has already been...
Precisely.
The zombies have already surrounded the town...
N-No!
Another zombie?!
My name is Dire.
A kick? But it's so slow...
Deathblow! Thunder Split Attack!
W-What an amazing man!
Any other man would have flinched to avoid that attack...
...but you attacked with a headbutt, even though it ended up hurting you!
Wait, Jonathan Joestar!
I am a human.
Please excuse me for testing the skills you learned from Zeppeli.
You knew Mr. Zeppeli?!
Yes... Zeppeli and I trained under the same master.
We underwent the same hardships together,
and have been friends for over 20 years.
Indeed...
I am Straits... Take a look at this.
A letter?
It was sent by...
...Mr. Zeppeli!?
Precisely...
A letter from Zeppeli, requesting our assistance.
Upon learning the location of the stone mask and the identity of the holder, he sent us the details.
This is our master, Tompetty.
A pleasure to meet you.
You're Mr. Zeppeli's master... The elder, Tompetty.
We do not share the same customs, you see...
This is how we greet one another.
So, where is Zeppeli?
I see, then Zeppeli has already passed on...
Even if we had arrived sooner, his fate would not have changed...
I must say, this Dio exudes a very unnerving power...
He life force is incredibly malevolent!
In little more than a night, this town now entirely belongs to me...
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
Next Episode
You fell for it, fool!
I, Straits, will show no mercy!
I feel no guilt putting an end to you!
Come, Jojo!
Episode 8:
"Jojo & Dio's Bloody Battle!"