-1868 England-
Oy, look at this! There's been an accident!
Bloody hell, looks like he died right away...
Horse must'a slipped on the rocks and the whole lot tumbled down here.
These nobles are quite the picture of wealth, wouldn't you say?
Dario!
The woman in there is dead, but the baby's still alive!
She must have sacrificed herself to save it...
I don't give a rat's arse about some baby!
W-What are you doing?!
Ain't it obvious, you bint!?
We're relievin' em of their valuables!
What have we here?
Some bizarre lookin' mask...
It ain't worth keeping.
Give me a hand here!
Grab his teeth, we can sell em' to a dentist!
Fetch a fair price, they will!
Y-you there... did... did you save me?
Thank you...
My wife...
My wife and my son... were you able to rescue them?
The bitch... err, I mean... the lady seems to have passed away, unfortunately.
The kid seems all right, though.
Perhaps this is fate at work...
I am from the house of Joestar...
I would like to repay you for saving my life.
Please, before I lose consciousness again, please tell me your name.
This damned fool thinks I'm the one that saved his life!
Bloody idiot! Let's see how far I can play this fool...
The name is Dario Brando, my good man.
Mister Brando...
The Joestars... always stand by their word.
-12 Years Later-
That's a good boy!
Father, I'm off!
Be careful, Jojo!
Let's go, Danny!
Some-Stuffs Presents
Dio!
Please, come here...
Dio, can you hear me?!
What now, father? More medicine?
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
I don't need no bleedin' elixirs, you little git!
Get me booze! If you can afford medicine, then you can afford liquor!
Jojo... mind your manners.
I'm sorry.
Check.
Here, take it...
Timing:
Fadeout4
How's your dinner, you little brat?!
Quality Check:
Tonitonichopchop
Stop it!
Give it back! Give it back!
Oy, Erina!
Who bought you this doll?
That rich father of yours? That old quack...
Now...
Why don't we take a look underneath that dress?
Let's see if those naughty parts look like the real thing!
Visual Typesetting:
Fadeout4
She's crying!
Erina! Erina!
Erina the crybaby!
Stop that!
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Give her the doll back!
Who the hell are you?! One of Erina's friends?
Just because I don't know her doesn't mean I won't come to her aid!
You... little... punk!
Quit trying to show off!
Well look at what we have here: a little pansy!
I don't think I've ever seen anything so sad!
He comes runnin' in to save her, but takes a beating instead!
Come on now, he's the only son of the Joestar family!
I've got nothin' personal against the rich, I just hate them!
Now I'm really gonna let you have it!
And some of this!
Dio... I ain't got much longer...
You understand, right?
When I die, take this letter and go to the address written here...
Go and stay with the Joestars!
That old fool owes me...
And you're a sharp lad...You ought to be a rich and powerful man... who won't take no from anyone...
If you're so bloody rich, then go play in your mansion's yard!
Let's get goin'.
Are you...?
I'm fine! Leave me alone!
Please, leave me be! I didn't do this to endear myself to you!
I only did this because I made a vow to be a true gentleman!
I did it because you were a lady in need of assistance!
Even if your opponent is bigger, and you're sure that he can not be beaten...
In spite of these things, a gentleman will always stand up for what is right!
One of these days, I'll be strong enough to win...
You were a disgusting, petty man...
You put my mother through hell, at the cost of her life...
You were the worst father imaginable.
You say I could become the richest man around?
You're damn right I will.
I'll make use of anyone, and anything I can get my hands on.
That goes for this so-called noble Joestar as well...
You scrap of garbage!
And I will not be denied, not by anyone...
Jonathan Joestar...
This is the story of two young men, their fates intertwined by a mysterious stone mask... and the adventure that followed.
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
#some-stuffs@irc.rizon.net
Episode 1: "Dio the Intruder."
Who could he be?
Oh, you must be Dio Brando!
And you're Jonathan Joestar...
Everyone calls me Jojo. It's nice to meet you.
Danny!
Let me introduce you, this is Danny. He's my beloved pet...
Don't worry, he'd never bite anyone.
Wh-why did you do that?!
I'll never forgive you!
This is the heir to the Joestar family...
He's had his whole privileged life handed to him on a silver platter.
I'll push his mind to the breaking point, and eventually I, Dio, shall be...
What happened?
What's going on here?
My apologies, sir. The dog came at me so suddenly. I was startled...
Welcome, Dio, my boy!
As of today, you're part of the family.
All of you, this is Dio Brando, the son of the man who saved my life.
As of today, I want you to treat him the same way you do Jojo.
Very well, sir.
As for you, Dio... I hope you can enjoy the same lifestyle that Jojo has.
Lord Joestar, you have my deepest gratitude for your kindness.
Jojo lost his mother as well... and you're both the same age.
I hope you get along.
Jojo, the matter with Danny has been settled, I hope?
Yes, sir...
I suppose I'd be startled too, if a dog I didn't recognize came running at me...
I won't let it bother me.
I do wish he'd apologize...
But if we're going to be living together, I want to be friends as soon as possible.
Come along, Dio. I'll show you to your room.
Yes, sir.
What do you think you're doing? Keep your filthy hands off my luggage!
I'm telling you not to soil them with your grubby fingers, you buffoon!
I was going to carry them for-
That will be quite all right!
Let's have the servants carry them.
Listen here, Jojo...
Don't you dare get high and mighty with me,
because I'm living under the same roof as you now.
I adore being the best, being number one!
And I won't let anyone try to lord over me...
What?! I just want to be friends...
And one more thing: I hate dogs.
I'm not afraid of them. But their subservient attitude towards humans disgusts me.
So keep that simple-minded Danny far away from me.
What are you two doing? Hurry along now!
Yes, sir!
With Dio's sudden arrival, Jojo's once
carefree life has become filled with grief...
You made another mistake, Jojo!
Look at Dio! Twenty correct answers out of twenty questions!
Jojo! And you claim to be a gentleman?! Your etiquette is atrocious!
Take Jojo's food away.
There will be no dinner for you tonight!
Seeing Dio has made me realize how much I have spoiled you!
As a father, I am ashamed!
Dio's etiquette is perfect!
Buffoon...
And the next contender is... Jonathan Joestar!
He's been showing some real muscle lately!
And for his opponent... well, actually, there's been a change to the fight card...
We only know his name, but this young man just arrived in town...
I-It can't be...
Allow me to introduce...
Dio Brando!
Listen up! The first one to land a clean blow to the face wins the match!
Let's begin!
Get him, Jojo!
Show the newcomer what you're made of!
How's he doing that?!
I've never seen anyone move like that before!
I can't hit him!
Jojo... you're a lot better at throwing a punch than I expected.
But that doesn't matter!
Let me give you a little taste of the cutthroat world of back-alley boxing!
Take this!
There it is!
Jojo loses!
I'm not through with you yet, Jojo!
I'll drive my thumb right through your eye...
And put you down for good!
Amazing! He's really something!
Dio!
Dio! That was really impressive!
How'd you get to be so good?!
It was just some modern parrying methods that are used in the city.
I wouldn't mind showing you chaps some moves.
Really?!
But I wouldn't tell Jojo if I were you.
He's got a big mouth, after all.
Really...
I had no idea!
Why... That was deliberate... why would he do that?!
Solitude can sap a man of his will to live...
And I won't stop until Jojo's an empty shell.
I will take everything that he loves, one by one.
In the end. it will all be mine!
Dio, that scoundrel...
It's pathetic. I feel like he's taking over my entire life...
Come on, let's hurry up!
Hey, where are you guys going? Come on up here!
Hey, did you boys hear something?
Ignore him. He'll just tattle on us.
What did you say?!
Who are you calling a tattletale?!
Let's go.
Jojo the tattletale! Hang around him and he'll tell people everything!
Wait a moment! Get back here!
When did I ever tattle on anyone?!
Jojo the tattletale!
Dio! Dio's doing this to me!
He's spreading lies about me!
Everything he does seems to be deliberately against me!
Dio, you bastard!
Dio!
Dio! Dio!
My life is a mess now.
Ever since he came to live at the house... I'm all alone, now!
Danny... at least I'll always have a friend in you, no matter what Dio does...
Who was that girl just now?
I think I've seen her somewhere before...
My handkerchief!
I see! Thank you for the grapes!
I'll be here tomorrow, so come by again!
Leaving without saying a word...
What a cute girl...
Love!
Jojo was overwhelmed by that tender emotion.
The two of them quickly became friends, and
Jojo soon found her foremost in his thoughts.
Erina... Erina Pendleton.
She's absolutely dazzling!
Jojo, what are you doing?
Oh Jojo, you wicked boy!
I'm not with this ruffian!
See you later! Bye bye!
Hey there... you're Erina, right?
You certainly seem to be close friends with Jojo...
I thought it was strange...
He should have been tormented, after all...
But this certainly explains his good mood.
H-he did it!
That's Dio for you! He does things that normal men wouldn't dare to!
That's what makes him so electrifying! It's incredible!
Have you kissed Jojo yet?
Probably not...
And now your first kiss wasn't with Jojo...
It was with me, Dio!
The reason doesn't matter... only the fact that she kissed me!
Now her relationship with Jojo will be over...
I won't let Jojo have friends or lovers!
L-Look! That girl... she's...
She's washing her mouth with the water from that dirty puddle!
Is she mad?! There's a river right over there!
You... You foul bitch!
You'd dare rinse your mouth out with muddy water just to defy me?!
Damn her! How could I let a mere woman rattle me like that...
Enough!
Let's go...
Hey! Erina!
E-Erina! Wait!
Something's wrong... what happened to her?
Look here, boys! It's that loser, Jojo!
Someone ought to tell him why the poor lass was acting like that!
Oh, heavens no! I'd hate to see Jojo in tears again!
Y-You lot...
Erina...
What did you do to Erina?!
DIO!
That's a name you should speak with a great deal more reverence!
I'll never forgive you! You've been tormenting me since you got here!
But I don't care what you do to me!
Well now, could it be that you've heard about your dear Erina?
And now you plan to use those clenched fists to get your revenge?
I'll never forgive you for the way you disrespected her!
There's nothing more pathetic than a man sick with jealousy!
Do you really want to take another beating like you did in the ring, you imbecile?!
I... I can't lay a hand on him...
If I lose now, I'll spend the rest of my life cowering in Dio's shadow...
But more importantly, I have to fight...
I have to defend Erina's honor!
I'll take him down once and for all, and I'll do it fair and square!
I will ensure that my superiority over Jojo is etched into his entire being!
Whether in battle... or life itself!
Come on!
Amazing! What a thrilling sensation!
You... you're trying to grapple with me, even after that kick?!
I'll have to hit harder...
Dio!
This...
I'll keep beating you until I have you in tears!
This piece of trash is laying his hands on me... Dio!
Y-You...
You... how dare you...
How dare you do this to me!
H-He's crying?
You filthy idiot!
You two! What's going on here?!
Father!
There is a time and a place for a gentleman to fight!
But Jojo, from what I could see you were
attacking Dio while he was completely defenseless!
And that is not the way a gentleman behaves!
That's not-
No excuses! Both of you, go to your rooms!
I will decide your punishments later!
I wonder what that box is for...
Oh well, one of the maids must have thrown it away.
What... What the-?!
It sounds like something's hitting against the door!
Oh no...
There's someone inside!
This is awful! They're being burned alive!
Erina...
Damn you, Dio!
If this is what you were after with that damn kiss, then congratulations!
His body was so badly burned...
We took care of the burial to spare you the sight...
The police are saying it must have been a thief
that thought he was getting rid of a watchdog...
Dio...
Master Dio? He hasn't returned from school yet.
Jojo returned to his room and slept for two hours...
A while later, he awoke in his bed...
He remembered Danny's death... and cried.
I dealt with that disgusting mutt as payback for my humiliation, but I didn't think Jojo would explode like that.
I underestimated him...
He's not the type to back down under pressure, he rises up against it.
My pride is my greatest weakness... I'll have to reflect on this.
I need to learn how to better control my emotions!
And thus, seven years passed...
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
Next Episode
Seven years later...
Jonathan Joestar steals the ball!
I had a vision of something truly dreadful!
You don't mind losing your arm then, do you?
You'll lose that friendship!
I will protect my father, and the Joestar name!
Episode 2:
"Letter from the Past"