Umm, Mr. Rohan?
If you don't mind, I'd like to ask you a favor...
Hirose Koichi: High School Student
Kishibe Rohan: Comics Artist
What is it, Koichi?
So, the thing is,
I'm traveling abroad for spring break this year...
Hmm? Where?
I-Italy...
Italy?
Sir, will you please use Heaven's Door
to give me the ability to speak Italian?
What would compel me to do that?
I'm just nervous since this is
my first time going overseas...
I would feel less anxious if
you helped me speak the language.
Please, Sir!
You're going to Italy?
I had quite the interesting
experience there myself.
Huh?
Do you recall how my comic went on hiatus
after that punk assaulted me?
While I was recovering, I spent eight days in Venice investigating potential sources for new stories.
It was there that I caught wind
of a curious happening.
Episode #16
At a Confessional
The episode I'm about to recount is one that I,
Kishibe Rohan, heard with my own two ears.
It is a record of true terror.
Do you know what a confessional is?
They can be found in every Italian church.
Imagine them as two
side-by-side wooden phone booths.
A priest from the church enters the side
with the curtain, and the penitent the other.
The two sides are connected by a small window...
...which is designed so that the priest and penitent
are unable to see each other, but may still converse.
By speaking through the window,
the penitent is able to confess their sins in complete privacy.
No one can hold secrets in their heart
for years on end.
The deeper the secret,
the more the heart agonizes and yearns to cry out.
A confessional is where souls come to seek absolution,
and embodies the knowledge of those who came before us.
Though it is forbidden,
while the priest was gone...
...I discreetly took photos of the confessional
and examined its materials and engravings.
While I was there, I decided it wouldn't hurt to
confess to a priest for the novelty of the experience...
...and so I entered a box.
Experience breathes reality into
a piece of work, after all.
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
It is a grave sin I have come to confess.
I can no longer bear this burden alone, Father.
I must confess.
I've suffered countless sleepless nights.
I swear I didn't know at the time that
only priests should enter the curtained side!
This man had mistaken me for a priest!
Yet...
...was this my lucky day?
What was his "grave sin"?
Listening to him couldn't hurt, either.
Experience is what breathes reality
into a piece of work.
It didn't really matter
who listened to this man.
Ultimately, it was more important that
he believed he was confessing to a priest.
Father, is something the matter?
Go on. Keep talking.
I mean, please continue.
Of course. Where to begin?
Well, there was that evening...
Yes...
This all began that fateful evening.
I was twenty-four years old
and working at a food market.
I did manual labor.
I carried bags of corn and
loaded them into trucks and warehouses.
It was grueling, time-consuming work
that left me no time to have a girlfriend.
I hated that job more than anything.
It was already past six o'clock that evening,
but as per usual, I was working overtime.
That's when it happened.
That man approached me.
From his hobbling gait, lifeless gaze,
unkempt hair, and foul body odor...
...I knew at once that he was a vagrant.
Please, spare some food...
He spoke with a feeble voice.
I caught him stealing glances
at my lunch on the table.
A sudden anger came over me.
Here I was working overtime, while this man had
likely just been loitering at the park or behind the station.
Yet he expected me to give him food?
What an entitled wretch.
I work for my money,
then use what I earned to buy food. Why not try that?
You can have my food if you load
all this product into the warehouse.
I... I... I...
I'll do it!
Just please let me eat first!
I've had nothing for five days! I swear!
Give me just a little!
I'll work once I've eaten! I promise!
Slow on the uptake, huh?
You're not supposed to get paid 'till after you do the work.
So you good for it or not?
Hold up! Why are you taking
just one measly bag? Over here!
You got an hour to get it done!
Sooner I go home, the better!
Come on, hustle!
The quicker you work,
the quicker you eat!
This guy's had it easy for way too long!
Guess I gotta be the one
who whips him back into shape.
Hey!
Quit playing dead and get back to work!
It hasn't even been ten minutes!
Playing dead...
Do I look...
...like I'm playing dead to you?
What the hell are you?
My despair runs deeper
than the blackest ocean.
And it's all because of you!
I'll never forget this!
I know your face!
You'll pay for your transgressions.
I'll be back!
Once your happiness reaches its peak...
...I'll come back for you!
You hear me?!
Look!
Someone collapsed under that bag!
He's dead!
It killed him!
Doctor! Call a doctor!
Call the police!
I had no idea!
How could I have known he hadn't really eaten?
I truly didn't know!
W-Wait a minute...
Err, I beg your pardon...
Did you say that the vagrant
spoke to you after he passed away?
Are you certain it wasn't a dream?
A dream?
Oh, if only it were so...
Father, the events that followed
are what truly shook me.
From that day forward,
an unsettling number of good things happened to me.
I received an inheritance
from a distant relative...
...made money betting on
soccer matches...
...and all the land I bought with my earnings
sold for at least tenfold what I originally paid.
The cornflakes and corn snacks I created were picked up
by a major food company and sold beyond expectations.
They even did well around the world.
I hadn't even come close to having a girlfriend before then,
but I ended up getting married.
She was a former supermodel
who took part in Milan Fashion Week.
I earned more money
than I could ever hope to spend.
At my current residence,
I have fifteen servants and three chauffeurs.
My inordinate luck held me at constant unease.
Memories of that dead man
constantly occupied a corner of my mind.
And then, my daughter came along.
Papa! Papa!
A darling little girl who took after my wife.
Papa!
Papa, watch me! Ready?
Keep watching!
I missed!
So close! You almost had it!
Your eyes were closed, Madam.
Try again.
Okay!
As I watched my daughter play at the park...
...I carelessly thought,
"I am so happy right now."
As promised...
As promised, I've come back!
Back to get you!
Madam?! Is something the matt-
Shut it, old man!
Don't worry.
I'm just borrowing your daughter's body.
Stop this! Please, stop!
You're mistaken!
Let go of your unwarranted grudge!
Unwarranted grudge?
You've enjoyed nothing but good luck
for all these years, haven't you?
Wealth, fame, family, right?
You think you got this far on your own?
I was helping you from
the shadows this whole time!
All so that once you reached peak happiness
and came tumbling down...
...you would feel the deep despair I felt!
But y'know...
The only reason I wanted vengeance
was to save my soul.
It'd leave a bad taste in my mouth
if you thought my grudge was unwarranted.
I'll give you one chance!
We'll leave it up to God
whether or not my grudge was warranted.
Let's put fate to the test
and see if you still have a future.
If fate sides with you,
it means my grudge was unwarranted...
...and I'll disappear without killing you.
Your sentence will be handed down by fate!
Well?
You gonna test your luck or what?
I-I have no idea what you're talking about!
Fuck off!
Do you wanna test your luck or not?
Why?
Why is this happening to me?
Answer!
I'll save me some time and
rip your head off now if it's a no!
I... I will! I'll do it!
Do I even have a choice?
Good!
Take this!
Fate can be determined from
even the smallest, least significant things.
You're going to throw a piece of popcorn
higher than that lamppost, then catch it in your mouth.
Three times in a row!
If you pull it off,
I'll accept fate's decree and disappear.
You're using some stupid party trick to...
I need this to give my soul some closure.
Is that stupid to you?!
Toss it when I clap my hands.
If it doesn't clear the top of the lamppost,
or you toss it too late, I'll kill you.
Ready? Here we go!
H-Hold on!
The height...
Good!
Why is this happening to me?!
Forward!
It's falling forward!
W-Wait, no it's not!
C-Can't see!
That was close!
But it worked! I did it!
I made the catch!
Second toss time!
Grab your popcorn!
W-Wait!
Th-The sun was too bright!
I can do this in the shade, can't I?
And what will you demand next
if I say yes?
Huh?
We're doing this now!
Right here, right now!
Listen here!
Do it twice more.
I'll kill you if you fail!
If you win,
I'll disappear as promised.
Now toss the second one!
So you'll disappear for good if I win, huh?
You'll spare my life
if I beat you, is that right?!
Quit yapping!
Toss it or you're dead!
Yes!
The clouds are blocking the sun!
I can see it falling straight down!
Hey!
What?!
Now that's nice!
They think you're trying
to feed them or something?
I did it!
See that?
I caught the second piece, too!
Go to hell!
This is too easy!
I was scared at first,
but now I'm calm and collected!
I got this!
I got this in the bag!
Save the celebration for
after you catch the last one!
Ready?
You know it!
This last one will be easy as...
What's going on?!
You're the one who got
all these pigeons to flock here!
You're also the one who spilled
every last piece of popcorn you had!
Th-This one piece...
If I throw it higher than the lamppost...
Get the hell out of here! Shoo!
There's no food left for you!
Here we go!
It's the final round!
Wait! Please, wait!
Huh?!
How's that?!
You think the pigeons will go for burning popcorn?!
You think they'll want to eat something
covered in flaming oil?!
Yes!
It's coming straight down!
I can't see!
Since the popcorn's on fire...
...it's blending into the sunlight!
I can't see!
I can't see it!
Wh-Where is it?!
The verdict is...
...my grudge wasn't unwarranted!
"So how are you still alive?"
Is that what you're thinking, Father?
It's for that reason
that I've come to confess.
I can no longer keep this to myself.
I've committed a terrible sin.
That vagrant made me wealthy enough
to possess whatever I pleased.
Wealthy enough that I could even find
a servant who obeys my every command.
Master...
Get out here...
You can repent all you want,
but that won't make my grudge go away!
You lured me in with money
and had me get reconstructive surgery...
Your trickery led to such an awful thing happening to me,
so now my grudge against you...
...master...
...can never be forgiven!
So you can even enter churches?
When your daughter's happiness reaches its peak,
I'll be back to take my vengeance!
Don't bother with that.
The only way we won't get tricked again
is if we watch this piece of shit day and night!
Whoa!
Spooky!
Okuyasu!
Yukako!
Mr. Rohan, did all that shit really happen?!
Hey, lady!
Get me a tapioca milk tea!
Is that why you interrupted us?
Are you accusing me of lying?
Nuh-uh!
It ain't nothin' like that!
But're you sure it ain't just
some Stand users dukin' it out...
...and's got nothin' t'do with cranky spirits?
Those vengeful spirits
need to slow down.
I'd go insane if I was
possessed for the rest of my life!
Koichi, if a vengeful spirit ever
tries to possess you, tell me right away!
I'll free you from its curse!
Uh... Sure...
Thanks...
To this day,
I'm unaware as to what became of that man.
Perhaps in a year or two
I'll go on another research trip and see him again.
Staying vigilant even while
possessed by vengeful spirits...
He's lived a lonely and proactive life.
Though I regard him as despicable,
I find myself respecting that.
Be that as it may...
...I might be alone in thinking that.
I wanna know the truth of life that never ends
To unchain the mystic rites I'm calling
I'm on my way to find the eternal verities
Exploding all the teardrops by the sun
I can feel my heart beating
I can see my fate all spinning around beyond the time
Rise up to the sky, like a butterfly
Show me what's inside, don't ever let go
Shining stars will guide me to somewhere high
Finding the truth beyond the Heaven's Door