Mr. Rohan, thanks for meeting with me.
Pretty nice out today, huh?
(Started less than a year ago.
Married without children.)
Kaigamori Minoru (23), Comics editor
(Started less than a year ago.
Married without children.)
Kaigamori Minoru (23), Comics editor
Whatcha reading about?
De Staël.
De Staël?
That a new band or something?
A painter.
He was a painter from Russia who died in 1955.
Listen, Kaigamori...
(11 years since
debut. Single.)
Kishibe Rohan (27) Comics Artist
Arriving late to a meeting is unacceptable,
as you're clearly well aware...
...but arriving six minutes early for
a meeting with a comics artist?
Isn't that rather unbecoming for an editor?
S-Sorry about that...
So showing up early is rude, too?
Fortunately I'm rather equable.
Anyway, let's go over my
upcoming sixty-one page one-shot together.
Sorry to bother you, Mr. Rohan!
We're big fans of yours!
Can we have your autograph?
Make mine out to Otoishi, please!
Knock it off!
He's not doing a signing right now!
We're in the middle of a meeting!
He doesn't have time!
I already finished them.
Don't presume I'm as slow as other artists.
Take my autograph with special thanks!
Did he just make these awesome
drip paintings... with coffee?!
Thank you a bunch!
We appreciate the hell out of this!
Holy crap! Holy crap! Holy crap!
By the way, may we discuss my
current circumstances before we begin?
Sure...
To be frank, it's about money.
More specifically, regarding my pay. Do you follow?
Will you allow me an advance?
I just recently declared bankruptcy.
Huh?
I have no outstanding debts,
but I'm currently homeless.
Huh?!
I'm staying at my friend Koichi's house,
and I lack a desk for drawing.
Huh?
I had to sell my Sailor Moon figurines,
Led Zeppelin record jackets, and Rurouni Kenshin comics.
Are you serious?!
You have nowhere to work?!
You're broke?
But weren't you planning to build a
villa on the mountain you just bought?
Let me explain!
I was researching the supernatural beings
living on the mountain for the comic I was drawing.
Then a development company made plans
to build a resort trail right through it.
So naturally, I purchased six mountains in
the surrounding area to put a stop to them.
I had to buy up as much land as possible, right?
In order to foil their plan, obviously.
But now that the resort trail isn't being made,
I essentially own worthless land.
Those six mountains
may as well be piles of dirt.
All this to say: I'm broke.
So will you grant me an advance or not?
L-Let me get this straight...
You bought those mountains to
gather reference material for your comic?
Yes.
Not as an investment?
Precisely.
My work requires reality.
All to gather reference material
on supernatural beings?
Enough questions!
Consider the consequences had the trail been built!
The supernatural beings may have fled!
All my efforts would have been for naught!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's with the look?
Are you intentionally averting your gaze?
Ah hah! You are!
Do you believe I'm of unsound mind,
Mr. Editor?
Consider this!
Buying supercars or building expensive basement game rooms
aren't the only ways comics artists spend their money!
Besides, they were actually there.
I gathered all the material I needed.
Listen closely. Your editorial department,
and no one else, will be told of this matter.
Th-They were there?
What was there?
Have you listened to a single word I've said?
I witnessed it with my own eyes.
The supernatural beings of Mutsukabe Hill.
They're there at this very moment!
I'm sorry, Mr. Rohan...
Could you please repeat that again?
What was there?
Osato Naoko was a college student
preparing to graduate during the coming spring...
...but at the end of that September,
she murdered her boyfriend.
EPISODE ＃02
“MUTSUKABE HILL”
Osato Naoko.
Her family had found success producing miso in Mutsukabe Hill
for the last three hundred years, and she was their sole heir.
Their mansion was located
at the end of a long dirt road.
Essentially, that entire mountain was
private property of her family.
Hey...
Can you go now?
Huh?
And put that game away.
What's wrong?
Someone coming from the main building?
Just leave, okay?
Go out the back door.
C'mon, Nao!
Lately, it's like...
you've been acting real cold.
I hate thinking about it,
but if there's another guy-
This should be easy since you got the hint.
Let's leave our good times together in the past.
It's not like my dad would ever approve of us.
You're just a part-time gardener.
I'm the only heir to our family fortune.
I'm not going anywhere!
You gotta be kidding me, right?
What's wrong with how things are, Nao?
Let go of me...
There's no reason to break up.
Let me go!
How about we let
the new guy and your dad...
...catch me holding you like this?
I said let go!
Wh-
What?!
S-Sorry...
But... Y-You hit me first...
I'm seriously in love with you, Nao.
I'm okay with how things are.
Nobody needs to find out.
Get out!
Get out and don't come back!
Nao, hey...
Get out!
Take your money and leave!
She may be in a bit of a tizzy
since we're here unannounced.
I wouldn't be surprised if she's
throwing on makeup right now.
Not good... They're headed this way...
Please, just take your things and go!
To be honest with you...
...I think you're amazing.
But he's my fiancé.
Our wedding was already
arranged for next spring after I graduate.
That's why we're through!
We can't keep doing this!
Huh?
Gunpei?
Hey...
No...
You're teasing me again...
...aren't you?
Gunpei...
Quit fooling around!
There's no pulse!
H-He's dead!
Osato Naoko felt she should
treat Gunpei's wound, at the very least.
She covered it with a nearby towel.
This is just another one of Gunpei's pranks...
Something here definitely doesn't add up!
I barely even pushed him!
What were those golf clubs even doing there?
Why?!
It looks like I... like I...
...like I hit him with a golf club!
Gunpei!
Wh-What should I do?
Doctor!
I need to call a doctor!
But can a doctor even help
if he's already dead?
Should I call the police?
Naoko, are you in there? It's Dad.
Shuichi's come to visit.
He's eager to see you!
I'm gone...
I'm not really here right now...
I don't exist anywhere anymore!
The door's locked.
Could Naoko be out right now?
I may have imagined it, sir,
but I believe I saw the divider behind the window move.
I... I have to hide him!
S-Somewhere!
I need to get Gunpei out of here!
Under the sofa?
What's going on?
Even though he doesn't have a
pulse and his heart stopped beating...
Why is this happening?
Naoko, are you in there?
What's the matter?
This isn't like you.
I have a spare key.
I'll peek inside.
Dad!
I-I didn't hear you!
I was cleaning the kitchen!
Oh, Naoko, you're there?
Shuichi's come to visit.
O-Oh, that's wonderful!
Wait in the main building, please!
You sound troubled.
Are you okay?
Do you need help?
I'm fine!
Just changing right now!
Don't come in!
I'll be right with you!
You'd better...
You'd better not open that door!
First Aid Kit
Disinfectant
Wh-What?
What's going on?!
Do people normally
keep bleeding after they die?
Naoko?
You've had the water running
an awfully long time.
What's going on?
It's Shuichi.
Are you wondering why I'm still at the door?
Actually, your dad gave me
the spare key so we could be alone.
No! Don't!
Don't you dare come in here!
Naoko...
To tell you the truth,
I saw someone else through the window earlier.
There isn't actually anyone else in there, is there?
Are you really alone right now?
I thought I saw someone else with you.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
But this is all your fault!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Wh-What's wrong, Naoko?
So someone else is in there!
Please, Gunpei!
Stop!
Stop bleeding!
I'm coming in!
You saw someone else in here with me?
Who did you think you saw, Shuichi?
Oh...
Please...
Stop...
Gunpei, forgive me!
Stop!
Please forgive me...
Sorry. I was wrong.
Guess my imagination was running wild.
I'll wait with your dad in the main building.
As per their arrangement,
Osato Naoko's wedding took place that spring...
...and Shuichi became
a son-in-law of the Osato family.
Yet since that first day...
...without fail...
...Kamafusa Gunpei continued to bleed.
Each day he quietly bled
about three-hundred cubic centimeters.
So long as his body lay undisturbed...
...he bled out no more than that.
All in spite of the fact that
his life functions had completely ceased.
Osato Naoko never traveled
far from home after her wedding.
Each morning...
...she covertly disposed of Gunpei's accumulated blood
in a glass bottle as part of her daily routine.
She carried out this duty every day,
carefully ensuring her family never took notice.
Hey, Naoko!
Come eat with us!
I'll be right there!
Eventually, the guest bedroom was
torn down for remodeling.
Since then, in the attic above the closet...
...Gunpei's body was stored.
One day, Naoko noticed something.
If she sprayed water onto
Gunpei's body with a spray bottle...
...inexplicably,
his skin would be temporarily rejuvenated.
You look so precious while you sleep...
...Gunpei.
I alone, now and forever...
...have to take care of you.
Just who was he?
He had no doubt died
on that day long ago, and yet...
When I first came to learn of Kamafusa Gunpei...
...I had already visited the region several times to
research the legends of the supernatural beings who dwell there.
As I was sayin',
no one's gonna give you a better deal than me, Mr. Kishibe.
You got nothin' to lose!
Enough already.
Try convincing me all you like.
The mountain isn't for sale.
Come on, you're missing out!
Huh?!
Yes, hello!
Batsudera speaking.
As to how I learned of this...
I just so happened to cross paths
with Osato Naoko...
...and read her memories with Heaven's Door.
And with a stroke of good luck,
I learned of this man's existence.
Yes?
Huh? Hello?
Damn reception...
O-One moment, please.
What in the world are you, Gunpei?
I want to see your true form
with my own eyes.
I want to know...
...what your goal is.
In the attic above the closet in the mansion.
That's where I'll find him.
You're Kishibe Rohan, aren't you?
The comics artist?
I know you.
You've been snooping around here lately,
haven't you?
Who are you?
My parents told me not to talk to strangers.
There's been a lot of creepy people
around here lately.
Hey! Stop!
Are you okay?
What were you thinking?
Why did you suddenly run-
Sh-She's dead!
Wh-What just happened?
Sh-She couldn't be...
I-Impossible!
That's absurd!
Now it looks like...
...I somehow...
did something to this girl!
What?
This girl...
Could she really be...?
It can't be!
Is she Gunpei's daughter?
Osato Naoko became pregnant and had a child
with the corpse in the attic?!
Mr. Kishibe, where did you go?
Mr. Kishibe!
Where are you?
Damn!
She's trying to haunt me!
Heaven's Door!
This is bad!
The memories of her life
written inside her body...!
They're fading away!
Damn, they're going to disappear!
Once they're gone,
she'll never come back to life!
Before that happens...
Note: I know no one named Kishibe Rohan.
If we ever crossed paths, I would be unable to see him.
Mom!
I'm hungry!
Th-That was close...
Had I been any slower,
she would have haunted me.
It would have meant... my utter ruin...
What a terrifying creature.
A moment more, and...
Oh! There you are, Mr. Kishibe!
I'm awfully sorry!
My boss just gave me a call.
I'm never going to sell it to you.
Huh?
Huh?!
That's the supernatural being
I was researching.
I dubbed it the Mutsukabe Hill Phantom.
When did it emerge?
Perhaps in the distant past?
It relies on human love
and spiritual weakness...
...forcing them to attend to their needs...
...to ensure it will never bear any manual labor,
responsibility, hardships, or other struggles.
A phantom with no purpose
other than to proliferate.
In truth, it may be more
accurately described as a living being.
The happiest moment of its life...
...is when it dies in another's presence.
As such,
these beings could exist elsewhere in the world.
Thriving by ending their life
in the presence of another.
Did all that really happen?
Seems a bit far-fetched.
Ya can't be totally sure it ain't true, though...
You ever heard of this?
Yes. I believe there to be a comparable
organism in the Orion constellation.
H-Hey, listen to me!
You guys can't just sit he-
By the way, I've been pondering this for some time,
but are you really a space alien?
Yes. I departed the
Magellanic Clouds to inhabit Earth.
My spaceship is currently on standby 1,500,000 kilometers above Earth. Aboard it...
Fuckin' annoying space alien...
How many other Mutsukabe Hill Phantoms
are out in the world?
I suppose it doesn't matter.
Osato Naoko seems to be happy
in her own way...
...and I worked out their goal.
Besides, I'm neither a journalist nor a scholar.
I'm just a comics artist.
Mom...
Do you think I'll marry
someone wonderful someday?
I'm sure you will.
I wanna know the truth of life that never ends
To unchain the mystic rites I'm calling
I'm on my way to find the eternal verities
Exploding all the teardrops by the sun
I can feel my heart beating
I can see my fate all spinning around beyond the time
Rise up to the sky, like a butterfly
Show me what's inside, don't ever let go
Shining stars will guide me to somewhere high
Finding the truth beyond the Heaven's Door