Bend both wrists to make a right angle
with your arms and hands.
Hold them straight while keeping the fingers still.
Palms face forward, elbows straight,
and while maintaining the angle of the wrists...
...bend each finger one by one.
One, two, three, four, five.
Now extend them in reverse.
Complete.
Thus concludes my comic drawing warm-up routine.
Episode #05
Millionaire Village
Oh yeah, Mr. Rohan...
Remember that forty-five page one-shot comic of yours
that's due by the end of this summer?
Did you decide what it will be about yet?
Hmm, let's see...
Kishibe Rohan (27) Comics Artist
What about an annular eclipse?
Wow! That is such a great idea!
Izumi Kyoka (25) Comics Magazine Editor
But if you'll hold that thought for a moment...
...what if instead you made it about
someone purchasing a villa in the mountains?
Come again?
Is that too dull for you?
It is, isn't it?
Wait. Hold on a second!
What was that about
a villa in the mountains?
I think it's a good idea for a comic!
You could use the opportunity
to gather reference material for the one-shot!
Not that!
You mentioned making a purchase?
I'm sure I heard you
bring up purchasing a villa!
You found out I went bankrupt
from purchasing a mountain the other day, didn't you?
That's not it at all, Sir!
It would be a trip purely for gathering reference material!
Here...
Look at this.
I made an interesting discovery...
There isn't a single road which
goes through these mountains, yet somehow...
...I found a village here containing eleven posh villas.
The mountain in question is a little over
eighty kilometers north-west of Morioh.
Not only that, no electricity cables
or telephone lines go up there, either!
No electric companies provide service there,
and it's unreachable by public transportation.
Yet they clearly have electricity,
and even a helipad is visible.
The residents only seem to travel by helicopter!
No kidding...
Those villas certainly do look extravagant...
Isn't that an Isetan department store logo
near the tennis court?
You're right!
They have an Isetan! Amazing!
Anyway, I found out soon after
that one of the villas is currently up for sale.
They're asking for three million yen!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Seriously! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
So you do want me to buy a villa!
Like I said, Sir,
you'll only be gathering reference material!
I'll be the one making the purchase!
You?
The property is about 2,650 square meters,
and the asking price is three million yen.
With my salary, I should be able to get a loan...
I'll stay in my apartment during the week
for work and city life...
...then spend my weekends
living in a wonderful forest villa!
Hold on!
Just tell me this...
Are you purchasing it for yourself, or for Shueisha?
TL Note: Company which publishes Weekly Shounen Jump.
For myself, of course!
And you're asking me to
make my comic about it?
Yes, about my purchase of it, Sir!
It really is a great idea!
I put a lot of research into this!
The owner of the first villa is
the president of a shipbuilding company.
The second villa is owned by
a CEO in the pharmaceutical industry.
The family living in the third villa
has strong connections to the printing industry.
The man who bought the fourth villa
now owns a successful cosmetics company.
Basically, the owners of these villas
are some of the wealthiest people in the world!
They all have beautiful wives and families...
They're truly happy!
You mentioned researching this earlier...
...but something is off here!
Sure it's in the mountains,
but only 3 million yen to live in such an exclusive village?
It's a complete sham!
No it's not, Mr. Rohan.
I didn't tell you the most important part yet.
The current owners purchased their villas
at the age of twenty-five.
They were all ordinary men
from different parts of Japan.
The last villa to go up for sale
was the eleventh one in 1989.
The buyer was a twenty-five year old
delivery driver from Tokyo.
Now he's the CEO of a large air mail company
with an estimated net worth of over thirty billion yen!
None of these people were born into wealth!
They were all normal twenty-five year old men.
But soon after purchasing their villas,
they became fabulously wealthy!
Is that really just a coincidence?
They were all twenty-five!
And, well, I'm twenty-five years old now...
Sir, will you accompany me
to gather reference material?
Will you join me
to purchase this lucky villa?
Does the editorial department have a helicopter?
How are we getting there?
In the mountains, 80 km away from Morioh
Mr. Rohan, I forgot to tell you
something important earlier.
The broker we're meeting
is the village representative...
...and they're very particular
about proper manners.
They'll refuse anyone
who doesn't meet their standards.
Having proper manners is crucial!
So, please, Sir...
Please, what?
I'm not doing the buying here!
You are!
That's what worries me!
We'll both be sent away
if your manners aren't perfect, Sir!
We'll have come all this way for nothing...
Sir, you know you have
that kind of personality, right?
Everything about you screams
"I'm better than you!".
And by that you mean...?
All I ask is that you have some tact
and be respectful of our host!
Why don't we do a quick test of your manners?
Where and when should you remove
your overcoat when visiting someone?
Did you learn this while
preparing for a job interview or something?
In front of the main entrance.
Not inside the house,
but just before entering.
It's because overcoats can be dirty or dusty.
Well put, Sir!
That's right!
More importantly, what should we do about that?
It's right in front of the entrance.
See? It's a baby bird.
Poor thing...
Its nest should be in one of these trees.
It must have fallen from it.
What should we do?
Another animal could come by and eat it if we leave it here...
Well, that's nature for you.
It's your lucky day, little birdie!
I'll take care of you.
You can stay in my candy box! Here.
I wonder which tree it fell from.
We'll look for its nest
once we're done here.
Greetings.
I welcome you, honorable guests from afar.
We have been blessed
with splendid weather this day.
Please, come this way.
Please, enter.
My name is Izumi Kyoka.
Thank you for accepting to see me
in regards to purchasing the villa.
This is my companion, Kishibe Rohan.
He's a renowned comics artist.
You may call me Ikkyu.
Henceforth, I shall be your escort
through these premises, honorable guests.
Please, come in.
If it pleases you, I may fetch refreshments.
Please, step up here.
Hey!
I shall inform the owner
of your arrival posthaste.
Please wait here in the meantime.
I have a sinking feeling
this has already begun...
The whole manners thing. Manners.
This is a test, isn't it?
To see if we know how to properly drink tea?
I wonder if they're watching us...
Do you know the answer to this test?
Should I look it up on the internet?
It's fine.
I'm the one making the purchase.
Don't worry about me.
While drinking or eating, distasteful noises
and movements should be avoided at all costs...
Pardon my intrusion.
I must regrettably report that
the owner shall not be seeing you.
Please, leave for today.
You have displayed three instances of
improper manners up to this point, Miss Izumi.
This land shall not be sold
to those with poor manners.
Please, leave for today.
What are you saying?!
Me? When did I?
Firstly, unless explicitly asked to do so,
guests should never sit on the house seats facing the entrance.
Entrance
➃ Guest Seat
➂ Guest Seat
➁ House Seat
➀ House Seat
They should sit in the guest seats.
Proper manners dictate that all guests
must sit in the guest seats until the arrival of the owner.
Secondly, upon entering a Japanese-style room,
one must never set foot on the borders of any tatami mats.
Thirdly, though you are holding your plate as is proper
with the height of the table being below your knees...
...inserting one's finger into the handle of a teacup
is an abhorrent breach of proper manners.
Vulgar
Correct
Manners are either proper or improper.
They leave no room for interpretation.
Please, I entreat you.
Leave for today.
What? It's over already?
I-I beg your pardon!
You said only for today?
If that means you'll permit me to try again
another day, then please, let me!
What?
If at all possible,
please give me another chance!
I'm begging you!
Correct me if I am mistaken...
...but you wish to have your manners
tested for a second time?
Huh? Can I?
Noted. I shall return shortly upon
speaking with the owner on the matter.
Please!
Please, just one more time!
Hey, let's head back.
This isn't good reference material.
I just really, really like this villa...
Acting with proper manners
feels so natural here...
Don't you see how wonderful this place is?
Yes? Kyoka speaking.
What the hell is going on?!
It can't be!
It can't...
W-We have to go!
M-My mother... is gone...
They just told me...
She was in a car accident...
And my boyfriend...
My fiancé was with her...
We were going to get married next year...
She had a heart attack
while they were driving, and then...
...they crashed and died!
What happened?!
The baby bird in the box...
Pardon my intrusion.
The owner has permitted you
yet another test of your manners.
Shall we continue?
You brat!
What the hell are you?
Heaven’s Door!
"My role is to tend to guests
at the main entrance."
"I am a vessel for the will of the land."
"If a guest fails to observe proper manners on this mountain,
he or she shall forfeit something held dear."
"Such is the retribution of the mountain."
"Manners leave no room for interpretation."
"Guests shall either gain
or forfeit something."
"This is the law of the land,
and likewise the power of the mountain."
"Those who pay obeisance to the mountain shall prosper,
and those who do not shall languish."
This kid isn't a Stand user...
He's being used to show people around,
but he has no power of his own.
I have a really bad feeling about this!
Our real enemy...
is the gods of this mountain!
"The woman lost something
for the three instances she displayed improper manners."
"What's more, she requested to be tested again!"
"Such a brusque request
bespeaks true arrogance!"
"Moreover..."
"To turn someone into a book and
peer at their innermost thoughts without consent..."
"...is a severe breach of proper manners!"
This is bad...
It can't be!
W-We're in serious danger!
My... My chest...!
I-It hurts...! My chest...
Miss Izumi...
She appears to have suffered a heart attack.
Mister Kishibe Rohan, you too shall forfeit
something for your display of improper manners.
Is she... Is she going to die?
Now, then...
Do you wish to be tested again?
Or would you prefer to leave for today?
There's...
There's no way I can leave like this!
Please... Forgive her!
She just wanted to be happy!
She thought coming here would give me good ideas for my comic...
She gave me that advice as my editor!
Manners leave no room for interpretation.
Either you shall gain...
...or forfeit something.
How shall you go about eating this corn on the cob?
Well?
Do you wish to be tested again,
Mister Kishibe Rohan?
Or would you prefer to leave for today?
Never underestimate Kishibe Rohan!
A knife? A fork? Chopsticks?
They all reek of a dirty trap!
Even a blind man could see that!
You eat it with your hands! Furthermore...
I have an observation to make.
Brat...
...you're stepping on it.
It would seem it's your manners that are lacking.
I just so happened to write a little something inside you
while you were a book earlier.
My ability is called Heaven's Door.
Note: "I cannot see the borders of tatami mats."
Hey, you're still stepping on it...
...with both feet.
That's how my ability works, you see.
You have my thanks for instructing me
in the ways of proper manners.
"Either you shall gain or forfeit something", right?
I've won.
I appear to have been right
about the corn on the cob.
Now return everything she lost.
Her mother and boyfriend were taken, weren't they?
This is a ruse...
Those who seek to deceive the mountain gods
shall incite their wrath!
Do you wish to be tested again,
Mister Kishibe Rohan?
Or would you prefer to leave for today?
No, I haven't incited anyone's wrath.
After all, you were the one
who had improper manners.
Still, I'm leaving!
And I won't be back again.
Huh, so that's what you were up to...
By the way, what happened to
your editor's mother and fiancé?
They were fine. Her relatives panicked
and mistakenly thought they had died in the crash.
Well, that's a relief!
That reminds me, Koichi.
I'll be out past eight tonight collecting reference material.
All right...
Hey, Mr. Rohan...
How long're ya plannin' t'keep freeloadin' at Koichi's place?
I know it's not ideal.
I'd much prefer a private room for drawing comics.
Right now it's beyond my financial means.
Wanna crash at my place?
We got loadsa empty rooms!
That's not a bad idea!
Besides, I'm fascinated by your father's condition.
You kiddin' me?! Come over today!
An' couldja try makin' my dad normal again with Heaven's Door?
I refuse!
Aww, for real?
Whatever, man!
I wanna know the truth of life that never ends
To unchain the mystic rites I'm calling
I'm on my way to find the eternal verities
Exploding all the teardrops by the sun
I can feel my heart beating
I can see my fate all spinning around beyond the time
Rise up to the sky, like a butterfly
Show me what's inside, don't ever let go
Shining stars will guide me to somewhere high
Finding the truth beyond the Heaven's Door