What was it?
I feel like there's something I've needed to do since last night...
Jeez, my shoes and bag feel so heavy today...
Huh?
Th-This house...
Why?
I walked all the way to Mr. Rohan's house without realizing it.
The door's wide open...
I'd like to stop in and thank him for yesterday,
but I'll be late for school...
This isn't a good idea...
He could be sleeping right now since he's a comics artist.
I really shouldn't just barge into his house like this...
This is a bad idea...
Mr. Rohan...
He's working so frantically...
But what's this feeling?
I can't help but feel that I'm in a terrifying place right now...
What is it?
I'm glad you're back.
I've been waiting for you.
You're right on time.
Huh?
However, could I ask you to wait a little while?
I have just two pages left to finish for next week's manuscript.
It should only take me about twenty minutes.
Twenty minutes?
Did he really just say he would
finish two pages in twenty minutes?
Am I hearing things?
Two totally blank pages of manuscript in twenty minutes?
No way... And did he say it was for next week?
We were reading this week's manuscript yesterday,
and he had only just finished it...
What?! You're not gonna sketch it first?!
I-I can't believe it!
He didn't even sketch out the page in pencil first!
He just keeps adding to it!
And he's drawing in the background at the same time!
Wh-What was that?!
I know he did something, but what was it?!
What?! H-He's filling in the blacks!
He's flinging ink at the page like tiny throwing stars,
and hitting each spot without missing a single drop!
Th-This technique...
Aren't you supposed to fill in the blacks with a brush by hand?!
He already finished filling them in!
That page was completely white just two minutes ago!
I have you to thank for this, Koichi!
I feel overwhelmed with the desire to work!
I can't help but want to draw!
I want to keep drawing and drawing!
This is the first time I've ever drawn
nineteen pages in a single night!
I'm creating my magnum opus!
Your experiences are astounding!
They're elevating my story to an entirely new level, Koichi!
Huh?
What is he saying?
Quickly now! I need more of your reality!
Show me your next page!
The more pages I take, the more weight you'll lose...
...but you're fine with that, right?
As you should be since your experiences will become
an everlasting masterpiece for the ages!
I-I remember now!
Heaven's Door!
Y-You're a Stand user!
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Calm down!
Episode 15:  Let's Go Visit the Comics Artist's House Part 2
I have an entire volume's worth of material
from just one of your pages!
This is outstanding!
I've grown as a comics artist, as well as a Stand user!
I'm going to give this a quick read, Koichi.
Oh my...
That's Higashikata Josuke with his Crazy Diamond, and Nijimura Okuyasu with his The Hand, isn't it?
Interesting...
Why did those two come to my house?
Koichi couldn't have said something to them about me.
How peculiar...
Huh?
I-It's Josuke and Okuyasu!
I don't know how they figured out I was here, but...
...n-now they can save me, somehow!
Somehow...
...I have to get them to save me!
Huh? Okuyasu and Josuke?
How did you guys know I was here?
Let's see...
I have no interest in Josuke or Okuyasu right now.
I'll simply have to finish up the last two pages for next week...
...and take even more material from Koichi!
I can't wait!
Huh? Ya were watchin' some dude draw comics?
There's a comics artist livin' here?
Kishibe Rohan?
He famous or somethin'?
Ya ever heard of this guy, Josuke?
Nah. I was made fun of by that asshole Hazamada for not even knowing what Perman was.
This isn't right...
That isn't what I wanted to tell them...
What was it?
Well, we only followed you here since we were wondering why you had wandered off.
But since you're okay, it's all good.
You had us worried there!
Sorry!
Do you guys wanna come inside and watch him with me?
Nah, I'll pass.
I'm a nervous wreck around famous people.
Me, too.
Guess I'm just glad ya didn't
come out here t'meet some chick!
See ya later, Koichi!
Bye!
I'm sure I'm forgetting something...
I needed to tell them something really important...
I remember now!
I-I needed their help!
Josuke! Okuyasu!
I'll see you guys at school!
See ya!
Don't be late!
Got it!
N-No!
That's not what I wanted to say!
Note: I cannot bring harm to comics artist Kishibe Rohan.
Note: "...cannot..."
It's no use... I can't ask them for help!
H-How is it possible for a Stand to be this terrifying?!
Heaven's Door is way too strong!
There's no way to attack it!
Ah, I see!
If this keeps up, he's gonna tear me apart until I'm dead!
Someone is breaking into my house!
What did you do while you were downstairs, Koichi?
Huh?
Okuyasu!
Hold up! Ya better not turn around!
Move even a little, and I'll beatcha with my Stand, stupid!
Okuyasu!
I have no idea how you knew I was in danger, but I'm so relieved!
It seems to me that he figured it out coincidentally, Koichi.
I just realized that the cut on your hand
made him aware something was amiss.
You must have cut yourself on something
while you crawled to the door.
I-I was too preoccupied to notice...
Is this how you figured it out, Nijimura Okuyasu?
Stand name: The Hand...
You have a complex regarding your dead brother, Keicho.
And whenever you're faced with a difficult decision...
...you wish your brother were there to make it for you.
Wha...?
What the hell?!
Who the fuck do ya think you are?!
Hey, Koichi! What kinda Stand does this guy got?
W-Well...
I-I can't do it!
I can't say anything that could bring harm to Kishibe Rohan!
If he sees even one panel, it's over!
I would do anything to tell you not to look!
Please don't look at his comic!
Hey, I toldja not t'move!
Okuyasu, I had no interest in you before,
but you've left me with no choice now that you've entered my house.
Now you too will become material for my work!
Damn you!
What?!
H-He's fast!
Okuyasu!
The fuck is goin' on?!
Higashikata Josuke...
...you're right over there, aren't you?
Hea
Heave
Heaven
Heaven'
Heaven's
Heaven's Do
Heaven's Doo
Heaven's Door
Kishi
Kishibe
Power: D
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Kishibe Ro
Kishibe Rohan
Okuyasu!
The fuck is this guy's problem?!
Shut your mouth!
Anyway, Koichi... I have a question for you.
Huh?
Why do you think Higashikata Josuke
is hiding behind that door?
Well? What do you think?
Why won't he come out, Koichi?
Josuke is hiding there so he won't
accidentally look at your comic!
Indeed. That's correct. You're quite sharp.
Nijimura Okuyasu wasn't aware of Heaven's Door,
so I was able to trick him.
Unfortunately, the same can't be said of Higashikata Josuke.
For this reason, I may be...
...no, without a doubt, I'm at a disadvantage.
For you see, there's another reason why
Higashikata Josuke is hiding behind that door.
Would you care to guess what it is?
If I'm to prevent the inevitable...
...I must drag him out from behind that door at any cost.
He's figurin' out which way he's gonna kill ya!
That's also certainly true.
But it isn't the answer I was looking for.
The correct answer is...
...Higashikata Josuke is contemplating whether or not
he should cut his losses and flee from my house alone!
Josuke would never do that!
You're right, Koichi.
It was written in your file that Higashikata Josuke's personality
would never allow him to forsake his friends.
But you see, being a comics artist causes your brain
to consider every possibility in a given situation.
So I must ask myself, what possible course of action would the protagonist caught in this scenario take?
In this situation, Josuke running away with
knowledge of my ability would be quite problematic.
Run away... Yeah, that ain't a bad idea!
He could get Mr. Jotaro!
An' Yukako'd throw a bitch fit if she knew ya were messin' with Koichi like this!
Ah! She could beat him with her hair!
I'd rather not see her again, though!
Josuke, hurry up an' tell everyone!
You fools!
I explained all of this to you so I could avoid it!
Okuyasu! I already wrote something into your body!
Huh?
I'll give you the honor of reading what I wrote inside of him, Koichi.
No way!
What'd he write, Koichi?
B-But that's... No way...
He can't run away anymore!
There's no way to run away from this!
Just tell me what he wrote there, Koichi!
Note: If Higashikata Josuke brings harm to Kishibe Rohan,
I will commit suicide by self-immolation.
S-Suicide?!
You'll commit suicide if Josuke tries to help us!
H-Hey, hey! I'm gonna commit suicide by burnin' myself?
Ya gotta be kiddin' me! I ain't gonna do myself in like that!
Huh?
You will! He's invincible!
We can't defy him, no matter what!
Quit doin' that, stupid hand!
You've finally shown yourself!
He wouldn't have barged in here
if you hadn't forced him to!
Ah... That's a rather simple idea,
but it may end up working for him.
This room is small and difficult to escape from.
If he's able to defeat me with a single blow,
the effect of my Heaven's Door will disappear...
...and Okuyasu will refrain from committing suicide.
Josuke!
Closing his eyes is simple, but it should work!
Heaven's Door is useless as long as he doesn't see the manuscript!
Keep charging ahead!
No problem.
All I have to do is open his eyes somehow!
Oh! He hardly flinched!
This isn't good...
If he's able to charge into me, I won't be able to take it.
If I were the protagonist of a comic in this situation,
what course of action would I take?
seconds
How would I force his eyes open?
Keep going, Josuke!
Josuke, hurry up!
That's it!
I recall something written in Koichi's file!
There! This is it!
I can't help but laugh when I look at your hairstyle, Josuke!
Did you discover it in a history book?
Do you seriously think it makes you look cool?
Something like this?
My words seem to have angered him, haven't they?
It's hard to believe my words could
enrage him like this, but the file never lies.
It's one hundred percent accurate.
What did you just say?!
J-Josuke, calm down!
Try saying that to me again!
Your eyes opened...
Couldn't hear me the first time?
You may think you have a cool hairstyle,
but it's by far the ugliest hair I've ever seen!
It's pathetic!
Perhaps a bird will make its nest in that unkempt mass of hairspray and grease you call hair, Josuke.
I know I wouldn't!
Dorararara!
Heaven's Door!
I've won.
Huh?!
What?!
Dorararara!
Wh-What was that?
I-I'm sure I made him open his eyes and look at my manuscript!
W-We're back to normal!
I'm certain he saw it... so why?
Where the hell did you fly off to?!
Get your bitch ass out here!
Nah, guess he saw nothin'...
He didn't see it?
Do you really think he got so worked up
that he couldn't see what was in front of him?
Where are you hiding, shithead?!
Get out here!
Yeah... He's the kinda guy that'll get
blinded with rage if ya talk shit about his hair...
I never thought he could get this mad!
This is worse than I imagined!
Why did this happen?
D-Did Koichi not know of an aspect of Josuke's personality?
There was information about him he didn't have on file?
Why? Why does insulting his hair send him into such a rage?
There must be a reason. Why...?
I won't forgive anyone who talks shit about my hair!
No matter who it is, I won't let it slide!
The reason he's so defensive of his hair...
I remember he told me something about it before...
Could that be the reason why?
Huh? Whatcha talkin' about?
It's something Josuke told me happened to him as a kid, but...
I'll have to fill in the blanks myself to explain what happened.
When Josuke was four years old,
he passed out from an inexplicably high fever...
...and for fifty days, nobody knew if he would live through it.
Josuke...
It turned out that Mr. Jotaro and Mr. Joestar were
headed to Egypt to defeat a man named Dio around this time.
But they had no way of knowing that at the time,
so Josuke's mom drove him to the hospital in S city.
But on that day,
Morioh was hit with its worst blizzard in eighteen years.
It's no use... What should I do?
Cars almost never drive through here,
and there aren't any pay phones...
I should have called an ambulance from the house...
I never should have driven with Josuke out into the snow!
But then something happened...
Wh-What do you want from me? Go away!
Yo
Your
Your ki
Your kid
Your kid i
Your kid is
Your kid is si
Your kid is sick
Your kid is sick,
Your kid is sick, ri
Your kid is sick, right
Your kid is sick, right?
I'll
I'll push
I'll push yo
I'll push your
I'll push your car
I'll push your car for
I'll push your car for you.
Huh?
Hu
Hurr
Hurry
Hurry u
Hurry up
Hurry up a
Hurry up an
Hurry up and
step
step on
step on the
step on the gas.
O
On
Once
Once y
Once yo
Once you
Once you g
Once you ge
Once you get
Once you get mo
Once you get movi
Once you get moving,
Once you get moving, do
Once you get moving, don
Once you get moving, don't
Once you get moving, don't st
Once you get moving, don't sto
Once you get moving, don't stop
Once you get moving, don't stop.
Once you get moving, don't stop..
Once you get moving, don't stop...
Other
Otherwise,
Otherwise, your
Otherwise, your tires
Otherwise, your tires are
Otherwise, your tires are gon
Otherwise, your tires are gonna
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get stu
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get stuck
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get stuck in
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get stuck in the
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get stuck in the snow
Otherwise, your tires are gonna get stuck in the snow again.
O-Okay...
Thank you!
His mom later tried searching for the young man, but she couldn't find a single lead.
Even though he didn't personally save Josuke's life...
...four-year-old Josuke viewed the young man as a hero.
He left a permanent impression on Josuke's heart,
influencing how he lived his life.
That's why when anybody insults his hair, something deep in his heart snaps.
I have no idea who he is...
...but he was cool enough that I decided to copy his hairstyle.
I'll never forgive anyone who insults my hair, since insulting mine is like insulting his.
That story could be why it makes him so upset.
I thought Josuke was making it up when he told me,
so I wasn't listening very carefully.
Huh... Never knew somethin' like that happened...
Rohan's holding a pen!
Bastard! What're ya tryin' t'pull?!
N-N-Nothing!
I just want to make some notes
and draw a sketch before I pass out...
Such a moving story!
I feel as though I witnessed it myself...
I'm so happy!
Experiences like this are few and far between...
If I can work this into one of my stories...
How fortunate!
Moving to Morioh was a wonderful idea!
This guy's hopeless!
It don't matter what we do to him! He's gonna keep puttin' whatever we say in his comics 'till he's dead!
I have to give him some credit!
Even though he has questionable morals,
you have to admire his attitude!
He really is a super comics artist!
There you are, you asshole comics artist!
I wasn't finished punching the shit out of you!
Gotta give Josuke some credit, too...
Y-Yeah...
Dora! Dora! Dora!
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Kishibe Rohan's Pink Dark Boy will be taking a one month hiatus!
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
Thank you as always
for reading
Pink Dark Boy!
For personal reasons,
we will be taking
a one month hiatus.
dddddl - Editor
— Notice of Hiatus —
PINK DARK BOY
KISHIBE ROHAN'S
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 16
Let's
Go
Hunt
ing!
Let's
Hunt
Go
ing!
Let's
Hunt