surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 13:  Picking Up Something Dangerous!
It's Morioh Radio!
Up next, we have a letter from a "Troubled Lonesome Boy."
"Kai, I gotta tell you something...
I can't get a hold of my girlfriend, and it's got me feeling down.
You think my sudden proposal upset her or something?
I already spent my entire paycheck on
a ruby engagement ring, which is her birthstone..."
I'm glad we finally found the bow and arrow.
Yeah, it was at Otoishi Akira's place.
He was using his Stand to commit theft.
Stole five hundred million yen in goods in total.
The police are still investigating.
Go ahead and try using your Stand against me.
I'll find and kill you no matter where you run.
I'm fine with prison!
Chili Pepper's in pieces.
Even if he gets out, he won't try anything.
Mr. Jotaro, what will you do with the bow and arrow?
I'm handing it over to the Speedwagon Foundation for research.
It's an important piece of evidence in
uncovering the mystery behind Stands.
Great!
I'm glad to hear it!
That means this is finally over!
It was a bit anti-climactic, but yay! We're done!
I'm still questioning Otoishi about the Stand users created from it.
But don't let your guard down.
Got it.
Okay.
Japanese coffee really hits the spot.
Ms. waitress, may I have a refill?
Whoa! Jeez...
Be careful! I can't take my eyes off you for a second...
Josuke, don't you have to go? The bus will be here soon.
You're right. Come on, let's go. Get up.
Will those two be okay?
I'm worried.
Whoa, this cake's fuckin' delicious!
Waitress, gimme more!
Hello, Higashikata resid-
Hey, Mom! It's me.
Josuke? You're the last person I expected to be calling.
Do you need something?
Well, uh...
You're gonna be staying at home for the rest of the day, right?
Yeah. Why do you ask?
N-No reason! Just wanted to be sure! Bye!
Oh, he-
What was that all about?
He better not be planning something weird again...
Man, I hope Mom didn't think that sounded weird...
Oh, come on...
I told him to wait until I was off the phone!
Hey, wait!
Hello? Can you hear me? Hey!
Were you trying to call me just now?
Yeah. There's no way we'll get a taxi this late,
so we're gonna take the bus to my house.
And... Listen, I know I'm being pushy,
but I wanna make sure we're on the same page here.
You can only look from a distance.
Don't even think about talking to my mom!
I need you to promise.
My mom won't be happy if you show up out of nowhere.
She'd be a total wreck.
Don't need to tell me twice. I promise.
Also, one more thing.
I'm gonna call you "Mr. Joestar."
Huh?
W-Well... Guess I should be straight with you...
This may seem cold...
...but I can't call a guy I just met "Dad" or "Pops" or whatever...
After you see my mom,
I want you to go right back to America.
I see...
That's fine with me. I understand.
Man, this is so awkward...
I know being honest is best,
but maybe some things are better left unsaid...
Hey, Mr. Joestar...
Excuse me, but did you see where
that buff old guy standing here just went?
He just got on that long-distance bus.
Bright Deer
Long Distance Bus
Destination:
Sapporo
Bright Deer
Long Distance Bus
Destination:
Sapporo
Y-You've gotta be kidding me, dammit!
Sorry about that...
You said we were getting on a bus, so...
I'm impressed you caught up to it on foot!
We nearly made it onto the highway.
Honestly, I'm starting to think I should have just let you ride all the way to Hokkaido!
Ugh, my stomach...
I'm really sorry...
Josuke...
It feels like something is tugging at my trousers.
Oh, really? Whatever you do, don't let it drag you off again.
Wha-
J-Josuke! There's a Stand user nearby!
Yeah, yeah, there sure is. You and me...
Anyway, you see any vending machines around here?
I'm dying of thirst.
Wh-What is this? These aren't footsteps...
Hands? Hand prints?
Oh my god!
Josuke, the Stand just laughed!
See? Right here! On the sand!
There's no way I'm letting this guy see my mom...
He's off his freakin' rocker...
It's on the concrete!
Where did it go? Where is it? It's gone!
Where did it go? It's gone!
Great... This guy is seriously bad news...
Hermit Purple!
Get out of here, you mutt! Shoo! Shoo!
You hear that crying sound?
It's coming from right here, Josuke!
A baby! I'm holding a naked baby in my hands!
I can tell now that I'm touching it. It's invisible!
What?!
I-I can feel it!
I can really feel it!
It's all squishy.
I can't believe it!
It's an invisible baby!
It feels like it's only about six months old or so.
But how did a baby turn invisible out here?
I'm assuming it's a Stand ability, but...
Why would an enemy Stand user turn a baby invisible, and where the hell did its mother go?
Josuke, I think the baby actually is the Stand user.
It doesn't realize it's a Stand user.
Since it became separated from its mother,
it instinctively turned invisible.
Huh?
Even adults can develop ulcers, bald spots, and gray hair
before they realize it for psychological reasons, right?
I believe finding its mother is the only way to solve this.
H-Hey, hurry up and make it stop crying!
I-I'm not really sure what to do...
I was in a situation similar to this before, but that was such a long time ago....
There, there...
Th-This is...
Did you figure something out?
Yes, when I touched it just now...
It's a little girl!
Oh yeah, you can tell if it's a boy or girl
by what's between their legs!
Figure something else out?
Josuke...
...do you have any tissues?
Th-That smell...
I-Is it on your hand? A big one?!
I-It's invisible, so I couldn't tell for sure until I smelled it.
And I just scratched my beard with this hand!
C
Cr
Cra
Craz
Crazy
Crazy D
Crazy Di
Crazy Dia
Crazy Diam
Crazy Diamo
Crazy Diamon
Crazy Diamond
Higashi
Higashikata
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Higashikata Jo
Higashikata Josuke
Here's your manuscript back.
I eagerly await the fixes for the volume release, Sir.
For the time being, we're gonna have to get milk and diapers.
And since she's naked, we need to get her some clothes.
I'm counting on you, Mr. Joestar.
What? I-I'm buying them?
Of course. Look at me.
It's too embarrassing for me to buy baby stuff.
Rumors would start flying around about a sixteen-year-old delinquent who got some chick knocked up.
But I only have American traveler's checks.
Fine, whatever...
You can use my credit card.
Sorry.
Don't buy anything too expensive!
I worked hard to build up my savings, and I don't have a lot!
I got it, I got it.
Welcome!
Is there anything I can help you with?
Umm... Do you carry disposable diapers?
Of course! Is this your first visit here?
Why, yes it is, but...
These diapers are easy to change,
even if you're living on your own.
They even work overnight!
Umm... I need diapers for a baby, not me...
M-My apologies! So you're in need of baby diapers?
Do you need cloth diapers, or disposable pull-ups?
Uh... Come again?
As you can see, this one requires a diaper cover...
...but disposable pull-ups like this are simple and economical.
I-I'm not really sure which to get, so could you just...
Which size do you need?
Size?
How old is the baby?
Depending on the baby's size, we have newborn, S-size, M-size,
L-size, and XL-size for both boys and girls.
Th-There are that many options nowadays?
W-Well, she's a girl, and she felt about this big while I held her.
What do you mean by "while I held her," sir?
It would be very inconvenient for everyone if you bought
the wrong size and tried to return them after they were soiled.
Oh, fine then! Give me every size.
I also need baby wipes, powdered milk, and a baby bottle.
For baby bottles, we have both glass and plastic.
Huh?
Glass ones don't scratch or start to smell as easily, but some babies may have trouble holding them.
Plastic ones are easier to hold,
but may take on a noticeable scent.
Which do you prefer?
U-U-Uh... Umm...
Both variants come in many shapes and designs.
Some are even shaped like rocket ships and racing cars.
The baby can hold this one by itself.
And if you turn this one upside-down,
the tiny doll inside moves about.
I-I'm not sure which to get,
so if you could just toss a few in...
And which bottle nipples would you like?
The rubber ones are soft, but don't last very long.
Silicon ones last, but they're a bit hard.
This is a vented nipple.
There's a diaphragm where the nipple goes in the mouth,
and the flow of milk is adjusted by how hard the baby sucks on it.
This one is a German NUK nipple.
It has a slightly flattened shape,
which is said to more closely mimic the feel of a mother's breast.
And much like while drinking breast milk,
the milk won't come out unless the baby uses its jaws.
O-Oh, all right. They're all fine! I'll take them all!
And as for the nipple hole shapes,
we have round, Y-shaped, and cross-shaped!
J-Just give me all of them!
And throw in some baby socks and clothes, too.
I'm paying for all of this by card.
Thank you very much, sir.
130,000... I'm not very familiar with yen...
How much is that supposed to be in dollars?
If one hundred yen is about eighty cents...
Bah, never mind!
I need all of these things, and it's just baby stuff.
Surely it can't be that expensive...
Man...
What is he doing? He's taking forever...
By the way...
Did you hear about the girl who got the ring? I wonder what happened with that.
He never got an answer, so I'm curious if she said no.
Maybe she's just feeling conflicted about it?
I-I gotta get the hell away from here...
If anyone from school saw me here...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Josuke!
Here's your card back.
You're done? A-All right, let's go!
We don't have to worry about losing her anymore, but...
...if anyone walks by and notices that
she doesn't have a face, they'll freak out.
No need to worry...
I picked up some makeup, too.
Let's put some foundation on her. Just a little bit more...
Hey, she actually looks kinda cute now!
My, what a darling!
Knowing what she looks like should help us find her mom!
Finally a shred of hope! We got this!
What a nice idea!
You really think so?
All right, now let's put on some lipstick.
Now for the eyebrows and eyelashes... Just like that...
I knew he'd react that way...
He's the kind of old guy who gets
carried away by one simple compliment...
Now we can carry you around
without having to worry about losing you!
We can't put makeup on your eyes,
so you'll just have to wear these sunglasses!
They look great!
Here, her milk.
Perhaps I went a bit light on the foundation...
It looks as though it may be coming off...
I-It's not that!
What's going on?! Sh-She's...
Sh-She disappeared! Along with my hands!
The baby isn't just making herself invisible!
She's making everything around her invisible, too!
Mr. Joestar! Let go of her!
Hurry up and let go of her!
M-My hands are still invisible!
She's powering up!
This is bad!
It looks like everything within
thirty centimeters of her is turning invisible.
But this makes no sense...
If she's constantly protecting herself with her Stand,
who was able to feed and take care of her before?
She must be doing this because she feels anxious.
It's stress...
She doesn't want to be touched by any strangers.
If she powers up any more,
nobody will be able to get close to her.
We'll end up invisible, too.
What a weird piece of crap.
Who's gonna clean that up?
Guess someone will get to it eventually.
Sure ain't gonna be me.
Look out!
What happened?
The lit cigarette butt... Oh, you can't see it...
What the hell are you doing, Mr. Joestar?!
You can't space out at a time like this!
I, uh...
The stroller completely disappeared!
The ground, too!
She really is stressed!
The more scared she is, the bigger her range becomes!
That sounds like the stroller flipped over!
The baby... fell into the water?!
Wh-Where is she? Make some noise!
I can't even see any bubbles! Where is she?!
J-Josuke...
Shut the hell up!
This wouldn't have happened if he had just kept it together!
Stupid old geezer!
How can my dad be such an irresponsible guy?
He was irresponsible enough to
abandon my mom for sixteen years...
I could never respect someone like him.
We'll never get along!
Stay the hell out of this!
Where is she? She should be right around here...
I don't care if I turn invisible, too...
Just touch me already! Hurry!
Come on!
She's not here... Come on!
Dammit! How the hell am I supposed to
find an invisible baby in clear water?!
Josuke, I...
I may die in the next few moments,
so if I do, give your mother my regards...
I mean...
I'm quite old now...
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm adding color to the water...
She's in the center...
The color of the blood is turning invisible...
You'll find her in the center...
Mr. Joestar...
Nobody else would have even
considered doing something like that...
Especially not for someone else's kid...
Nobody would go this far.
I just wanted to look cool...
...in front of you.
He
Her
Herm
Hermi
Hermit
Hermit Pu
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purp
Hermit Purple
J
Jo
Jose
Josep
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Joseph
Joseph J
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Joseph Joes
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
Well, a lot happened...
...but it looks like everything's good for now.
130,000 yen?!
M-My hard-earned savings...
That stupid geezer!
There, there.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 14
Let's Go
Visit
the Comics
Artist's
House Part 1
Visit
Artist's
Let's Go
the Comics
House Part 1
Visit
Artist's