I've already carried out my plan.
What?!
Okuyasu's big bro was a great threat.
Koichi, let's get the hell out of here.
Huh?
Wh-What about the bow and arrow that hit me?
The bow and arrow?
Okuyasu's big bro must've hidden it somewhere.
Wanna go look for it?
Y-Yeah...
You know, I could have sworn they mentioned
they lived with their dad or something.
I got beat up pretty bad, so let's call it quits for today.
W-We can't!
I-I'm lucky you were here to save me
and heal my wounds, but...
...if anyone else gets hit by the bow and arrow,
they could actually die!
Someone from our town!
J-Just wait here for me!
I-I'll go find it myself!
A-Anyway, I don't think their dad is even here right now.
I-If he were, h-he would have come out by now...
He's a lot braver than I thought.
He's pretty tough when push comes to shove...
or maybe just reckless.
Still, we really need to hurry up and get out of this place.
Hey...
Wh-What? D-Don't try to stop me!
I won't.
Let's hurry up and snap that bow and arrow in half, then get the hell out of here together, Koichi.
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 5:  The Nijimura Brothers Part 3
They have an attic. Maybe the bow and arrow is up here.
Th-There it is!
The bow and arrow!
It's hanging on the far wall!
Hey, maybe we shouldn't go in there after all...
What do you think they got chained up in there?
A-A dog, maybe?
Those noises aren't human...
I-It sounds like an animal...
I can't take this! What should we do?
"What should we do"?
You're the one who wanted to do this!
Yeah, but...
Let's just get this over with!
Listen up, Koichi...
You're gonna kick in the door
as hard as you can on the count of three!
That should startle it!
Then, I'm gonna make a break for
the bow and arrow and snap it in half.
You with me?
Yeah.
Here we go.
One...
Two...
Three!
What the hell is that?!
Koichi!
H-Help me!
That hand doesn't belong to a Stand! It's real!
This thing is a real creature!
H-Help me!
Dora!
I didn't mean to smash it off...
Wh-What the hell is this thing?
I can't believe a thing like this
has been living so close to my house...
So, now you've seen it... The skeleton hidden in our closet.
Asshole!
The abomination you're gawking at... is our dad...
I'm not done using this thing just yet...
Th-The bow and arrow...
I need to find a Stand user for our dad.
That's why no matter what,
I can't let anyone steal or destroy this bow and arrow!
He's got some kind of disease?
Disease? If only.
He's in perfect health. Has an appetite and everything.
But all he ever does is moan,
and he can't even recognize his own sons anymore.
So you're looking for a Stand user to heal your dad?
Heal?
You think I want him to be healed? Guess again.
It's the opposite...
I've been looking for a Stand user who can finally end him!
Nothing I've tried works!
I've tried bashing his head in, grinding up his body, and ripping his limbs off, but nothing works!
I just want him to die like a normal person...
I swore as a child to do everything in my power to make that happen.
The only way I'll succeed is with this bow and arrow!
If I fail, our dad will probably live like this forever.
And it's all because that Dio guy
implanted those damn cells in his head!
Dio?! Did you just say Dio?
That's the guy Mr. Jotaro told me about!
Let me tell you a bit about my past...
...Higashikata Josuke.
After all, this concerns you now, too.
It all happened eleven years ago, in 1988.
I was just seven years old, and Okuyasu was four.
We were living in Tokyo.
Things were looking up thanks to the bubble economy, but our dad wasn't reaping any of the benefits.
Our mom died of disease,
and he went into massive debt after his business went under.
He took his anger out on the two of us.
Our dad was a total loser.
But then, without warning...
...a ton of money began to come his way.
Sometimes he would even get jewels and precious metals.
But he wasn't working for any of it.
After doing some research later on,
I found out by that point he had already sold his soul to Dio.
He became one of his minions in exchange for wealth.
Back then, Dio was searching for anyone who could potentially obtain a Stand.
Somehow, he figured out that our dad had the potential, but...
...I never found out what kind of Stand he had.
Then one day... A day ten years ago
that I can remember like it was yesterday...
When I got home from school, at around two o'clock...
Okuyasu!
Did Dad hit you again? That dirtbag!
N-Nuh-uh!
Huh?
Dio...
Dio's dead...
That must be why!
Dad?
Dad, I'm calling an ambulance...
It's too late! This isn't a disease!
The flesh bud inside me is going berserk!
I'm done for!
Dad!
A year later, he become this fat blob of flesh,
completely incapable of recognizing his own sons...
Dio implanted his cells into the heads of those he didn't trust,
then gave them orders when he needed someone to do his bidding.
He implanted them inside our dad's brain.
I spent ten years researching it.
I learned about Stands, and about Jotaro...
Then I obtained the bow and arrow for myself after learning about that old hag, Enya.
But the more I learned, the more obvious it became that our dad was never going to get better.
He and Dio's immortal cells had become one.
This is all he does now.
Every single day...
Day in and day out, for the last ten years,
he's been pointlessly digging around inside that box of junk.
Whenever I take the box away from him, he doesn't stop crying.
It pisses me off!
Watching him makes me despise life itself!
How many times have I told you not to make a mess?!
Normally he listens to me if I punish him,
but no matter how many times I do it...
...he never stops digging around in this stupid fucking box!
Hey! You're the one who needs to stop!
He's your dad!
Yeah, you're right.
We're related by blood.
But he's not the dad I once knew.
He sold his soul to Dio and got what was coming to him.
On the other hand, do you have any idea how much it pains me to see him live like this, even though he's hardly my dad anymore?
That's why I want him to have a normal death!
Once he's dead, I can finally go back to a normal life!
Goddammit! I told you to stop that!
Quit pissing me off!
Hey!
Stop doing that!
I won't let you have the bow and arrow!
No matter what!
Don't get me wrong!
I'll worry about the bow and arrow later!
But right now, I need to focus on that box!
Dora!
Th-The box?
I saw him grabbing at some scraps of paper,
and it caught my interest.
It all makes sense now.
It's a family photo...
S-So he did have a reason!
He really did have a reason for doing the same thing for the last ten years!
He was looking for the photo of his sons from when he remembered them!
Even though he doesn't understand what's going on anymore,
he still has his memories locked deep down inside him!
Memories of his past!
Th
The
The Ha
The Han
The Hand
Niji
Nijimura
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Nijimura Oku
Nijimura Okuyasu
If you stop looking for a Stand user who can kill him...
...and start looking for one who can cure him...
...I can help you guys out.
But you have to hand the bow and arrow over to us.
I'm gonna snap it in half.
You plan on running away?
Big bro, no more of this...
Okuyasu!
C'mon. We don't gotta do this no more, so let's quit it, okay?
You were still here?
Maybe Dad'll get better someday!
Even if he's stuck like this for good...
...maybe he'll remember us an' go back t'bein' dad again...
...right?
Okuyasu! What do you think you're doing?!
B-Big bro...
Step aside, Okuyasu!
There's no turning back for me, no matter what happens!
I've killed too many people in this town with the bow and arrow!
Besides, I don't even see you as my little brother anymore!
I won't feel a thing if I kill you!
B-Big bro...
Hey, fellas...
...you got any other family living here besides your dad?
Family? Just the three of us...
Th-That's...
I-It came from the electrical outlet...!
Okuyasu! Get your head out of your ass, idiot!
Big bro!
This bow and arrow's all mine, Nijimura Keicho!
You're the one who struck me with the bow and arrow and brought out my awesome Stand ability!
Y-You think a guy like you can handle the bow and arrow?
Nijimura Keicho!
You said Stand abilities come from the spirit, right?
Well, mine has grown!
How else could my Stand,
Red Hot Chili Pepper, grow to be this powerful?
Bad Company!
Shut the fuck up!
Th-That's...!
E-Electricity!
Okuyasu's brother is being converted into electricity!
And so is the bow and arrow!
Big bro!
Don't touch me!
He'll just drag us both in!
Big bro!
D-Dammit! This thing is taking the bow and arrow!
Okuyasu...
...you were always holding me back!
Big bro!
Josuke!
Just now, I'm sure I saw the user
looking at us through the window.
Do you know anything about the Stand we just saw, Okuyasu?
N-Nuh-uh... My big bro didn't tell me squat 'bout no Stand users.
J-Josuke! O-Over there...
Okuyasu...
My big bro... He knew he had this comin'...
He never woulda gone down the straight an' narrow path.
It's fate...
But y'know...
When push came to shove, my big bro...
My big bro kept me safe when push came to shove, didn't he?
Josuke, ya saw he did, right?!
Yeah. I sure did.
Your big bro kept you safe.
Is Mr. Kujo Jotaro there?
I don't recognize your voice.
Who are you?
Doesn't matter.
Kujo Jotaro, I'm gonna have to ask you to leave Morioh, pronto.
I won't leave just because some stranger over the phone asks me to.
Would you leave if you were in my position?
I'm the guy with the bow and arrow now.
I took it from Nijimura Keicho's dead body.
You'll wind up the same as him if you don't listen to me, Mr. Jotaro.
I hear you got the ability to stop time for a few seconds at a time.
I figure you're a pretty tough guy,
so I'm giving you a nice warning first.
Are you a Stand user, too?
What do you plan to do with the bow and arrow?
I'm not gonna make any trouble for you if that's what you're thinking.
As long as you and Higashikata Josuke
don't try anything funny, I'll leave you both alone.
Unavailable Number  Public Phone
I got my Stand ability not too long ago.
I just wanna have a little fun with it!
I'm fed up with spending my time taking
college entrance exams and looking for a job.
So you're a student?
What's it to ya?!
Listen up! If you stay here any longer,
you and Josuke are in for it! You got that?!
How many other Stand users are in this town?
Gimme a break...
Nijimura Keicho was buried in
Kunimi Pass Cemetery, just west of Morioh.
The stolen bow and arrow remains missing.
Nijimura Family
Nijimura Okuyasu decided to settle down
with his father in Morioh for the time being.
Meanwhile...
Josuke, can you get the door?
Hello?
Yo, Josuke! Ya ready for school?
Huh?
Startin' today, you an' me's goin' to the same school!
That doesn't mean we have to walk there together!
We're not in middle school!
Man, ain't it weird how close we live together?
Yeah, it's really something else...
C'mon, let's go already!
Oh, Josuke, is he a friend of yours?
Hi! My name's Nijimura Okuyasu!
Feel free to come in and
have a cup of coffee while you wait!
You kiddin' me?! Don't mind if I do!
Your mom's a total babe, dude!
Comin' through!
Just great... This is heavy...
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 6
Hirose
Koichi (Echoes)
Ko
ichi (Echoes)