Yamagishi Yukako was feeling depressed as of late.
What?! You're into someone right now?
Yeah, we really like each other!
So I was at the Angelo Stone earlier,
and I saw a bunch of tourists taking pictures of it.
Heh, it's pretty famous now, huh?
What's wrong, Koichi?
"Just being able to think about Koichi makes me so happy..."
I thought this once upon a time, but it isn't so simple...
I wish he would just look at me again...
I don't know what to do with myself...
Note: "Makeup that will help you find your one true love."
Cinderella?
How is happiness like this possible?!
I can't believe such a wonderful man proposed to me!
Thank you, Dr. Aya! Thank you so much!
I suppose a woman's youth is better spent joyous and ugly than glum and beautiful.
Do come in.
Makeup that will help you find your one true love.
I take the motto on this sign quite seriously.
So if you're interested...
Episode 20:  Yamagishi Yukako's Cinderella Fantasy
Welcome to Salon Cinderella.
Please, come in.
My name is Tsuji Aya.
I'm a beautician, as well as the owner of this place.
I may speak as though I have low blood pressure,
but don't let it bother you.
I'm very motivated by what I do.
You...
...are quite the beauty.
I never suspected one as beautiful as you
could live here in Morioh.
Please, have a seat right over there.
Write your name and address on the form.
I haven't decided if I'm doing this yet.
Here, these are my prices.
Makeup Menu
Makeup to Find True Love...
Makeup to Capture Love...
Makeup to Get Proposed to...
Makeup to Make Men Submit...
Makeup to Marry into Wealth...
Makeup to Marry a Celebrity...
"Makeup to Marry a Celebrity"?
My salon is a bit different from other salons.
I'm a beautician who specializes in putting joy on people's faces.
I use physiognomy, the ability to read one's
personality from their face, to alter their luck.
Having a face with a propensity to be loved
will increase your chances of finding the love you desire.
Hmm... A pity...
The shapes of your eyes and eyebrows are all wrong.
Let me be blunt with you.
This whole thing is unbelievably stupid.
You charge people money for this?
With a face like that, the more you love a boy,
the more he'll be repelled by you.
Am I wrong?
Does this ring a bell?
You're wrong!
I've never experienced anything like that before.
Oh, it doesn't? Very well, then...
In that case...
Oh, I do apologize.
I'm still unaccustomed to working with CG.
This is a face that will find true love.
Wait a minute... I would need surgery to look like that!
You perform surgeries?
This face can be achieved simply with
a beauty massage and makeup application.
However, it will only last for thirty minutes.
In the event that you don't find true love,
I'll refund you the one thousand yen fee.
Would you like to try it?
Fine. Since it's just makeup...
I have nothing to lose, so it won't hurt to try.
Thank you. Then let's get started.
Close your eyes.
Make sure they stay shut.
Don't move even a little bit.
My hands may slip if you do.
Koichi...
This makeup will help me find my true love?
Could altering the shape of my eyes
and eyebrows really change my luck?
Koichi?
I-I was looking for you, Yukako!
Huh? For me?
Yeah. You passed by Cafe Rengatei earlier, right?
You looked really depressed,
a-and I got a bit worried about you...
Worried?
You were worried about me?
Y-Yeah... A lot happened between us, but I'm over it now...
I don't want you to feel bad about it anymore.
R-Really?
Yeah...
I can't believe it...
Could this be because of the makeup?
K-Koichi...
Instead of just standing here,
why don't we find someplace to sit and chat?
Huh?
U-Umm... That is, if you'd like to...
To tell you the truth...
...I was just starting to feel thirsty!
Huh? Huh?!
I really am lucky!
Things are finally looking up for me!
I get to be near the cute, yet strong, Koichi...
I feel like eating a chocolate parfait all of a sudden!
You think that's a bit girly?
Huh? No! Not at all!
That's just what I wanted, too!
I feel like I'm dreaming...
Physiognomy really works!
Everything is going my way!
I'm having such good luck!
I... I can't believe it...
I'm feeling Koichi's warmth and the beating of his heart...
I'm so happy...
I've never been happier in all my life...
Ah, it's 4 o'clock! It's already so late!
W-What?!
M-My stomach hurts!
It's so bad!
Y-Yukako, I'm sorry!
I need to go home!
K-Koichi!
Why...
Why only thirty minutes?!
Hey, lady! Can't you see the light's red?
Shut your mouth!
Blame the light for turning red!
Why does it only last for thirty minutes?!
I need more time!
You found your true love, didn't you?
You should be satisfied with that, and come again tomorrow.
Just as my previous customers have done.
No! I have no use for luck that only lets me be with Koichi
for thirty minutes before tearing us apart!
Do something that will let me capture love!
You can do that, can't you?
You're very bad at listening to others, aren't you?
Just do it!
Yukako...
In spite of the torment Cinderella endured,
she found her true love due to the purity in her heart.
She held onto the desire to find true love in her heart.
Do you think you can do that?
Desire? What do you mean?
Physiognomy alone isn't enough
to permanently change your luck.
I became a beautician because I admired the Fairy Godmother from Cinderella.
Like the Fairy Godmother,
I wanted to bring people happiness.
You're a beautiful young woman, and I've grown fond of you...
...so I'll do this especially for you.
However...
We'll need to work on more than just your face...
It's your whole body...
Your entire body must be transformed in order to capture love.
And the desire I spoke of lies in this.
You must apply this lipstick every thirty minutes,
except for when you sleep.
This is the only way to maintain your body once I've worked on it.
If you do this, you'll be able to
capture love for all of eternity.
It will be 72,000 yen for twenty-four hours.
Fine. Do it.
Good... Now, stay very still...
You mustn't open your eyes...
I knew you weren't an ordinary beautician.
Th-This power...
You can see my Cinderella?
I see... You used your Stand's power.
But come to think of it, I don't really care.
If you wanted to harm me,
you already would have by now.
I trust you. You're my Fairy Godmother.
That startled me...
Do it already.
What a wonderful girl...
Very well. I'll work my magic.
Cinderella is a Stand that transforms the body's image.
The work I've done to your body
will surely help you capture love.
Yukako, your body is unrivaled in its propensity to be loved.
My stomach ache suddenly went away...
Oh, I have Yukako's bag! Damn!
I need to bring it back to her!
Koichi.
Y-Yukako...
O-Oh yeah! Here! I had your bag!
Huh?
The one you're holding is mine.
I accidentally took yours. Sorry about that!
W-Well, catch you later!
W-Wait a minute, Koichi!
Look at me!
Don't you feel something when you look at me now?
W-Well... Well...
Well...
Hey! If it isn't Koichi!
Mr. Rohan!
I'm headed to the Kame Yu
department store to look for inspiration.
I'd like you to join me.
But I was planning on going home...
You know, it's awfully embarrassing to be taking pictures in a department store all by myself. So will you?
Wh... What's going on?
You're so needy... Jeez...
Aren't I supposed to be an unrivaled heroine?!
Why isn't your Cinderella's power working like it should be?!
Don't fret. Koichi's heart surely belongs to you now.
Oh, munchkin!
Oh, Mom. Sis.
His judgment is still getting in the way.
Did something happen between you and Koichi in the past?
That must be it.
Oh, this gentleman is a comics artist?!
How wonderful! May we join you?
You have nothing to worry about.
Luck will be on your side before long.
Cinderella is absolute.
By the way, it's 4:45. It's nearly been thirty minutes.
Don't forget to apply the lipstick.
Right, I'm putting it on now.
Luck will be on my side, huh?
What? You're going to Kame Yu? So are we!
Huh?!
Where did all of these people come from?!
There's so many of them!
Not to mention the person I want here the least,
his mother, is here!
Luck isn't on my side at all!
I'll kill that salon-running bitch!
I suppose here is a good spot to snap some pictures.
H-Hey, is your flash turned on?
This isn't good, Josuke!
The stress from being startled is making her disappear!
H-Hey, Gramps! Get outside!
P-Pardon me!
Please, get out of the way!
Huh?
What's going on?
Ah!
Whoa! I'm sorry, Koichi!
Y-Yukako...
K-Koichi...
This... is luck...
This is it!
Our hearts are beating as one now!
Koichi's heart is becoming one with my own...
This means everything to me...
My life will change for the better from now on...
Ci
Cin
Cinde
Cindere
Cinderella
Tsuji
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: C
Durability: C
Precision: A
Growth Potential: C
Tsuji Aya
Josuke, Okuyasu...
Yukako and I ended up kissing. Yeah...
What the hell did she do to you?!
She must be up to something again!
Calm down! It's not that!
It's just...
I think I'm actually in love with Yukako.
Huh?
I think I finally got used to her demeanor...
It makes me feel warm inside.
Is this really love?
I have no idea...
Hey, Okuyasu, you hearing this?
Even a Stand would be blown to the moon after hearing that!
He and Yukako...
Hey, hey, hey! You don't need to cry about it!
Still, Koichi...
I don't know what led to you taking a 180 like this...
...but if you and Yukako really have feelings for each other,
then you have nothing to worry about.
But that's just it...
Yukako has refused to see me ever since.
It's a complete mystery.
She hasn't been to school in two days.
She won't pick up the phone,
and she hasn't tried contacting me. I've heard nothing.
Y-Ya mean since the two of ya kissed...
You haven't heard anything?
Nothing.
Hmm... That's kinda bizarre...
To tell ya the truth,
I got a lotta respect for Yukako's dedication t'love.
Honestly, I don't think you'll get any answers unless you confront Yukako face-to-face.
We probably shouldn't get involved, though...
Y-Yeah...
Just say the word if ya think you're in danger!
We got your back!
Thanks! I'm gonna go now.
Okay.
Still...
Fuck you, Koichi! I can't believe ya kissed a girl!
Seriously, you have no reason to cry over this!
Th-That hair!
Yukako!
W-Wait up, Yukako!
U-Umm...
I'm... not the person you're looking for...
W-Well, you looked just like her from behind...
Wait, don't go!
K-Koichi...
How dare you do this to me, you stupid whore!
My face won't stop falling apart!
Your makeup isn't working!
You... fucking bitch!
Turn my face back to normal!
It appears to me...
...that you've broken your promise.
Such a pity.
I made it as clear as I could that you must apply the Cinderella lipstick every thirty minutes.
I only forgot to do it once!
Wh-What's going on? My hands...
They're turning into mush!
Your palm lines and fingerprints are disappearing.
You really shouldn't have broken your promise.
That lipstick is what assured your good luck.
A vast amount of energy is required to alter someone's luck.
They're gone forever, now.
It's your own fault for underestimating how bad your luck was.
D-Do you want to die?!
Die?
I didn't start this salon for the sake of fame or fortune.
My only desire was to bring people happiness, like the Fairy Godmother from Cinderella.
It truly is a pity.
I never should have granted your wish.
Your face and palm lines are gone forever.
They no longer exist in this world.
What did you say...?
They've disappeared.
I'm afraid there's nothing I can do
for a person with missing parts.
My face... is gone?
What kind of life can I live with parts of me missing?
Yukako!
K-Koichi!
Why is he...?
No, I can't let him know who I am.
N-No, you have the wrong person...
Dr. Aya, men aren't allowed in here, are they?
Please make him leave.
That demeanor...
That tough-as-nails demeanor...
You're definitely Yukako.
I think I started warming up to your demeanor...
That woman there is a Stand user, right?
She must have done something to you...
It's all over...
I can't live like this!
I'll kill you, Tsuji Aya!
I'll kill you!
Calm yourself.
That's...
A-A bunch of faces just went flying everywhere!
There we go.
So, this is Koichi...
He figured out that you were Yamagishi Yukako,
despite your face being completely different.
Even though you denied who you were,
he had no trouble figuring out it was you.
Very well, Yukako.
On his behalf, I as your Fairy Godmother
will give you one last chance for redemption.
Your last chance is to choose one of these.
Your real face is lost forever...
...but my Cinderella knows the face of every person it has ever worked on.
Choose your own face from these.
If chosen correctly, your face will be returned to normal.
Your palm lines and fingerprints will return too, naturally.
Just as Cinderella's glass slippers perfectly fit her,
you must choose the face that perfectly fits you.
You should have let me do this
in the first place, you dumb bitch!
Figuring out which one is mine couldn't be easier!
I look at my face in the mirror every day!
But be warned, if the face you choose
belongs to someone else, it will never suit you.
In fact, if I were to judge your new visage by my high standards of beauty...
...I would consider you to be quite hideous.
From then on, your luck would be dictated by that face.
Y-Yukako...
Choose carefully.
Don't forget that your face is reversed in the mirror.
R-Right...
The sad truth is that none of those faces are yours.
Not a single one of those faces belongs to you.
If you come to that realization, I'll fix your face.
That is my rule as Fairy Godmother.
If I think about it too much,
several of them seem like they could be mine...
But...
This is it! I'm sure of it!
I know my own face when I see it!
Are you certain?
Once you put it on, you'll know for sure.
N-No... This isn't my face...
My eyes are a bit more slanted than this...
Wh-Which one is it?
I-I can't really tell after all...
What's the matter? Hurry up and choose.
No, I refuse to decide.
Huh?
What are you saying?
Have you resigned yourself to live without a face?
I'm going to have Koichi choose for me.
Because... No matter whose face it is
or the luck it may carry...
...so long as Koichi is the one who chooses it,
I'll be happy with his decision.
I can live with that.
I won't have any regrets.
B-But that's not...!
I don't care.
Please choose for me, Koichi.
O-Okay...
It's this one.
I don't know why, but I feel like it's this one.
But if it isn't the right face...
This is my Stand, Echoes...
U-Umm... If I chose the wrong one,
use your Stand to remove Echoes' eyes.
I know she said she wouldn't regret it,
but knowing how Yukako is...
...she won't want me to look at her face if it isn't her own.
I've fallen in love with Yukako,
and I couldn't stand to see that happen.
That's why I think it's best if I don't see it if I'm wrong.
Koichi...
All right, Yukako...
Yes...
L-Look, Koichi!
It fits perfectly!
Koichi!
We did it, Yukako!
It's all because you chose my face for me, Koichi!
I never considered that he would be willing
to go blind to avoid seeing the wrong face.
I had to bend my rules as your
Fairy Godmother for it, but I fixed your face.
If I had taken the eyesight of someone who wasn't involved in this, my reputation as Fairy Godmother would have been tarnished.
Yukako, it seems you know a good man when you see one, at the very least.
Salon Cinderella remained open.
"Makeup that will help you find your one true love," indeed.
Episode 21
Kira Yoshi
kage
Wants a
Quiet
Life Part 1
kage
Quiet
Kira Yoshi
Wants a
Life Part 1
kage
Quiet