That Hazamada guy really didn't know nothin'
'bout that electro-freak who killed my big bro?
Yeah. He said they only ever talked by phone.
Josuke, ya just believed him like that? Didja torture him?
If Hazamada actually knew who that guy was,
he would have been killed by now.
Y-You're right... Just like my big bro...
Yeah. Since Hazamada is still alive,
it proves he doesn't know anything.
But Hazamada said something interesting earlier...
For some reason, Stand users are subconsciously drawn to each other, even if they've never met.
They call people who are destined to be married "soulmates," right?
It's like that.
You're bound to meet them eventually.
They could be an enemy, a friend,
the guy who accidentally stepped on your foot on the bus...
...or even someone living right next door.
There's no way to know.
Morioh's not a big place...
I dunno how many Stand users are in this town right now...
...but no matter how well they hide,
they'll eventually expose themselves.
That guy knows it'll happen to him eventually.
He wants you both gone!
Goddammit!
What a coward!
He shoulda attacked us already!
He hasn't attacked us yet because he's cautious.
When a guy like him attacks...
...it means he's sure he's gonna win.
Oh?
Hey, it's Koichi!
Why's he sitting there sipping on tea?
Hey, Ko-
Wha-
A-A girl?!
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 8:  Yamagishi Yukako Falls in Love Part 1
Koichi, was asking you to meet me here... umm...
...a nuisance?
Huh? No, it's no trouble at all...
I'm just wondering why we met here of all places.
Wow, so Koichi's with a girl...
We're in the same class!
That's Yamagishi Yukako!
All right! Let's get a better look!
I don't know if you wanted to see my notes or something,
but my grades aren't very good, and my handwriting is sloppy.
If you need money, I could maybe give you a thousand yen...
Or is this about switching weekly duties with me?
It's nothing like that...
Huh? It's not? Then what is it?
If this is about taking in a puppy or kitten...
...I can't since I already have my own dumb dog at home.
Koichi!
I'm just going to say it!
Koichi...
...I really like you a lot!
Huh?
What'd she say?!
U-Umm... Uh, umm... Wh-What did you just say?!
You're all I can think about lately, Koichi...
I was so scared to show you my true feelings...
...but if I hadn't, I don't know what I would have done!
It's fine if you don't like me...
...but I needed to be honest with you.
A-Am I hearing things,
or did she really just confess her feelings for me?!
Is this actually happening right now?!
Th-This is amazing!
Why'd she pick Koichi?
Ya gotta be kiddin' me! Come on!
I ain't never had nobody tell me that!
Get a grip, man!
But for real, she likes Koichi?
Koichi, you must already have a girlfriend...
Huh? I-I don't...
But... are you being serious right now?
I'm serious!
Koichi, I've noticed your face
looks much more defined lately!
You have such a confident and courageous demeanor.
But when you smile, your face becomes so cute!
Yeah, I can see that now.
My face looks defined too, don't it?!
You can tell a lot about a man by how his future looks.
And your future is shining bright!
Y-You shouldn't speak so highly of me...
You must hate girls like me who aren't cute, huh?
Huh? Not cute? That's not true at all!
Dammit, she is cute!
Just tell her already!
That jerk's got all the luck!
Do you hate me?
Huh? Uh, I don't hate you, but...
Then do you like me?
Huh? Hold on... It's just that, umm...
So you do hate me...
Huh? It's not that!
The thing is, you're asking me so suddenly and-
Which is it?! Do you love me?! Or don't you?!
Spit it out already!
I just poured my heart out to you!
And now I spilled my coffee! This is all your fault!
Oh, I'm so sorry! Sometimes I get worked up and I...
Anyway, we'll see each other again, right?
Y-Y'know... I feel like a balloon that just got all the air let out...
An' my jealousy went with it...
Y-Yeah...
Let's just pretend we didn't see this.
Yeah...
What happened to my cola?!
I-I-It has clumps of hair in it!
Stand users are drawn to each other, huh?
There's no way...
Chemistry Lab
Koichi, it's me!
Y-Yukako!
What are you doing?
Well, it's my turn to clean the lab today...
Fourth period was chemistry lab.
Koichi...
...I said some strange things to you yesterday.
Just forget it.
I get a bit worked up when I think too hard.
It's so embarrassing...
I need to start thinking with a clearer head...
Uh, s-sure...
It caught me off guard, but I didn't think much of it...
If it's okay with you, can we still be friends?
O-Of course! I'd love to be your friend!
Thank god!
I was up all night worrying about
what I would do if you hated me!
That's a bit excessive!
And since I want to completely make it up to you... Here.
I spent all night knitting this especially for you!
Thank god! It's perfect on you!
I knew your height and chest size,
but I wasn't so sure about your shoulder length.
I made you a good luck charm, too.
It will help you find undying love!
And to top it all off,
I prepared a delicious lunch for us to eat together!
I picked up the shrimp at a fish market this morning.
A regular store is no place to buy fresh food.
See this flounder meunière?
I lovingly picked out the bones one-by-one with tweezers.
Here. Say, "Ahh."
Ahh...
I know one thing for sure now...
Yamagishi Yukako is a really weird girl!
Ahh...
I can't accept this stuff!
If I eat this, it'll make her think I accepted all of it!
Ahh!
But if I don't, she's gonna be mad at me!
What am I gonna do?!
Hirose!
Why aren't you finished yet?
You need to throw away all this trash before class begins.
I-I'm saved!
R-Right! Right!
B-Better get this taken care of!
Oh, you're hopeless.
Let me help you.
I can carry half of it.
Huh? Th-That's okay, I'd feel bad about it...
Just give it to me!
I would be the one getting the blame for this since I'm the class rep.
I swear!
S-Sorry...
Hey, you.
Don't bother Koichi ever again.
Koichi? You mean Hirose Koichi?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I know your type.
You reek of a man-stealing whore.
Stealing?! What are you talking about?
Listen closely. If you ever go near my Koichi again...
...you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
Don't just walk away from me!
I'm trying to be nice about this, but...
...Hirose Koichi?!
I don't care for him at all!
You have no right to tell me what I can or can't do, you bitch!
Oww!
What was that?
What's her deal?
She's so messed up!
She actually likes Hirose?
Hmph! What a joke!
Wait until I tell the whole school!
Huh?
What is that?
I feel something hot... Something's wrong...
This is so strange...
It's getting really hot...
W-Water!
S-Someone! Someone! Wa-
Hey, Josuke...
Guess Yamagishi Yukako really was a Stand user.
She's got a Stand that makes her hair move.
Yeah. Even so, I don't think she'll attack Koichi, and it doesn't seem like she's an enemy.
By the way, Okuyasu, what are you gonna do about this girl's hair?
I can't restore anything that's been erased by The Hand.
That ain't nothin'. She'd be bald if it wasn't for me.
Sorry, but I sure as hell ain't no hairdresser!
E
Ech
Echo
Echoes
Echoes A
Echoes Ac
Echoes Act
Echoes Act 1
Hiro
Hirose
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: B
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Hirose Ko
Hirose Koichi
What am I gonna do?!
I just got this English test back...
I'm so worried about this thing with Yukako,
I can't concentrate on anything else...
Even stupid ol' me got a better score!
Only thirty-two points, though...
Honestly, I was really happy
about all the attention I was getting at first.
I've never had a girl tell me she likes me before...
I feel ya! I really feel for ya! It sure as shit ain't easy!
But still, it's my fault for not being
direct with her and letting it come to this...
I need to tell her straight-up that I don't like her back!
Otherwise, she'll never leave me alone!
That's a pretty bad idea, Koichi.
If you say that, you'll just fan the flames
of Yukako's passionate personality even harder.
She'll get really upset.
Y-You think so?
Absolutely! Listen up...
We can't focus on convincing Yamagishi Yukako not to abuse her hair Stand right now.
We need to figure out how to divert her attention away from you so she'll spare you.
But how?
No matter how much she likes you right now...
...if she gets it in her head that you're a charmless, no-good, boring guy...
...then everything will work itself out, right?
Y-Yeah...
You just need to act that way in front of her on purpose!
Yeah! I get it! That's fuckin' genius!
You're so smart, Josuke!
Hehe, thanks!
Though that doesn't mean much coming from you...
What do I have to do to make Yukako think I'm no good?
Well, most girls don't like guys who are gross or too attached to their mom, right?
I-I can't have her think that!
That could make her jealous and put my mom in danger!
Guess you're gonna hafta stink it up, then!
No more soap for you!
Huh?!
Yeah, and stop brushing your teeth and changing your underwear!
How 'bout we put lice an' spiders an' shit in your hair?
Smelly socks will definitely repulse her!
Make sure ya fart all around her, too!
Yeah, she'll definitely hate that!
Quit joking around! This is serious!
I'm bein' serious too, man!
Ya gotta start snottin' and droolin' everywhere!
Huh?!
If you don't wanna do all this,
then you need to become a guy with a bleak future.
She has to completely give up on you.
We'll help you get through this. Okay?
Hirose Koichi is really a thief? I can't believe it!
And you're telling me he shoplifts, too? What an asshole!
Yeah! Koichi said it himself!
He was actin' all proud an' stuff!
You know, Koichi never keeps his promises, too.
I lent him some money, and he totally stiffed me!
I hear he cheats on his tests an' steals girls' panties!
He ain't got no future! He's the self-destructive type!
I'm never hanging out with him again!
Same here!
Geez, she's crazy intense...
Assuming Koichi tells her he did all that stuff by tomorrow...
...she should stop bothering him.
Josuke, Okuyasu...
I hope you guys did a good job convincing her...
I really hope she finally gives up on me...
What is that?
My eyes are closed... Is this a dream?
A woman?
I-It's Yukako!
I can't believe this!
She's even appearing in my dreams...
I can't catch a break anywhere!
Koichi, it seems to me like
your friends don't think too highly of you.
But it's okay! You have me, now.
I'll show you proper discipline and turn you into the perfect man!
I see something in you I've never seen in any other man.
I want to make sure you live up to your potential.
J-Josuke! This completely backfired!
Where am I?
Koichi, are you hungry?
Breakfast is just about ready!
O-Okay...
I can't forget she has that hair Stand...
I'll just have to wait for my chance to escape!
It's my only hope!
Th-There's something I wanted to ask you...
What is it?
Your hair last night... What was that?
Were you scared?
I'm not surprised. Anyone who suddenly saw that would be.
Around February of this year...
...someone struck me with an arrow through my chest.
Or not... I may have dreamt it up.
When I woke up,
my wound was completely healed, and I had that ability.
Nijimura Keicho!
D-Do you know anyone else who can do something like that?
I don't.
She doesn't realize I'm a Stand user!
Now, have a seat. You're a growing boy, after all!
If you don't receive proper nourishment...
...you'll never grow into a perfect man for me!
I-I'll just play along with her for now...
This looks amazing! I can't wait to dig in!
You can't eat yet, Koichi!
You got a sixteen on your English exam!
Even if a man is more than just his brains, this is unacceptable.
I've decided to have you study while you eat.
Okay?
I've prepared some questions for you.
You will answer them by choosing box A, B, or C,
then eat whatever is inside the one you chose.
H-Hold on a second...
You have no choice in the matter!
While living in this house,
everything we do together will be for your betterment!
Do you understand now?
Here's the first question.
Prince often sings the lyric "funky music."
What is the closest phrase to this in Japanese?
A: Passionate music.
B: Primal music.
C: Fantasy music.
I-I'll be in big trouble if I get this wrong...
B-But I have no idea what the right answer is!
I have a feeling it's A, but B and C also sound right...
Whatever, I'll just pick one!
I think it's... B...
You're right!
I'm so relieved! This box contains boiled eggs!
I'll peel them for you. Do you want them salted?
By the way, if you had chosen box A,
I would have made you eat this eraser!
Huh?!
Box C contained soap!
Wh-What?!
Answer this next one right, and you'll get bacon and eggs. Good luck!
Question:  How is the word "contrast" written in Japanese?
Note: The second character for each answer is different.
A: Taisho.
B: Taisho.
C: Taisho.
Sh-She's serious...
If I choose the wrong box,
she'll definitely make me eat whatever's inside it!
Come now, hurry up and answer!
Your food is getting cold.
U-Umm, uh...
What am I gonna do? This is ridiculous!
I-I think it's C...
Koichi, you chose your answer from looking at
the expression on my face, didn't you?
Huh?!
So the rumors about you
thieving and shoplifting and cheating are true!
As punishment, you have to eat both A and B now!
A is English vocabulary corn flakes.
B is asparagus wrapped in pages from an English dictionary.
I'm going to make sure you learn while you eat!
Here!
Open your mouth! I'll feed it to you.
What's the matter? Eat it!
I'm done playing around!
You think I'm gonna put up with this? I can't take it anymore!
I'm getting out of here!
I'm being pulled! By my scalp!
Th-There's moving hair mixed in with my own!
That's right.
I planted a few hundred of my own hairs into your scalp.
Koichi...
...you may come to hate me for all of this...
...but once you leave this house, you'll see a much better man in the mirror, and you'll have me to thank for it.
Soon you'll realize you were in desperate need
of a woman like me in your life.
You won't know how you lived before you met Yamagishi Yukako.
And just so you're aware,
until you finish eating the food on plates A and B...
...you won't be getting the next dish.
This place is the vacation home of some company's president.
No one will come here until summer.
S-Summer?!
Regardless, even if someone does come here...
...our love is unbreakable.
S-Somebody help me!
Episode 9
Yamagishi
Yukako Falls in
Love
Part 2
Yu
Love
Yamagishi
kako Falls in
Part 2
Yu
Love