July 15th (Thursday) 8:30 PM
This is bad... This is horrifically bad!
I must inform Yoshikage at once!
Reimi!
Did you take these photos, Rohan?
I did.
What's wrong with the one you marked here?
You circled this little boy holding a video camera.
Oh, him...
I didn't have a reason, really...
He appeared to be investigating like I was,
which caught my attention.
But... didn't you notice this boy, Kawajiri Hayato,
has the same surname as this man?
Huh? Really?
Look!
Note: Kawajiri Hayato, Kawajiri Kosaku
It's the same.
This is your research, isn't it?
Their surnames really do match...
At this rate, Kishibe Rohan will find my Yoshikage!
July 15th (Thursday) 8:48 PM
Hayato? Hayato!
I swear...
Hayato, answer me when I call you!
Don't ignore me!
D-Darling!
I thought Hayato was bathing right now.
Just look at the mess Hayato left!
He left his clothes all over the hallway
as if they exploded off his body.
I wish he would stop being such a slob
and listen to me like he listens to you.
He won't even answer me when I call him...
He must be wearing headphones
and reading his comic books again.
Oh, darling! Your fingers are bleeding!
What happened?
We need to bandage that up!
L-Let me do it...
Let me put... the bandage on myself...
Okay...
My fingers just got caught in the door. That's all.
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
July 15th (Thursday) 8:50 PM
Kawajiri Hayato?
You're telling me this grade-school kid
has something to do with Kira Yoshikage?
Episode 35:  Another One Bites the Dust Part 1
We're not 100% sure yet...
...but Mr. Rohan said something seemed off about him.
Yeah, something's definitely going on
for this kid to be secretly filming his dad.
Sometime tomorrow morning, a few of us plan on
meeting up and checking out Kawajiri Hayato's house.
I think Mr. Rohan already found his address.
Rohan sure is a fast-acting son of a bitch.
Sounds like a plan.
I'll ask Okuyasu to come along with me, okay?
Can't forget about Mr. Jotaro, too.
I'll talk to Mr. Jotaro.
See you tomorrow!
We'll meet at 8:30 AM at the intersection with the huge Pepsi sign.
Got it.
8:30 AM, huh? I'm gonna be late for school...
But if we talk to this kid, maybe we can figure something out.
Are you okay?
You're acting a bit strange, darling...
You look so pale.
I told you, it's fine.
My fingers just got caught in the door.
I'm pale from the shock.
Anyway, could you make me some tea?
I'll go downstairs in a bit.
Of course!
This may seem random,
but lately I've felt like you became invincible somehow.
I'll get to making that tea now.
If anything happens to me, your secret is gonna get out!
You better not hurt Mama or me!
You don't have a say in this!
You have to listen to what I say! Got it?!
You naïve brat!
Did you really think I would listen to the words of a brat like you?
I can't believe you actually rid yourself of Hayato...
Such a foolish mistake!
I'm trying to think of what options I have!
There's nothing for you to think about!
I see you made his death appear to be an accident,
but the timing of this is very bad.
Kishibe Rohan is starting to investigate Kawajiri Hayato!
They still don't know you became Kawajiri Kosaku,
but they plan on coming to this house tomorrow.
You can't afford to stay here any longer!
Please stop talking! I need to think!
Ever since you were a little boy, you've bitten your nails nonstop whenever you found yourself in a helpless situation.
You poor boy.
I can't imagine the despair you must be feeling right now.
You've run out of options!
Your only choice is to flee this town, Yoshikage!
You can flee undiscovered if you leave tonight!
Are you seriously suggesting I abandon Morioh?
You should know by now that I refuse to live my life in fear,
fleeing from those who endlessly pursue me!
I won't ever leave this town!
What?!
The arrow acted of its own accord!
That wasn't me!
I didn't even touch it!
Th-The arrow...
Y-Yoshikage!
Hayato! Hayato?!
July 16th (Friday) 7:30 AM
Do you plan on sleeping the day away, Hayato?
Hurry and get u-
Well look at you, already wide awake! I'm in shock.
Hayato, breakfast is ready.
Honestly, why can't you just answer me for once?
I didn't sleep well last night...
He... He found out that I saw him kill someone...
Anyway, I made sure that he won't
lay a finger on Mama or me, but...
What should I do now?
I-I don't understand... Yoshikage, what happened?
You've been acting strange since last night!
Listen to me, Yoshikage!
Kishibe Rohan is starting to investigate Kawajiri Hayato!
They plan on coming to this house tomorrow!
That doesn't concern me.
B-But, Yoshikage!
Killer Queen has acquired a third ability.
I... I don't understand...
What has happened to make you act so carefree?
Beef tongue stewed in miso.
Huh?! You're kidding! We're already on air?
Uh, well... It is currently 7:55,
so here's today's weather for the prefecture.
Today is looking to be bright and sunny...
Hayato! Hey, Hayato! Answer the phone!
After that bath last night, he changed!
Wh-What changed for him since last night?
Hayato! I just asked you to answer the phone!
My precious tea set!
This is your fault!
Why do you always ignore me?!
Fine then! I'm nothing but a huge nag to you, aren't I?
Do whatever the hell you want!
Now, now. Let's not fight first thing in the morning.
If you can't fix it, I'll buy you another one.
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
No, it's not.
They had the wrong number.
Hayato is just going through a phase
where he doesn't feel like talking much.
We're family, so it's important that we get along.
Important, indeed.
Anyway, I need to get to work.
Would you like a goodbye kiss first?
Huh?
I'll be home soon.
H-He left!
No, I'm right here.
Why don't you and I walk part of the way together?
I've been going back and forth between
feeling despair and relief lately.
After all I've been through for the last several months,
my life feels like an emotional roller coaster.
But from now on, I'll always feel at ease.
After you cornered me last night, I grew stronger.
I'm still impressed with how strong-willed you are.
To think that you would turn around
and threaten me, Kira Yoshikage...
K-Kira Yoshikage?
Did I just let that slip?
A-Are you gonna kill me after all?!
Kill you?
Because you found out my secret?
There's no need for that. I'm stronger now.
It doesn't matter where you go or what you try to do,
because no one can rival me.
I have no interest in you anymore.
If I were to have killed you...
...I would have done so last night.
We're going to get along and
live happily together from now on.
Relax. Just pretend we're family.
Well, Papa has to head to the station.
Study hard and do your best, Hayato.
Rival... He said nobody can rival him...
That must mean there are other people with abilities like his.
But why was he acting so confident and creepy?
If he's unrivaled, does that mean he gained a new ability?
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
You're...
...Kawajiri Hayato...
...aren't you?
Ki
Kill
Killer
Killer Qu
Killer Que
Killer Quee
Killer Queen
Kawa
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: A
Kawajiri
Kawajiri Ko
Kawajiri Kosaku
July 16th (Friday) 8:24 AM
I've been waiting for you.
My name is Kishibe Rohan.
I've been meaning to ask you something
to satisfy my curiosity.
It's about this photo.
This is you, correct?
Were you filming your father in the corner there?
Wait!
What's... happening...?
That was a bit sudden, but...
Reading Kawajiri Hayato's memories will be faster than attempting to force the answers out of him.
His answers will be honest this way, too.
Note: [WARNING] Do not read any further.
Huh? What's the meaning of this?
Heaven's Door should have turned this boy's memories into a book without any falsehoods.
Yet somehow... there's a warning?
Note: [WARNING] Do not read any further.
What on earth is this?
Is this warning something he experienced?
I had originally intended to only
read through the memories I needed...
...but this warning has piqued my interest.
Note: [WARNING] Do not read any further.
Do not read any further?
Who could this warning be meant for?
Note: An old man walked by with his fly down.
Note: He sneezed and said, "Dammit."
Note: Two women laughed at him.
Wh-What is this?
I'm more confused than I was before!
What does it mean?
Dammit!
J-Just who is this boy?
Note: It rained.
Damn, the weather forecast didn't say it would rain!
Note: At 8:27 AM, lightning struck above the Pepsi sign.
8:27 AM...
Wh-What is going on with Kawajiri Hayato?
Why has he experienced future events?
Could he be a Stand user?!
No... This is too strange even for a Stand ability.
My Heaven's Door is only capable of reading events which a person has personally experienced.
The answer must be written within him somewhere.
Note: My Papa isn't my Papa.
Note: He blew up a man and a woman in an apartment in Jozenji.
Note: He's a murderer. I know who he is. He has inhuman abilities.
Note: My Papa's name is Kira Yoshikage.
Kira...
I-I did it!
This boy had the answer!
I finally know who he is!
Kira Yoshikage is Kawajiri Kosaku!
He disguised himself as this boy's father!
Kishi
then
mur
der
ed.
Kishibe Rohan was then murdered?
"Because Kira had grown stronger...
...he murdered him."
Killer Queen Tertiary Bomb: Bites the Dust!
Heaven's Door!
It's too late, Kishibe Rohan!
Killer Queen has entered your eye!
This is what you now see!
The switch for Killer Queen's tertiary bomb...
...has already been activated!
Killer Queen's third ability...
...is to blow up anyone who attempts to come after me!
It will act upon anyone who tries to learn information about me through Hayato!
Note: Kishibe Rohan was then murdered.
Because Kira had grown stronger, he murdered him.
It will also activate if Hayato reveals my identity to anyone!
Even if he wrote down my name,
it would activate immediately.
Simply put, I've implanted a bomb inside of Hayato!
I-I just remembered...
I promised to meet Koichi and the others here at 8:30 AM...
Finally... I've figured out Kira Yoshikage's new identity...
Koichi is coming... I have to tell him...
I... I finally... found him...
Kira Yoshikage is Kawajiri Kosaku...!
I found him with my Heaven's Door!
I have to tell...
...Koichi...
And now...
...witness the power of Killer Queen's third ability!
K-Koichi!
I... I was dreaming?
I slept horribly last night...
I kept having weird dreams all night...
Hayato!
Do you plan on sleeping the day away, Hayato?
Hurry and get u-
Well look at you, already wide awake!
I'm in shock.
Hayato, breakfast is ready.
Honestly, why don't you ever answer me?
D-Didn't this...?
Huh?! You're kidding! We're already on air?
Th-The morning news on TV!
Hayato! Hey, Hayato! Answer the phone!
Th-This isn't a dream!
Those dreams I had last night were real!
Th-This is the same morning!
It's repeating...
I'm repeating the same morning!
Kira Yoshikage... His name is Kira Yoshikage!
He's doing all of this!
He used his unrivaled ability to plant something inside of me!
Hayato! I just asked you to answer the phone!
That's right!
Ouch...
You caught that almost as if you knew it was going to fall...
If you can hear me, the least you could do is answer!
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
Huh? No, it's not.
It seems like I'm the only person in the world who realizes that this morning is repeating!
It's almost as if you knew that would happen, huh?
You seem to have blown someone up and come back, Hayato.
No, really. I have no idea what you did to trigger it.
I call this ability Killer Queen: Bites the Dust.
It automatically protects me...
...from inside of you, Hayato.
Did you know I already killed you once last night?
As if to remedy the despair I felt
from the hopeless situation I was in...
...I gained this brand new ability.
By using this ability on you, time went back by an hour...
...and my act of murdering you disappeared.
At the same time, you became a bomb to protect me.
You told someone of me,
activated the bomb, then came back here.
Who did you blow up, hmm?  I'd love to know.
Who did you kill?
I-I didn't tell anyone...
I see! Then someone must have been prying you for questions.
Most likely Kishibe Rohan.
Even if you have no intention of telling anyone,
as soon as someone asks you about me, Bites the Dust will activate.
It will blow you up and cause you to return here.
The very fact that Kishibe Rohan
encountered you has disappeared!
That is Killer Queen: Bites the Dust!
You'll never be able to tell a soul about it!
And nobody will ever be able to get answers out of you!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 36
An
other One
Bi
tes the Dust Part 2
An
Bi
other One
tes the Dust Part 2
An
Bi