This arrow is extremely valuable. It's the only one in existence.
Which is why my current objective is so important.
Retrieve it at any cost.
Don't even think about pulling that arrow out!
He'll bleed to death!
Since my little brother is a complete idiot, I'll have to kill you myself.
I can't let anything happen to this arrow.
It would be very unfortunate if
the old lady next door happened to see it.
I'm very meticulous by nature, so I want to
make sure the arrow is properly taken care of.
Once you've finished listening to a CD, you take care of it
by putting it in its case before listening to the next one, right?
That's how everyone does it.
Myself included.
Oh? You've decided to come inside my house?
No shit I have!
I wouldn't be able to kick your ass and heal Koichi if I didn't!
Big bro! I ain't through with 'im!
Don't attack 'im just yet!
Attack?
Me and you ain't fuckin' finished, ya hear me?!
There's something coming...
...from that dark spot in the ceiling!
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 4:  The Nijimura Brothers Part 2
Okuyasu...
Your stupidity never ceases to amaze me.
If you hadn't come staggering in here,
my Bad Company would have defeated Josuke for sure.
And worst of all, you got caught in the crossfire.
Big bro...
The Hand is a terrifying Stand,
but you're completely incompetent.
I've been telling you since you were a kid that
incompetent imbeciles drag down everyone around them, haven't I?
How many times do I have to tell you that only those
who grow from their experiences have a right to live?
What's with his injuries?
What kind of attack wounds someone like that?
Anyway, there's definitely something weird happening here.
Little brother...
You only have yourself to blame for dying like this!
It made a bunch of holes again!
What is he attacking me with?
Crazy Diamond!
Are you trying to attack your brother, too?!
Higashikata Josuke...
I doubt he's going to abandon this "Koichi" brat.
I'm sure he'll make his way back in.
I have to kill him, no matter what...
Anyone who defies the will of the arrow...
...deserves to be killed without mercy!
Talk to me; what kind of Stand does your big bro have?
What kind of Stand is it?!
I'll treat your wounds if you tell me.
Ya ain't... gettin' nothin' outta me...
...s-stupid...
Didn't think so.
In that case, you've given me no choice!
I'm going back inside, so you better stay out of my way, Okuyasu.
Koichi doesn't have much time left!
His Stand was attacking me from somewhere in the dark...
I'm taking a big risk by going back in here...
Still... As long as I stay on my toes, I'll be fine.
Hey, hold up!
Huh?
Why, Josuke? Why'dja help me?
Shut up. I'll tell you later.
Who says I ain't gonna attack ya?! We ain't friends or nothin'!
Is that what you want?
Just gimme an answer! Why'dja help me?
I ain't too bright, so ya better tell me real quick!
I see your hand bleedin'!
Ya get that from pullin' me outside or what?
Why wouldja go through that t'save a guy like me?
It was because of one nagging thought in my head.
"Letting him die would be senseless."
That's the only reason.
Koichi...
His trail of blood is leading upstairs.
I ain't through with you, Josuke!
Wh-What's your deal?!
I'm begging you, just let me save Koichi!
Why?!
Why ain'tcha usin' your Stand t'heal yourself?
Alls ya gotta do is the same thing ya did t'my face!
I can't heal my own wounds with Crazy Diamond.
In reality, things are never that easy.
But more importantly...
...I have no way of healing the dead, either.
I need you to realize something, Okuyasu.
If Koichi dies, I can't promise that I won't hurt your big bro.
Don't hold it against me.
It's your big bro's fault for starting this.
Got it? If you do, stay outside.
Koichi!
Damn... This is definitely a trap.
He's gonna attack me from somewhere out of sight
as soon as I get close to Koichi...
Still...
Even if it's a trap, I have no choice but to try!
Koichi could only have seconds to live!
What?!
Okuyasu, you asshole!
Josuke!
Koichi just...
Since I ain't so bright, I listen t'my heart.
Just this once, I'm repayin' ya for helpin' me.
But that's all I'm doin'.
I ain't gonna help my big bro, an' I ain't helpin' you again, neither.
I'm done here.
You're a great guy, Okuyasu.
Yo! You were in pretty great danger, Koichi.
I'm glad you finally came to.
How many fingers am I holding up?
Five...
I-I remember getting my head trapped in that gate...
...and then, uh...
Wh-Where are we?
We're still in the same bad situation we were in earlier, Koichi.
My plan is for us to go back downstairs and make a run for the door.
I just hope Okuyasu's big bro won't get in our way...
Something's up there...
There's something moving in the dark near the ceiling...
What was that?
Something just scurried by!
Josuke, what's going on?
Koichi, I know you have no idea what's going on right now...
...but until we're out of this,
you need to stop asking questions and stay close to me.
At first I felt nervous since I couldn't see what was attacking me...
...but now that I have, I'm relieved.
It just looks like a tiny person.
I'll end this in a flash with Crazy Diamond
once the little bastard shows himself again!
Gotcha!
What the hell? There's more of them!
And those uniforms...
Wh-What's...?!
There's a bunch of things that like
toy soldiers falling from the ceiling...
Is this Okuyasu's big bro's Stand?
O-Ouch!
You assholes!
Dorararara!
Seems like attacking just a few of them at a time isn't gonna do very much...
The wounds they inflict are tiny,
but their combined firepower is no joke...
I'm gonna get seriously messed up
if I try to fight these things by myself...
My stupid little brother, Okuyasu,
really messed up my plans by saving that brat...
Still, you'll never make it out of this house...
...and you'll never escape this battlefield
controlled by my Stand, Bad Company, in one piece!
B
Ba
Bad
Bad C
Bad Co
Bad Com
Bad Compa
Bad Compan
Bad Company
Niji
Nijimura
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Nijimura Kei
Nijimura Keicho
Bad Company?
Josuke, wh-what's...?
No time for questions!
I know you're confused, but be quiet and stand back!
We're in deep shit!
Company, halt!
Ready, aim...
...fire!
Left face!
Fire!
I knew it! Their combined power is enough
to blow off our limbs if they land a direct hit!
Lucky! There's windows up here!
Koichi, I know we're on the second floor,
but we have to break through those windows and jump outside!
Guess I spoke too soon...
Great... He has helicopters, too?
They look just like American Apache helicopters!
Look out! He has a tank!
Dora!
Dorararara!
I can't believe he has tanks, too...
Koichi, be care-
What?
Wh-What did you just say, Koichi?
You can see them?
These soldiers, tanks, and helicopters...
You can see them?!
Yeah! I don't know why, but I can see them...
Did getting shot by that arrow
somehow turn you into a Stand user?
Oh? Are you telling me pipsqueak here...
...obtained himself a Stand ability?
So that's where you were, Okuyasu's big bro.
You've got a lot of nerve
to put yourself out in the open like this!
Dora!
My Stand, Bad Company, has an impenetrable defense.
It's my personal army which never takes prisoners.
I can tell you're growing desperate to defeat me, but...
...your Crazy Diamond's attacks don't stand a chance of making it past my Company's defenses!
Just look at them! Notice how perfect their formation is?
Company, maintain battle formation! At ease!
My chest swells with pride
seeing them hold such a perfect formation!
Though it's aggravating that their perfect formation is a bit off
on account of you killing a few of them earlier.
You really are meticulous, huh?
You exposed yourself just to explain that?
No, the reason I showed you where I am...
...is so that I could watch you, brat!
M-Me?
Damn right.
Koichi, was it?
I guess you really did have the potential to obtain a Stand.
I want you to call out your Stand, then show me what it can do.
It may have just the ability I've been looking for!
If it does what I need, I'll let you live!
B-But...
The ability you've been looking for?
Just what kind of ability do you need?
You're in no position to be asking fucking questions here, Josuke!
I haven't changed my mind about killing you!
Be thankful you get to live even a little bit longer!
Great...
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
Call out your Stand, brat!
S-Stand? I still have no idea what's going on...
What? Is this your first time? No problem!
In that case, Josuke, show him how to call out his Stand!
Huh?
Your Crazy Diamond has an effective range of less than a meter.
If this pipsqueak's ability is able to compensate for that...
...it could allow you to escape my Company!
True. Would be a nice break
if he had a Stand that could beat yours.
Look, calling out your Stand is easy, Koichi.
All you gotta do is search inside yourself
for an overwhelming feeling to fight or protect something.
Huh?
The rest will come naturally.
A unique Stand should come from your spirit.
Y-You have to be kidding me!
I can't figure out how to do it this fast!
You can't figure it out?
Then I'll make you understand by brute force!
Green Beret, get him!
What?!
That's...
Hey, Koichi... Try moving it!
M-Move what?
Your Stand!
Stand?
I-I made this appear?!
Now what's it supposed to do?
What kind of abilities could an egg-thing even have?
Abilities? I hate to break it to you, but it won't do anything!
This is it!
What? That's it?!
His Stand...
Enough! That's all I needed to see!
Company, assume battle position!
Koichi, call back your Stand!
You'll get hurt if they attack it!
Call it back? How am I supposed to do that?!
Fire at will!
Dorara!
Dorararara!
J-Josuke!
Excellent. Now Koichi and Josuke are separated.
That crack in the egg...
The brat hasn't realized it yet,
but he may have something special on his hands.
I just need to focus on killing Josuke!
Oww...
Okuyasu's big bro...
...if you're gonna attack me with
enough force to bring your house down...
...then I'll do the same!
This is gonna be great!
Higashikata Josuke...
Is it true that you fly into an unstoppable rage
when someone insults your hair?
Why don't you see for yourself?
Nah, I won't do that.
I'll do you one better and promise to
blow off the very head your hair rests on!
First, my Bad Company will take out your leg.
That will stop you from running away.
Then, I'll make it blow your arm off.
That will stop you from protecting yourself.
And finally, I'll have it blast your brains across the wall,
taking your hair along with it!
I see. Pretty solid plan you got going there...
...if you ignore the fact that it's totally impossible!
I'm very meticulous, you see.
I always do things in the proper order.
That's why I made it a promise.
He's wide open...
I just need to make that Stand-thing appear again...
Even though it's just some egg-like thing, maybe I can have it ram into him...
Maybe I really can beat him!
I-I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna be brave!
I'm gonna beat him!
I'm very intrigued by your Stand...
...which is why I won't kill you just yet!
Asshole!
Company, charge!
Dorararara!
Just like Moses parted the Red Sea
and safely walked across the sea floor...
...I'm gonna make my way through your army and kick your ass!
Idiot! Everything is going exactly as planned, Higashikata Josuke!
A-A landmine?!
There goes your leg!
Now, Apaches! Fire missiles at target!
Dora!
My arm!
First your leg, and now your arm!
Nothing feels better than carrying out a successful plan!
Let's see if you can survive a barrage of every missile, shell,
and round my Bad Company has with that injured arm of yours!
You've lost this war, Higashikata Josuke!
Company!
Prepare to fire at once!
What do you think you're doing, Higashikata Josuke?
Are you surrendering?
You want me to let you go?
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Company, open fire!
I've already carried out my plan.
What?!
The missiles that just attacked Josuke's arm...
Did you already forget?
My Crazy Diamond can restore damaged objects.
If you forgot already, I recommend writing it down.
Real meticulously.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 5
The
Nijimura Brothers Part 3
Niji
mura Brothers Part 3