That old hag in Egypt, Enya,
told me to shoot the arrow at whomever it chooses.
They will become my allies!
Those struck by the arrow will have a special ability brought out from deep within their hearts.
I believe she referred to these abilities as Stands.
Kujo Jotaro and the others...
If there really are so many people in Morioh trying to stop my Yoshikage, then I need to create more Stand users who will ally with me!
Show me, arrow! Whom do you choose?
Choose! Choose someone!
A telephone pole?
Why would you choose a-
Could it be? You've chosen that child?
Do you mean to tell me that child will be my ally?
V-Very well!
All I have to do is strike that child?!
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 26:  Rock, Paper, Scissors Kid is Coming!
Well, if it isn't the famous comics artist, Kishibe Rohan!
Good morning, Mr. Joestar.
What are you taking photos of?
Any unsuspecting businessmen I happen to see walking around.
Considering Kira Yoshikage switched places with someone at Salon Cinderella...
...it's only natural that he would begin going to that person's place of work.
Going to work...
Since we know he's a man between the age of twenty-five and thirty-five, and that he's 175 centimeters tall...
...we can narrow down the suspects quite significantly.
I see...
But how do you know for sure that
he comes through this station?
He may take a car to work.
Possibly.
However, only his face was changed.
I don't believe he fully became someone else.
I suspect his new family has already noticed some bizarre behavior from him.
I fear that if this family discovers
Kira's true identity, he'll dispose of them.
I don't condone vigilante justice,
but Kira must be found before that happens.
Hey, Mister!
Mister, ya wanna play Rock, Paper, Scissors with me?
Rock, Paper...!
C'mon, it's not gonna kill ya!
What's up with him?
Rock, Paper...!
Every station seems to have an annoying person like this.
Regardless, if you find any clues,
please tell me right away, Mr. Joestar.
Just promise me you won't get into
any dangerous situations by yourself.
Hey, Mister! You're that comic-making guy, right?
Wasn't your series just on break?
I read Shonen Jump every week!
Note: Shonen Jump is the weekly comics magazine Diamond is Unbreakable was printed in.
So, c'mon!
Can'tcha play a game of Rock, Paper, Scissors with me?
What is your problem?! Scram!
I just wanna play Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Please? Pretty please?!
What's with this kid?
He has a gaping hole in his cheek!
I-It's really deep...
C'mon, I said please! Please?!
Does it go all the way into his mouth?
Don't take it personally if ya lose!
We'll play again if we tie!
Shoot too late and ya lose!
Got it? Ready, and...!
Rock, Paper...!
What an oddly persistent brat...
Could he be a Stand user?
Ready, and...! Rock, Paper...!
Heaven's Door!
Let's see...
His name is Oyanagi Ken, age eleven.
I don't see any information concerning Stands...
The hole in his cheek came from falling off a telephone pole...
Note: Loves Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Wants to play real bad. Plays Scissors first.
I guess this kid just really wants to play Rock, Paper, Scissors...
It's absurd, but...
Excuse me, sirs? Are you getting in or not?
Can you wait another thirty seconds?
Let's do this!
I'll play. That's what you want, right?
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Later, kid!
I... I lost...
I've done enough work for today.
Yo, Mr. Rohan!
You done working already?
Why don't you come sit and hang with us?
It's that shit stain, Josuke,
with his idiotic friend, Okuyasu...
...and that moody bitch, Yukako.
All of whom I have nothing in common with.
Sorry, but my work isn't done.
Some other time, perhaps.
Sure...
It's you! What are you doing? You took my seat!
Ya din't sid down yet, did ya?
Nobuhee wus sittin' here, so I tuk the sphot.
Whoopsie!
What is your deal? You're following me!
Let's play Rock, Paper, Scissors to decide who gets the seat! 'Kay?
Again?!
No! I sat here first!
This seat is mine!
Sir...
Hold on...
Mr. Rohan, let him have the seat!
He's just a little kid!
You made him cry!
Try being the bigger person.
Can't you just sit next to him?
Shut up! That's enough from all of you!
Fine! Let's play!
You want to play Rock, Paper, Scissors, right?
That's the spirit!
H-Here we go!
Rock, Paper...
...Scissors!
Oh? Y-Yes! I won!
How do you like that?
I've never felt so happy to win a game of
Rock, Paper, Scissors in all my life!
What a jerk...
Sorry, but there's no better feeling than besting a whiny brat!
D-Darn it!
This is good reference material.
Who knew such a book would be sold here in Morioh?
7500 yen, huh?
Do I have enough with me?
'Scuse me, can I have this book?
You little brat!
Wanna play Rock, Paper, Scissors for it?
Fine!
Here we go! Rock, Paper...
Rock!
Quit bothering me!
I won. See?
I finally beat you!
One win, two losses!
What's going on here?
Wh-
Wh-What?!
Th-That's impossible! The hole...!
Could this child be a Stand user?
What?!
S-So cool!
I didn't think something so cool would come out!
I can feel a rush of pure energy flowing into me!
I feel a lot better now!
H-Heaven's Door!
Turn this kid into a book!
Note: I cannot attack Kishibe Rohan.
This kid...
He's showing clear signs of possessing a Stand.
Is it possible that he's becoming a Stand user?
Hmph. "I wanna beat Rohan at Rock, Paper, Scissors," huh?
"Rock, Paper, Scissors isn't a game of chance.
It's a test of mental strength.
Beating Rohan at Rock, Paper, Scissors
is the same as mentally defeating him.
Kishibe Rohan is just twenty years old,
and he's already facing the world all by himself.
Lots of people look up to him because of his work.
If I beat someone like him who
a lot of people look up to, I'll be better than them.
I wanna become someone people look up to, just like Rohan."
This kid really is becoming a Stand user!
The arrow must have struck him just recently!
Ability... "Takes the energy of opponents defeated at Rock, Paper, Scissors.
However, it must be best of five.
If three wins are not achieved, nothing is taken."
Best of five?
Note: I cannot attack Kishibe Rohan.
Note: I ... attack Kishibe Rohan.
Note: I can attack Kishibe Rohan.
Wh-What?
Neato! So this ability is called a Stand?
Maybe you thought you won,
but I already absorbed a third of your Stand!
I-Its right arm is missing!
I can move one third of Heaven's Door now!
I won't let you read my mind again!
Kid...
If I win two more times, your ability is mine!
You insufferable brat! Who do you think you are?!
Wasn't very smart of you to hit me with that Rock earlier!
Consider it payback, you jerk!
It looks like the only way I'll be able to
get Heaven's Door's arm back...
...is to beat this kid at Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Let's go!
Good!
5 Matches
Hea
Heave
Heaven
Heaven'
Heaven's
Heaven's Do
Heaven's Doo
Heaven's Door
Kishi
Power: D
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Kishibe
Kishibe Ro
Kishibe Rohan
Do you understand the weight of this situation?
You can't afford another loss.
Has it dawned on you that I have you cornered?
Now that I know you're a Stand user, I won't hold back!
Once you've returned my right arm to me,
I'm going to defeat you for good!
Understand?
You trying to pressure me?
Now, let's do this!
No, we can't start yet.
Since I just beat ya using Paper, I'd normally go with
Rock or Scissors next, but that's something a dumb kid would do.
But the wise Mr. Rohan will see right through that, so I was thinking I'd go with Paper again.
All right, I got it!
Here we go!
Rock, Paper...
...Scissors!
What?!
I did it! I mentally defeated Mr. Rohan and won with Paper!
Ken
Rohan
5 Matches
Now it's two wins to two losses!
And since I won...
I took your lower half.
Wanna go sit on that bench over there to get some rest?
No, I'm fine.
In the event of victory,
it's appropriate to be looking down on your opponent.
I've got two wins and two losses,
so it could go either way at this point.
But y'know, I have a good feeling I'm not gonna lose.
I won twice after losing twice in a row...
You're in the opposite situation.
You lost twice in a row!
You're playing this match with your luck on the decline!
Fantastic!
No wonder the arrow chose this kid!
If this kid is able to obtain Kishibe Rohan's ability to read minds, we'll be invincible!
His power will greatly benefit my Yoshikage!
Kid...
...you seem to have finally learned
how to pressure your opponent.
It's a fact that you just lost twice in a row!
It's a fact, huh? You're right.
In that case, let me lay down a fact of my own for you.
During our next match, you will definitely not use Paper.
I wouldn't be so sure!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, not so fast.
I used Rock twice in a row and lost.
That means Rock is the unluckiest choice for me.
Am I wrong?
It only stands to reason that
I wouldn't want to use my unlucky Rock a third time.
Since you said my luck is on the decline,
you won't be able to use Paper.
By playing Paper,
you've admitted to yourself that my luck will turn.
I'll make this a winning hand for sure!
Let's go, Kishibe Rohan!
It's on!
Rock...
...Paper...
...Scissors!
He still used Paper after all of that!
His mental strength has grown!
I'm not gonna lose to you!
I definitely still have the upper hand in this match!
I'll use Paper four times in a row!
This will be a winning hand for sure!
Fine! Rock! I'll make my unlucky Rock work in my favor!
Once more!
M-My knees are giving out!
What? He's not using the same form!
Rohan still hasn't played Scissors yet!
Crap... Going with Paper again was a bad idea!
No!
My Rock wasn't unlucky after all!
Feh! Damn that Rohan!
I-Is that...?
Hey, Mister!
Hey, Mr. Rohan...
Those guys are probably Stand users too, right?
They are, aren't they? I can feel it.
I wanna test my luck!
If my luck's on the decline,
those two will come over here.
But if my luck's on the rise,
they won't get anywhere near us!
Hey, isn't that Rohan?
Hey! Hey!
I seriously hate that guy...
Let's just smile and walk away.
Hmm... Well, you know... Hmm...
That little boy!
He must be...
...one of his fans!
It was nice seeing you!
Later!
Guess my luck's on the rise, Mr. Rohan!
I got a good feeling I won't be losing the next match!
My luck is protecting me!
Right now, I bet I could survive Russian Roulette with five rounds in the chamber if I wanted!
It's a shower of glass!
So, let's have this final match and see who will win, Mr. Rohan!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get into your Rock, Paper, Scissors pose!
I'm not the one who needs to hurry up and get started.
I've made my move.
Quit messing around.
No, I'm dead serious.
You said you were going to surpass me, but having lived nine years longer than you, I'll let you in on something...
It isn't very difficult to make someone lose.
The most difficult thing is- Listen closely!
The most difficult thing is...
...to surpass one's self!
I'm going to surpass my own luck!
Let's go, Rohan!
It's on!
Rock, Paper...
..Scissors!
Yes! How's that feel, Kishibe Rohan?!
Wh-What?
What?!
Huh?
Wh-What's going on?
Why did my hand play Rock?!
That gives me three wins and two losses.
You got the unlucky Rock.
When Joseph Joestar passed by here earlier, my good luck came along with him.
The invisible baby.
Huh?!
Note: I will save Rohan when he's in danger.
I will become invisible and make the kid's hand into "Rock."
You relied on a sudden burst of good luck,
but I changed my luck entirely.
That is what it means to surpass one's self.
That said, now I'm going to defeat you for good like I promised.
I'm going to write...
"I can never win at Rock, Paper, Scissors ever again.
My Stand will become completely useless."
Sh-Shut your mouth!
Rohan, don't get near me!
I-If ya do, this baby's gonna...
Do you realize what you're doing right now?
Hmph! We're fighting with words now!
You didn't really beat me!
You won because you cheated, you coward!
Let the baby go.
Face me one more time!
I won't do anything to the baby if you win!
I said... let the baby go.
I accept your challenge.
I'll make you lose! Rock, Paper...
...Scissors, Scissors, Scissors!
I-I-I can't beat him!
D-Dammit!
I turned him into a Stand user, and he still lost!
I'm outta here!
I won't kill you.
I'm just going to render your Stand useless.
If...
If I gotta listen to whatever you write inside me...
If I have to live with you controlling my mind...
...then I'd rather just die!
Take that, Kishibe Rohan!
Excellent! You have spunk, kid!
When I witness people like you
who have a flair for the dramatic...
...I feel moved!
Wha-?!
Y-You're gonna get ran over, too!
Are you sure?
What the hell? Th-The wind!
Whoa, where'd this photo come from?!
I-I can't see the road!
I-It swerved and missed us?
E-Even though you could have died,
you jumped in front of that truck for me...
Was that just luck?
You've really managed to impress me
in such a short amount of time.
I won't defeat you for good.
However, you can't use your Stand for evil anymore.
I can't believe he ran into me! Dammit!
I lost... I completely lost...
Hey, Rohan!
H-Have you seen the baby?
We can't find her, Sir!
N-No, we may just not be able to see her right now...
D-Damn...
She's gone...
Hey, where'd you go?!
I'll play dumb and help them look...
Wh-Where did you go? Where are you?
Rock, Paper, Scissors Kid. Real name: Oyanagi Ken.
Hey!
Stand name: Boy II Man.
Rendered unable to fight.
For some reason, the hole in his cheek remained.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 27
I Am a Space
Alien