Man, I'm starvin'...
Let's grab some food after visitin' my big bro's grave, Josuke.
I'm not really hungry, though.
Note: Italian Cuisine: Trussardi, 100 meters to the right
Some Italian joint just opened up. It's right up here.
But the cemetery is up ahead, too.
Nobody's gonna eat at a restaurant so close to it.
Josuke, ya think maybe nobody cares
an' just wants a good place to chow down?
Eatin' there must make people all like,
"Aww, man! I'm droolin' all over the place!"
Let's go! Let's go!
This place?
TRUSSARDI
I always thought this was just an empty building...
Coulda just fixed 'er up. It ain't too shabby.
What? "Depends on the customer"?
Note: Today's Course: Depends on the customer. Includes coffee and dessert - 3,500 yen
Inside ain't too shabby, neither!
Greetings!
Episode 10:  Let's Go out for Italian
Table for two?
Please, have yourselves a seat.
Uh... Thanks...
Please.
S-Sure...
Uh, you a foreigner, pal?
Si, Signore. I am an Italian.
Tonio Trussardi. But you may call me Tonio.
Well, ain't this swell! We're gettin' real Italian eats!
I have traveled this world far and wide.
I have done study into many kinds of food to improve the cuisine of my motherland.
Japan has finally given me this chance.
Morioh is a wonderous place.
There are many farms with fresh produce,
and the seafood is also very good.
It makes me so happy.
With the best ingredients in Morioh,
I will prepare you a meal that will have you feeling at your best.
Killer! But what am I gonna get...
Couldja give us the menu, already?
Menu?
We have no such thing here.
Whaddya mean? Ya ain't got a menu?
I serve food tailored to each customer!
Then gimme a menu!
No, no! I am trying to tell you that I am the one
who decides what my customers are to have.
You kiddin' me?
Ya tryin' t'tell me I can't pick my own food?
You were having the runs last night, were you not?
Your intestinal walls are inflamed.
You did not receive nearly enough sleep.
Only about four hours, yes?
It is no wonder you have such puffy eyes.
Now, show me your left hand.
Yes, yes... The athlete's foot is afflicting your right foot.
You also suffer from two cavities, and a stiff left shoulder, yes?
H-Howdja know all that?!
It's all true!
By looking at your hands,
I am able to know the state of your health.
Oh, I am so very sorry!
What about you, signore?
Yeah, I'm not really hungry. I'll have a coffee.
A cappuccino, please.
Ho capito!
Healthy food that's made to be
really good for you usually tastes pretty gross.
If you don't like it, we don't have to pay.
We'll just complain, then leave.
Yeah...
J-Josuke...
This water... No, this mineral water...
What about it?
I-I ain't never had such good tastin' water in all my life!
It's like... exquisite or some shit!
Like somethin' a princess in the Alps playin' a harp'd drink!
It's that good!
Just like takin' that first sip of water
after bein' lost in the desert for three days!
Y-You're right! It's really good!
So good!
No kidding! It's amazing!
What brand of water is this?
I-It's so good, it's makin' me wanna cry...
Hey, no need to cry over a little water.
Maybe it's just really pure...
You got a handkerchief?
The tears ain't stoppin'!
They just keep flowin'! They ain't stoppin'!
O-Okuyasu! There's something wrong with you!
You okay?
O-Okuyasu!
Wh-What the hell're these tears?!
It's like a fuckin' flood!
O-Okuyasu, y-your eyes! The white parts...
They're all shriveled up and squishy looking!
Momento! Do not panic, please!
Y-You asshole!
What did you put in Okuyasu's drink?
Please, calm yourself!
His eyes will be shriveled for only a moment more.
The mineral water I have given you comes from snow
on Mt. Kilimanjaro which fell fifty-thousand years ago.
The water flushes out the inside of the eyeball,
while also helping with the symptoms of insomnia.
You did not start crying like him
since you had enough sleep last night.
Josuke!
I ain't sleepy at all no more!
I feel fuckin' great!
Like I got ten hours of sleep!
Seriously?
O-Okuyasu, are you sure there's nothing wrong with your eyes?
Josuke, when ya drink water like this for the first time,
it's bound t'make ya weepy-eyed!
I cried more than when I first saw The Champ!
Really?
Yeah!
Here is your cappuccino.
R-Right...
So, shall we continue with the meal?
Hey, this looks pretty good!
Ingredients:
• Mozzarella cheese (4 thin slices)
• Tomatoes (5 thin slices)
Tonio's Special Dressing:
• 1 Anchovy • Seaweed • Olive oil
• White wine vinegar
• Lemon juice • Salt • Pepper
• Balsamic vinegar (just a splash)
• Toast • Lettuce (for garnish)
(Best eaten within 15 minutes
of preparation)
For the antipasto, we have a salad
with slices of mozzarella cheese and tomato.
M-M-Mozzaza?!
Mozzarella cheese is a soft, fresh cheese
which has had its fat removed.
All of us in Italy love it!
The Italians were the first people to
make use of tomatoes inside their cooking.
There is no comparison to how an Italian prepares tomatoes.
I do not say this to brag. It is merely pride.
Please, help yourself.
Will do!
Yeah, that ain't bad...
Tastes good. Pretty damn good...
I dunno why, but this cheese is pretty bland, though.
No! No!
You must eat it together with the tomato!
What? With the tomato?
Well, I guess your foreign food
just ain't cut out for Japanese taste buds.
So good!
The juicy part of the tomato goes perfect with the cheese!
The cheese goes good with the tomato,
and the tomato goes good with the cheese!
They got like a harmony or somethin'! It just works!
Kinda like a Simon and Garfunkel duet!
Or like Ucchan and Nanchan's comedy!
Note: Japanese comic about an orphaned young man trying to become a world-champion boxer.
Maybe even like Takamori Asao and Chiba Tetsuya workin' on Tomorrow's Joe together!
Grazie! It makes me so happy that you have enjoyed it!
H-Hey, Okuyasu! Let me try some!
Hell no!
Get your own food!
Ain't no way you're havin' mine!
I wouldn't share with ya even if I saw ya starvin' half to death!
It's so good!
Thanks for bringin' me into this world, Mom!
Dammit! I knew you were cheap,
but I didn't know you were this bad!
Fine, then! I'll have what he's having!
Ho capito!
However...
I must tell you that only a customer with a stiff shoulder will receive any benefit from eating this dish.
Huh? Stiff shoulder?
Y-Y'know, my neck's startin' t'feel kinda hot...
I'm gettin' all sweaty!
Sir, I would highly suggest that you remove your jacket.
F-For some reason...
...I-I-I'm startin' t'get all itchy!
Th-There's some kinda sticky shit all over my fingers!
That would be your dead skin.
Dead skin?!
It is a sign that your metabolism has improved and your blood is circulating well.
The calcium, vitamins, and minerals
in the antipasto you have just consumed...
...stimulated the thyroid gland in your throat
which controls your metabolism.
Your bad cells are leaving your body as dead skin.
Please continue to scratch and remove all the dead skin!
Okuyasu, quit scratching!
You've made a softball's worth of dead skin already!
You're starting to dig at the muscle in your shoulder!
N-No! I ain't doin' that, Josuke!
It's so light!
My shoulder feels super light, now!
Feels like somebody put a balloon in it or somethin'!
Look! It's all flexible now!
I ain't never done this before!
Now my shoulder ain't stiff at all!
Now, if you will excuse me for a moment...
I must ensure the pasta comes to a proper boil.
Goddamn! That Chef Tonio's a real fuckin' genius!
N-No...
There's definitely something going on here!
Something's up with this guy's cooking!
Morioh Landmark #3
Italian Ristorante Trussardi
Location: One minute's walk
after getting off the bus headed
toward Morioh's Kunimi Pass
Cemetery
An unusual restaurant with no set
menu. The chef decides what to serve
each customer based on how they're
feeling that day. Because seating is
limited, it is recommended that you
make a reservation.
So, we shall continue the meal, yes?
Next is the primo piatto.
This is the pasta course.
This dish is called spaghetti alla puttanesca!
Ingredients:
• Spaghetti • Pitted black olives
• Olive oil • Anchovies
• Garlic • Red peppers
• Cherry tomatoes
•Misc: Parsley, salt, pepper, etc
•Parmesan cheese
(Best eaten while hot)
The name of this dish means "spaghetti in the style of a prostitute," for the women who would prepare it using whichever ingredients they had.
One normally wouldn't put cheese on pasta with garlic, but this dish is an exception.
Does this spaghetti got red peppers in it?
Yes, it does.
Spaghetti alla puttanesca uses
one of the oldest pasta sauces in Italian cuisine.
It was created in my hometown of Naples...
...which is why I fully recommend this dish!
Uh, well... I ain't too good with spicy stuff...
I don't even eat curry rice unless it's got
mild Vermont Curry sauce with apple an' honey flavor on it.
Don't eat sushi with wasabi, neither.
Ain't happenin'! Too spicy!
This shit's too spicy!
If you don't like eating spicy food, Okuyasu...
...then don't eat it.
Do not worry if you are unable to eat it!
I am perfectly content not to charge you for this pasta.
I shall go prepare the secondo piatto, the main dish.
However, I must tell you that my spaghetti is made in such a way that even those who do not enjoy spicy food will be able to eat it.
Even if they don't like spicy stuff?
Hot!
I ain't denyin' Tonio's a kickass chef!
The guy's definitely a fuckin' genius!
But this ain't so good...
Well, maybe you're lucky you can't eat it.
Doesn't the food and water he's served us seem really weird?
It makes me really suspicious!
Suspicious? 'Bout what?
Hot!
You lost a softball's worth of dead skin, and you cried your eyes out!
That so?
I was at Shirabu Hot Springs in Yamagata once,
an' I lost so much dead skin that my back pain went away!
Ain't nothin' weird about it!
Hot!
Listen! I just remembered something Hazamada Toshikazu said!
For some reason, even if they've never met before...
...Stand users are drawn to other Stand users!
Josuke!
You sayin' Tonio's a Stand user?!
Shh! I don't know yet!
That's why I'm saying he's suspicious!
Suspicious, eh?
Hot! Still ain't happenin'!
If you can't handle spicy food, then stop licking it!
Y-Ya got a point...
I-I ain't good at eatin' spicy food, but y'know...
...I just wanna keep licking this spaghetti sauce!
Why are you eating it?!
I-I know! Normally I'd never eat stuff this spicy...
...but...
I can't help it! One taste an' now I'm hooked on the spiciness!
Note: A festival where beans are thrown to ward off evil spirits,
then each person eats the number of beans corresponding to their age.
It's like when ya eat your age in beans at the Setsubun Festival...
...an' even though they ain't very good, before ya know it...
...ya ate a whole bag's worth of 'em!
Hey, I told you to stop eating it!
M-My stomach's openin' up!
The more I eat, the hungrier I get!
So good!
Dammit, Okuyasu!
Your tooth! Your tooth just flew out of your mouth!
That's my cavity! My rotten tooth fell out!
Y-Y'know, I got a cavity in my lower jaw, too...
There it is!
Your tooth! How is your molar growing in so fast?!
Enough is enough! I'm not sure what he's planning, but...
Crazy Diamond!
Dora!
But... But I ain't done eatin' that yet!
I'm gonna restore the spaghetti to its raw ingredients!
The hell were those things?
It's a Stand!
Tonio Trussardi really is a Stand user!
Are you okay, Okuyasu?!
I ain't sleepy no more...
My shoulder ain't stiff neither,
and I got new teeth once my cavities came out, but...
...m-my stomach hurts! It's fuckin' killin' me!
Wait here!
Tonio! What the hell are you trying to pull?!
Where is he?
He finished the main dish...
Good, good... Please eat it all up.
It seems as though my main dish,
lamb in an apple sauce, is a success.
What?!
What are you doing here?
Did you see?!
Have you come in here to spy on me?!
You will be paying for this! Prepare yourself!
Why should I listen to you telling me to pay?
That's my line!
What the hell are you trying to do with your cooking?!
Okuyasu!
What the hell are you doing?!
I can't help it! My stomach hurts, but I just can't stop eatin'!
Tastin' the tanginess from the apple sauce an' the juice from the lamb is makin' me feel real happy an' stuff!
Who'da thought somethin' this good is real!
Don't eat that meat, Okuyasu!
I'm so happy! I just keep feelin' happier an' happier!
So good!
M-My guts!
My stomach!
Okuyasu!
I will make you pay for this!
You asshole!
Wash your hands with soap this instant!
Huh?!
Unforgivable!
Entering the kitchen without permission is unforgivable!
Listen to me! The kitchen must stay perfectly spotless!
S-Soap? You want me to wash my hands?
Hey, Josuke!
My guts feel all better! An' I'm full, too!
That was the best!
Huh?!
My fucked up stomach's all better!
What?!
I am so very happy for you!
Nothing makes me more happy than to see a customer who has enjoyed my cooking and become so healthy!
The puppy...
I was unsure of this dish, so I had him try it for me.
His tummy was a bit upset, too.
Y-You really just wanted to feed Okuyasu good food?
What more could a chef ask for?
This is what I live for. I could not hope for more.
You're a Stand user, aren't you?
So are we.
Oh, I cannot believe it!
When... When I traveled the world searching for ways to improve my cooking, I discovered that I had received this ability.
I have never met others with powers like mine before!
But you! You are lacking common sense!
Huh?
You were touching things without washing your hands, yes?!
The number one enemy in every kitchen is germs!
This is why I became angry!
H-Huh? I-I'm sorry! I-I didn't mean it!
I hope you are prepared to pay!
Now, let us continue with the cooking!
Pudding for dessert?
I'm too tough for this shit!
Hmph! A guy like me's got a reputation t'keep!
So good!
You really are a fuckin' genius!
I'm so happy we got a chef like you in Morioh!
Damn you, Okuyasu!
He seems so very happy with it!
You! I must see your hands moving!
This is the worst...
My athlete's foot's all better!
Please, do come again! Grazie!
TRUSSARDI
P
Pea
Pear
Pearl
Pearl J
Pearl Ja
Pearl Jam
To
Ton
Toni
Tonio
Power: E
Speed: C
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Tonio T
Tonio Tr
Tonio Tru
Tonio Trus
Tonio Truss
Tonio Trussar
Tonio Trussardi
You're Mr. Kujo Jotaro, correct?
I'm with the Speedwagon Foundation.
I've been told that going near electrical wires is dangerous, including phone lines and power lines...
...so I'm here to deliver this message to you in person.
"I should arrive at Morioh's port tomorrow at noon.
Regards, Joseph Joestar."
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 11
Re
d
Hot Ch
ili
Pepper Part 1
d
ili
Re
Hot Ch
Pepper Part 1
d
ili