Arrow, where are you taking me?
You wish to strike that man?
That young man is destined to become a Stand user...
The sixth one so far...
But that's more than enough!
They will surely defeat anyone who tries to get near my Yoshikage!
What?!
Ouch.
Wh-What is the meaning of this?
The arrow chose him, yet it deflected off his skin!
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichini mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days
Episode 27:  I Am a Space Alien
That's all the information we've managed to retrieve.
He's done a good job covering his tracks until now.
Kira Yoshikage...
Who have you become, and what's your new name?
Where are you hiding?
Summer...
I've seen a lot of tourists around here lately.
Yeah...
He won't be able to ignore his urges much longer.
Knowing him, it's only a matter of time before he makes a move.
The summer season is finally upon us!
On July 1st, the beaches and rivers of Morioh
once again opened to the public.
The hordes of incoming tourists coming from the capital
and S city are making the town livelier than ever before.
Relaxing at a summer villa, camping, fishing, yachting...
There's no end to the fun times to be had at this time of year!
How do you lovely people plan to enjoy this summer?
Yes, "fun times to be had", indeed.
Surely that man...
...has many fun things in mind.
Most people live their entire lives
hiding their true selves deep within their hearts...
And yet...
...is there a person capable of
keeping their true self hidden from everyone forever?
Dammit...
I want to reveal the true Kira Yoshikage to that woman.
I want her to know the depths of my heart's desires...
To take her soft and slender neck in my hands and strangle the life from her body...
I can't suppress my urges while my nails are growing like this...
I need to calm myself down until it subsides...
I still haven't perfected his handwriting yet.
Note: Kawajiri Kosaku
Note: Kosaku
Higashikata Josuke... and that Kujo Jotaro...
It's their fault I'm in this mess.
Umm...
Uh... What... are you doing right now?
R-Right! It's obvious!
You're just reading a book.
Well, I made some tea for you.
I know I don't normally do these
kind of things for you, but if you want it...
It's fine if you're not thirsty, though.
Oh, look at the time!
I need to get some sleep.
Open up your heart to this woman...
Show her your true self, Kira Yoshikage...
D-Darling?!
Damn. Opening up to her would be a mistake.
They would find me in an instant.
I'm sorry I startled you...
W-Was he trying to help me undo my buttons?
I'm sorry I startled you?
Don't be! The way you've been acting lately
makes my heart feel like it will beat right out of my chest!
I feel so excited whenever I'm near you now! I...
...I think I've finally fallen in love with you!
J-Josuke, l-look at that!
What are you talking abou-
Could it be? Ya think it's a...?
...T-Terry Funk!
It's a crop circle!
Yeah! A crop circle!
I-It's fuckin' crazy!
Who'da thought somethin' like this'd show up in Morioh!
Something doesn't feel right here, Okuyasu...
Look! There's something weird in the middle of the ring.
Something is definitely wrong here!
You gonna check it out?
Not like I have a choice!
Careful, man...
Yeah.
H-He breathin'?
There's a scratch on the back of his neck, but I think he's just unconscious.
Wake up! Are you okay? Hey!
I ain't never seen this guy at our school.
Oh, he's wakin' up!
Where...
Where am I?
Where?
You're right in the middle of a field in Budogaoka, Morioh.
Have I reached Earth?
The previous night, I suddenly became deathly ill.
I must have been rendered comatose.
It is past 8:00 AM,
meaning I was immobile for thirteen Earth hours.
This motherfucker really got us good!
Hot damn!
That's one hell of an elaborate prank you pulled on us!
You sure got us!
You're a real funny guy!
You made a crop circle just so you could
wait under the grass until some gullible saps walked by?
Amazing! You're really something!
I-I can't breathe! My stomach hurts!
Note: Stomach medicine
That's gold!
What school do you go to?
You're one hell of a guy!
School?
My planet of origin was located in
the Magellanic Clouds, but it has been destroyed.
I have traveled here to Earth to determine its suitability
as my new home, as well as if the inhabitants are friendly or not.
Okay, we get it...
It was really funny at first,
but now you're just taking the joke too far.
Here, have a tissue.
Thank you. It was scrumptious.
W-Well, guess we oughta get goin' t'school...
Y-Yeah, definitely!
Let's go!
He ate the fuckin' tissues...
Talk about taking a joke too far...
The ice cream shop's closed!
It's all that keeps me goin' on Monday mornings!
Guess we'll have to live with it.
No ice cream for us today.
Would you like me to give you both ice cream?
Well? Would you like some?
Well, yeah, but there ain't nothin' we can do since it's closed.
Do not give up so easily.
I happen to have two in my bag.
For graciously giving me the tissue, I offer these to you.
Earth appears to be a rather pleasant place to live.
It's still cold...
Wh-What were ya doin' with ice cream in your bag?!
Is the ice cream I've given you insufficient?
I ain't askin' you that! Who the hell are you?!
I'm certain I relayed my origin to you earlier.
Ah! Would you like me to formally introduce myself?
I should have known.
My name is Nu Mikitakazo N'shi.
I am 216 years old.
I work as a spaceship pilot.
I care for animals as a hobby.
I am currently carrying a wild mouse with me in my bag.
It becomes quite content when I stroke its back.
This guy's a Stand user! Ain't no doubt about it!
Let's kick his ass, Josuke!
Calm down, Okuyasu...
Do you really think a Stand user would
tell us they're from the Magellanic Clouds?
Th-Then what the fuck's his deal?!
There, there, there.
I don't know...
We need to investigate.
Don't eat his ice cream!
Huh?!
So you're 216, huh?
Yes.
And ya work as a spaceship pilot?
Why're ya copyin' me?
So let me get this straight...
This is completely insane,
but are you saying you're some kinda space alien?
A space alien!
A space alien, of course!
I should have referred to myself as such from the outset.
I am a space alien.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
So, you have a spaceship?
You mind showing it to us?
You can, can't you?
Of course.
Unfortunately, however, it is currently on standby 1,500,000
kilometers away, and would take three days to arrive on Earth.
I cannot summon it immediately.
You use that watch to call it to you?
Oh, how did you know?
Please keep this a secret.
You cannot tell anyone of this.
This guy's totally fucked in the head!
He wasn't even jokin' with us!
He's a stupid, crazy fucker!
Should I punch him?
You always wanna punch first and ask questions later...
Let's play along a bit longer, just to be sure.
Do you have a ray gun
and an Ultra Hyper Anti-Gravity device?
Of course I do.
But I did not travel to earth to engage in violence,
so I left them on my spaceship.
C'mon, man! If you're really a space alien, ya gotta prove it!
Ya ain't even got green blood or nothin'!
Yeah, alien blood is always green.
Do I sense doubt from you two?
Hey, hey, calm down!
Ya finally get it, stupid?
I don't got no problem with pranks,
but I sure as fuck ain't got time to play along with dipshits like you!
You didn't have to put it so bluntly like that!
Shut up! Ya gotta give it straight for guys like this!
Huh? There a fire happenin' somewhere?
Wh-What the hell?
This sound... I cannot stand this sound!
This sound!
Make this sound stop!
I cannot stand this sound!
I am allergic to it!
Make it stop!
Josuke, this guy's a nutcase!
Let's leave! I don't wanna fuck with him!
Don't you think it's kinda cruel to leave him like this?
Ya really think he's allergic to sound? Just leave him!
I'm outta here, Josuke.
Hey!
Dammit, Okuyasu...
H-Hey, are you okay?
No... Please...
...take me somewhere away from this wretched sound...
Wh-What?!
Please take me away from here!
A-Are you actually...?!
I have the ability to transform my body into anything I choose!
H-Hurry... I feel as though my head will
split open unless I escape this awful noise!
Please!
I am transforming my body into a pair of sneakers,
so please wear them and escape from this noise!
I will return the favor to the best of my ability!
Are you a Stand user?!
Whoa! Y-You're super fast!
With our combined power,
our speed and jumping strength are doubled!
Are you seriously a space alien?!
Ea
Ear
Eart
Earth,
Earth, W
Earth, Wi
Earth, Win
Earth, Wind
Earth, Wind a
Earth, Wind an
Earth, Wind and
Earth, Wind and F
Earth, Wind and Fi
Earth, Wind and Fir
Earth, Wind and Fire
Haze
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: n/a
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Hazekura
Hazekura Mi
Hazekura Miki
Hazekura Mikitaka
What the hell is going on?!
You...
You can't see anything in front of you?
He can't see it!
He's not a Stand user!
What the hell kind of power does he have?
Who the hell are you?!
You do not listen very well, do you?
I made it quite clear that I am a space alien.
Hang on a sec...
I-I need to let this all sink in...
Anyway, it was very kind of you
to take me away from that awful din.
The people of my planet cannot tolerate the sound of a siren.
That sound is capable of agitating our nerves.
I would like to return your act of kindness
by doing a favor for you.
Would you like me to become a fan and fan you?
Or perhaps a back scratcher
so that I may remedy the itchiness of your back?
Whoa, I didn't save you so you'd do me a favor or anything!
You'll do anything for me?
Far out! That's awesome!
What would you like me to do?
C-Can you really turn into anything?
Like something light, or a bunch of something?
Yes. I am capable of transforming into nearly anything.
However, I am incapable of turning into complicated machinery
or anything that exceeds my own physical strength.
I see, I see! Makes sense! You're a cool guy!
So you're gonna repay the favor, right?
Yes.
I-I just got an amazing idea!
An idea that'll make everyone happy!
Happy?
Yeah!
You see, a little while ago I got
a lot of money for winning the lottery...
...but my mom found out and froze the account I put it all in...
Once she's caught on to that kind of stuff,
there's no stopping her.
It's such a drag not having any money
to spend for the entire summer...
So listen up!
Can you turn into this? See?
What is this object?
They're dice! Dice!
Once I've made good money with these,
you and I can split the profits, and everyone will be happy!
What utility does it have?
Huh? You've never heard of dice before?
P-Please excuse my ignorance...
No need to act all sorry about it.
They're really simple. I'll show you.
People who play a lot of games really like these things.
They're hard, and they have six sides.
Each side is numbered from one to six,
which is represented by the number of pips on it.
Yes, yes! I believe I understand now.
So five pips means this is the fifth side, correct?
You got it, my space alien friend!
And three pips represents the third side!
Yeah! Now try turning into one!
Understood!
How simple!
What are you talking about? You're way too big...
You should only be about this big.
Also, you have five pips on two sides.
The die needs to have the numbers one through six on it.
And the numbers on either side should always add up to seven.
Oh, my mistake.
Is this acceptable?
Th-That tickles!
Hey, quit laughing! Dice can't talk!
Huh?
I'm counting on you.
I-I will do my best.
I'm a bit nervous about this, but...
Yeah, this'll work! This'll definitely work! You're perfect!
Now I'll have some fun!
Kishibe Rohan, you better be ready to pay up!
I-I cannot breathe...
Oh, look who it is.
What brings Higashikata Josuke to my humble abode?
This certainly is an unusual occurrence.
Have you found any new information on Kira?
No, not exactly...
Well, umm...
You done working for today?
I just wanted to know if I could get
a quick peek at your next chapter...
What are you up to?
Tell me.
Y-You catch on fast!
Can't get anything past you, Mr. Rohan!
Fine! I'll tell you the truth!
Please! I wanna play Cee-lo with you!
Cee-lo?
To tell you the truth...
...I don't have any spending money for this summer.
Well, I do have thirty-thousand yen. It's my life savings.
But you know...
Nowadays, thirty-thousand yen disappears in an instant if you go to the amusement park or grab some food every so often.
So my only options are make more money or go broke!
I want the thrill of gambling for it!
Isn't that what youth is all about?
I sure think it is! You agree with me?
I'll be honest. I couldn't care less about you.
For what reason should I play Cee-lo with you?
Yeah, you have a good point...
You're definitely not hurting for spending money like I am...
...so there's no reason you'd wanna play me...
Well... All right.
Huh?! You'll play me?
I don't dislike games, and it will be good fun.
Come around to the back.
Thanks a bunch, Mr. Rohan!
Are these rules acceptable for you?
The shooter rolls three dice into the bowl
This roll means the shooter pays double
This roll means the shooter wins double
The larger
number wins
(Here, the six)
No objections here.
Chips are worth one-thousand yen each.
Once all three dice have been rolled into the bowl, you'll lose your turn if one of them rolls out.
Got it.
Good. I'll tape the rules up here.
Okay, let's do this!
Wait.
We aren't using your dice.
Huh?!
We're going to use the dice in my house.
U-Umm, is there something wrong with mine?
I haven't a clue. I just don't trust them.
And...
When I said this would be good fun,
I didn't mean playing Cee-lo with you.
I meant it would be good fun to take
thirty thousand yen from you.
Once you've lost, I expect you to pay me in full.
It doesn't matter how well acquainted we are, Josuke, my friend.
Hell yeah!
Those are the dice I had the space alien turn into!
Good thing I slipped them into his house ahead of time!
I'm such a villain!
It won't be much, but I'm gonna make
some decent money off you, Mr. Rohan!
All right, let's see who will roll first.
Four.
Sweet!
All right, you're first. Roll.
Ouch!
Ou...
O-Ouch! I nicked myself on the table!
Just make your bet and roll the dice.
S-Sure...
I-I'll start off with two, I think,
so that'll be two-thousand yen.
Okay, here's two.
If I roll a one, a two, and a three, I'll have to pay double...
...so I really need to make sure I don't get one, two, and three!
Better not get a one, two, and three!
Definitely not a one, two, and three!
I-I'll go really lightly on the first roll.
Just to see how it goes...
Here we go... Lightly...
So, what'll it be?
Huh?!
What?
I-I-It's an omen!
But how?
Triple sixes, AKA an "omen."
Josuke wins five times what he bet from Rohan.
S-Stupid! Don't give me that right off the bat!
U-Uh, I mean...
I mean, that was some stupid good luck!
Getting an omen means you gotta pay me five times my bet!
You would think I cheated to get a roll like that!
Hmph. That was a quick ten-thousand yen
in spending money you earned.
I don't play Cee-lo much, so I can't believe I got so lucky...
Let's continue the game.
It's my turn next.
I would like to earn back what I just lost, so...
...I'm going with ten.
Ten?
All right! Go!
One, two, and three. The bet is doubled!
The shooter rolls 3 dice into the bowl
This will result in paying double
Rohan has to pay Josuke double what he bet!
This is too much! This is way too much!
Does this space alien know the meaning of holding back?
Damn... He's totally suspicious of me!
Episode 28
High
way
St
ar Part 1
way
St
High
ar Part 1
way
St