Good morning!
Greetings, all. It's Morioh Radio!
Coming at you once again is yours truly, Kai Harada.
Beautiful morning we're having, isn't it?
I have the perfect tune lined up here to start your day off right.
Have a listen to our first song of the morning!
Oh, there it goes.
The reception usually gets better
once you're past the transmission tower.
Sir, is this your first time visiting Morioh?
Yeah.
What's it like?
Morioh? Hmm...
Oh! They make delicious beef tongue stewed in miso there!
Ever notice anything weird there? Strange incidents?
Don't think so.
Sorry, I'm not familiar with the happenings there.
Oh yeah, where did you say you wanted to be dropped off at?
Front of the station is fine.
Sounds good.
Gimme a break...
Here's hoping this isn't too much of a pain.
During April of 1999, on my first day
of high school, I met two very bizarre men.
Episode 1:  Kujo Jotaro Meets Higashikata Josuke!
My very first day of high school!
I wonder what my classmates will be like...
My name is Hirose Koichi.
But don't worry about remembering that.
I was so nervous on my way to school that I-
Eh? H-Huh? For some reason, I thought I saw all the stuff fly out of my bag after I hit you...
Sorry, I wasn't watching where I was going.
S-So tall! He must be 190 centimeters tall!
I have a question for you.
You know of anyone named Higashikata in this town?
Higashikata? Nope...
In that case, could you give me directions?
I'm looking for Jozenji 1-6.
Kujo Jotaro...
You need to take bus #3 to get to Jozenji.
It should be here soon.
Thanks.
The first of those men I met was this guy, Kujo Jotaro.
I didn't know it at the time,
but he's twenty-eight years old, and a marine biologist.
He's renowned within the scientific community
for his ecological research.
I would describe him as intelligent,
intense, and, as a whole... pretty cool.
Hey! You a first-year?
Tell us who you are, kid!
O-Okay! I'm a first-year: Hirose Koichi!
Good morning, seniors!
Good! Keep it up!
Th-That was scary!
Oh, don't worry about them.
They're getting on a different bus.
Watcha up to, loser?
Who the fuck are you?!
What am I up to?
This tortoise just finished hibernating, so I'm keeping an eye on it.
I'm not very good with tortoises...
They give me the heebie jeebies...
But I decided it was about time I got over my fear...
You think we give a shit?
Get up, retard!
You're pretty tall for a first-year.
Still, if you wanted to dress up like that...
You dumb shit! Who said you could wear that?
...you shoulda got permission from us first!
D-Don't! Reptiles scare me!
They're so creepy...
Wipe that stupid fucking smirk off your face!
Sorry! I shouldn't have done that, senior.
I've seen a lot of sorry dumb shits like you
end up in the hospital for not knowing any better!
Do you wanna end up...
...like this stupid tortoise?! Huh?!
Th-They're awful...
We'll let you off the hook this time.
But ditch the uniform and don't come back for it.
And leave all your cash!
Of course! I'm really sorry!
If he didn't want those kids to antagonize him,
he shouldn't have dressed like that.
He's a lost cause if what they did to that tortoise
didn't even make him flinch.
Hey, princess... How about you give us your name?
Okay.
I'm from class 1-B: Higashikata Josuke.
What? Higashikata Josuke?!
"Jo" and "Jo," eh?
Josuke, we're just gonna call you "Jojo" from now on!
Okay... Thank you, guys.
Hurry up and take it off!
The bus is here!
Make it quick, or I'm gonna fuck up that
Astro Boy hairdo you got going on!
What's the hold-up? Hurry the fuck up!
Hey, senior...
What the hell did you just say about my hair?
What? A Stand!
My nose! My nose!
If you think you can say whatever the hell you want about my hair,
then you've got another thing coming!
Note: "Sazae" is the titular character of a popular Japanese comic and animated TV series.
You think you can get away with saying my hair looks like Sazae's?
Huh?! I-I never said-
I heard what you said loud and clear, asshole!
Wow! He sent him flying!
I definitely just saw a Stand appear behind him.
Huh? The tortoise's injuries...
Wh-What the hell?
The spot where he decked him in the face is healing itself!
He's all better!
But doesn't it look like it healed a bit funny?
There's something funky going on with his face!
Huh?
No way! What's wrong with me? H-Hey!
Thanks to you, I had to touch that tortoise,
even though I didn't want to.
What are you gonna do about that, huh?!
W-Wait! My nose! What's wrong with it? H-Hey!
Gimme a break. So this is him...
Somebody help me!
Jeez, it's just you again.
It's true! The tortoise is completely healed!
Higashikata Josuke...
Born in 1983.
Your mother's name is Tomoko.
She was twenty-one years old and attending college in Tokyo at the time of your birth.
You've lived here since the day you were born.
In 1987, when you were four years old,
you came down with a fever of unknown origin...
...which had you on the verge of death for fifty days.
Your father's name is...
Gimme a break. Why does it have to be me telling him this?
Your father's name is Joseph Joestar.
He's currently seventy-eight years old.
He's the founder of Joestar Realty.
I've heard of him before...
Apparently he's a huge real estate tycoon in the US.
He's doing fine for his age,
but when I started looking into how his inheritance would be split...
...I discovered he had a son living in Japan.
He never even knew himself.
The old fucker...
He always went on and on about only having eyes for his wife...
...yet it turned out he had a son
from an affair he had when he was sixty-two.
Whoops. I should watch what I say.
My name's Kujo Jotaro.
Technically, you could say I'm your nephew.
It's pretty bizarre.
Nephew? Oh, nice to meet you...
Let's walk and talk.
Eventually, you'll get a third of Gramps' inheritance.
I came here to tell you that.
The Joestar household has been a mess
ever since news of his affair came to light.
Is it that bad?
Yeah. My grandma, Suzi Q, is the angriest
she's ever been since they got married sixty-one years ago.
I-I'm so sorry! I never meant to be such a problem!
Hey, hold on...
What's with the apology?
Well, you know, it isn't good that
I caused your family so much trouble.
My mom used to tell me she was
in love with my dad when I was born.
So I accept some responsibility.
Do you think you could tell my dad...
...I mean, Mr. Joestar, that he shouldn't worry about us?
That's all.
What's with this kid?
I came here expecting to take a punch for Gramps,
but now I'm getting an apology?
Ah, it's Josuke!
It totally is!
Josuke!
How's it going?
We're so lucky!
You should totally walk to school with us!
Your hair is looking way cool today!
You're so handsome!
The other guys are so lame compared to you!
Uh... I'm actually in the middle of something right now...
Huh? What do you mean?
We're gonna be late if you don't come now!
Just deal with it later.
Hey, Josuke...
I'm not finished with you.
Tell them to leave.
What's his deal?
Hey, you can talk about your stupid hair with them later.
H-He seriously just said that!
He made fun of his hair!
Asshole...
What the hell did you just say about my hair?
This is bad!
It's not my fault!
Nothing makes Josuke angrier than making fun of his hair!
This is just like what happened earlier!
Hey, calm down, Josuke.
I wasn't trying to insult-
Fuck! Here it comes!
Josuke!
He's bleeding!
Did you see that, Josuke?
That was a Stand.
It's the physical manifestation of your mental energy.
Joseph Joestar has one, too.
Only Stand users can see Stands.
It really pisses me off when people talk shit about my hair!
Don't say I didn't warn you!
So that's Josuke's Stand!
Dorara!
Dora!
H-He's so strong!
You're wide open below the chin!
You punk!
What?!
Huh?
When did he...
What's going on?
When the hell did you-
Josuke!
No!
Shut the hell up!
Your screams are pissing me off! Get out of here!
Fine...
I think they know each other...
That guy is scary...
He's kinda hot, though...
I'm so confused...
I have no idea what's going on...
...but something crazy is definitely happening here!
It's been a while...
At least ten years now...
...but I stopped time for half a second.
If I hadn't stopped time...
...we'd both be injured, or possibly even dead.
Here, Josuke.
Ah, uh... No. It's okay...
I see.
I actually had another reason I wanted to see you.
It has to do with these photos.
There's something lurking in this town.
Something dangerous is coming.
When my Gramps, Joseph,
tried taking a spirit photo of you, he got these instead.
We're not sure why...
...but this guy is probably a Stand user.
I doubt you'll get involved in this,
but I figured I should warn you.
Be careful from now on.
Koichi...
If you happen to see this guy, stay the hell away from him.
The police won't be able to help you.
Just run.
Josuke...
Don't lose your temper and go after him, either.
You'll get hurt like you were earlier.
Oh! The entrance ceremony!
We're late!
Aww, man...
What's my mom gonna do to me if I'm late on my first day?!
Look, you can tell me whatever you want after school!
Hey, Koichi, was it? Let's go!
Huh?
Hurry!
Right!
The other bizarre man I met that day
was Higashikata Josuke.
He's unpredictable, going from carefree to seething with rage in an instant.
I guess his family situation is complicated.
Not to mention, we only just met...
Higashikata Josuke... What a strange guy.
Not to mention his Stand...
My hat... It transformed?
His Stand must have something to do with
transforming damaged objects.
If he had hit my head or face...
Best not to think about it.
Anyway, if I look at him as a potential ally, I could rely on him.
If I can overlook his ridiculous personality, that is.
I hope Josuke has nothing to do with this guy.
C
Cr
Cra
Craz
Crazy
Crazy D
Crazy Di
Crazy Dia
Crazy Diam
Crazy Diamo
Crazy Diamon
Crazy Diamond
Higashi
Higashikata
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Higashikata Jo
Higashikata Josuke
What's shaking, baby?
Where you headed? Come hitch a ride with me!
C'mon, you don't gotta be so cold!
C'mon! C'mon!
Whoa, v-very pretty!
You'll go wherever I want?
Sure thing! I'd go anywhere for you!
Then go to hell and never come back!
Huh?
Sir, you okay?
Officer!
G-Go arrest that crazy bitch!
She just commited a crime! A crime!
Nah, I can't do that.
What?!
That's my daughter.
Huh?
You know how it is.
I can't arrest my daughter, and you're making problems for people.
I'll let it go this once, but be careful in the future.
Ms. Murakami, are you okay?
Here, let me help you with your bag.
Hey, Tomoko!
Hi, Dad.
You headed home?
Yeah.
I'm done for the day, so I'll tag along with you.
How's Josuke holding up?
Today was his entrance ceremony, right?
I hope he's not up to any mischief.
Hmph. Who knows?
That dummy can be calm one minute and enraged the next.
Makes me wonder who he took after.
Come on, now...
Still...
Deep down, he's a good kid.
I'm not worried about him.
Oh, that's right!
Why don't we celebrate him starting high school tonight?
Yeah, that's the plan.
Do you think he'll come straight home?
He'll probably stop somewhere like always.
No doubt.
Hey, let's stop by Kame Yu!
Huh? I just got ya an expensive bag the other day!
I just wanna look at clothes all day!
Watch it, dumbass!
Quit walkin' like you're half awake.
What a freak!
Who the hell doesn't apologize for bumping into someone?
Forget him. Come on!
Yeah. We're just going to Kame Yu, right?
Huh?
Katagiri Anjuro, nicknamed Angelo.
Born in Morioh in 1964.
Has an IQ of 160.
Got sent to juvie for theft and rape when he was twelve.
Since committing his first crime...
...he's become one of the most infamous and despicable criminals in Japanese history.
Most of his youth was spent in jail for his crimes.
A total of twenty years by the time he turned thirty-four.
His last crime was so terrible,
it would make a rat living in a dirty bathroom sick to its stomach.
Once he was finally arrested, he got the death sentence.
However, the execution failed to kill him.
Shortly after, Angelo escaped.
He most likely became a Stand user right before his execution.
I'm not sure why...
...but he's hiding out in this quiet town...
...somewhere...
Oh, Koichi, heading home?
Ah, yeah.
We're in the same class.
Yeah, what a coincidence.
Well, see ya tomorrow.
Ah... Hey! J-Josuke!
Huh?
So, you wanna know what that Jotaro guy has to say?
It's been bugging me, especially since it has to do with our town.
You're something else. I'm not gonna go.
How come?
I'm kinda curious, but when I thought about it...
...I decided it wasn't a good idea to get involved with a guy who has so many secrets.
Why?
Well, you know...
Everything's fine as it is.
Makes sense...
What's going on?
Maybe an accident or something?
Wanna check it out?
Yeah.
What's going on?
Step away from the crime scene! Step back!
What a commotion!
A man tried robbing the convenience store
and took an employee hostage!
Huh?
Look! He's coming out!
Don't move! Drop the knife!
Let the woman go!
Shut up! Back up!
I-I've been rung up by her before!
He's got a crazy look in his eyes. He'll kill her if he loses it.
All of you, back the fuck up! I'm getting in that car!
This isn't good, Josuke! We need to back up!
R-Right...
Hey, kid with the stupid hair!
Sorry, we need to back—
I just said I'm getting in that car!
I'll kill her, idiot!
I have...
...a bad feeling about this!
I knew it!
O-Oh no! Here it comes!
He just had to get worked up at a time like this!
Mr. Jotaro just warned him about this!
Who's that?
H-Hey! Stop, kid!
What the hell did you just say?
Wh-Who the fuck are you? Back off!
Don't you care what happens to her?!
Get back here, punk!
What are you gonna do if he loses it?
I told you guys to stay back, too!
M-Motherfucker! You're really pissing me off!
That's it! I'm gonna stab this bitch!
Oh, really?
Dora!
H-He punched a hole through them!
"You're pissing me off"?
That's my line!
Huh? I-I'm not hurt?
She's completely healed! It happened again!
M-My army knife! It's inside my stomach!
H-How?!
You should get a surgeon to remove that for you...
in a prison hospital.
A-Arrest him!
What the hell happened?
Josuke!
Hey, Koichi.
Are you okay?! That was...
What's going on?
What is he opening his mouth for?
Who'da thought...
...I'd find another Stand user here?
I just possessed that guy so I could
have a little fun robbing that store...
You've got some nerve getting in my way!
That's the thing from the photo!
I'm gonna keep an eye on you!
I'll always be watching...
What did you say, bastard?!
Josuke!
You idiot! Get him!
What were you thinking?!
M-Mr. Officer! W-Wait a sec...
What Mr. Jotaro said was true...
Lemme go! I did nothing wrong!
There's something lurking in this town...
It feels like a presence we know nothing about is hiding here.
Something awful is about to happen in Morioh...
Hey, Josuke! Answer the phone!
Josuke! Answer the damn phone!
Yeah, yeah. One sec.
Hello?
It's Jotaro.
Oh, 'sup?
I didn't get a chance to finish talking to you yesterday.
I need to tell you more about the guy hiding here in town.
Oh, I wanted to talk about that, too.
Mr. Jotaro, where are you right now?
The Morioh Grand Hotel.
What happened?
Well...
Damn, what a pain.
Where the hell did I put the shovel?
That little shit...
Looks like he's got himself a nice family.
Not to mention his mom is a total babe...
I'm jealous.
Higashikata Josuke, don't get cocky, now.
I'm gonna destroy your livelihood, your soul, and your life!
Episode 2
Higashikata
Josuke Meets Angelo!
Jo
suke Meets Angelo!