Like a disease lying dormant
inside a seemingly healthy person's body...
...a vile serial killer hides among us in our town of Morioh...
...and, undeterred, they've continued to take even more lives.
And worst of all, it doesn't seem like anyone here even realizes these murders are happening.
It's such a shocking fact that anyone who hears about them
can't help but feel a chill crawl up their spine.
But as of right now,
we have no way to track the killer down.
We don't even know how many other Stand users
are living in Morioh right now.
And rather than worry about
this huge problem lurking in the shadows...
...the people here are more concerned about things like what they'll be eating for dinner...
...since that problem stares them right in the face.
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Transaction No.
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Transaction Amount:
Balance:
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Balance:
Bank No.
Branch No.
Window No.
Balance:
Branch No.
I only have 285 yen left in my savings!
Balance:
Branch No.
I was sure I had twenty thousand left in there!
Twelve yen?!
I was weak!
The twenty thousand yen that I was saving up
to buy those killer name-brand shoes...
I don't even remember what I spent it all on!
This is all that stupid old geezer's fault!
He wasted my entire 130,000 yen savings to buy a bunch of useless baby crap!
I had him pay me back the 130,000 later, but...
...I felt like splurging a bit here and there,
and I totally lost track of how much I was spending!
I wonder if I tucked away a thousand yen somewhere and just forgot about it...
A cockroach!
Guess it makes sense that a bank could have them, too...
A-A Stand?
I gots one yen!
Y-You little pest!
I-It's a Stand!
A new Stand appeared!
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 18:  Shigechi's Harvest Part 1
Where the hell is it going?
There's another one!
Goddammit! What in the fuck are ya?!
I'll kill ya, dammit!
Okuyasu!
Oh, Josuke!
Look, it's an enemy Stand! I'm gonna kill it!
There're two of 'em now!
Yeah. I started following one after it left the bank.
How did it attack you?
Well, I ain't got attacked or nothin'...
I was gettin' some Calpis Water, then all of a sudden,
the fuckin' thing pops out right under the vendin' machine!
What? It didn't attack you?
Then why did you just say you were gonna kill it?
'Cause it scared the shit outta me
an' I spilled my Calpis Water all over my uniform!
Goddammit! Gimme back my money!
Gotcha!
Hey, there's another one!
Gotcha! Gotcha!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What the hell're these things?!
A buncha 'em are all comin' together!
Okuyasu, it's just like your brother Keicho's Stand.
But...
The way they're ignoring us gives me a
completely different kind of creeped out vibe...
Yeah...
Be careful! The user's probably nearby!
It's...
It's money!
Come to think of it, I saw one of them find a 1 yen coin
underneath that machine at the bank earlier!
It's mostly 1 and 10 yen coins, but it's all real!
Nice job, fellers!
"A penny saved's a penny earned."
Dis's all gots t'be five thousand yen!
Long's I gots my Harvest buddies,
I don't ever gots t'worry 'bout money!
Hey, is that the user?
He's talking to his Stand...
Yeah...
Guess he turned into a Stand user 'cause of the bow and arrow,
but at least he ain't tryin' t'hurt us.
Hey, you guys...
...y'all can see my Harvest?
Hey, ya can, can'tcha?!
Yeah. They're called Stands.
I'm Higashikata Josuke.
My friend here is Nijimura Okuyasu.
Friends! Ain't never had none of dose b-b'fore!
My name's Yangu Shigekiyo!
I'm a second-year at Budogaoka Middle School!
I weighs a hundred an' ten kilograms!
Papa and Mama calls me Shigechi!
"Shige-chan" ended up becomin' "Shigechi!"
Note: "chan" is a Japanese suffix used to express endearment.
I gots a turtle at home an' his name's Gonta!
Jus' yesterday, I gots t'wonderin' if dem
41, 62, an' 150 yen stamps tasted any different...
...but soon as I started lickin' 'em, Mama yelled at me.
I gots a photo of Mama right here!
A photo?
Whoa, your mom's a babe...
Weird...
U-Umm...
So, you call these things Harvest?
Did they really gather all this for you?
Sure did! Dey wents t'ditches
an' under vendin' machines an' stuffs...
...but I ain't no thief!
Mr. Police Officer told me
I don't gots t'give back any coins less'n a hundred yen!
Doin' bad stuffs makes me all mad!
It's not bad at all!
I think what you're doing is great for society!
Even though it's not much,
you're putting lost change back into the Japanese economy.
You're doing good work!
Really?! I'm doin' good?!
Hey, wouldja say I'm a good guy?
I guess you could say he cornered an unwanted market.
Most people would never resort to this to earn money.
I'm jealous! You're a fuckin' genius!
D-Didja jus' calls me a genius?!
N-Nobody's ever said something like dat t'me b'fore!
I only gots about 120,000 yen, but...
120,000?!
...B-But y'all sayin' dat about me's gots me so happy!
A t-total of 120,000?!
Ain't I da bestest?
J-Just here in Morioh?
Ayup! No way I'd leave Morioh!
I don't wants t'get lost or kidnapped or somethin'!
120,000... And I only have twelve yen...
Okuyasu...
What's wrong with your left foot?
Whoa, the hell?!
There's three 50 yen coins sittin' here on the ground!
These're yours, Shigekiyo?
I ain't had no idea!
Greedy bastard...
If ya want, I'll give y'all halfa dis.
Huh?!
We're best buddies now, ain't we?
We gots da same kinda powers!
R-Really?!
Lucky!
N-No... Wait a sec...
Look kid, you shouldn't just give out your money so easily!
Den I just gotta makes it hard fer ya!
Y'all can have it! We's buddies, ain't we?
Hey, I didn't mean you should harden your expression!
W-Wait!
Lemme just talk to him for a sec, Shigechi, my pal!
Hey, Josuke! Quit actin' like some goody two-shoes!
If he's willin' t'cough it up, we should just take it, stupid!
I have too much pride to do that! It's not the Josuke way!
I'll take whatever comes my way
so long as it ain't some disease or somethin', got it?!
Calm down! I get what you're saying.
Now quit crying!
But...
I'm really broke right now, too...
And lucky for us, I have an idea that will make all three of us happy!
Huh? An idea that'll make us all happy?
Just leave it to me!
Ha
Har
Harv
Harve
Harves
Harvest
Yan
Power: E
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Yangu
Yangu Shi
Yangu Shige
Yangu Shigekiyo
Note: "To all the good little boys and girls of Morioh: Let's play nice together!" - Town of Morioh
Hey, Shigekiyo... Actually, can I call you Shigechi?
Sure thing!
Shigechi, we can't take this from you.
Giving away money to people you just met is
pretty much the same as buying their friendship.
Huh? B-But I didn't mean dat!
Friendship is something that forms
between people who share a common bond!
But I jus'... y'know...
I get it. I know how you feel.
We're all Stand buddies.
So...
Why don't we start a joint business venture together to strengthen our friendship?
Business?
Yeah. A joint business venture that
makes use of all three of our powers!
Like dis?
Not that kind of joint!
Basically, I think you've just about made
as much as you can from finding loose change.
That's why I came up with an idea that will let
your Harvest earn even more money than before!
Huh?
An idea that'll get us more money
than Harvest pickin' up change?
It isn't bad for anyone, and we won't be causing trouble.
S-So what's yer idea?
That's where the business aspect comes in!
Split half of what you make between
Okuyasu and I for our idea fee.
The other half is all yours, Shigechi.
If the three of us work together to pull off this huge project,
we can all be happy together!
O-Okay! Dat's nifty an' stuffs, b-but what am I gunna do?
You know what this is, right?
A b-blue stamp!
Exactly! When you shop at one of the biggest
department store chains in Eastern Japan, Kame Yu...
...you get a sticker for every one hundred yen you spend.
I bet a lot of people don't even bother
collecting these and just throw them away.
And then there are these.
A voucher from the stationery store Meiwado worth twenty yen...
...a coupon from CD Shop Oscar which lets you trade in
ten of these for two thousand yen in merch...
...the cleaners, the toy shop Märchen Kids...
...and this is a card from Yotsuba Electronics.
Now, this is the important part.
At Kame Yu, for example, you can get cash back for these.
Ah! Y-Ya gotta be kiddin'... I get it now, Josuke!
I know just what you're thinkin'!
Fellers, let's go!
Just one or two of 'em ain't no better than havin' scraps of paper...
But if Harvest is pickin' up thousands
an' thousands of 'em all around town...
Gotcha!
Inside this trash can!
Inside that trash can!
Gotcha! Gotcha!
Gotcha!
Gotcha! Gotcha! Gotcha!
Th-They keep comin'! More an' more of 'em!
Y-Your Stand is amazing!
You're amazing, Shigechi!
He jus' said somethin' nice again!
My Crazy Diamond can restore any ripped up pieces of paper!
Hooray! Ya think we got a couple thousand here?!
No, we have more than 100,000 by now!
Fuck yeah!
We're an invincible trio!
Let's go get our money!
Damn, Josuke, you're too fuckin' good!
Even after ya said all that stuff about pride an' shit!
It's fine since all three of us are happy now!
H-Havin' buddies is da bestest...
O-Okuyasu, i-is Josuke gonna b-be okay?
We really gunna gets moneys fer all dis?
Don't worry, Shigechi! Josuke's got this shit in the bag!
It's Okuyasu! And...
Who is that?
Okuyasu!
Josuke! H-How'd it go?
Didja get the money?
They tell ya t'fuck off?!
I wasn't able to get cash back at the CD shop or the toy store...
But they said I could exchange the coupons for about 40,000 yen's worth of CDs or video games.
I ain't askin' about that!
What about Kame Yu?
Didja get cash back on the Kame Yu stickers?
To tell you the truth, something unexpected happened.
S-Somethin' unexpected?
I unexpectedly got 61,500 yen back!
Here! It's the real deal, Shigechi!
I-It's da real deal!
Seein' all this money right in fronta my face is like a dream!
You're amazing, Shigechi!
Your Stand, Harvest, has a super amazing ability!
Y-Ya really thinks it's amazin'?
Y-Y'know... Folks don't say nothin' good 'bout me too much...
Ya really thinks I'm amazin'?
Hey, ya gotta have more confidence, Shigechi!
You're the only person who could use their ability like this!
Okuyasu... Josuke...
Hup!
Hey, lady! I gots some fat stacks!
Ya wanna go haves some fun?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ah, das right. Here, Josuke, Okuyasu.
I gots yer ten thousand yen fer ya.
Shigechi, what is this?
We's buddies, ain't we? Real best buddies.
Yeah, best buddies.
Dat dere's a token of our friendship!
Hey, wait up!
This isn't what you promised us, Shigechi.
You said you were okay with keeping
half for yourself and giving the rest to us.
Half of 61,500 yen is 30,750 yen.
R-Really? Am I da one who saids dat?
What?
W-W-When ya thinks 'bout it...
...my H-Harvest was doin' all da work to get dose!
I dids all da work!
Y-You guys jus' saids a buncha stuff and dids nothin'.
An' if Josuke hadn't given ya that idea, ya never woulda thought to find all those fuckin' things in the first place!
I woulda thoughts of it b'fore long! I'm an' amazin' guy!
N-No! You never woulda thought of this
with that fuckin' pea brain of yours!
Hey, cut it out, Okuyasu!
C-C'mon! Come here for a sec!
This is just great...
Apparently a few thousand yen was fine,
but going over ten thousand made him reconsider.
I don't think he's trying to screw us over,
but since we're dealing with someone with the mentality of a little kid...
...no matter how we explain it to him,
he's gonna feel like we tricked him.
Let's be the bigger people here and let it slide.
We got ten thousand yen out of it, so let's not push it.
...I guess if you're cool with it, I ain't gonna fight about it, but...
This shit fuckin' pisses me off, man!
You sure he ain't playin' us for suckers?
He's not, Okuyasu. There's no reason to fight him on it.
We just need to set an example for Shigechi about how adults make agreements.
Heh, so ya can make some more money?
You sly dog!
But that's what I love about ya!
All right, we just wanted to say thanks for this.
Okuyasu...
Ya wants a drink?
If ya wants somethin' t'drink, I'll getcha one.
You're gonna get one for me?
I know! Calpis Water sounds good!
Den go gets some.
Ah! Hey! Why're ya throwin' that stuff out?!
They're just worthless crap tickets, like for the year-end lottery.
There's a reason I told Shigechi here
t'pick these things up!
You mean these losing New Year's Lottery tickets?
How do ya know they're losin' tickets?
No one would throw out a winning ticket, stupid!
There're loads of people who don't check their numbers an' miss out on winnin'!
If any of these win, I get half the prize!
Ya better fuckin' promise, dammit!
Sure thing! Half's good!
But I don't wants it if ya just wins stamps!
Man, you really like those cheap and annoying ways of gambling, don't you?
Ah, that ain't no good... How 'bout this one?
Y'know, I ain't so sure we can even claim lottery tickets
since we're still in high school an' all...
Lottery?
Note: In Japan, a custom stamp with your name on it is used in conjunction with a signature.
Should be fine as long as you got your ID and name stamp.
SG Group 121314...
Damn, this one ain't a winner neither...
I thought I'd have a good chance, but...
SG Group 121314...
Umm...
Hey, so, uh, if I happen t'win...
...do I gotta take it to the cops?
Dumbass! Of course you don't have to!
Harvest picked them up after they were already thrown away.
Anyway, you shouldn't even be
thinking about this until you've actually won.
Good luck with that!
The fuck?! SG Group 121314?!
SG Group 121314?!
SG Group 121314!
On Book: "Winning Numbers List"
Hey, what's all the yelling for?
Note: Prize...
Note: Prize - five million yen
Five million!
It's true! I fuckin' won!
What?! You better not be screwing with me, dammit!
Note: Five million yen
Yippee! It's a dream come true! A fantasy!
There ain't nothin' as good as this!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Cool it, Okuyasu!
Let's calmly confirm it one more time!
SG Group 121314... Prize, five million yen...
It's true!
It's too good to be true, but it is!
And since this thing was thrown away,
it would have just ended up in the incinerator, anyway!
We still have a few days before it expires.
When we get to the bank,
even if they start asking annoying questions...
...we can just confidently say that we bought it!
You got that?
I sure do!
This means the five million yen is ours!
I wonder what I should buy...
First, I'm gonna get some killer Italian shoes!
Then I'll buy a high-end suit with a sexy silhouette...
...and go all-out at Tonio's place
and eat the most expensive food he has!
I can even go overseas now!
I'm gonna put it all in savings!
Man, that's super lame!
M-My Harvest's the one who gots dat thing...
Five million... A-Ain't no way I'm givin' up halfa dat!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 19
Shi
gechi's
Har
vest Part 2
Shi
Har
gechi's
vest Part 2
Shi
Har