When I first happened to meet that horribly boring man...
...I was still attending community college.
He was going to a different, higher-ranked college than me.
Since I knew my friends would be jealous
if I went out with such a suave and cool man...
...I started dating him to feel better about myself.
We eventually had a son together.
Ah, right... Since it's three times the speed, the image quality...
Hey, Hayato. Shouldn't you tell your mother when you're home?
I'm home.
My husband isn't a bad man.
It's not like he's an alcoholic or anything...
And even though his pay is pitiful,
he always shows up for work.
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Still...
I married him without ever experiencing true love...
Hmph. Sounds like he's home.
The only words he understands are eat, shower, and sleep.
He's so boring...
I'm home.
Is dinner ready?
Oh, you're home? I didn't even hear you walk in.
I was busy today, so that's all there is.
But you like that stuff, right?
Is he mad at me?
If you're feeling angry, then go ahead and show me.
Too bad you'll sit and eat your food in silence like you always do.
Good evening! It's Morioh Radio!
Coming at you once again is yours truly, Kai Harada.
What are you doing?
How has this lovely evening been treating you all?
Coming up is the perfect song to cap off the day.
Episode 25:  Atom Heart Father
Fifteen minutes by car from Morioh Station...
That's where we found his house in the resort area filled with villas.
Or rather, the house that belonged to
Kira Yoshikage before he changed his identity.
Kira
Now he has a new face, household register, job, and a completely different place to call home.
I doubt he'll ever come near this place again.
He ain't got no corpses in the fridge, does he?
Even so, we had to search every inch of it.
Now that he's assumed a new identity,
his old house is the only place we'll find any clues.
Is that his photo album?
Looks just like him.
Kira Yoshikage...
Born in Morioh on January 30th, 1966.
175 centimeters tall. Weighs sixty-five kilograms. Blood type is A.
He was born to elderly parents.
His father, Yoshihiro, died of illness
when Yoshikage was twenty-one.
His mother died of old age shortly after.
In 1988, he graduated from
D Academy's Department of Literature.
That same year, he started working for S city's Kame Yu department store.
He transferred to the Morioh branch in 1993.
No previous criminal history.
No record of marriage. No close friends.
No girlfriend. No surgeries.
It's impossible to find him using
fingerprints, teeth, or surgery scars.
Talk about useless information...
Look. These trophies and awards...
High School Music Recital
Violin
3rd Place
Kira Yoshikage
They're all third place.
Middle School Track Meet
200 Meter Hurdles
3rd Place
Kira Yoshikage
He certainly wasn't a school hero.
Award
Grade School
Writing Contest
Overall 3rd Place
It's hard to tell exactly what he was good at.
Sports? Music? Writing?
He's positioned himself in every photo to not stand out.
He was most likely never the subject of envy or ridicule.
He's a man who keeps his strengths and weaknesses hidden.
Then that means...
It was all deliberate, of course.
He keeps his abilities and high intellect hidden.
He knew it was the only way to stay out of trouble.
I was hoping something in his house would
clue us in on some kind of hobby he has, but...
Hobby? Come to think of it...
...I remember seeing a bunch of jars in his drawer.
See?
Looks like they're some kinda paper scraps.
What do these numbers mean?
1983... Could be the year, I guess...
They smell kinda funny...
What do you think they are?
Looks like nail clippings to me.
Huh?
Wh-Whose nails are they?!
C-Could they be...?
No, they're his nails.
He didn't take them from his victims.
The data is in this notebook.
Data? You mean the numbers on the jars?
Are you saying he's been collecting
his nail clippings since 1983?
For the last fifteen years?
Gah! He recorded every finger! He's so meticulous!
Thumb
Index
Middle
Ring
Pinky
Middle
Index
Thumb
[Years my nails grew
more than 30cm]
Right Hand
Does this mean that in 1983,
the thumbnail on his right hand grew 31.5 centimeters?
1983 is the same year Sugimoto Reimi was murdered!
That's the same year his records begin.
It was probably around that time where he stopped being able to keep his murderous tendencies at bay.
Whoa! He's got his toenail lengths on the next page!
Looks like we found the hobby of a man who spent his entire life trying to appear as boring as possible.
Look.
Note: My nails grew more than 30cm. I'm on a roll!! No one can stop me.
This data gave him future insight.
Reminds me of how Jewish merchants used to observe the movement of sunspots to determine how well their businesses would do.
Similarly, Kira Yoshikage uses the length of his nails to determine how successful he'll be.
Naturally, it's how he decided when best to kill.
1999!
They've grown more than twenty centimeters from the beginning of this year until last June!
He's insane! What a sicko!
Unfortunately, this won't help us track him down.
There may be something else here.
Hold on...
Could there be someone else inside this house with us?
Seems like it. Josuke, stay on your guard.
You think he's working with a partner?
No. Definitely not.
Crimes can be traced from interactions with others.
A partner could possibly rat him out.
He wouldn't trust anyone.
Is that...?
M-Mr. Jotaro, look at the camera!
I-It's his father... Kira's father!
He's sitting right behind us in the photo!
But...
This is not good! This is so not good!
Does this mean he's a ghost?
Yeah. Considering Sugimoto Reimi is in a similar situation...
...it's possible that his father also couldn't pass on
to the next world and became stuck here as a soul's energy.
Look at his expression.
It looks like he wants us to get the hell out of here.
You trying to scare us with your ghost energy bullshit?
Still, this definitely means we shouldn't leave here.
Hurry up and answer the phone, slowpokes!
I'm the one making it ring!
Does it really look like I want you to leave?
It's the opposite, you halfwits!
I'm making that face because
I'm never going to let you leave this house!
Anyone who tries to stop my son will die.
You asshole!
You know about all the messed up shit your son is doing?!
Hey, somethin' wrong? What's all the racket?
Where are you hiding?!
Show yourself, you old-ass ghost!
Ghost?!
Josuke, he isn't hiding.
Huh?
It looks like Kira's father has been here this whole time.
Look.
When did he...?!
He's moving inside the photo.
That's how he was able to call us.
He probably threw the receiver from inside the photo, too.
Die...
Anyone who dares
prey on my beloved son will die!
Josuke!
It's possible to attack ghosts with your Stand!
Mr. Rohan used his Heaven's Door
to read Reimi's memories!
Asshole!
Take this!
What?!
D-Dammit!
Any damage done to us in the photo happens to us for real!
Hurry and restore it, Josuke!
We're being ripped apart!
Josuke! Mr. Jotaro!
That ability... I see!
You two have the same kind of abilities as my son!
Okuyasu, it's up to you!
Use The Hand to remove the old man from the photo!
Right! I gotcha covered, Josuke!
Huh?
O-Okuyasu?
Wh-What the fuck?!
How'd I run right into the window?!
M-My hands are popping out on the other side!
I can't reach you guys from here!
Is this...?
Dora!
A-A wall!
There's some kind of invisible wall here!
It won't break! I-It can't be!
You finally figured it out?
That's the frame of the photo!
It may look like you're still in that room,
but that couldn't be further from the truth!
I'm a ghost who lives within photos...
I can control the dimension created
within any photo I appear in.
I can also use the camera to trap energy from
the souls of the living inside the photos with me!
How's that for an ability?
This room is inside the photo!
If you damage the photo, the energy from your soul
will be hurt and transfer the damage to you, as well!
Inside the photo?
But I see everything right in fronta me!
If you're as dumb as you look,
you shouldn't bother thinking about it too hard.
After I kill these two, the rest of you are next!
J-Josuke! Mr. Jotaro!
Die!
You asshole! Cut this shit out!
Mr. Jotaro, what are you doing?!
Do something with that invincible Star Platinum of yours!
Josuke... I give up.
Huh?
I can't think of any way to stop this guy's attack.
If all the damage is just gonna come back to us...
...then even if I stop time with Star Platinum, we can't do a thing.
If something doesn't work, I give up.
What did you just say, Mr. Jotaro?
What the hell are you saying?!
Die!
Your heads went flying!
A-A knife!
Dorara!
What?!
I can't touch it! M-Mr. Jotaro!
I've given up on stopping the old man, but...
Huh?
If he controls any photo he's in...
...all I have to do is use the camera to take a photo of him, leaving him all alone.
What?!
I can't believe you avoided my attack! Shit!
Josuke, give him a good one-liner.
Just make sure it's cool.
You didn't scare me even a little bit, dumbass!
Th
The
The Ha
The Han
The Hand
Niji
Nijimura
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Nijimura Oku
Nijimura Okuyasu
Damn you!
You guys definitely have fighting experience!
I bet you've fought people with
the same kind of abilities as my son countless times!
He can probably get himself out of there since he's a ghost!
Ora!
Let's make sure he stays put and keeps his mouth shut.
There's definitely something in this house
that he doesn't want us to find.
That's why he attacked us.
I get it!
He ain't got a way out if he's folded in half!
No runnin' away for him!
Okuyasu and Koichi will search this room.
You and I will check the one on the right.
Now I can't even protect my son! Dammit!
If that thing falls into their hands...
Still, what could be in here
that he doesn't want us to find?
Can't say I thought too much about it...
So long as it makes Kira's old man
go white in the face, we're good.
I-I can't breathe...
I-It's too cramped here...
Please, cut me some slack!
Just make a tiny hole in the tape so I can breathe!
Y-You really can't breathe?
Hey, Koichi, he's just pretendin'! Pretendin'!
He's tryin' t'escape through a hole in the tape.
I-I know you probably don't believe me, but I'm in serious agony here!
I'm claustrophobic myself, so I understand how he feels...
Aww, put a sock in it!
You wanna give him an air hole so bad?
I gotcha, I gotcha! I'll give ya loads of air holes!
Usin' tacks, anyway!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Damn you! Let me out of here, you sadistic brat!
Looks like I got ya pegged now!
I ain't removin' none of those tacks.
Tacks? I can't see, so I have to assume
I'm attached to a post right now.
I just got a great idea!
Your tacks just gave me the perfect escape route out of here!
It's so simple! Thanks for that!
Anyway, later losers!
Ya fuckin' bastard!
What was that noise?! What didja do?!
Say somethin', goddamn you!
O-Okuyasu, this is bad! I think he got away!
Mr. Jotaro! H-He got away!
I-It's all my fault! H-He did somethin' usin' my tacks!
That was a trick, you moron!
Looks like I won this battle of wits!
What?!
I-Is this...?
What is this doing here?
It can't be!
It's the bow and arrow! But we already found it...
The bow and arrow should be
with the Speedwagon Foundation...
Is there another set?
Josuke, be careful! Kira's father escaped!
What?!
This arrow drew Killer Queen out of Yoshikage!
The arrow is the important part!
I'll never let you have it!
U-Use Echoes, Koichi! Have Act 1 go after him!
H-He's too far away!
Seriously?
The thing Kira's father didn't want us to find
was the bow and arrow!
F-Fuck! It's all my fault!
No, Okuyasu. He was just a stronger opponent.
Like father, like son.
We lost to their family's intense will to survive at all costs.
As long as the arrow is mine, everything is fine!
I'm gonna make even more enemies for you guys!
The bow and arrow, huh? I see.
I figured there may have been more than one set.
Now I know exactly how Dio and the others
gathered so many enemy Stand users in such a short time.
They created them all over the world
using multiple bow and arrows.
I assume Kira's father got this set
from that old woman, Enya...
...then eventually Okuyasu's brother, Keicho,
got a hold of one of his own and came to this town.
I suppose Stand users really do attract other Stand users.
Yoshikage, where are you right now?
You never could help but kill women,
even when you were a boy...
But if that's what brings you happiness, I'll protect you!
Because...
...you're my one and only son...
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
Kawajiri
What's gotten into you? You're actually cooking?
I-I mean, I didn't know you even knew how...
Two plates? Is one for me?
You want me to eat your cooking?
Are you out of your mind?
Hey! Clip your nails later!
Didn't you just clip them last night?
They must grow fast...
Oh! Th-This is actually really good!
A
At
Ato
Atom
Atom He
Atom Hea
Atom Hear
Atom Heart
Atom Heart F
Atom Heart Fa
Atom Heart Fath
Atom Heart Fathe
Atom Heart Father
Ki
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: n/a
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Kira
Kira Yoshi
Kira Yoshihiro
You poor kitty!
What happened?
Were you crying at the top of the tree all night
waiting for someone to let you in?
What's wrong with you?!
What made you think you could shut the window by the tree?!
It feels like every day I've had to tell you to leave it open!
What's wrong, kitty? Why are you so upset?
Cats just don't like water.
I'm sorry about that. I shut the window without thinking.
It won't happen again.
That's weird... He seems different somehow...
He cooked out of the blue for the first time last night,
and instead of using his electric shaver, he shaved his face with a razor.
He always gets razor burns when he uses a blade...
What's the deal?! You still haven't paid last month's rent!
You owe me 260,000 yen for this month and the last now!
Give me my damn money!
Rent?
You heard him! Hurry up and fetch it from the safe!
Safe?
Hurry! You know I don't know the combination!
Hey, what are you...?
I'm sorry you troubled yourself
to come so early in the morning, sir...
...but I'm afraid I don't have
quite enough money right now.
Huh?
Don't you mess with me!
It's not my fault you decided to rent my lovely house making the crap wages you do, you idiot!
Live within your means, stupid!
Umm, I'll get it for you in just-
No. You have me all wrong.
When I said I don't have quite enough, look.
I meant I only had a bit over 500,000 yen.
I can only afford to pay you for this month,
last month, and the next two months in advance.
Is that okay?
S-Sure, that's plenty!
Thanks a bunch!
Pleasure doing business with you!
Y-You...
Did you just steal that money from our landlord?
I'm not sure how you did it...
...but you grabbed it out of his bag, didn't you?
Most people would probably be afraid
and consider him human scum...
But my husband's actions...
Stealing all of that money...
For the first time, after living with him for so many years, I'm...
...I'm starting to have romantic feelings for him...
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 26
Rock, Paper,
Scissors
Kid is
Com
ing!
Scissors
Com
Rock, Paper,
Kid is
ing!
Scissors
Com