They're nothing compared to
the spirit of justice that's here right now!
It's definitely here!
There's no doubt about it!
Compared to that spirit, you're nothing!
I-I'm dreaming...
This... is just a dream...
To be cornered like this with nowhere to hide...
This must be a dream!
You ain't got nowhere...
...left to run away to!
You're finished!
J-Josuke looks really hurt!
While we were waiting,
it seems the battle had already begun.
This means...
...that's Kira Yoshikage!
Someone is injured over here!
Stand back! There's a gas leak that could cause an explosion!
Bring the ambulance over here!
Get me a stretcher!
This area is dangerous, so please stand back!
Are you okay?
Stand all the way back!
Can you hear me? An ambulance is on the way!
You're going to be fine.
Don't let her get near Kira!
We'll have you in the hospital and being treated in no time.
You have nothing to worry about.
You'll be fine. Don't worry.
Th-This is bad!
He turned that lady into a bomb!
How many fingers am I holding up?
Mr. Jotaro, you'll have to use Star Platinum.
I know.
But it won't help us unless I get closer.
Even if I stopped time, I'm too far away to do anything to him.
I need to be at least five meters closer.
So you've resorted to taking someone hostage and turning them into a bomb?
Just try me! I'll heal her up in a heartbeat!
No! This isn't as simple as him taking a hostage!
He has a hidden ability!
It's called Bites the Dust, and he can use it to blow away time!
Episode 39:  Farewell, Morioh: Town of Golden Hearts
I bet it only works on people who aren't Stand users, like me and that lady...
...and only when Kira is
backed into a corner with no way to escape!
Basically, when he feels completely hopeless, his ability activates and he can turn people into a bomb that will let him go an hour back in time!
Are you kidding me?!
The knuckles and skin on your hand are so soft and smooth...
You have such attractive, fair fingers...
Please, will you rub my cheek?
Huh?
Having my cheek rubbed is so calming...
When I was a child...
You've heard of Leonardo da Vinci's Mona Lisa, right?
The first time I saw that painting in an art book...
When I first saw it... How can I say this?
This is a bit unseemly, but...
...I had a throbbing erection.
I specifically cut out the portion of the picture with her hands and hung it in my room.
I would like to cut off your hands, too.
What are you doing?!
My name is Kira Yoshikage!
I've killed forty-eight women with beautiful hands thus far!
You're the only one!
You're the only one who will know my identity!
Th-This is bad! Bites the Dust is about to activate!
If we don't defeat him right now,
everyone but that lady will be blown up and die!
Mr. Jotaro!
Coming for me, Jotaro?
I gained the ability of Bites the Dust
precisely so I would never have to directly fight you!
Approach me, if you dare!
Just try and stop time!
How long are you able to stop it?
Go ahead and push me even further into a corner!
Bringing me to my limit will make Bites the Dust appear again!
Mr. Jotaro, stop time!
You can't let him trigger Killer Queen's switch!
Wh-What?
I'm at my limit! I'm going to trigger it!
Now!
I-I did it! It activated!
I've returned!
It worked once again!
Bites the Dust pulled through for me once again!
I've finally defeated them!
From now on, I'm free!
What was that?
The birds came from behind me, then...
What just happened?
Come to think of it, this isn't the usual route I take to work...
If Bites the Dust had succeeded in turning back time an hour, I would be on my way to work...
What time is it?
That's right. I forgot I had put my wristwatch in my breast pocket.
It can't be...
Why is it broken?!
It should be 8:29!
Bites the Dust should have taken effect!
This watch Hayato broke using Stray Cat
should have returned to normal!
Don't you realize what happened?
So that man in the photo Rohan took
named Kawajiri Kosaku really was Kira Yoshikage...
This is finally over now, isn't it?
After all this time, they finally cornered you, Kira Yoshikage.
And just who are you?
You don't remember me?
I suppose that isn't a surprise.
You encountered me fifteen years ago.
Something very traumatic must have happened to you.
Something so traumatic that it
made you forget what happened.
Are you a new Stand user?!
You don't understand! You've died!
What did you say?
This isn't a Stand ability!
This is proof that all that remains of you is the tainted black soul of a serial killer!
Well? Now do you remember how you died?
If I stop time now, I still won't be close enough!
You can't let him trigger the switch!
I'm at my limit! I'm going to trigger it!
Now!
Act 3! 3 Freeze!
He is now within five meters!
S-H-I-T!
You fucking pieces of shit!
Star Platinum! The World!
Koichi, you really are a guy I can rely on.
I'm glad I came to this town and met you.
Anyway...
Gimme a break.
I made it in time.
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Resume time.
H-He did it!
He made it in time!
I'll trigger it... I'm gonna trigger it...
I'm going to... activate Bites the Dust... once again...
Wh-What happened?
He suddenly flew backwards!
I'm gonna do it... I-I'm really gonna do it...
I'm... gonna trigger... the switch now...
I know he's our enemy, but this is appalling.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
There's someone on the ground behind you!
What?!
Th-This is terrible!
This man was run over by an ambulance!
I didn't realize he was there!
Forward! Drive forward!
All of you! Get outside of the tape!
Get back! Get back immediately!
Were you injured, too?
It's too late. He's dead. Died on impact.
He's dead?
It's like he intentionally dove under the tire...
I take full responsibility.
I'm not trying to make any excuses,
but I didn't have a chance to restrain him.
Unbelievable.
His head was crushed between the tire and the pavement...
The skin on his face tore clean off.
Excuse us.
Do you happen to know the identity of the deceased?
He told me his name was Kira Yoshikage.
Kira...
There's a family by the name of Kira
in Kotodai who go back generations.
I heard the only living member lives alone, so he may not have any family.
An accident...
He was killed by complete accident...
This is a fitting end.
The legal system wouldn't have been
capable of properly punishing him.
This is the best we could have asked for.
I... I never really got along with my Papa very well...
But that man... He murdered him...
I wanted him to be punished.
I wanted anyone who could punish him to help me.
You seem to remember now, Kira Yoshikage.
You remember how you died.
I can tell you do!
What the hell are you?!
Who the hell are you?!
Fifteen years ago, you didn't have a Stand ability, so you couldn't make corpses disappear.
That's why, when I died, it made major news.
Do you remember the wound
you gave me on my back?
Or perhaps you don't remember since it was
your first murder and you forgot to take my hand with you!
It's you...
Your name is... Sugimoto Reimi...
Why have you been waiting here for fifteen years?!
Wait...
Why would you go to the trouble of showing me
the wound on your back and telling me who you are?
This wouldn't happen to be the place where you're not supposed to turn around, would it?
My father once told me there was a road
in this town where the spirits of the dead roam...
...and that if you ever found yourself there,
you should never turn around.
If you were to turn around,
an unstoppable power would drag you off somewhere.
You weren't trying to force me to turn around
by showing me the wound on your back, were you?
You wouldn't ever consider deceiving me like that, right?
I'll have you turn around instead.
Hmm? I'm curious to see what will happen.
Come on! Turn around!
You will turn around!
Do you really think I wasn't
expecting you to pull a stunt like this?
We've waited here for
fifteen years for you to show up...
We?
Arnold!
What?!
The time of your punishment is at hand, Kira Yoshikage.
What? What are these things?!
Killer Queen!
Make these things explode!
I-I...
Wh-Where are these things going to take me?!
Who knows?
But...
...I'm sure it's a place where you'll never rest in peace.
At long last...
...we can finally go.
The two of us...
Reimi! Are you really leaving for good?!
It would be okay if you stayed
for a little bit longer, wouldn't it?
It feels like our town is losing its guardian angel...
I feel anxious knowing you're leaving!
Thank you! But we have no business
left to take care of in this town.
The time has come for us to leave this place.
We have to go.
What about you, Rohan?
Are you going to miss me and cry once I'm gone?
Don't be absurd!
Why would I ever miss you?
You already died fifteen years ago.
I've said it before, but I firmly believe you ghosts would find more relief by not clinging to earthly attachments and passing on from this world.
Oh, fine!
Since this is the last time I'll see you, I'll be honest!
I'm going to miss you!
I don't want you to leave!
Yo!
Josuke! Everyone!
It's finally over, Reimi!
Yukako! Hazamada, and everyone else!
We have arrived to see you off!
Everyone...
This is kinda weird to say
to a dead person, but take care.
I'm gonna miss ya, too!
You're a wonderful young lady.
Reimi! Thank you for everything!
This town is finally safe thanks to you!
Thank you, Koichi.
But in my heart,
I believe it was all of us who saved Morioh.
I promise nobody here will ever forget you.
Thank you, everyone.
Goodbye, everyone!
Goodbye, Reimi!
Goodbye...
He's awfully late tonight...
Must be overtime at work.
He could have called, at least...
Oh, Hayato...
Go ahead and eat before it gets cold.
I'll eat once Papa gets home.
Hayato?
I'll wait for him, too...
Once Papa is home...
...I'll eat with you, too...
Really?
By the way, have you gotten a bit taller recently?
Our town, Morioh, was deeply hurt.
It was hurt by the monster it spawned named Kira Yoshikage.
Hayato's mom will wait forever for her husband to return.
Shigechi's parents will also wait forever for him to return.
The families who had daughters and sisters killed
by Kira Yoshikage will forever await their return, too.
The pain from their wounds will only ever grow deeper.
How can we possibly ease their suffering?
Will their pain threaten the future of this town,
or will it eventually fade?
I honestly don't know.
Are you worried, Jotaro?
About leaving this town?
Yeah, a bit.
After watching Josuke and the others become involved in
this incident in Morioh, I can only come to one conclusion.
The young people in this town have golden spirits.
The same golden spirits shining with justice
as those we met on our journey to Egypt.
I see it in Josuke and the others.
They'll be fine if they cling tightly to it.
We'll never have to worry about the safety of this town.
Hey, Gramps!
Can you hear me, Gramps?
Well, I suppose I should say goodbye
to the son I'm so proud of.
That photo I gave you of my mom...
You still got it?
Of course!
Put it right in my wallet, just like you asked!
Although I'm leaving without seeing her,
I wish her nothing but happiness!
So, you really did put it in your wallet...
I've got the edge of that photo!
Crazy Diamond!
I'll be taking this!
A good dad should give his son an allowance anyway, right?
If I let you take that photo home with you,
your old lady would just get pissed at you again!
Y-You little brat...
Gonna take back what you said
about his golden spirit, Gramps?
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Take care!
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze,
through the tunnel past the tower's beams
The invisible baby's mother was never found,
so Mr. Joseph Joestar ended up adopting her.
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
Mr. Kujo Jotaro received his doctorate from a thesis he wrote
about the starfish population on the beach here in Morioh.
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
Josuke, you little shit!
You ate the snack I was saving for myself again!
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Ugh!
I'll just have to drink his juice!
Let the voice of love take you higher!
Koichi!
I'm sorry!
I was busy making us lunch and lost track of time!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
Huh? You made us lunch? Thanks!
1999 Bizarre Summer
I can't wait to eat it!
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
So good!
Oh? Oh, here it comes!
Fuck yeah! It's real intense!
Maybe it'll turn ya back t'normal, Pops!
Song of praises hibikase
Song of praises rings far and wide
Brand-new up town surechigau keshiki
Brand-new up town feel it coursing through the land
Well, whatever.
kumo no kirema ni sasu, hikari ga hora furisosogi
Watching the silver lining in the clouds,
a brilliant light comes pouring in
My skin is so soft!
My eyes feel so clear!
The food here was so good!
inishie no komichi e sasoikomu
And is drawn into that familiar old alleyway
Right? I'm so much sexier than before,
I don't even know what to do with my bad self!
kirameki (kirameki)
Our glimmering (Our glimmering)
Yutie-pie, you're glowing!
So shiny!
michibiku machi
Town will show the way
Hmm, think so?
I'm glowing, eh?
tagiru ougon no spirits
To those with golden spirits
Grazie!
sore wa hateshinai kizuna
Who share an eternal bond
I most patiently await your next visit.
I just saw Munchkin holding hands
with this really pretty girl!
Let the joy of love give you an answer!
Huh? Was he really?
He hasn't told me a thing!
wakare no toki sae kudakenuishi de
With a meaning which is unbreakable even when we're apart
Did you hear about how Mr. Kira went missing?
I did! You're talking about how they
found him as a faceless corpse, right?
1999 Bizarre Summer
How awful...
What're you gonna do about this?
Huh?!
jibun norikoe tsukami tore mirai
Surpass yourself and take hold of the future
That can you kicked sprayed juice
all over my comic book!
Not my problem!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
All right. Warm-up routine complete.
Is looking toward the town all the time really that interesting?
Nothing ever changes.
It certainly is.
Let the voice of love take you higher!
I find this town to be quite fascinating.
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
For most people, the summer of 1999 came
and went just like every other summer before it.
Let the joy of love give you an answer!
Wakare no toki sae kudakenuishi de
With a meaning which is unbreakable even when we're apart
Hey, didja hear?
I heard Rohan got caught stealin' somethin' at Kame Yu!
1999 Bizarre Summer
Huh?!
Seriously? That's pretty weird.
I know! But I ain't too sure it's true...
Kawasu yuki ga umu sanka
Our shared courage will give rise to a song of praise
You're not sure it's true?
Jeez... Anyway, let's go!
Great Days!
The End