July 15th (Thursday) 4:43 PM
It's open. Come in.
Mr. Rohan?
Where are...?
I'm here, Koichi.
Mr. Rohan!
What's wrong?
You didn't really explain much over the phone...
I'm in need of your assistance.
I'm under attack by an enemy Stand.
Huh?!
A-A Stand? Where is it? Where?!
On my back. My back has been possessed!
Your back?
Umm... Your back is being attacked?
Precisely. This Stand is extremely dangerous!
I'm at a loss for what to do.
Can you show it to me?
No.
But if you don't show it to me...
It will transfer over to you and kill me in the process if I do!
Hurry up and burn 'em, 'kay?
You see? It's talking! This is it, Koichi!
Huh?
Why are you hiding it from me?!
Did you call me over just to mess with me?
What are you saying?!
I just told you I would die if I showed you my back!
It would be just like you
to mess with me like this, Sir!
I knew something was up.
You're wrong! I couldn't be more serious right now!
There's a corpse upstairs!
Huh? A-A corpse?!
Uh... What are you doing, Sir?
Climb over me and go on ahead!
Please, go on ahead of me! Please!
Jeez, what is with you?
Well? Now do you believe me?
It's gone!
It can't be!
Right here, Koichi!
Look, Koichi! This is Kinoto Masazo!
He had the life sucked from his decaying body,
and now he's all dried up!
Wow, that's amazing! It's really convincing!
But this is a bad time to be
messing around like this, Sir!
The new Stand users created by
that old man in the photo are still coming after us.
You made me rush over here thinking you had been attacked or something!
Excuse me?
Then this thing is...
Anyway, stay safe!
Bye!
W-Wait, Koichi!
I purposely asked you first since I knew those shit stains Okuyasu and Josuke would never believe me!
Please believe me! We're friends, aren't we?!
Koichi!
Don't feel blue, 'kay?
'Cause that's really gotta sting!
I, Kishibe Rohan, have never faced such humiliation in all my life!
You little creep... You'll regret this!
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
July 15th (Thursday) 5:25 PM
Recently, my nails have been growing too quickly.
Episode 34:  July 15th (Thursday) Part 4
Much too quickly.
That woman running her fingers
through her beautiful, well-cared-for hair...
You're lucky. Today won't be the day I pick you as my victim.
You'll be safe until I can completely
blend into Kawajiri Kosaku's lifestyle, at least.
So like, whenever I leave the house,
my dad starts following me and checking out where I go and stuff.
You just keep going out too late.
Yeah, and whose fault is that?
Now I'm like, super pissed off at him,
so I stole something right in front of him on purpose.
That's why I'm going to your place with you.
You serious?
The cops are probably looking all over for you right now.
Hey... Why did you just touch my bag?
What's wrong?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
You a pickpocket?
Trying to get touchy-feely? Give me a break.
Aww, crap! We're already at Morioh!
Come on, it's our stop.
That hurt, man!
What's your deal?
Watch where you're going for once in your life!
Hey, did you see that?
His nail clippers looked like a bowling pin.
Having a pair of bowling pin
nail clippers at his age... What a loser.
July 15th (Thursday) 5:07 PM
You got the photos?
Hey... Where're you taking 'em?
The Morioh Grand Hotel.
Going there is my only hope.
Wanna see Jotaro? It's no use going there, 'kay?
Just give up and burn the photos!
Good job!
Though who knows who could be
watching you from a window...
This is pretty risky!
Ya see now, 'kay?
Every street here has an intersection!
'Kay? Good luck getting across!
Someone'll see your back!
The roads only get wider from here,
and we'll see even more people.
So let's not go! 'Kay?
You'll never make it across!
Is that so?
Kinoto Masazo managed to make it to my home.
Therefore, he must have also crossed this intersection.
If I can figure out how he did it, I, too, can cross.
He must have done it... like this!
This is incredibly embarrassing,
but I should be able to make it to the station this way.
Not bad, Kishibe Rohan!
But you forgot something!
While Kinoto Masazo was crossing,
I didn't do anything to stop him!
Hey, retard! Get your ass in gear!
What did you just say?
'Kay?
Uh... hey! Turn the fuck around!
What did you say?!
You're the one who forgot something, Cheap Trick.
I have something Kinoto Masazo didn't...
I have my Heaven's Door!
Note: I cannot turn around for one minute.
What?!
Good. I shouldn't have any more issues
making it across without exposing my back.
You'll receive your comeuppance soon, you pest.
Wh-What did you say?
You're never gonna make it!
You're gonna die with your dick all shriveled up!
Go ahead and keep running your mouth.
Your only ability is to talk,
and I've already taken care of that.
Wh-Wh-Who the fuck do you think you're talking to?!
July 15th (Thursday) 5:32 PM
I don't believe I'll run into any major intersections for a while.
Hey, your Heaven's Door works on animals too, right?
Yes, if the animal is sufficiently intelligent.
Then if an animal sees your back,
I can transfer over to it, too!
It's even easier than a human seeing it, huh?
I'll just have to be careful around animals, too.
I hate cats.
The way they glare at you creeps me out.
Hey, shoo!
What?! Impossible!
So just one of 'em's gotta see your back, 'kay?
It's true my only ability is to speak...
But listen, 'kay?
You humans aren't the only ones I can speak to!
I called these animals here!
They hate your guts!
I told them all you love killing cats and dogs!
Get him!
Heaven's Door!
I-It's no use! There's too many of them!
I won!
3 Freeze!
These animals have done no wrong!
I ask that all of you leave at once. Shoo.
Th-That Stand...
Koichi!
What?!
I thought maybe you were just messing with me...
...but part of me was still worried,
so I came back and saw you still acting weird, Mr. Rohan.
You kept using walls to hide your back,
and I saw you crossing the street back-to-back with a total stranger.
So you really do have an enemy Stand on your back.
This is precisely why I came to admire you in the first place!
You're a true friend!
It's on your back, right?
All I have to do is remove
the enemy from your back, right?
Echoes 3 Freeze!
Heavy...
H-He did it!
A bit naïve, huh?
I'm using my ability to stick to your back, not my strength!
Trying to force me off your back is still gonna kill you!
Huh?!
Why don'tcha tell Koichi, 'kay?
Hurry up and tell him!
M-Mr. Rohan?
K-Koichi...
I'm glad you came here to help me, and forever grateful...
...but I must ask that you withdraw Act 3 right away.
You can't see it, but my back has begun to tear ever so slightly...
Act 3! Undo your 3 Freeze!
S-H-I-T! Understood!
M-Mr. Rohan! A-Are...?
I'm far from fucking okay, Hirose Koichi!
It's your fault I'm hurt, isn't it?
Get it now? You'll never get rid of me!
Peeling me off your back, Rohan,
means you'll have to peel your entire back off along with me!
Hey...
This's just gonna wear you out.
You're either gonna pass out from exhaustion and pain...
...or go insane and kill yourself!
Find the meanest Stand you want,
but it'll never beat my ability to speak!
'Kay?
That Stand on your back! Just what kind of...
What kind? You want to see...
...what kind of Stand it is?
Fine...
I'll... just have to show you!
M-Mr. Rohan!
You finally lost your marbles!
Guess you finally gave up on getting to Jotaro, too!
Jotaro?
I hadn't intended to go see Jotaro in the first place.
This was my destination.
I was so happy to have finally made it here
that I couldn't help but laugh.
What're you blabbing about?
You showed someone your back!
Now I'm gonna transfer to Hirose Koichi!
Th-This place... That mailbox!
Cheap Trick, you turned around in this alleyway.
Even if you had chosen not to turn around knowing the nature of this place...
...because of your ability,
you would have been forced to look Koichi's way, anyway.
Wh-What?!
This is Reimi's alley,
where you can't turn around no matter what!
It's true that if any Stand tried to get rid of you,
no matter how they did it, it would still hurt me, too.
But there exists something that will get rid of you alone...
Something that takes only those who look back at it!
Something that will only take your soul!
Lemme go, 'kay?! Lemme go!
Where're you taking me?! Hey!
The afterlife.
I couldn't tell you if Heaven or Hell truly exist...
...but just in case, I'll write this in for you.
Note: I'm going to burn in Hell.
Even though all it could do was talk,
dealing with it was a pain.
Koichi, if not for you, I never would have made it here, and it would have killed me.
But I had no idea we'd end up here
since that thing was distracting me!
Reimi!
Did you take these photos, Rohan?
I did.
Something about them bothers me...
Ch
Che
Chea
Cheap
Cheap T
Cheap Tr
Cheap Tri
Cheap Trick
Kinoto
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Kinoto Masa
Kinoto Masazo
July 15th (Thursday) 6:04 PM
Hey, did you hear what Mika got?
Her boyfriend bought her some super expensive earrings.
Buy some for me, too!
I will next time!
What the hell are you doing in my apartment?!
Hey, don't come in here!
Hmm... A one-bedroom apartment...
My name is Kira Yoshikage.
Would you be kind enough to tell me yours?
My nails have grown quite long, haven't they?
Just look at them.
Does there exist a person capable of
willing their nails to stop growing?
There doesn't.
Much like how one cannot will their nails to stop growing...
...one cannot halt the destiny they were born to fulfill.
You still haven't told me your name.
M-My boyfriend... What did you do to my-
Don't answer a question with a question!
Didn't they teach you in school never to answer a question with a question?!
I asked you to tell me your name!
M-Minako! Mi-Mi-Minako!
Minako...
That's a beautiful name your parents gave you.
I like it.
Minako, there's something I must request of you.
It would make me happy if you held onto these.
I want you to clip my nails with these "loser" nail clippers.
Have you ever clipped someone else's nails before?
There's a first time for everything.
Be careful not to clip them too short.
Help me... Please...
Help... Please forgive me...
Forgive you?
Hold on a minute...
I'm not mad at you or anything.
I just enjoy this.
I chose you since you suited my tastes.
I was born with these tastes,
so I completely accept them as part of me.
Completely, indeed...
I overheard you asking your boyfriend for a new pair of earrings.
He left these ones just for you.
It's a present.
You're very good at clipping my nails. I like that about you.
I also like how cute you are when you're silent.
What shall we do together, Minako?
I would love to take you home with me,
but it's too risky to bring you near the Kawajiri household.
Still, this is so refreshing!
So refreshing, indeed!
Th-The man and woman he followed from the station...
He killed them and made them disappear!
That's... Hayato!
What is he doing in a place like this?
This is the opposite direction from the house and his school...
What is that?
I didn't lock the door...
Hayato... He...
He couldn't have...
He isn't human!
What the heck is that thing disguised as my Papa?!
There's evidence they've been back here...
And there's a blood stain on the floor...
Did he finally make his move?
July 15th (Thursday) 8:36 PM
The object in Hayato's hand was definitely a Handycam.
I can't find it anywhere in his room...
Hayato...
He's been acting strange since the other day.
I need to find out what he was doing there, no matter what!
I must know for sure.
C-Calm down...
I need to calm down and think...
First, this videotape...
Should I show it to someone?
I can't show Mama!
She trusts him completely.
Should I show the police?
Would they believe that a person got blown up and disappeared?
But worst of all, he isn't human...
Could the police even catch someone like him?
No... Could anyone in the world even catch someone like him?
What should I do?
Mama and I will be killed eventually...
What am I supposed to do?!
Would you mind if I joined you...
...in the bath, Hayato?
It's been a while.
I-I'm gonna get out now...
Come on, don't do that.
You and I are family, after all...
Wh-What does he want from me?
I'll be in big trouble if he finds this tape!
Excuse me, Hayato, but could you let go of the bucket?
I need to fill it with water to wash myself.
I-I can wash your back for you, Papa!
That's a great idea.
However, I should wash yours first.
You got in the bath before me.
I'll wash your back, then you'll wash mine.
Now, sit down.
What's the matter? I can tell you're sweating quite a bit.
Is it too hot in here?
Y-Yeah...
Then why are you shivering?
Isn't it strange to shiver when it's too hot?
You're tickling me, Papa!
You know I've always been really ticklish!
How could I forget?
You certainly always have been ticklish, Hayato.
I-I'll wash my front...
I see. You'll do it yourself?
By the way, I just remembered something...
This evening, I was in the Jozenji area in the opposite direction from home...
...and I saw you there...
Huh?!
...with a video camera!
What were you doing there?
Now I know for sure!
This little brat was watching me!
How could this have happened?
I thought I could peacefully blend in with this household...
This year has been filled with nothing but misfortune...
It's been awful.
Killing this brat will bring a lot of unwanted attention to myself...
...but after what he's seen, I have no choice!
I've turned one of the strands of his hair into a bomb...
If I create a small explosion near his head,
it will appear as if he slipped and hit his head on the hard floor...
An accident like that is nothing unusual.
I must kill him!
Now die, brat!
Are you going to kill me, too?
Even though I have video footage of you...
...and am filming you right now?!
What?
I've been suspicious of you for a long time!
Your shoes not fitting and the time you spent practicing your signature are all on video!
I have other tapes of you, too!
I even have footage of that cat-like plant up in the attic!
I'm the only one who knows where the tapes are!
If something happens to me,
I'm sure someone will find them!
What?
You better not lay a finger on me! Got it?
You little shit! You dare threaten me?!
I won't let you touch Mama, either!
Episode 35
An
other One
Bi
tes the Dust Part 1
An
Bi
other One
tes the Dust Part 1
An
Bi