Look over here.
M-Mr. Jotaro! L-Look!
Be careful, Koichi! Don't get any closer to it!
Hey, I told you to look over here!
Is that his Stand?!
M-Mr. Jotaro!
H-He's here! He's trying to take the jacket!
Gimme a break...
I can't believe he chose now to pick up his suit...
That jacket is important evidence!
Wait!
Don't make any hasty decisions without thinking.
Something about this Stand...
...seems really dangerous!
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 23:  Sheer Heart Attack Part 1
A bomb... It's a bomb Stand!
Is this how he got Shigechi?
No wonder we couldn't find his body!
H-H-He's getting away!
Don't pursue him, Koichi.
Huh? Don't pursue him?
Are you serious?
If we catch him,
we'll know for sure who killed Reimi and Shigechi!
We need to act carefully and deliberately, Koichi.
Wh-What are you saying?
Not seeing the name tag inside the jacket was unfortunate.
However, just from looking at the jacket,
we can infer that this guy is about 175 centimeters tall.
He's unmarried and works an office job.
If he had a wife, he wouldn't have brought his jacket here for a simple button repair.
He's somewhere around twenty-five to
thirty-five years old, and wealthy to boot.
Judging by the material and design,
his jacket is a designer brand.
Even if we let him go, we've significantly
lowered the number of potential culprits.
I-I see...
W-Wait! That doesn't mean we shouldn't go after him!
He's a murderer!
It's not that I don't want to, but we can't.
That bomb Stand is still hiding somewhere around here.
Huh?! His Stand?
Y-You saw it?
I didn't, but it has to be here.
We need to carefully exit through the door.
It has to be? Wait a minute...
How can you say that for sure
when you can't even see it?
If he were the kind of guy that would leave
right after killing the store owner...
...there's no way he would have gotten away
with his crimes for the last fifteen years.
He'll get rid of any evidence.
In effect, he'll get rid of us.
Wait a minute...
Don't you think you're being a bit paranoid?
If his Stand isn't here,
then the serial killer and his jacket must be long gone by now.
Listen up, Koichi.
Observation doesn't mean looking around, it means looking around carefully.
Note: Look... Carefully.
To not just listen, but to listen well.
Note: Listen... Well.
If we don't...
...we're as good as dead.
H-He's acting like he knows everything,
but my Echoes isn't useless!
Is Mr. Jotaro underestimating me
even though I've grown so much stronger?
Do you really think that bomb Stand
is still somewhere around here?
We're gonna look pretty dumb if it isn't!
Look over here!
I-It really was here!
If I don't get it off me, it's gonna explode!
Star Platinum!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
It took all my punches... This thing is tough.
It's gonna explode!
Star Platinum: The World!
I hate drawn-out battles, so let's finish this right now.
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Y-You did it! You must have stopped time!
Now we can touch it all we want, and it won't explode!
Those who search for I, Kira Yoshikage...
...will perish in an explosion.
My Stand, Killer Queen's Sheer Heart Attack,
always eliminates its targets without fail.
N-No way! Star Platinum's power wasn't enough to destroy it!
A-A Stand that's this tough... Impossible!
Stand back, Koichi!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
It's still coming for us! It hasn't even slowed down!
Get back, Koichi!
Even though you've hurt yourself from attacking it...
...it still hasn't been damaged at all!
You need to get farther back, Koichi!
Ora!
Oww, oww, oww, oww!
What are you doing?!
It will explode if you keep touching it! Let it go!
Ora!
Look over here!
Gimme a break. I've never encountered such a sturdy Stand.
My resolve is gonna break before this thing does.
M-Mr. Jotaro, we're gonna get
blown to bits if we don't do something!
You need to get farther away!
I'll rip it apart for sure this time.
L-Listen to me for once!
If a Stand is controlled from far away, it can't move with that much power!
So if you consider the power behind
that thing's explosive attacks...
There's no way that kind of power
is possible unless the user is nearby!
The user has to be at most fifteen...
No, ten meters from here!
And?
And?! It's only ten meters!
My Echoes has a fifty meter range!
It can find the serial killer!
I already told you, Koichi. Don't go after him.
Right now you need to be able to protect yourself with Echoes.
Don't send it away from you.
Wh-Why?!
The killer is long gone from here.
His Stand is remotely controlled.
I've been through enough Stand encounters
to know it when I see it.
Look over here!
Its actions are too simple to be the result of direct control.
You know it when you see it?
That makes no sense!
There's no way such a powerful Stand
could be controlled remotely!
The user is definitely close!
Mr. Jotaro isn't taking me seriously!
I've grown a lot stronger!
I can find the killer and defeat him myself!
Distance, ten meters!
Th-There he is! It's him!
He's holding the jacket!
But this doesn't make any sense... H-He's too far away!
He's more than fifty meters away!
And he's getting farther away!
He's outside of Echoes' range!
H-His bomb Stand is being controlled remotely?!
That's impossible!
That much power working from so far away makes no sense!
Look over here!
Wh-What? It's coming for me!
I figured it out!
His Stand chooses its target
by attacking where it senses the most heat!
That's why it's so powerful,
despite its user being so far away.
Call out Echoes and protect yourself!
Even if I stop time, you're too far away!
O-Oh no!
Echoes...
...is still fifty meters away near the killer!
I'm sorry!
Gimme a break...
Star Platinum: The World!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
That thing attacked the store owner first
since he was holding a hot drink in his hand.
Then it targeted Koichi since his body temperature rose after he started getting worked up.
If it senses something hotter, it should target that first.
Resume time!
I was right.
It targets whatever is giving off the most heat.
I'm saved...
But come to think of it, if the heat from a person's body is enough to set it off, then being near a fire...
This power!
Huh?!
Mr. Jotaro!
Sh
She
Sheer
Sheer He
Sheer Hear
Sheer Heart
Sheer Heart A
Sheer Heart At
Sheer Heart Atta
Sheer Heart Attack
Ki
Power: A
Speed: C
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Kira
Kira Yoshi
Kira Yoshikage
How could this happen?
This is all my fault, Mr. Jotaro!
It's all because I went after the killer!
If you hadn't stopped time and started the fire to protect me, it wouldn't have gotten you!
Wake up, Mr. Jotaro!
Mr. Jotaro! Mr. Jotaro!
That explosion was not set off by a person!
Look over here.
It's trying to finish us off!
It's way too strong!
It's just like Mr. Jotaro said!
It will attack anything giving off
more heat than a human body first!
Look over here!
Now's my chance to run!
I need to call Josuke!
He can heal Mr. Jotaro!
I have to call him!
This is... the kitchen!
There's loads of heat sources in here!
I need to buy some time so we can escape through the door!
There's a phone!
W-Wait a minute... This isn't a gas stove!
Why did this house have to have an electric stove?!
It's gonna take too long to warm up!
The oven is electric, too!
Wh-What should I do?
I know! This should have some hot water in it!
Target this!
It's empty!
Look over here!
Wait... Now that I'm observing carefully like Mr. Jotaro said...
...I know what this thing's weakness is!
A weakness I didn't think of earlier!
I'm starting to get really mad!
Why should I have to be a coward and
run away in fear while asking God to save me?
It should be the other way around!
And why the hell should I be the one who feels like they'd rather be searching for a public restroom with a bad case of the runs?
That's ridiculous!
If anyone should be running away in fear...
...it's you, you serial killer!
It's been attacking the hottest targets this whole time...
...but that's exactly what its biggest weakness is!
Being relentless is its biggest weakness!
It's been almost three minutes...
I don't know what's going on at that shoe store...
...but there's one thing I know to be truer
than anything else in this world.
Sheer Heart Attack has no weaknesses.
It will track down its targets, no matter what!
With that taken care of, now I can finally call Josuke!
Hopefully he's home right now...
SFX: Sizzle
It's lost track of us for good.
Have fun chasing that sizzling sound effect around forever!
It's just like a donkey chasing a carrot
dangling in front of its face.
That's your biggest weakness.
Hello, Higashikata residence.
Josuke, it's Koichi! We're in trouble!
Mr. Jotaro is hurt bad, and it's all my fault!
Just hurry and get here!
What did you say?! You can't just drop that on me!
I don't know what you're talking about!
Just hurry up and get over here! We finally did it!
We found the serial killer!
I captured his Stand!
You captured what now?!
Hey, I still don't understand! Where are you?
Wh-What's going on?
It's hot! I turned it off, but it keeps getting hotter and hotter...
What's with this piece of junk?
How are you supposed to cook with this?!
Hey, Koichi! You gotta tell me where you are right now!
Look over here!
Damn! It's ignoring the sound effect and coming this way!
Koichi, where are you? Hurry up and tell me, stupid!
I'm at Centipede Shoes! Hurry!
Damn! The sound effect on Echoes' tail...
It got destroyed in the explosion!
That damage...
That explosion was not set off by a person!
Look over here!
I-It's coming! It's coming after me again!
But I can't use the tail's sound effect anymore...
Wh-What can I do?
How can I fight it?
Echoes Act 2!
What's going on? Echoes Act 2!
Act 2!
Where are you, Act 2?!
Why won't you come?!
Act 2! It was killed in the explosion!
It split in half!
N-No, wait!
If the explosion had killed it,
I would have died along with it since I'm its user!
I-I remember now!
There was another time Echoes looked like it had died!
I-It...
C-Could it be?
Echoes Act 3!
Umm, do you want me to call you sir?
What is your command?
D-Does this mean I've grown?!
My Act 3 is amazing!
What is your command?
Well, I don't know what you can do yet, s-so for now...
Protect us, Act 3!
Umm, will you protect us, please?
You can do that, right?
Understood.
This wind!
M-My Stand is so fast now!
It's even faster than Act 1 and Act 2!
Finishing Blow: Echoes 3 Freeze!
H-Hey, Act 3?!
This enemy is strong. My punches were ineffective.
Ineffective?!
The enemy possesses a very heavy power.
S-H-I-T!
I was outmatched.
Outmatched? Are you kidding me?!
I told you to protect us!
I have succeeded in protecting you.
Just as I was commanded.
Look over here!
You succeeded?! In what way?!
You're completely useless!
I haven't grown at all!
Look over he-
Wh-What?
This is taking too long...
Why is Sheer Heart Attack taking so long?
Wh-What's going on? My left hand just...
My hand that released Sheer Heart Attack suddenly feels...
Good sir, is something the matter? Is everything okay?
Oh, it's fine. I'll pay for the broken cup.
I'm leaving, so could you get me the check?
Th-This is...
M-My left hand... is so heavy!
S-Sir?
I-Impossible! My left hand! My left hand...
It feels like someone attached a heavy weight to it!
What's going on over there?
Are you okay, sir?
D-Don't mind me...
Please, let me help.
It's heavy!
What are you doing, sir? How could you?!
It sank into the pavement and can barely move...
Act 3! What did you do? This power...
3 Freeze!
I just combined three and freeze.
Act 3, what kind of power is that?
Why is it moving so slowly? Tell me!
I simply afflicted it in way beyond your comprehension.
My hand feels so heavy...
Sheer Heart Attack somehow became incredibly heavy...
This is bad. I need to get it back...
I need to get Sheer Heart Attack back at all costs!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 24
Sh
eer Heart
Att
ack Part 2
Sh
Att
eer Heart
ack Part 2
Sh
Att