Greetings, all. It's Morioh Radio!
Coming at you once again is yours truly, Kai Harada.
Have a listen to our first song of the morning!
Okay, let's eat.
Oh, that's right... I have a present for you.
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 21:  Kira Yoshikage Wants a Quiet Life Part 1
Mr. Kira? Umm, Mr. Kira?
Mr. Kira, if you aren't busy,
would you like to have lunch with us?
Sorry, but I'll have to pass.
I need to go deliver these documents.
I'll see you later.
Give up on him!
He never feels like socializing with anyone.
Whenever we have him with us during group outings, I can never tell if he's enjoying it or not.
Kira Yoshikage, age thirty-three, single.
Even though he's dedicated to his work
and gets it done efficiently, he has absolutely no passion.
I'm sure he's a decent guy, but he's really plain.
Now, now, what have I done to upset you this time?
The new women at work simply
invited me out for lunch, nothing more.
I already promised that
I would be having lunch with you...
...and I'm very much a man of my word.
You heard me decline them immediately, didn't you?
Have I ever left you by yourself? Hmm?
Anyway, you shouldn't concern yourself with it, so let's just pick out our sandwiches and leave.
Here. Which one would you like?
Doesn't the bread feel incredibly moist?
This place is popular for its sandwiches
since they're made with bread freshly baked at 11:00 AM.
By 1:00 PM, they're usually completely sold out.
You can feel their warmth right through the wrapper.
The cutlets they use in their sandwiches
are crispy and freshly fried, too.
Oh no...
You pierced the wrapper,
and now all the sauce is spilling out...
You naughty girl.
Well... Since this one has a hole in it,
let's buy the one below instead.
Thank you very much!
Morioh is such a beautiful town!
Could there possibly be another town as beautiful as ours?
It feels like we're having a picnic.
She's beginning to smell foul...
I suppose it's about time the two of us broke up.
I'll sever all ties.
"Sever" all ties...
Perhaps I'll find a new girl vacationing here or something.
Oh, it's just a dog.
Oh?
Shigechi!
Guh?
Mr. Josuke, Mr. Okuyasu!
Yo! You're just the guy we were lookin' for, Shigechi!
This is kinda short notice,
but could you lend us some lunch money?
We forgot to bring money today...
Huh? Whatcha talkin' 'bout?
You fellers gots all dat money from da lottery!
We put it all in savings!
It's a big pain in the ass goin' to the bank for a little lunch money!
All we need's a thousand yen!
Yeah!
C'mon, can'tcha?
We'll go to the bank right after school!
That bag! You got a sandwich at St. Gentlemen, didn't you?
You got there before they sold out?
Dis's all mine! Y'all ain't gettin' nuthin'!
Guess I gots no choice... I'll gives y'all da money...
That's the spirit!
Thank you!
I'm gunna puts a lil' note in my planner,
so y'all better pays me back!
You're the one who never pays us!
Lesse... "June 24th."
Anyway, thanks again for helping us out, Shigechi!
"Lended 1,000 yen"... Lended?
See ya!
Umm, how's dat kanji for lended go again?
Lended...
Oh wells!
I jus' gots t'write it in hiragana!
I dunno how t'write Josuke an' Okuyasu in kanji, anyways.
Huh?
M-My sandwich!
Wh-Where'd it go?!
Ah, yeah, it's right dere!
I dunno how it gots dere, but oh wells.
Th-That's...
Hey, Mr. Josuke, Mr. Okuyasu, waits fer me!
Y'all still gots t'put your thumbprints in my planner!
Your thumbprints!
Did that really just happen? You little brat!
Did he take my bag after mistaking it for his own?
Man, what a pain...
How can we even do that right now?
That's easy! Ya just gotta cut your thumb with a knife!
I-It don't gots t'be like dat!
Well, jus' signs it fer me.
Hey, let's get a move on to St. Gentlemen!
They're gonna sell out!
This is bad... If he opens that bag...
She's wearing the ring I bought for her!
And she's covered in my fingerprints...
Once the police get involved, it will only be
a matter of time before they trace the ring back to me!
I, Kira Yoshikage, haven't left behind
a single piece of evidence in fifteen years.
I'm not about to let some brat ruin everything!
Josuke, we gotta hurry!
Yeah!
I'll waits fer y'all outside.
What should I do?
I need to take it from him.
My best course of action is to
take it while he isn't looking.
Shigechi!
You're one lucky son of a bitch, dammit!
St. Gentlemen is already sold out of
sandwiches for the day! Dammit!
Oh, really?! Dey's all solds out?
Ain't dat a shame!
If ya likes, I'll gives ya mine fer jus' ten thousand yen!
You're such a fuckin' cheapskate!
Guess we ain't got no choice. Let's go to Hokaben, Josuke.
Hokaben, huh?
We won't be able to get enough food with a drink if we only spend five hundred yen each.
Should be enough if we just get
our regular school lunch, though.
Koichi said he was getting school lunch, too.
No way! He's with Yamagishi Yukako, ain't he?
Ya expect me t'eat lunch with those two lovebirds?
An' anyway, the school lunch meat's just a milimeter thick...
...an' do ya got any idea what
that shit in the miso soup really is?
Y'know, dey gots lotsa drinks in
da prep room at my school's gym!
Da gym teacher's always in dere
sneakin' coffee an' tea an' stuffs.
'Cause all da teachers're in da break room fer lunch,
I sometimes gets t'sneaks in the window and gets some, too.
Wanna gets yer lunch an' go with me t'school?
What the hell, man? Are you stealing from your school?
You're a total cheapskate!
Least we can do is buy our own drinks!
We ain't that greedy!
See ya!
Gah, I was jus' tryin' t'be nice...
Bye-bye! Oh, an' ya better be payin' me backs tomorrow!
Oh, 'scuse me, mister!
I should be watchin' wheres I'm goin'.
I'm sorry!
Damn...
It's good that he separated from his friends,
but he's going back to school.
He must be waiting to eat there...
What should I do?
They called him Shigechi, didn't they?
He'll definitely open the bag within the next few minutes...
This is very bad...
Finally, I gets t'eats my lunch in peace an' quiet!
Whoopsie! Almost forgot!
I gots t'brew my coffee b'fore I eats my sandwiches!
Always gots t'have my coffee b'fore I leave!
You're very fortunate, Shigechi.
I would have eliminated you if you had caught
so much as a glimpse of the contents of that bag.
Hey, Josuke! This's the place!
Not as big as I thought...
Wh-What?
They said they weren't coming here earlier!
Shigechi, you here?
Shigechi!
Oh, heya! If it ain't Mr. Okuyasu an' Mr. Josuke!
We thought about it,
and we decided we could go for some free coffee.
We got ourselves a five hundred yen
rice, fish, meat, and veggies lunch!
Hmph! An' y'all were callin' me a dirty ol' thief...
Y'all gots some nerve!
C'mon, you don't need to be like that!
Sometimes people change their mind after a little while!
What should I do?
Eliminating one of them would be simple,
but all three at once is too much...
Damn! She's only a few centimeters away...
Shigechi, get me a drink, too!
I'll have Japanese tea instead of coffee, though.
There any black tea? Like milk tea?
Yucky! Yer gunna eat dat stuff with milk tea? Dat's nasty!
Damn! He's going to eat his lunch up there!
At this rate, he's going to open the bag right in front of them!
Aww, soy sauce again...
These cutlets always come with soy sauce...
Huh? Cutlets are supposed to be eaten with soy sauce.
Huh?! Stupid!
They're supposed to be eaten with cutlet sauce!
Ya gotta use cutlet sauce since it's got the same name!
Who cares?
I have it!
Wh-What?
Damn!
Huh?
Morioh Landmark #7
St. Gentlemen Bakery
Location: Two minute's walk from
the bus stop near Budogaoka
High School. It's the bakery on
the green road leading from the
station.
St. Gentlemen is renowned for its
delicious bread cooked inside a
stone oven. Typical customers include
students, housewives, and office
ladies. Their most popular food item
is their sandwiches, which
consistently sell out.
Damn!
Huh?
Hey! What're ya doin', Mr. Josuke?!
Ya wasn't tryin' t'steal my sandwich, was ya?!
Of course not! Don't be stupid!
I heard a weird noise near your bag,
so I went to take a look.
Don'tcha dare ever touch it!
No way ya'd jus' be lookin' at it!
"Dat dere teriyaki chicken sandwich is my favoritest one, Shigechi!
Gimme a bite!" is whatcha was thinkin'!
You sure are a selfish little guy...
You got my tea yet? Where's my tea?
Don't forget my milk tea!
I was jus' about t'make 'em!
Now!
I did it!
I gots yer tea!
I gots the Japanese tea an' da milk tea.
All right!
Thank you!
What's your problem?
Wh-Where d-didja puts my sandwich?!
Huh? Oh?
Looks like it's gone.
But we don't know where it went. Right, Okuyasu?
Yeah.
Quit messin' around!
How couldja not know?! Y'all're da only ones here!
Seriously, we have no idea!
Yeah, we ain't messin' with ya or nothin'!
No joke, we really ain't got a clue.
Y-You jerks! I'm abouts t'get real mad!
We're telling the truth!
You really gotta cut this shit out!
Why would we take your sand-
I'll know if y'all're lyin' soon enough!
I jus' gots t'get Harvest t'look through da room!
You're a real fuckin' pain! Go ahead!
Look around as much as ya want!
We have no reason to steal your sandwich.
What's going on?
I can't see what they're doing from here...
What is that brat up to?
Hey!
I can hear you in there!
Dat's da gym teacher!
Damn! We need to get out of here, Shigechi!
B-But my sandwich!
We don't have time for that!
Get back here!
Damn, I can't believe those kids.
I knew something was up when my coffee and tea
kept disappearing so quickly. No wonder.
I need to lock this place up more carefully.
It was a bit messy, but...
...I managed to overcome that difficult situation and successfully retrieve her.
I, Kira Yoshikage, have always felt
the guiding hand of lady luck protect me wherever I go.
As long as my actions are carefully planned and carried out without hesitation...
...I truly believe I can live
the rest of my life out in happiness.
What a close call.
I'm so happy that you've returned to me.
Gotcha!
What da heck's a feller like you doin' with my sandwich?
An' what're ya doin' bein' all sneaky
around my middle school?
Would you happen to be talking to me, little boy?
I haven't a clue what you're talking about.
This is my sandwich.
I bought it at St. Gentlemen earlier.
Nuh-uh! Dat bag's mine!
I gots proof dat it's mine!
You jus' ain't smart enough t'gets it!
Gets it back fer me, Harvest!
Wh-What? What's going on?
The bag is being pulled...
Wh-Wha... Wh-Wha... My sandwich...
Is... Is dat somebody's hand?!
What have you done? Now you've seen her...
And what's more, brat...
...you seem to have the same kind of power that I do.
Ya can sees my Harvest?
Tell me, what's dis hand?!
Why's ya walkin' around with a hand in yer bag?!
Are you by yourself? Those two friends of yours...
I believe you called them Josuke and Okuyasu?
Do they also have powers like yours?
Hey! Don't move!
Move even a little an' I'll attack!
Yer a real creepy feller! Stay away from me!
Yer givin' me da heebie jeebies!
Don't move! Don't move at all!
My name is Kira Yoshikage. I'm thirty-three years old.
My house is a villa located at the northeastern point of Morioh
with all the others, and I'm unmarried.
I work for the chain store Kame Yu,
and I'm always home by eight o'clock at the latest.
I don't smoke, but I do occasionally drink.
I'm in bed by eleven o'clock to ensure that
I get a full eight hours of sleep, no matter what.
Before going to sleep, I always drink a warm glass of milk
and do my twenty minutes of stretches...
...so that I can sleep soundly until morning.
Like an infant, I wake up feeling
no fatigue or stress in the morning.
My doctor told me I had no health issues
during my latest checkup.
Wh-What're ya sayin' t'me?!
I'm trying to explain to you how I live my quiet life.
I take care to avoid troubling things,
such as making enemies...
...winning or losing, and anything else
that could cause me restless sleep.
It's the only way I've found to cope with society.
I've gone to great lengths to ensure my continued happiness.
However, if the need to fight arises, I won't lose.
Simply put, Shigechi...
...you are a nuisance that will hinder my sleep if left unchecked.
That makes you my enemy.
D-Dat's...
Killer Queen! This is the name I've chosen for it.
Before you can speak another word,
I'm going to completely eliminate you...
...so that my sleep will go undisturbed tonight.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 22
Kira Yoshi
kage
Wants a
Quiet
Life Part 2
kage
Quiet
Kira Yoshi
Wants a
Life Part 2
kage
Quiet