Josuke, haven't you played enough already?
Turn it off right now or I'll do it myself!
Gimme five more minutes! Please!
I just need five more minutes!
It starts to get really intense at this part!
If I quit now, I'll never reach this point ever again,
and it'll weigh on me for the rest of my life!
Enough excuses! The kicking won't stop until you turn it off!
Do you really want me to live with that, Mom?!
Your back starting to hurt yet?
I-I lost...
Crap...
Now put it away and do your homework!
And would it kill you to take off your uniform when you get home?
It's already evening!
We can never see one another again...
Why, Sachiko? Do you not love me anymore?
That's weird. I thought I turned it off.
It isn't that... I just want to get out of this town.
Will you forget me while you're away?
Huh? It won't turn off.
Guess Kujo Jotaro isn't leaving town like I asked him to...
Can't say I didn't warn him!
Hey. How's it going, Higashikata Josuke?
It's you!
Red Hot Chili Pepper!
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 11:  Red Hot Chili Pepper Part 1
What are you doing here?
Took you long enough to notice me!
I've been coming over to check up on you every once in a while.
What?!
Has he seriously been spying on me this whole time?
I've also paid a few visits to Keicho's younger brother.
That idiot, Okuyasu.
I also learned about Hirose Koichi's Echoes
and that Yamagishi Yukako chick since we last met.
Plus I heard Hazamada Toshikazu and
Kobayashi Tamami got sent to the hospital!
I just wanna know why you waited so long to reveal yourself...
...considering you've been sneaking around
like a spineless coward this whole time.
Maybe I'm reading this wrong,
but you don't think you'll be able to kick my ass, do you?
Kick your ass?
I don't wanna do anything like that.
I just wanna kill you nice and quick.
That's a bad joke no matter how you slice it, good sir!
I already told Jotaro this,
but Star Platinum could be enough to defeat me.
Jotaro himself is always on top of things,
and Star Platinum's ability to stop time could be an issue.
Anyway, the main reason I came here was to test out how much stronger my Stand got since we last met.
Before I duke it out with Jotaro,
I wanna test my strength against you, Higashikata Josuke.
Come a bit closer.
Closer! Until you're close enough to attack
just as quickly and precisely as Star Platinum, Josuke!
Come on! If you're too far away,
it'll feel like you're punching me with wet noodles!
You mocking me?
Not at all!
I just see right through your abilities.
So get over here and hit me as hard as you like!
Right here. Hit me right here. Come on! Come closer!
Huh? H-He's so fast...
Quit daydreaming!
Dorararara!
He's way faster than I expected!
If all you're gonna do is daydream,
I'll put you to sleep for good!
Consider this a warning!
Mr. Jotaro's Star Platinum is even stronger than this!
I made a big mistake...
I got cocky and underestimated him...
Dora!
What?!
Josuke! What's with the racket?
The Stand power behind that attack
felt like the force of a jet engine...
He may be even stronger than Mr. Jotaro...
You're pretty tough, Josuke!
Your Crazy Diamond really caught me off guard!
Guess I'm not the only one who toughened up.
I'll keep waiting.
Unless my Red Hot Chili Pepper grows stronger,
it'll never defeat Jotaro.
That thing can appear anywhere there's electricity...
Plus it's really strong and can be remotely controlled by the user.
Josuke, what was all that noise?!
I didn't hear a thing!
Gah! I just got a bug bite!
Man... Ya'd think the bugs're in love with me or somethin'...
Ah, Josuke!
Hey! Sorry I kept you waiting.
What didja wanna tell us, Josuke?
Did we really gotta meet in a place like this?
Got somethin' against Tonio's or the usual café?
I'm not the one who called you guys out here. Mr. Jotaro did.
Mr. Jotaro did? What does he want?
Probably something about Chili Pepper.
What?! Chili Pepper?
You mean that Stand, Red Hot Chili Pepper?!
Finally showed up again?
Yeah, it did. Last night at my place.
Bastard! Why didn'tcha tell me?!
Okuyasu... His whole attitude changes
when Red Hot Chili Pepper is brought up.
It's hard to blame him since it killed his brother, but...
I told Josuke not to say anything.
It's dangerous to talk openly in a town with running electricity everywhere.
Mr. Jotaro!
I had you guys come out here so it wouldn't overhear us.
Okuyasu, Chili Pepper really pisses me off, too.
It got inside my house without me even noticing it.
It can overhear anything we say and take whatever it wants.
Now that you mention it,
my homework from the other day disappeared from my desk!
I thought my mom had confused it for trash or-
That doesn't matter right now, Koichi!
The only reason Chili Pepper hasn't been
causing problems for us is because it knows we can beat it.
But it could very well be dragging people through the phone lines
with as much effort as it takes to make a prank call.
Not to mention, it may have already started using the bow and arrow on more people.
I saw how much stronger it's become with my own eyes.
We have to figure out where its user is hiding, and fast!
B-But how?
That's exactly what we're here to figure out. Right, Mr. Jotaro?
No, not quite.
Finding him isn't a problem.
There's a guy arriving at Morioh's port tomorrow who can do it.
Huh?
There's a guy who can find him?
Is he a Stand user?!
He is.
His Stand is called Hermit Purple.
Only problem is that he's too old and frail to fight anymore.
Too old? Just how old is he?
Mr. Jotaro, you know this guy?
Yeah. I know him pretty well.
He used to be pretty buff...
...but you wouldn't have guessed that now.
He's eighty... No, about seventy-nine years old.
Seventy-nine?! He's super old!
His legs have become weak, so he uses a cane.
Two years ago he had to have gallstones removed, and he also suffers from cataracts.
He has a full set of dentures and complains that he can't eat T-bone steaks anymore.
He's started to become forgetful.
Are you serious?
You're not gonna tell me he chats up mailboxes in his spare time, are you?
This is crazy!
I gathered you guys here to discuss
how we'll protect him once he gets here.
If Chili Pepper finds out about him, it will probably kill him.
The thing Chili Pepper fears most is us finding out who its user is.
Yeah... But can an old guy like that really help us?
I tried stopping him, but he decided to come to Japan himself after hearing about the bow and arrow.
To Japan? Mr. Jotaro, is he a foreigner?
Yeah.
Josuke, th-this is serious!
Huh? What? What is?
Josuke, if this guy is a
seventy-nine-year-old foreign Stand user...
Y-You can't mean...!
Thanks for all the juicy info!
Red Hot Chili Pepper!
No way! How did it find us here?
Morioh Landmark #4
Morioh Grand Hotel
Location: From bus stop #1,
take the bus headed for the Morioh
Grand Swimming Area and
disembark at the Morioh Grand Hotel
stop. From there, it's a short walk.
Located near many expensive villas,
it is an elegant hotel with a rich history.
A wide variety of guests have stayed
there, and it is beloved by all. The beef
tongue served at the hotel restaurant is
considered a delicacy and is
always the talk of the town.
Wh-Why?! How did it get here without a power line?!
The bike's battery!
Dammit! It must have snuck here inside the bike's battery!
In my bike?
It heard everything!
The port at noon?
There's some decrepit old Stand user who can find my user?
I'll kill him the instant he reaches port!
Now it knows about Gramps...
...and by the same token, Josuke's father!
This is bad.
If we let it get away, it'll get to Gramps before we do.
Josuke! We should try destroying the bike by throwing a rock at it!
Nah, hold it.
If anyone's gettin' revenge on that motherfucker...
...it's gonna be me, Nijimura Okuyasu!
He erased the air!
Keicho's younger brother!
You an' I got unfinished business!
Get ready t'be erased!
Okuyasu, I gotta hand it to ya...
...teleporting directly to the bike was a bold move.
But that long swiping motion you do with The Hand...
...is way too slow compared to
the full speed of my Red Hot Chili Pepper!
So slow it hurts!
Ya ain't payin' attention, stupid.
The thing I was tryin' t'erase...
...was the bike!
The front wheel!
You ain't gettin' away that easy!
Way to finally think ahead, Okuyasu! You got it!
Chili Pepper isn't gonna wander too far from the bike's battery.
And look over there!
The closest power line is over a hundred meters away!
It's as good as caught!
That was close!
No, I wouldn't call it caught just yet.
It can still use the bike's battery to its advantage.
It's gonna do whatever it takes to kill Okuyasu and escape.
Let's go!
Got it!
You think you got me cornered here?
Still want revenge for your brother Keicho?
Nope.
My big bro...
...was askin' t'die.
I knew he'd get himself killed.
He was doin' bad stuff...
And when ya do bad stuff like my big bro did,
it always bites ya in the ass before long.
Even a guy like me knows that.
If ya tell me who your user is and where he lives, I'll letcha live.
You'll let me live if I tell you?
Can't say I expected you to be this calm.
I thought you'd be foaming at the mouth with rage by now!
Nothing'd make me happier than if ya didn't tell me!
I could erase the fuck outta ya, dipshit!
I knew it!
But do you really think you can?
With a pathetically slow right hand like that?
Should I be laughing, or taking a nap right now?
You're making this really hard for me!
Fucker!
I'm gonna kill ya!
Let me demonstrate to you just how slow your Stand really is!
See what I mean? It's slow as shit!
Okuyasu!
Sh-Shit!
Jotaro's coming...
I need to make a break for it.
What?! He's behind me?!
Maybe I missed, but I still erased the space...
...so I could teleport right to ya!
Didja forget I could do that?!
Gotcha now!
Ya fuckin' jerk!
Looks like ya got a lot slower.
Ya think you can dodge my next attack?
Look! Red Hot Chili Pepper's electric spark is fading!
It's getting weaker!
It must be running out of Stand power!
Does this mean Okuyasu beat it?
Okuyasu! Don't kill it yet!
Wait for us to get there!
You won!
We still have to get it to tell us where the bow and arrow is!
It's true... I'm getting weaker...
Your Stand has a slow right hand, but it's still scary as hell.
But be honest...
Are you sure it's a good idea not to finish me off?
Maybe I'm just pretending to get weaker, Okuyasu.
What?!
Did you stop to think maybe I'm just waiting for Jotaro to get closer so I can slice his head off?
The fuck are you talkin' about?
Doesn't really matter!
What're you gonna do? Finish me off now...
...or wait for Jotaro to get here?
Damn you...
Hold on... Why wouldja tell me that?
If it'd said nothin', it coulda tricked me an' beat me an' Mr. Jotaro...
So that means, uh...
'Cause it says it's okay, I got zero chance of gettin' attacked, right?
You got a death wish or somethin'?!
I'll let you figure that out for yourself!
Is it tellin' me the truth?
Or is it lyin' t'me and it's really okay?
I dunno which one!
You gonna attack me or not?
If it's okay, I gotta finish this right now!
But maybe it's tryin' somethin' sneaky on me...
What should I do?!
Okuyasu... Something's wrong...
Okuyasu, just make up your mind already!
Fuck this!
All this thinkin's makin' my head hurt, dammit!
Okuyasu!
Ya ain't gonna stop me, Mr. Jotaro!
This fucker killed my big bro! I'm gonna end this!
Deep in my heart, this's the only thing I know I gotta do!
You're dead meat, motherfucker!
Great. It's gonna be a real pain in the ass
to find the bow and arrow now.
At least this is finally done with.
No, something's not right.
It looked like Chili Pepper was goading him into attacking.
Huh?!
There're electrical cables underground?
The fuckin' liar! It wanted me t'dig this up!
I really was weakened.
That bike only had a 12-volt battery.
You almost had me there!
Ya little...
I'm even stronger than before thanks to you!
Okuyasu!
If you had been an obedient little dipshit and done what Jotaro
told you to do, I would have died when the battery ran out of juice!
Wha-
I've memorized the locations of all the electrical lines in this town!
I wanted to use them to escape, but the bike was too far away!
I didn't have the strength to dig them up myself!
Dammit... Ya fuckin' bastard!
Now it's even...
Now I can use the underground electricity
to finish you off for good!
Okuyasu!
Your brother, Keicho, used to say you were nothing but a hindrance.
I guess nothing's changed!
You're just as dumb as a little kid.
You never stood a chance of avenging your brother, you dumb shit!
Bye-bye, Jotaro, Josuke!
That guy's name is Joseph Joestar, right?
I'll make sure that old fart shares
the same fate as the Nijimura brothers!
I win!
Okuyasu!
It dragged him in!
Gimme a break...
Can't believe it escaped after we had it cornered.
It's a pretty dangerous Stand.
It can be controlled remotely, and it has near infinite power when it has direct access to power lines.
What? What are you two talking about?!
Why are you calmly talking about the enemy's abilities
when Okuyasu just died?!
That's right. I guess we should take care of Okuyasu.
I suppose so.
Talk about a silver lining.
Okuyasu really lucked out here.
It's a good thing his arm got chopped off.
Huh?
Crazy Diamond!
If I heal his arm, it will force his body to come back.
Goddammit!
Hooray! Okuyasu is back!
Shit! I-I...
That motherfucker totally got me...
Fuck! Fuck!
This isn't about revenge or winning or losing.
We have to focus on keeping Joseph Joestar safe, Okuyasu.
He'll be able to help us defeat Red Hot Chili Pepper.
You need to stay strong. Everyone's counting on us!
Our entire town is at stake...
Mr. Jotaro, this isn't looking good.
I wasn't taking this seriously enough before.
Yeah. We need to get to Gramps' ship before Chili Pepper does.
Let's go.
Hey, you two!
Aren't you acting a bit too cool about this?
Okuyasu's still in shock!
We'll reach the port faster if we go this way.
You're right.
Wait up!
Can I be better than my big bro?
Ya sure taught me a lesson, Chili Pepper.
Mr. Joestar...
We'll be arriving at Morioh's port any minute now.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 12
Re
d
Hot Ch
ili
Pepper Part 2
Re
d
Hot Ch
ili
Pepper Part 2
d
ili
Re
Hot Ch
Pepper Part 2
Re
Hot Ch
Pepper Part 2
d
ili