Another tiring day...
I wish I were at home relaxing already...
K-Koichi?
Hazamada?
Hey, how's it going?
Thanks for everything the other day...
Umm, are you feeling better now?
Kinda. They let me leave the hospital two days ago.
Where's that asshole- I mean, where's Josuke?
He already went home.
I heard he found an invisible baby yesterday,
but he's still trying to figure out who her mom is.
Is the baby a Stand user?
Apparently.
She gets upset and turns everything invisible when Josuke's dad, Mr. Joestar, isn't around.
So this Mr. Joestar guy is gonna stick around for a while, then?
I think so.
I see...
Oh yeah, Koichi, you like reading comics?
Comics? Sure, as much as anyone, I guess.
Ever heard of Kishibe Rohan's Pink Dark Boy?
Pink Dark Boy? Of course I have!
I'm a huge fan!
Really?! You like it?
It's considered "horror suspense," right?
A few of the scenes are really gross...
...but it really pulls you in with its
thrilling action and realistic characters, doesn't it?
You're totally right!
You know Kishibe Rohan actually lives in Morioh?
Huh?!
What?! He lives here in Morioh?!
No way! You can't be serious! Seriously?!
I couldn't believe it either!
But I heard some realtors mention where he lives!
I know it sounds like I'm making this up, but it's true!
So, you wanna see if we can
snag ourselves some autographs?!
Definitely! Let's go!
You and I think alike!
You think so?
Kishibe
Over there!
You think that's his studio up there?
The light's on!
You're right...
I wonder if he has any family living here.
I heard he lives alone.
He made his debut at sixteen, and now he's twenty.
Twenty?! He's so young!
He became a pro at my age...
Koichi, we shouldn't waste our time waiting out here.
Kishibe
Try ringing the doorbell!
Huh?! M-Me?
Come on! You should listen to me since I'm older than you!
I'm too nervous!
What? That's not fair...
Episode 14:  Let's Go Visit the Comics Artist's House Part 1
That face!
Kishibe Rohan!
He looks just like his picture from
the New Year's Deluxe issue!
Uh, I mean Mr. Rohan!
H-Huh?
Who are you two?
What are you doing here? Pulling a prank?
N-No! We would never!
Umm, we're students at Budogaoka High School!
W-We're big fans of yours, Sir!
Fans? Of mine? You're readers?
So my address was leaked...
N-No, uh... I just overheard it somewhere!
I know this is really sudden,
but we'd be stoked if we could get your autograph!
Fans of mine, eh?
Excellent.
Perhaps we're on the same wavelength.
Huh?
Nothing, don't mind me. Come in.
I'll whip up autographs for both of you, no problem.
Yes! Coming here was a great idea!
Here's a thought...
As long as you're here, would you like a tour of my studio?
Huh?
You'll let us inside your studio?!
I've finished up my work for today, so if you'd like...
We do!
After you...
Thanks for letting us in!
In here...
Whoa, this is the coolest!
Wow! Raw four-color manuscript!
So cool!
Seeing it in person like this feels way more impactful!
I-I can't stop crying! I-I-I'm so glad we came here!
How long have you been working in Morioh?
I moved here about three months ago.
I mostly grew up in S city,
but I also lived here for a time as a child.
Living in Tokyo is convenient, but frenetic.
The constant hustle and bustle make it
much more difficult to work there than in Morioh.
Besides...
...using fax machines and copiers like we have nowadays...
...I've created a system in which I can submit a completed manuscript in a mere four hours.
Living in the city serves no purpose anymore,
other than to achieve worthless status.
Umm... Where are your assistants and other staff?
I have none. I draw by myself.
Huh? All by yourself?!
You draw nineteen pages of detailed art in just one week?!
It only takes four days. Five if there are color pages.
Really?!
It allows me to take trips in my spare time.
I'm not much of a people person,
which is why I chose to become a comics artist.
Dealing with an assistant would only increase my workload.
That's really impressive! Wow!
You're a genius!
Please excuse me.
Whoa, a s-spider!
This truly is the suburbs...
So many bugs and spiders...
Umm... Sir?
Fascinating... It's an Araneus ventricosus...
This particular species is found in homes and mountainous regions across Japan.
Despite being an orb-weaver,
this species actively weaves webs night and day.
By the way, do either of you know what the most important element of a compelling comic is?
Reality!
A sense of reality breathes life into a piece of work,
and goes hand in hand with entertainment.
Most assume good comics indulge in
imagination and fantasy, but this is completely untrue!
The drawings I create stemming from my past experiences
or works that have moved me are far more compelling!
Taking this spider for example, most city dwellers
would have been repulsed by it and attempted to kill it.
As a comics artist,
it's imperative that one knows how its legs connect...
...where its eyes are, and how to tell the difference between a male and a female in order to accurately draw it.
Knowing a spider's webbing hardens when exposed to air is one thing, but one must also know which hole that webbing comes from...
...and how its internal organs are laid out.
When a spider's belly is sliced open,
how does it suffer before death?
One must know these things to accurately depict reality!
That's horrible!
Horrible?!
Who are you to criticize me, Kishibe Rohan?!
N-No! I wasn't trying to criticize you! I'm sorry!
I should see what it tastes like.
Comics artists really are just as weird as everyone thinks they are!
Excellent! That nauseated expression...
A perfect representation of vomiting!
I need to sketch it!
R-Really?
You're faking it now.
Never mind. I won't do it.
I'll gain nothing from it.
I-I'm sorry...
You wanted autographs, yes?
I'll go fetch my autograph pen from the kitchen.
I'll bring out some tea, as well.
Oh, you don't have to...
But wow! I had no idea...
Pink Dark Boy must be so amazing since he
goes so far to learn about the stuff he writes about...
Uh, Hazamada...
I know we just got here, but...
But, umm, maybe we should go home...
Go home? You wanna go home? Why? This is so cool!
I don't really have a good reason, but...
I have a bad feeling about all this!
I'm not usually very perceptive, but...
...I get the feeling Mr. Rohan is more dangerous than he lets on.
Dangerous?
You think he could be a Stand user?
No! I don't think that! It's just, uh...
You shouldn't assume Mr. Rohan is a Stand user
just because he's a bit eccentric!
I'm not saying he is...
I just said I have a bad feeling.
Besides, if Mr. Rohan is actually a Stand user,
doesn't that bode well for us?
It would mean we share something in common
with a famous comics artist!
But fine, have it your way.
If you've got a bad feeling, we can head home.
We can come back later.
However!
I wanna look at that folder before we go!
Huh? What folder?
Jeez, you're so slow, Koichi!
Sitting on the desk, next to the phone!
Take a good look!
Oh! C-Could it be?!
Yup! He said he just finished working, right?
I've had my eye on it this whole time!
A completed manuscript for
the next chapter of Pink Dark Boy?!
Does that mean nobody else has seen this yet?!
We can go home after I get a look at it!
Shouldn't you ask him first?
Koichi, you don't know comics artists at all!
These manuscripts are top secret
before they go off to the printers!
He'd never let outsiders like us read a manuscript before even his editors had a chance to check it!
I'll take a quick peek, then put it right back.
That's even worse!
It's fine! I'm not hurting anything!
Huh?
What is this feeling?
His comic is always thrilling,
but is this the impact you get from reading a raw manuscript?!
It's giving me goosebumps!
It's so good!
Hurry up and turn the page, Hazamada!
I feel so moved!
It's true...
My manuscript is compatible with the two of you after all.
I figured you would read it.
Only those who are the first to read
my manuscript and are compatible with it...
H-Hazamada...
K-Koichi...
...will have their hearts opened by my ability, Heaven's Door!
A-Ability?!
My hand!
K-Koichi! What's going on?!
Morioh Landmark #5:
Comics Artist Kishibe
Rohan's House
Location: One minute's walk
from the Kotodai 2nd Street
bus stop.
Grounds: A mansion with an attic
situated on 340 square meters of land.
Attempting to visit is futile since
Rohan will pretend to be out.
The human body is capable of storing
vast amounts of information.
Including all your thoughts and memories
from the time of your birth.
To access this information,
I've turned you both into books.
Books that have chronicled every moment of your lives!
Help me!
You read my comic as well, correct?
H-Hazamada!
It's happening to me, too!
My ability can't physically harm you, so don't worry about it.
Wh-What are you trying to do?!
I told you earlier that a sense of reality
is crucial to making a good comic, right?
Reading about your lives and the things you've experienced
will make for excellent realistic material.
This information isn't obtainable through interviews!
I'll get a 100% realistic glimpse into your life,
as if I had experienced it myself!
Hirose Koichi. Born March 28th, 1984,
at 6:27 AM at Red Cross Hospital in S city.
You were born premature at 2325 grams, and spent a week in an incubator.
You're from a family of four,
and your older sister's name is Ayana...
Hmm...
Your elementary school and
middle school days were fairly typical.
You have a very honest personality.
I find that commendable.
What's this?
What is this ability I see you have?! Echoes?
There are others besides myself who have abilities?!
You, too?
Stand users! Incredible...
Your life since April of this year has been extraordinary!
You've had nothing but incredible experiences since then!
Higashikata Josuke, Kujo Jotaro...
...Yamagishi Yukako, Nijimura Okuyasu, Kobayashi Tamami...
Unbelievable...
This is fantastic! And so enthralling!
You've given me the greatest inspiration
a comics artist could hope for, Hirose Koichi!
Crazy Diamond...
Star Platinum...
The Hand, Love Deluxe, et cetera, et cetera!
Wh-What are you gonna do with us?!
I'm going to take your memories
and use them as material for my comic!
Echoes!
Stop attacking us with your Stand right now!
If you don't...
You'll have Echoes Act 2 attack me with sound?
I will! Release me from your Stand's power!
I won't hold back!
Of course you won't. It's written on your eleventh page.
You're more timid than most,
and constantly misjudged to be weak...
...but when necessary,
your courage allows you to overcome your fear.
Outstanding!
This is truly outstanding!
I'm sure my readers will take a liking to your personality.
I'm serious! I'll really hurt you!
I've heard enough...
Go ahead and try!
Echoes Act 2!
SFX: Crash!
Huh? I-I missed!
Was that an accident,
or are you purposely trying to miss him?!
Your aim is totally off!
How about this?!
SFX: Crash!
Why are you attacking there?!
Koichi, I'm sorry to tell you,
but I've put a safety lock on your Echoes.
Huh?
I've made it impossible for you to attack me.
Safety lock?
See? I wrote a little something on your eleventh page.
Note: I cannot bring harm to comics artist Kishibe Rohan.
This is the ability of Heaven's Door!
It allows me to view people's life experiences via words and images,
as well as write my own words into their memories.
You will be incapable of harming me
in any way, shape, or form from now on.
Wh-What?!
But that will be the extent of my meddling.
If I alter your memories any further,
your life will become artificial and of no use to my work.
Anyway...
Perhaps I should have a look at Hazamada over there, too.
Sir, you're a true genius! I completely respect you!
Huh... I see.
What's this?
You take pleasure in subjugating those
weaker than yourself, such as kittens and small birds.
You would like to force yourself onto Junko from class 3-E,
but your cowardice prevents you.
Your scrotum often becomes sweaty during class,
and when you go to adjust it...
...it excites you that one of your
fellow classmates may catch you.
You're a disgrace.
My readers would never accept
a character like you in my comic.
You're worthless.
It's hopeless! I'm such a fuck-up!
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Even without using my experiences,
you're an amazing comics artist!
The entire world knows that!
You already have an amazing house like this
at just twenty years old!
You're way better off than most people your age!
What do you need my memories for?!
Do you think that I, Kishibe Rohan,
draw comics for the sake of fame and fortune?!
The only comics I create are those that people want to read!
The reason I draw them is to bring others happiness!
It's a simple reason, but it's all that matters to me!
To keep my readers intrigued,
I look for material with a sense of reality every single day!
Listen well!
When I complete a manuscript, the feeling is indescribable!
Most people feel good once they've
completed their work, correct?
But this is a fleeting feeling.
Before long...
...I begin to doubt that anyone will read my completed comics,
which causes mounting feelings of insecurity inside me.
My insecurities cause me to believe that the next week...
...no one will read my comic, which will make me uncertain of what to draw, which will completely kill my motivation.
I've had these reoccurring feelings
countless times since I turned sixteen.
That is, until I was shot with an arrow
three months ago and gained my ability of Heaven's Door.
Nijimura Keicho...
Yes, I found that written inside you.
I doubt either of you understand the feeling one experiences
upon coming across material fit for creating a masterpiece!
But I'm feeling it right now!
It's exhilarating!
Koichi, your reality belongs to me now!
See, Koichi? Wasn't Mr. Rohan a great guy?
Aren't you glad we went?
Yeah, that was a lot of fun!
Not only did he give us these great autographs, he even served us tea and cookies!
I can't wait to go again!
Yeah! We'll definitely do this again!
Well, my house is this way, so...
He really was a great guy!
You'll never speak of what happened here, Koichi.
Huh?!
Wh-Why?!
How did I lose twenty kilograms?
I don't look any different!
It's reading five kilograms...
The scale isn't broken...
Th-This is impossible!
Th-This must be the work of an enemy Stand!
There's no other way I could lose a whopping twenty kilograms!
Who could have done this?
I need to ask Josuke about this!
What's the matter, munchkin?
Huh?
Me? U-Uh...
Wait... What was it?
What are you talking about? Weirdo.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. My little brother was spacing out in his underwear.
What was it?
I swear I was just thinking about something really important...
Well, it couldn't have been that important if I already forgot.
Jeez, my shoes and bag feel so heavy today...
Huh?
Th-This house...
Why?
I walked all the way to Mr. Rohan's house without realizing it.
The door's wide open...
I'd like to stop in and thank him for yesterday,
but I'll be late for school...
This isn't a good idea...
He could be sleeping right now since he's a comics artist.
I really shouldn't just barge into his house like this...
This is a bad idea...
Hey, you see that, Okuyasu?
Yeah...
I knew it was a good idea for us to tail Koichi
when I saw him walk in the opposite direction from school...
...but what the hell is he doing here?
Whodya think lives there?
I got my doubts, but it ain't some chick, right?
Mr. Rohan...
He's working so frantically...
But what's this feeling?
I can't help but feel that I'm in a terrifying place right now...
What is this?
I'm glad you're back.
I've been waiting for you. You're right on time.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 15
Let's Go
Visit
the Comics
Artist's
House Part 2
Visit
Artist's
Let's Go
the Comics
House Part 2
Visit
Artist's