surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 3:  The Nijimura Brothers Part 1
Yeah. The Angelo situation was taken care of.
I have to stay here a bit longer, though.
There's something I need you to do for me.
Send me that other photo right away.
Yeah, the one the Speedwagon Foundation
found in Egypt ten years ago.
I may have found new information about it.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah, that I learned thanks to him.
Josuke! I may have killed your grandpa,
but that doesn't give you any right to kill me!
You're just as bad as I am if you kill me in cold blood!
Dora!
Don't tell me what I can or can't do!
M-M-My hand! My fucking hand!
Neither of us are gonna kill you.
I won't, and neither will Mr. Jotaro.
But just because we won't kill you,
it doesn't mean we'll send you back to prison.
Josuke, he's all yours.
Wh-What the hell are you gonna do to me?!
I'm gonna memorialize you, Angelo!
As a reminder for what you did to my grandpa,
and all the innocent people you've hurt!
Dorararara!
Goddammit!
Don't let beating me get to your head!
At least that other guy will end up taking you guys out, anyway!
Huh? Another guy?
That's right!
That guy I met wearing a school uniform who gave me this power!
What?
It can't be...
Are you telling me there's someone out there
who can give people Stands?
Scared now?
Huh? Why would that scare us?
Think about it... Angelo wasn't born a Stand user.
We had no clue how he suddenly got a Stand until now.
But if there's someone out there who can give people Stands...
Pretty scary, huh?
You wanna know about him?
This happened about a year ago, in 1998...
I was awake in my cell one night,
about two weeks before they were gonna kill me.
That night, I couldn't get any sleep...
I was just staring at the ceiling in silence.
You couldn't hear even a peep that night.
But then...
I was supposed to be the only person in my cell.
But that guy was there, too.
He was wearing a school uniform!
H-Hey! When the hell did you get in here?!
Where were you hiding?!
Wha-
He was holding some ancient looking bow and arrow.
I had the feeling that thing was
at least a hundred years old or something.
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
I was so scared, my balls crawled right back up into my body!
But before I could even scream...!
You're alive. Congratulations.
This means you have potential.
If you didn't, that would have killed you just now.
Now you have a brand new ability.
Actually, it's more like an ability awoke within you
that was lying dormant within your spirit.
The more evil you are, the greater your potential.
It's an ability a man known as Dio called a Stand.
Dio?
Did you say Dio?
Mr. Jotaro? What's-
What?!
You dumb shits!
You got so caught up in my story
that you forgot all about my Aqua Necklace!
Angelo, you bastard!
Josuke! Get me out of this rock right now!
I guess deep down in my heart...
...I wasn't as angry with you as I could have been.
The fuck are you doing?!
Quit messing around with your stupid hair!
I swear I'll kill this little shit! Now let me go!
What the hell did you just say...
Don't do it, Josuke!
...about my hair?!
I-I'm warning you! If you kill me,
that guy wearing the school uniform is gonna get pissed!
He lives right here in town!
What? Josuke, wait!
Dorararara!
I really wasn't angry enough at him earlier.
Hopefully I did a great job of combining this asshole with the rock.
Gimme a break.
I wasn't done getting info out of him.
Huh? You seriously believed all the crap he was saying?
It wasn't crap. He mentioned Dio by name.
Who the hell is that?
A man the Joestar family was
locked in battle with for over one hundred years.
A long time ago, several allies and I fought and defeated Dio.
But there was one question we never had answered...
Back in 1987, how did Dio suddenly obtain a Stand?
Do you think that guy he was going on about made him a Stand user?
Yeah. The man he described wearing
a school uniform could be a new enemy.
Another possibility is that the arrow itself did it.
If he's hiding somewhere in this town...
...then Angelo isn't the only crisis Morioh will have to deal with.
Gimme a break...
Mr. Jotaro was right...
Now I know for sure that something
worse than we could imagine is hiding in this town.
This town is about to face a huge crisis.
No, it already is...
Since the beginning of 1999,
eighty-one people have gone missing in Morioh.
Forty-five of them were young boys and girls.
Even if some were runaways, that's nearly seven times more disappearances than Japan's national average.
That's way too many...
Not to mention...
Higashikata Ryohei: Dead
(Morioh Police Officer)
...whatever happened to Josuke's grandpa...
Hey, Koichi, still got your nose in the books?
It's time to go home!
Oh, okay.
What a relief. It seems like Josuke feels a lot better now.
Yo, Angelo!
Uh... Huh? Hey, has this always been here?
Yeah, but it looked a bit different before.
Before?
Well, whatever. Yo, Angelo!
By the way, what's going on with Mr. Jotaro?
Oh, he said he had a few things to look in to.
He's staying at the Grand Hotel.
Does it have to do with our town?
Wouldn't surprise me.
I see.
The crisis our town is facing...
Huh? Josuke?
Nobody's lived here for at least three or four years, right?
Yeah. This place is such a dump, it will never sell.
They should tear it down and rebuild.
No, someone definitely lives here. Maybe they just moved in?
I just saw someone through the window.
Huh? Nah, no way. My house is over there.
I would know if someone moved in.
Besides, there's always realtors coming by
making sure homeless people haven't broken in.
In that case, you're probably right.
How weird. I hope I didn't see a ghost...
H-Hey, don't say stuff like that!
Ghosts freak me out! And this is right near my house!
Quit starin' at my house, pipsqueak!
Talk, dammit!
Koichi!
Hey! What the hell do you think you're doing?
Huh? Took the words right outta my mouth.
You guys're standin' right in fronta my house!
Morioh Landmark No. 1
The Angelo Stone
Location: One minute's walk
from Morioh's Jozenji Street
bus stop #3.
The Angelo Stone is a famous
landmark where lovers are known
to meet. The residents of Morioh
are fond of it, despite its
unsettling appearance.
Enough already...
If you're from the newspaper,
I already told you I'm not interested!
Who is it?!
My father just died of a stroke,
and we're still busy sorting everything out.
Can you come back some other time?
Y-You're...
Jo...
Joseph!
You finally came back to me, Joseph!
I've been waiting so long for you!
Ever since Dad died, I've been so lonely and upset!
I can't believe you came to see me in my time of need, Joseph!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
I hate to be the bearer of bad news, but I'm not Joseph Joestar.
Huh?
Look at me. No wrinkles.
Oh... Now that you mention it...
You're way too young!
Gimme a break...
I'm Joseph's grandson. The name's Kujo Jotaro.
R-Really?
You can ask Josuke about me later.
No time for small talk.
I'm here to see Josuke. Is he here?
I need you to tell me where Josuke is.
Huh? Oh! Josuke hasn't come home from school yet...
Got it. I'll be back later.
Huh?
You're leaving already?
Oh yeah...
About your father...
Huh?
It's unfortunate.
If Joseph Joestar had come here instead of me...
...he would have stayed with you to protect you from danger.
But he's an old man now.
I told him not to come.
That's why I'm here and he's not.
Something still doesn't feel right.
That bow and arrow Angelo was talking about...
In the file the Speedwagon Foundation
put together regarding the witch, Enya...
...there's a photo showing her carrying a bow and arrow.
Supposedly it could give even a normal person a Stand.
Damn, I can barely believe it...
No Trespassing
Are you insane?
Let him go!
My old man got this place for us!
You two ain't got no business comin' here!
Beat it!
I don't care about that.
All I'm asking is that you let him go.
This is gonna get ugly if you don't.
C'mon, ya really tryin' t'act tough right now?
Ya can't just make threats like that right in fronta a guy's house...
That any way of talkin' t'someone?
It's how I talk to people who need to watch what they say!
What?!
Big bro?!
Why did I just shoot that kid with the bow and arrow, you ask?
It's because the guy you're talking to is Higashikata Josuke.
No Trespassing
You kiddin' me? This guy?
Since he managed to defeat Angelo,
he's a Stand user who poses a threat to us.
Stand user?!
You two are Stand users?!
Okuyasu! Make Higashikata Josuke disappear!
Koichi!
Hmph! I was hoping he would become a Stand user that I could manipulate like all the others, but...
...it looks like he won't make it.
He's done for.
M-Move!
I still have enough time to heal him with Crazy Diamond!
Ain't happenin'!
Higashikata Josuke! Get ready t'be erased by Nijimura Okuyasu's...
...The Hand!
Here goes!
Dora!
If you don't move, I'm gonna seriously ruin your face.
Pretty fast, ain'tcha?
Hey, Okuyasu...
Using a Stand is just like driving a car or riding a bike.
Spineless idiots who suck at driving deserve to be run off the road,
even if they're driving a monster truck.
Big bro!
Ya don't gotta get me mad t'beat this guy!
I just had no idea he'd be so fast.
Then quit fucking around, Okuyasu!
That Stand of yours, The Hand,
gives me chills just thinking about it!
You need to be careful when you use it.
Since Higashikata Josuke defeated Angelo, you need to treat him as a serious threat!
Otherwise he'll be a constant thorn in our side.
Ya don't gotta tell me-
Ah! I was in the middle of talkin'!
Th-That ain't fair!
You're a complete moron, aren't you?
What? Why?!
Why wouldja-
Dora!
I told you to move!
Koichi!
Thank god! He's still alive!
I should still be able to save-
That tears it! You'll fuckin' pay for that!
I just wanted you to move!
Get any closer and you're gonna regret it!
Just fuckin' try me, dammit! If ya got it in ya!
He seems really confident in his right hand...
This is bad!
I have a really bad feeling about his right hand...
Leggo of my right hand, doofus!
I was right!
Coward...
Don't you fuckin' run from me, Josuke!
I know you ain't gonna abandon your pal!
I can tell there's something up with your right hand!
I get the feeling it's really dangerous!
Feel whatever ya like once I kill ya!
Here goes, dammit!
Koichi... Hang on just a little longer...
No
passing
What's with the gate? That can't be right...
No
passing
No... passing?
No
passing
No   passing
No Trespassing
Quit backin' up, dumbass.
You're just gettin' further an' further from your pal.
Come get some!
That's it! The "Tres" is missing!
Just a hunch, but your Stand's right hand...
...can erase things, can't it?
It can erase space itself!
Correctomundo, Higashikata Josuke!
Everythin' its right hand touches goes bye-bye!
An' all the stuff near it...
...gets squished together, like nothin' even happened!
An' if ya were wonderin' where it all goes to...
...even I couldn't tell ya since I ain't got a fuckin' clue!
I got a little trick up my sleeve
for when dumbasses like you try gettin' away!
I just gotta erase the space between us, then...
...you're right in my range!
It's just like teleportin'!
Even my big bro's scared shitless by The Hand!
You're done runnin' away from me...
...Josuke!
No matter where ya go...
...you'll always...
...be in my range!
Loser!
Didja really beat Angelo like this?
Guess ya just don't know when t'give up.
Who's the complete moron now?!
Now fuckin' die, Josuke!
You really are a complete moron, aren't you?
What?!
That was a close one! Nijimura Okuyasu, huh?
You have a great Stand, but it's seriously scary.
No   passing
No Trespassing
It's not gonna be pretty if he wakes up and tries to attack me.
Guess I should strangle him a bit,
just to make sure he stays knocked out.
He needs to feel the gut-wrenching feeling of defeat from the bottom of his heart!
Here goes nothing...
K-Koichi's go-
I've had enough of this shit, assholes!
This arrow is extremely valuable. It's the only one in existence.
Which is why my current objective is so important.
Retrieve it at any cost.
According to Angelo's story,
this bow and arrow is what gave Dio his Stand ability.
It was responsible for creating The World.
After Enya died, someone else obtained the bow and arrow,
and now they're using it to create Stand users here in Morioh.
I need to hurry and destroy it as soon as possible...
Otherwise someone worse than Dio...
...could end up with a Stand even more powerful than The World.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 4
The
Nijimura Brothers Part 2
Niji
mura Brothers Part 2