I swear I'm gonna save you, so just wait for me, Rohan!
Those things remembered my scent?
Are they really gonna chase me
until they suck out all my nutrients?
Yes!
Those things can only go up to sixty kilometers per hour!
This bike can stay ahead of them no problem!
Still, how the hell am I supposed to find their user like this?
I guess I'll sort out everything I know so far.
First of all, why did he set his trap inside the tunnel?
Ambushing us from the side of the road
would have been way easier.
Secondly, I feel like there's something more to the whole nutrient-sucking thing.
There has to be a reason he chose the tunnel.
I need to investigate the tunnel!
I need all the information I can get on Twin Forest Tunnel!
Koichi!
I can call Koichi and have him use Echoes to find the user!
Now, now. What's wrong? There, there...
Okay, there should be plenty of distance between us now.
Where'd I put my card?
Y-You gotta be kidding me!
How did they appear here out of nowhere?!
I was driving at eighty kilometers per hour,
and they can only go sixty!
Doing some quick math,
it should have taken them at least two minutes to get here.
Those things are definitely a Stand.
They can disappear and reappear at will...
And since he made them reappear closer to me,
they'll keep up their attack...
...by following my scent!
S-Sixty kilometers!
Wh-What?!
Crap! A baby carriage!
What's wrong? You're so fussy...
If I slow down, I'm gonna die...
Rohan will die, too...
Sorry, but I have to keep going!
I'll just have to force my way through!
Help me out, Crazy Diamond!
Dorararara!
Restore it!
Awesome!
I'll never be able to make a phone call like this!
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichini mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days
Episode 29:  Highway Star Part 2
Listen here, Yoshioka!
In one minute, you're gonna get a
very important call on your cell phone!
This is a one billion yen deal!
Don't you dare botch this!
I'm counting on you, Yoshioka!
Y-Yes, sir! You can count on me!
Just what I needed! A cell phone!
I'm seriously glad I got this! Lucky!
I promise to do my best!
Talk about a silver lining!
Hello?
Huh?
Gah! One billion yen!
Did it break when I grabbed it?
My silver lining just disappeared!
If you really hate me, just hang up the phone!
H-How can you say that, Minayo?
Say it! Ask her to marry you!
Minayo, will you m-marry—
The good luck just keeps coming!
Huh? What? What did you say, Akira?
Now that's what I call good timing!
Hello, Hirose residence.
Koichi!
So that's what happened.
If I don't find the user, I'm done for!
If I had to guess, it's probably a guy who has
some kind of obsession or grudge with that tunnel.
Have there been any incidents at the tunnel recently?
Y-Yeah... There's an article in the paper from two days ago.
I remember seeing it on the news, too.
Some punk was drunk driving on his motorcycle and crashed at the entrance to the tunnel.
"The young man is currently unconcious and in critical condition from the injuries he sustained all over his body.
He's now undergoing intensive care at Budogaoka Hospital."
Sounds like this Stand got him, too.
Anything else?
W-Wait a second...
When I saw the crime scene on TV, there was blood everywhere.
Th-That Stand sucks up people's nutrients, right?
This sounds completely different!
Is it possible that the young man
in critical condition could be the Stand user?
He could definitely make use of
other people's nutrients to heal himself...
What? I-It's the ocean!
I'm screwed if I keep going straight!
If I don't turn quickly,
I'm going for a permanent swim in the ocean!
That corner!
I'll have to take it at sixty kilometers per hour!
Hello? Josuke? What's wrong?
Koichi! Stay on the line! Don't hang up!
Here I go, dammit!
Crap! I'm gonna crash!
No!
You can do this, Josuke!
You can do it! Make the turn, dammit!
Yes! I did it!
I hung in there like a champ! Take that!
Wh-What?!
The ocean's on this side, too!
Note: No Entry
It's Morioh Harbor!
Crazy Diamond!
Dorararara!
The crumbled wall...
Restore it!
Th-That was close...
They couldn't see the wall since their focus was on me.
Single-mindedly following my scent got them stuck like mosquitoes in a screen door!
They don't have the ability to think or plan their attacks.
Their only goal is to steal my nutrients.
Our theory that the critically injured guy
is the user makes sense.
It's all coming together!
Josuke!
Koichi, the hospital!
That guy who got in the accident must be the Stand user!
I need you to find out his name for me!
On it!
Man, this is heavy...
H-How the hell am I gonna get out of this one?
How far did he go?
That piece of shit, Josuke!
When the arrow chose to strike some punk
on the verge of death from a motorcycle accident...
...I thought to myself "What the hell is it thinking?!", but...
This is absolutely amazing!
I never dreamed it could create a Stand
as amazing as Highway Star!
A Stand's ability is the result of its user's mental strength!
The more they hunger, the stronger it will be!
No one stands a chance against a man
with such a powerful hunger to heal his injuries!
My only regret is not getting to see Josuke die with my own eyes!
What should I do? What should I do?
A drainage pipe!
I'm lucky I found a drainage pipe that leads to the ocean,
but these things are still gaining on me...
H-How am I gonna get out of here?
Wh-Which way should I go?
Well... The ocean is behind me,
which means it's also to my right.
I definitely don't wanna reach the ocean...
And I came from the left, I think!
Wh-Which way should I go?
The ocean may be to the left, but if I go right...
Th-There's the middle, too...
Wh-What's happening?
I'm hitting the gas, but my speed keeps dropping...
I-Is it breaking down?
Wh-What?! It's not broken?
Then why am I losing speed?
I'm gonna stop!
Th-They're coming!
No way...
Dora!
Am I out of gas?
Man, that scared the hell out of me.
I'm just out of gas.
That's not a problem!
I was worried it was some major problem
that even Crazy Diamond couldn't handle.
This is no problem at all!
Getting out of this will be a piece of cake!
I'm still good!
Dorararara!
I can restore this no problem!
And the motorcycle, too, of course.
I can't let my guard down since these things can teleport...
...but at least the gas situation is taken care of.
But... come to think of it,
I still have a major problem on my hands...
I'm totally lost!
Wh-Which way is the hospital?
Hi
High
Highw
Highwa
Highway
Highway S
Highway St
Highway Sta
Highway Star
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Note: Budogaoka General Hospital
Excuse me! I'm in a big hurry!
I need to know which room the guy who
got in the accident at Twin Forest Tunnel is staying in!
Can you tell me?
Please tell me!
I'm sorry, little boy...
Can you not read the sign?
Huh?
Note: Visiting hours are over for the day.
If you're in need of an eye exam, stop by at 9:30 AM tomorrow.
Well, I'm not exactly here to pay him a visit!
I just really need to know!
Please, tell me!
Can't you take a hint and go home, little boy?
I have no time to deal with good-for-nothing riffraff like you.
You're pretty short for a motorcycle gang member, huh?
Can your feet even touch the ground
while you're on your bike?
God...
Act 3...
Okay, Master! Let's kill da ho!
Beeetch!
O-Oh no!
That was close...
Each of these bottles of medicine cost fifty-thousand yen...
Huh?
They're so heavy!
They're going to fall!
Hey, you! Help me! Before I drop them!
When you said "Hey, you!", were you talking to me?
Of course! Who else?! These are really heavy!
That's true, but still...
You did just finish telling me to go home.
Not to mention I'm way too short,
so I probably couldn't reach.
Are you gonna get in trouble with your boss if those break?
I bet you'll be all like "Oh my god!", huh?
Fine, I get it! I'll tell you!
He's in room 525!
Fungami Yuya is staying in 525!
Just take the elevator to the fifth floor!
Huh?
Josuke!
Koichi!
You know where he is, Koichi?
Room 525! His name is Fungami Yuya!
Go to room 525!
Thank you, Koichi!
He's on the fifth floor!
Hurry and get in the elevator!
D-Dammit...
Th-They just keep coming!
Koichi! Echoes Act 3!
I can always count on the two of them!
I owe you big time, Koichi!
3 Freeze can't attack more than one thing at a time...
The rest of them are still going after Josuke!
There it is! Room 525!
I finally made it!
The vent!
Dorararara!
Dammit...
I'm just a few meters away from his room...
What a pain in the ass!
I just have to get through this and kick his ass!
You asshole!
I'm gonna get you, no matter what...
I'm gonna get over there... and kick your ass...
What's up with this brat?
This is Yutie Pie's room!
You must be real stupid to mistake his room for yours!
Quit bothering the poor guy.
You okay?
I was starting to wonder what
the hold up was after I drained that first guy.
So you're the second guy I've been chasing around, huh?
I'm surprised you actually made it here.
Shocked, even.
Yutie Pie, you know this guy?
Huh?
Nah, never met him before. He's a nobody.
Great job, Highway Star!
I'm already in way better shape.
If you can get nutrients from two or three more people
with abilities like his, I'll be better in no time.
Hey!
We just said you can't stay here, lazy ass!
And I just told you to quit bothering the poor guy!
Anyway, why don't you ladies
come over here and show me some love?
Poor ol' Yutie Pie here can't even move on his own.
I really gotta take a piss.
My bladder's gonna burst!
Ooh! That's my job!
I thought we promised we would take turns!
It's my turn!
What? No, it's mine!
I don't care who does it!
Just get the urine bottle before I piss myself.
Okay!
Well, if you're doing that...
Hey, Akemi...
That peach is rotten.
Peel a different one.
How can you tell it's rotten?
How? Because it reeks.
It smells rotten to the core.
From over there?
That's a good point...
I think my nose is more sensitive now or something...
Oh, you're right. It is rotten.
One of you is on your period right now, right?
Am I wrong? It's gotta be one of you, right?
Huh?
Ha, so it's you, Yoshie!
I'm so right when I'm right!
Y'know, I can smell that one of you
is really pissed off right now.
I can smell if someone is excited or mad
since their body starts to release adrenaline.
Did I do something to make you mad, Reiko?
Huh? I'm not mad at all.
We're all just so relieved that you're feeling better, Yutie Pie!
Yeah, it makes us so happy!
There's nothing for us to be mad about!
Hey, hey, that's kinda weird, then.
It reeks in here of someone who's super pissed.
Ya don't gotta lie to me!
Which one of you is mad?
I am.
All that adrenaline you're smelling is coming from me!
No fucking way!
You should be all dried up by now!
How the hell are you standing?!
It's because...
You were drinking my IV fluid?
It wasn't much, but I feel better now.
Release Rohan, the guy you're holding hostage in the tunnel!
Dumbass!
Highway Star still remembers your scent!
Dora!
Yutie Pie!
Don't any of you move!
My name is Higashikata Josuke.
My Stand's name is Crazy Diamond.
Even though its effective range is small,
it can throw punches way faster than a measly sixty kilometers per hour.
I've never actually measured it,
but it's probably closer to three-hundred kilometers per hour.
Hey, cut me some slack!
M-My spine is still broken!
I'm still stuck in bed with broken bones!
I'm critically injured!
You're really gonna beat up an injured guy like me?
Okay, okay, I get it...
I'll free the guy in the tunnel...
He's probably still alive!
Once his nutrients are replenished, he'll be good to go.
A-Anyway...
...you wouldn't resort to beating up an injured guy like a total coward, would you?
No real man would do that!
Yeah! That's cowardly!
Oh, you got me there.
I'd probably feel like shit if I beat up an injured person.
It's not manly, and I'd feel super guilty.
Exactly! You couldn't live it down if you kicked my ass!
Luckily, I already thought of that and just healed you.
Huh?!
Eh?
Can you move?
You can, right?
Your wounds are all healed up, right?
Th-They are!
Good.
So now that I healed all your wounds,
it won't be cowardly if I beat you up, will it?
Dorararara!
Fungami Yuya: Hospitalized until further notice!
In the event that he so much as tries to heal himself with
Highway Star again, Josuke promised to beat him up over and over.
I feel fantastic now!
Like I just slipped on a fresh
pair of underwear on New Year's morning!
Yutie Pie!
However, it is quite enviable that he will be nursed back to health by his three fangirls.
Meanwhile, Rohan...
Higashikata Josuke...
U-Umm, look, Mr. Rohan...
I know we have our differences, but I...
Why did you heal me?
Huh?
I didn't ask for your help.
Death would have been preferable to
being saved by the likes of you!
I'm still flabbergasted that you chose to
step into the enemy's trap after I warned you to run.
Are you really that stupid?
Wha-!
And to be clear, this is not a favor deserving of repayment!
...still does not get along with Josuke.
Also...
Hirose Koichi finally succeeded in taking his dog for a walk.
Hi
High
Highw
Highwa
Highway
Highway S
Highway St
Highway Sta
Highway Star
Fun
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Fungami
Fungami Yu
Fungami Yuya
Huh? It's a British Blue!
Where did you come from, little kitty?
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 30
The
Cat
Who Grew
Fond
of Kira Yoshikage
Cat
Fond
The
Who Grew
of Kira Yoshikage
Cat
Fond