Hey, Koichi's family don't know nothin', neither...
I heard 'em sayin' they're gonna call the cops.
So he really is missing. And Yukako's gone, too...
I'm startin' t'feel like it's my fault...
Ya don't think he's dead or nothin', do ya?!
Nah, I don't think he's dead yet.
She's probably keeping him somewhere.
We need to find him as soon as possible.
He could be in real danger.
It won't unlock!
This is the worst!
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
In what year did
Christopher Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the combination to the lock.
It's the title of a movie, isn't it?
I never watched it because it was too long!
Please tell me I almost have it...
1, 4, 0, 0...
Umm...
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 9:  Yamagishi Yukako Falls in Love Part 2
I washed your underwear and pajama pants for you.
What's wrong?
I can't do anything about it unless you tell me!
I-I'm a first-year high school student...
...and I've never felt so ashamed...
I'm long past embarrassed. I've never felt worse about myself...
Please, can you stop this?
You probably hate me now anyway, don't you?
You think I'm pathetic, right?
I just want to go home already!
How could you possibly still like me after I peed my pants?
Oh Koichi, you poor thing...
I must be tormenting your heart...
I'm not a good girl...
Nothing I say is getting through to her!
I-I can feel tears in my eyes...
Peeing my pants was bad enough, but now I'm crying?!
However, Koichi...
...even though you think so little of yourself...
...I still see a shining, fiery determination in your eyes.
You look like you're hiding a trick up your sleeve.
That's what I like about you.
I would love for you to show me!
If you truly love someone,
you should accept them poop, snot, and all, right?
I find it strange that it bothers you.
I've felt no greater joy than while I was washing your underwear.
Look!
I'm working on a chair that has electricity running through it!
It should be ready for our dinnertime study session!
I'm thinking about making us Italian for dinner.
I'm going out to get some olive oil.
Keep your appetite!
H-Help me!
She's getting worse by the minute!
If I don't escape soon, she's gonna kill me for real!
But...
...how am I gonna do that?
'Least Koichi's got Echoes.
He can call for help even if she's got him gagged up, right?
Maybe, but Echoes' range is only fifty meters.
She may have taken him somewhere remote.
That could be anywhere!
Wait!
Earlier, she said she was going to get olive oil...
...but I doubt she would go out shopping in a situation like this.
Is she ordering it by phone somehow?
Is it possible...
There it is! A pay phone!
Forty-eight meters! Yes!
It's just barely inside my range!
Echoes is a Stand that creates sound!
With this, I can let Josuke know I need help!
I don't have any ten yen coins!
I was still in my pajamas when she took me here!
Should I call the police instead?
Even if I did that, she could try to kill them!
I need to find a way to contact Josuke!
You were wondering if there was a pay phone nearby, weren't you?
Y-Yukako...
I know exactly what you're thinking.
You heard me say I was going to get olive oil, then figured out that the only way I could get it was to order it by pay phone.
But even if you could reach it, you have no money.
That's what you were thinking, right?
I-Is there a pay phone?
Hmph. You're playing dumb.
You'll never be able to use it to call someone, anyway.
I won't allow you to step foot outside this house.
But just to be safe,
I'm going to destroy the emergency service button.
Is there anything you would like me to get for you?
N-No, not really...
Sh-She's insane!
I-It's no use... I'll never contact anybody...
SFX: Beep Boop Beep Boop
What are these characters?
There's sound coming from my arm!
It's calling somewhere!
I haven't even dialed a number yet!
Hello, Higashikata residence.
It connected!
The phone just needs to hear the right tones to make a call!
Hello, is this Koichi?
It's me, Josuke!
Koichi, where are you?
What? I hear waves crashing!
Koichi, you...
You have an ability like mine, don't you?
I did it! Now Josuke will definitely find his way here!
It should only take fifteen or twenty minutes by taxi!
I just need to survive until he gets here!
N-No matter what!
Crashing waves... A pay phone...
That means Koichi...
...has to be around here!
Koichi!
She's coming back!
I-I have no choice but to fight!
Open the door this instant, Koichi!
Wh-Why don't you just break it down?
If Josuke sees a broken door,
he'll definitely know something's going on here!
Right now, I couldn't be happier!
It makes me so happy that you have an ability like I do!
Though I'm still a bit mad that
you felt the need to hide it from me.
Even so, it makes me so happy!
The most important things a man and woman can share are love, goals, and values, right?
Now we share something in common that no one else does!
We're completely compatible!
So please, Koichi...
Open the door for me.
I asked kindly, so don't make me ask again!
SFX: I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
W-We're completely compatible?!
Can't you tell how badly I want to get away from here?!
That sound won't go away until you
cry, apologize, and give up on me for good!
What do you mean? I don't hear a thing.
SFX: I hate you!
Huh?!
Th-This girl...
...isn't anything like Tamami!
She's completely deluded herself!
I never thought she would be this persistent!
Now I know for sure that the two of us are soulmates.
Most people never find theirs.
Don't you see how wonderful it is?
Koichi...
...I originally just wanted you to become
a perfect man, but now things are different.
You won't leave this house until you're madly in love with me.
I will make you love me!
Otherwise...
...I'll kill you.
I can't let her get in here, no matter what!
I need to attack her with Echoes again!
If I try harder, I should be able to make a louder sound!
Echoes!
There's something wrong with Echoes...
It stopped moving!
I-Is it dead?!
Did my Stand just die from falling into despair?!
Echoes is dead!
E
Ech
Echo
Echoes
Echoes A
Echoes Ac
Echoes Act
Echoes Act 1
Hiro
Hirose
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: B
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Hirose Ko
Hirose Koichi
N-No! M-My...
...My Echoes completely stopped moving!
Stands move by using mental strength!
I pushed it too far, and now it's lying dead on the ground!
My Echoes!
What?
Wh-What is that?
You called it a Stand, right?
What kind of Stand do you have?!
This cabinet is in my way!
I-I'm done for!
If she forces her way in here and catches me, she'll kill me!
Koichi, open this door!
I'm not opening the door for you!
If only the door would blow her far away...
It's gone! It shed its shell!
Where is it?
Huh?
Tell me what happened to whatever was inside that thing!
Huh?!
Th-
That's...
Wh-What is this thing? My Echoes...
...d-didn't die at all!
Did it form that shell around itself to take on this new form?
What is this?
It doesn't look much different from before, and now it's smaller.
Making it look like that doesn't change anything!
I-It's fast!
Wh-Where...
...is this wind coming from?!
I-It blew her away!
I don't know what it did,
but somehow she got blown away by a gust of wind!
Wh-What just...
...happened there?
Echoes' sound effect is printed on the door...
SFX: Fwoosh!
When she touched the sound effect
printed on the door, it became real!
The sensation of feeling a "Fwoosh!" actually blew her away!
SFX: Fwoosh!
Earlier, I wanted the door to just blow her away...
I must have been subconsciously controlling my ability!
This is the new and improved Echoes!
Echoes Act 2!
Koichi...
It's them...
She must have brought him here since it's by the sea
and nobody's living here right now.
But ya know, there's a lotta houses 'round here...
We ain't never gonna find it!
We need to find the pay phone!
That's how Koichi contacted us.
Let's find the pay phone, then scope out the houses nearby.
Okay!
My precious Koichi belongs to me alone!
No one else can have him!
I wouldn't get any closer if I were you, Yukako.
I thought about it, and I realized
there's no way you can beat my Echoes Act 2's ability!
You can't keep me here any longer!
My left eyelid is twitching...
The muscle in my eyelid only twitches when I'm worked up over something...
...and it makes me feel violent!
Don't act so arrogant just because you obtained a slightly different ability!
This is going to get violent, now!
SFX: Sizzle
It burns!
H-How could you?!
You burned my hand! You shithead!
When you said this was gonna get violent,
did you mean you were just gonna yell at me louder?
How could you treat me this way?!
You're such a brat!
You belong to me!
And yet you dare disobey me?!
I won't allow it!
Echoes Act 2!
I missed?
Josuke!
I heard it, too!
It sounded like something breaking!
Hey, ya think it's that place?
I-I didn't expect her hair to grow this long...
She has some serious mental strength!
Mental strength that makes her dark and spiteful...
You called that thing "Echoes"?
Now that you've shown me what it can do, I'm unimpressed.
I only need to avoid touching the sound effects it creates!
But before I continue, let me ask you again...
Do you love me?
Go ahead and try to tell me you don't!
I'll rip you and this house apart if I must!
You'll be mine forever if you die here!
Living on as a cherished memory in my heart!
Answer me this instant!
This whole thing spiraled out of control because you weren't listening when I told you earlier!
I said I hated you, and nothing will change that!
I'm going to kill you, Koichi!
SFX: Dagoom!
I already told you! You'll never be able to beat me!
The sound effect you touched will blow you away!
This "shithead" printed it on himself!
Her hair turned white!
She didn't die, did she?
She's alive!
Even though she's crazy and a bit crude, I'm glad she lived.
If I can't catch you...
...then I'll just have to defeat your Stand!
You little brat!
Idiot!
I-I can't believe you can still attack me...
Your mental strength is insane!
Shut your mouth!
How dare you, you little pants wetter?!
How could you do something so vile to me?!
My precious hair turned white...
...you impotent loser!
I really liked you, you know!
But what you've done to my hair is unforgivable!
I can never forgive you for ruining my beauty!
I'm going to rip off your dribbly little dick and pull all your innards out along with it!
D-Don't!
Shut your mouth!
Anything I do to this thing affects you too, doesn't it?!
What? What was that noise?
Let go of my Echoes and grab on to something!
The edge of the cliff is crumbling!
When I had Echoes hear the sound of your heart beat,
it also heard the ground cracking!
Hah! Don't spin such blatant lies
in a desperate attempt to save yourself!
I need to let go of this thing and grab on to something!
Oh no!
I-I don't have enough time!
SFX: Boing-Boing!
It crumbled just like I said it would...
Not that it matters since you never listen to a word I say.
Does this mean he had already written it there?
When I was trying to rip Echoes apart...
...he put that sound effect on the rock beneath the cliff?
So while I was trying to kill Koichi...
...he was looking out for my safety?
I-I've completely lost...
No... I lost from the moment I first laid eyes on him...
Hey, Koichi! You alive?!
Are you okay, Koichi?!
Josuke! Okuyasu!
Took you guys long enough to get here! Jeez!
B-But... Now I like him even more!
I don't mind if he ignores me!
Just being able to think about Koichi...
...makes me so happy!
Hey, look at that! Ain't that Yukako?
She's got white hair now!
Whoa, you're right!
But now that I'm lookin' at her...
Ain't that a smile on her face?
She's lookin' over here now!
Huh?!
You're right. It's creeping me out...
Let's get outta here!
Save me, Josuke!
You can't always depend on me!
Well ain't that somethin' else, Masaji?
Gramps, I ain't had that much to drink!
Morioh Landmark #2
Boing-Boing Cape:
Location: Ask any local fisherman where
"Boing-Boing Cape" is, and they'll gladly
take you there by boat.
Boing-Boing Cape.
A location made famous when two local fishermen claimed to see a young girl attempt to commit suicide there...
...only for her to bounce off a rock and back onto the cliff with a "boing-boing!" sound.
Hirose...
Good job on your exam.
I see you've applied yourself well.
Seriously...
I feel so conflicted...
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 10
Let's
Go
out
for
Italian
Go
for
Let's
out
Italian
Go
for