Every pair of shoes Kawajiri Kosaku owned
are too big for my feet.
I need to switch them out for similar-looking shoes in my size before I arouse suspicion.
Hayato...
Won't you say goodbye to me?
Have a good day.
Darling!
Something scary happened to me in the basement!
I'm still in shock!
I was sure I was going to die!
Even though it was scary, at least it gave me a good excuse to tightly cling to his chest!
Anyway, I found a strange cat that
I've never seen before in the basement!
A cat?
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
Episode 30:  The Cat Who Grew Fond of Kira Yoshikage
Before we go down there, let me tell you what scared me.
I went down to the basement
since we had run out of mineral water, and...
Well, you know how much I like cats, right?
I saw one down there and was all like, "Oh, it's a British Blue!"
It had perfect proportions, and golden eyes
that contrasted with its velvet-like blue-gray fur.
Where did you come from, sweet little kitty?
Oh no! It's acting defensive!
It must have come in from there.
But I can't let it stay down here forever...
It may have fleas,
and I can't have it peeing on the sack of potatoes...
I should be okay to get closer
if I don't make eye contact, right?
Oh, I remember now!
I need to make it feel at ease so it won't act hostile!
See? Posing like this with my belly up
means I'm submitting to you!
Let's be best friends!
Why am I trying to humor a cat?
Get out of here right now, or I'll throw this at you!
You hear me? I'll do it!
Come on!
You little...!
Then it clung to the ceiling like a creepy bug!
B-But what really creeped me out
was the giant hole it had in its throat!
It was the size of a 1 yen coin!
And then, I heard something from the hole...
A hole?
Could it be a hole created by the arrow?
I started swinging the broom everywhere, then ran away!
Will you please just check it out for me? I'm so scared...
Are you sure it had a hole in its throat?
Wait... is it gone? Did it run away?
No... it's dead.
Huh? Are you serious?
H-Hold-
One of the shards slit its throat.
Hold on a minute! I just...
It was an accident.
It can't be helped. It was bad luck.
It's not your fault.
It's no one's fault.
Even though it had a hole in its throat...
...it's too late to tell if it was a Stand user or not.
No, I'm sure it wasn't...
Good morning, Morioh!
Quite a lovely morning now that the rain has stopped, isn't it?
Right before I got to the studio, I saw a rainbow in the sky!
Do you think it's still there?
"Where am I? Meow!
What am I doing here? Meow, meow!" he pondered.
"Two days ago, I survived being struck by an arrow, but...
...m-my body feels different now!
It's shaped funny! It's all wrong!
Why can't I move?" he thought, bewildered.
Where did my husband bury that cat?
I'm so sorry, kitty... Please rest in peace.
He thought to himself: "Who's this human lady?
I'm getting a bad feeling from her...
The broom! Oh yeah! I remember now!
This woman...
That's right! I was stabbed by
a bunch of glass shards, then I couldn't move!
That woman is the reason
I became like this!" he angrily thought.
He was perplexed.
"What? Something came out!
When I got angry at that woman,
something came out of me!"
My toenail? Wh-Why?!
Is this a curse?
D-Did that cat do this?
Because he lived according to his instincts and desires,
the cat understood how to effectively use his new power.
It's a Stand user!
Why is this thing in the same place
I buried that cat yesterday?
What even is it?
What did it do to that sparrow?
I didn't see a Stand come from it.
But first, I need to figure out if it's an enemy or not.
Is it an enemy who would do me harm? Or is it...
Either way, I should probably kill it.
It fell asleep once it finished eating.
Is it a plant, or some kind of animal?
Killing it would be simple,
but I may benefit from observing it.
It reacted to the noises I made
the same way a cat would, too...
The way it's compulsively sniffing me
is also reminiscent of cat behavior.
I think it may be safe to pet it.
The way it's creepily purring as it tries to
fall asleep is also exactly how a cat would act.
However, I can't be sure if it
harbors any hostility toward me or not.
Time to find out.
Hmm... It's a bit angry, but the lack of hostility confirms it isn't my enemy.
This must be the cat I buried here yesterday.
The hole in its throat must have
come from the arrow after all.
D-Darling?
She's back!
That spot scares me...
That's where my toenail was torn off...
The cat attacked her since
it still holds a grudge from before!
If she learns the true nature of this thing...
...rumors of its existence
could reach Kujo Jotaro and the others!
I can't let that happen!
That's the spot where you buried the cat, right?
I'm afraid that spot could be cursed now...
I didn't bury it here.
Go back inside the house.
That's a lie!
You're lying to make me feel better, aren't you?
Damn! This cat really is hostile!
I don't know what kind of Stand ability it received, but I have to eliminate it!
Killer Queen!
It pains me, but I have to blow you up!
Primary bomb! Switch on!
What?!
Impossible! It can't be a dud!
Has it done something?
Is its ability preventing it from exploding?
Huh? What is that?!
Th-That plant is moving!
I told you to get inside the house!
Huh?
Shinobu!
The moment Killer Queen's bomb
moved away from the plant, it exploded!
Could this thing have the ability to...?!
The former cat-turned-plant thought to himself...
"I'm going to kill that woman!"
I can't let you hurt her any more!
It's time I eliminate you!
"In that case, I'll kill you, too!" he thought.
The only reason for my bomb to not explode
would be if there were no air surrounding it.
The plant knew instinctively just how it should kill the man!
Could its Stand ability be to freely control air?
It's coming!
I can't see it, but it released something!
Killer Queen!
It really did release something! It's air!
It's releasing bubbles of air!
You damn cat! I'll crush you!
I can't touch it!
It feels like I'm stepping on an invisible balloon!
It really is controlling the air!
What?
Y-You damn cat...
I can't see it, but I'm sure it released another air bubble!
This is bad! It's up to something!
What?
The cactus!
Sh-Shinobu!
What's this? Am I, Kira Yoshikage,
feeling relief that the cactus needles didn't pierce her eyes?
What is this feeling?
Am I feeling empathy for another person?
No, impossible!
I'm only worried that if she were to die,
Kujo Jotaro would become suspicious of this household!
There's no other reason for me to feel relief right now!
That's all there is to it...
That attack won't work anymore.
I may not be able to see it,
but I've solved the mystery behind your ability.
You have a simple ability that allows you
to blow air and create air bubbles.
You're no match for my Killer Queen!
What?!
Th-That cat... sent an air bubble directly into my vein!
It's traveling further into my body!
I'm not very knowledgeable of medical matters, but I've heard that if you inject more than 10cc of air into a human being's veins...
...it can create a blockage that leads to death!
This is definitely more than 10cc!
Dammit!
It's no use! This is bad!
I have no choice... It's this or death!
Killer Queen!
I underestimated this thing...
Its ability to freely control air...
...is a terrifying ability, indeed.
Wh-What should I do?
It's coming! It's going to attack again!
What should I do?
That was close...
For now, I'll let this go...
I've done enough.
S
St
Str
Stra
Stray
Stray C
Stray Ca
Stray Cat
For
Former
Former cat-
tur
turned
Former cat-
turned-pla
turned-plant
Yesterday, my husband told me he buried the cat's corpse far away from us.
He told me the cat's curse was just something I imagined because I was afraid.
I even fainted right in front of him...
It was so embarrassing...
Still...
He took care of me, even though it made him late for work.
It made me so happy.
I felt a connection between us deep in my heart!
It was the happiest morning of my life!
Well? How is it?
That Hayato...
He left without saying goodbye again.
Was that brat observing me?
Oh, darling!
That's my plate.
I know you don't like shiitake mushrooms,
so I took them out of yours...
Since when did you start liking them?
You already ate more than half!
But it makes me happy to see you enjoying my cooking!
I guess your dislike of them was all in your head, huh?
Yeah...
Anyway, I'm leaving now...
Have a good day, darling!
Aww... All I wanted was a goodbye kiss...
At least now we understand each other's feelings.
I'll seduce him before long!
He had to use a shoehorn to put on his shoes.
I'm sure I saw him put on 25.5cm size shoes.
Having two different shoe sizes is strange.
It's also strange that Mama and Papa
have been getting along lately.
He ate those shiitake mushrooms
even though he used to hate them.
This was strange, too...
Why was he writing out his name over and over?
And last night...
No matter how I look at it, that's potting soil.
And I think the bag he's holding is cat food.
Then he headed right for his closet.
These children are wearing hats.
Are they required to wear them for school?
Something feels off...
The attic?
Wh-What is this bizarrely shaped thing?
It's too dark for me to tell.
There it is. It's that bag.
Huh?
Wha-
I-It's moving!
It's not a plant! Those are eyes!
It has eyeballs that are looking right at me!
Did he buy the cat food to feed this thing?
Oh, darling...
What's wrong?
Did you forget something?
Oh, did you come back for your goodbye kiss?
No.
Come on...
Then what is it? Something I can help with?
No, I'm fine.
Why did he come back?
C-Crap!
Huh?!
Wha-?! Th-This thing...!
It feels like there's invisible balloons
holding down my arms and neck!
He's coming up! C-Crap!
The attic! I knew it! That brat!
I-It attacked me when I tried to shut the window?
Does that thing need sunlight to move?
I-I know! If these bubbles are filled with air...
I did it! It really was the sunlight!
That noise...
Did Stray Cat wear itself out using air
to attempt to retrieve the cat food on the shelf?
I assumed it would stay calm
without any sunlight hitting it...
...but it looks like some was leaking in.
Still...
I was almost sure Hayato came up here and discovered who I am, but thankfully it was only my imagination.
If that brat had discovered the truth about me...
...I would have had to kill him.
He may look like Papa, but that definitely isn't him!
Who...
Wh-Who the heck is he?
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 31
July 15th (
Thursday
) Part 1
July 15th (
Thursday