For the love of god...
What a pain in the ass.
Let's see... Where the hell did I leave that thing?
Katagiri Anjuro. Nickname: Angelo.
Infamous for committing some of the worst crimes in recent history.
At the age of twelve, he began his lifelong murder spree.
His last murder...
Mister milkman! Watch your step!
...put him on the same level as dog shit.
During March of 1994...
...he crossed paths with three fourteen year-old boys.
He raped and murdered two of them.
Did you step in it?
Yeah, I did.
Honestly, this pisses me off!
Letting your dog do that in front of someone else's house...
Just this once, I'd like to keep it
so I can shove it in the owner's pocket tomorrow morning.
Well... I left your milk at the door.
Goodbye, now.
Hold on...
You're not the usual milkman.
Yeah, I'm covering his shift this morning.
Once he learned that the last boy came from
a wealthy family, he demanded a ransom.
This led to his arrest.
I know I'm being picky,
but it looks like the seal on this milk is broken.
Is it?
Yeah. Look at it!
Oh, I see...
It's broken, right?
You're right. My apologies.
I'll be going now.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
That fucking bitch!
She's got a sharp eye, that's for sure.
If that bitch or her dumbass kid, Josuke, drank that milk...
...my Stand, Aqua Necklace, could have possessed them!
Again? You just don't stop, do you?
Once the police finally found where he was keeping the boy,
they were greeted by a horrific scene.
The boy was dead, and his genitals had been
forcibly removed and nailed to a pillar near his corpse.
Why the fuck didn't you clean up your dog's disgusting shit?
Plus, you just threw your cigarette butt on the ground!
Don't act like your better than everyone else!
Anyone who acts like they're above others...
...can choke on my Stand and die!
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 2:  Higashikata Josuke Meets Angelo!
So like I was saying, it looked like his Stand possessed
that guy robbing the convenience store or something, but...
...it could have just been hiding inside of him.
It didn't attack me, at least.
Was Angelo nearby? The guy from the photo.
Nope, didn't see him.
Damn, my hair isn't setting right...
Listen. His Stand is weak, but he can control it remotely.
It's the type of Stand capable of possessing people.
I'm heading to your place.
Huh? Right now?
Don't eat or drink anything until I get there.
That includes tap water.
Don't use the shower or flush the toilet, either. Got it?
Wait a second... I haven't told my mom about you yet...
Even though she has thick skin,
she'll be a mess if her feelings for Joseph Joestar resurface again.
She'll be able to tell you guys are related.
Josuke, where did these photos come from?
This looks like the milkman from earlier...
Do you know him?
Hey, Josuke! What's wrong?
Dammit! It's already too late!
That thing was in my Mom's coffee and got inside her mouth!
Hello? Josuke? Hey! Josuke!
Josuke, would you like some coffee, too?
Yeah, sounds good.
Could you put in the milk and sugar for me?
Milk and sugar, huh?
Josuke? You said milk and sugar, right?
Yeah.
Hello? Mr. Jotaro?
I just caught his Stand, but...
What?
What should I do with it?
This guy...
Be careful. Angelo is probably staking out your house.
Don't take your eyes off his Stand. I'll be right there.
Angelo probably escaped prison and death row using his Stand.
I still don't know what it can do, though.
Bottom of the 9th
Dead ball!
It's over!
The game ends with a dead ball!
There, there...
You motherfucker!
Josuke! You'll be late if you don't get going!
I'll kill them both! That little shit and his bangin' mom!
Okay!
I've either gotta take the cap off,
or break the bottle! But how...?
It's him...
I'm home.
Higashikata...
They got the same name...
Officer Higashikata lives here!
I was just a little kid the first time I met that asshole! Good times...
Lucky for me, I know all there is to know about him!
Don't move!
Josuke, how come you're not at school?
Grandpa, since when are you allowed to
take your gun home from work?!
Put a sock in it! Answer me!
I'm leaving soon! I'm just waiting for someone!
Don't be stupid! It's a fake gun.
You sure looked scared!
Guess that makes me the winner
of our weekly scaring contest, huh?
Yeah, yeah. I'm the loser.
Hmm? What's wrong?
Don't have any objections this time?
It's nothing. Mom already left.
You should get some sleep.
You're probably tired from work, right?
Now, our next story.
The number of reported casualties involving injuries
sustained to the eyes and ears from inside the body...
...has risen to seven as of this morning.
Police investigation into these bizarre deaths is still underway,
though all cases have been isolated to Morioh thus far.
The cause of their injuries is unknown at this time.
I've heard about this.
There's definitely something fishy going on.
I can't shake the feeling that someone really dangerous is hiding in our town.
Grandpa...
Morioh's staple food, beef tongue stewed in miso-
He's here...
I know you too well, Higashikata!
You always go for a shot of brandy once you finish your shift!
Josuke, grab the bottle and get in the car.
We need to bring it somewhere remote.
Gotcha.
G-Grandpa...
Higashikata Josuke, this is all your fault!
Serves you right for not keeping an eye on me!
You got cocky, kid!
It makes my fucking day to see
cocky bastards like you get knocked down a peg!
Dorararara!
Close one! You're stronger than I thought...
Too bad you're still just a cocky little shit!
Your days are numbered!
You hear me? You're finished!
My grandpa took off the bottle cap without knowing...
But this isn't a problem!
It's nothing serious. My Stand can easily...
All better.
It can't be...
He should be waking up!
My Stand can heal wounds!
I've been doing this since I was a kid!
I even healed my friend's broken bone once!
Hey, Grandpa!
You're really gonna get it if you're trying to scare me!
Was the night shift really that hard on you?
You don't have to scare me like this!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Josuke...
But there's nothing wrong...
Most people do more harm than good to others during their lives.
Your power allows you to do the world
a kindness nobody else can.
However, once someone is dead...
...they can't be brought back.
No Stand can bring the dead back to life.
For the last thirty-five years,
my grandpa has made it his sworn duty to protect this town.
He knew something was going on...
When he saw the news about the murders just like the ones committed by Angelo...
...you could see the conviction in his eyes.
Angelo has killed many people.
There are probably dead bodies hidden all over town because of him.
His entire existence is devoted to senseless murder.
It's like a hobby for him.
He'll never stop.
I hate to say it,
but he'll probably go after you and your mom next.
I...
I swear I'm gonna protect my mom, and this town...
...no matter what it takes!
A
Aq
Aqu
Aqua
Aqua Ne
Aqua Nec
Aqua Neck
Aqua Neckla
Aqua Necklace
Kata
Katagiri
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: E
Katagiri An
Katagiri Anju
Katagiri Anjuro
Although the man who once lived here has passed on,
a clean uniform still hangs inside his closet.
Neatly lined up below it
are a pair of shoes, socks, shirts, and pants...
...that the man would defend by proclaiming "They suit me just fine."
But like the man, they too must pass on from this place.
Even his daughter, still clinging to
the cherished memories those items held for her...
...knew she would never see her father wear them again.
Josuke... He probably doesn't want to talk to anyone right now...
Everything but sealed food and drinks are dangerous,
so don't consume anything else.
How's your mom holding up?
I told her to go to a relative's house after the funeral.
Good thinking. She can come back once we defeat Angelo.
I'm not really that angry, honestly...
Just got a bit worked up there.
I'm calm. Totally calm.
Calm, huh?
Well, it's your furniture, so do whatever you want with it.
By the way, that cut on your lip...
You got that from when I punched you.
Can't you use your Stand to heal yourself?
My Stand can't heal my own wounds.
What will you do if his Stand gets inside you
and starts tearing you to shreds?
Die, probably.
I'm toast if it gets inside me.
You think you can trap my Stand inside a bottle again?
That's not gonna work.
Josuke, I know what kind of abilities you have now.
Either tomorrow, or the day after...
...I'll get my chance to kill you!
— 3 Days Later —
He came this far just to stake out the house...
...yet he hasn't made a single move for three days.
What is he waiting for?
Rain...
Wait... Rain?
Ora!
What the hell?
I knew something was up with you!
You're a Stand user, too?
Well, whatever. I've been waiting for this!
This house belongs to me now!
You'll never be able to leave now that it's raining!
Josuke!
Look at all the water he started boiling!
He even broke the faucet!
Angelo's Stand is hiding somewhere inside your house.
He wasn't waiting for you to trip up and drink water...
He was waiting for it to rain!
His Stand can move freely through rain... Or rather...
...it can move freely through water!
Josuke! Get away from the kettle!
That thing turned into steam!
Dorararara!
Well isn't this just great?
We'll never catch him using a bottle.
Stay away from the steam.
You'll die if you inhale that thing.
We need to get out of here!
You're right... But now it doesn't make a difference
whether we stay inside or go out there.
Angelo poked a bunch of holes in the ceiling.
It's too dangerous to go anywhere now!
What a great situation...
I didn't think it would be this hard
to fight an enemy who can blend into water...
This was his plan all along.
What's so funny? He's got us cornered!
Hey!
I just realized something, Mr. Jotaro...
I'm within pummeling distance
of the asshole who killed my grandpa!
And that's just great!
Enough wasting time. Let's finish this!
Ora!
Well, Josuke...
How do you plan...
...to get us through this one?
To get us through this?
I won't just get us through this...
Dora!
...I'll smash us through!
Hurry! This way!
...it can move freely through water!
Gimme a break.
Well, looks like we got this under-
The humidifier!
Josuke!
I won! I knew you'd try that, Josuke!
I knew you would end up
breaking down the wall to get inside this room!
Dammit!
I feel like I just bet on a winning race horse,
or got every question right on a test!
I feel like laughing from all the good luck I'm having!
I can't hold it in!
Josuke!
What Angelo just said is wrong, Mr. Jotaro!
Josuke?
When things go exactly the way you want them to,
it shouldn't make you want to laugh...
Especially if you're a sick bastard like Angelo!
Seriously...
Got him. Sorry if I grossed you out.
I shredded up and swallowed a rubber glove earlier.
Dorarara!
I hear him. The user is over there.
G-Goddammit!
So...
...you're Angelo.
Motherfucker!
Y-You guys aren't gonna kill me, are you?!
Sure, I'm an escaped death row inmate...
...but being found guilty by Japanese law
doesn't give you jerks a reason to look down on me!
Josuke! I may have killed your grandpa,
but that doesn't give you any right to kill me!
You're just as bad as I am if you kill me in cold blood!
Dora!
Don't tell me what I can or can't do!
M-M-My hand! My fucking hand!
Neither of us are gonna kill you.
I won't, and neither will Mr. Jotaro.
But just because we won't kill you,
it doesn't mean we'll send you back to prison.
Josuke, he's all yours.
Wh-What the hell are you gonna do to me?!
I'm gonna memorialize you, Angelo!
As a reminder for what you did to my grandpa, and all the innocent people you've hurt!
Dorararara!
My grandpa swore to protect this town, and now you're immortalized in it.
The Angelo Stone.
Morioh Landmark #1
The Angelo Stone:
Location: One minute's walk from
Morioh's Jozenji Street bus stop #3
The Angelo Stone came to be considered a landmark,
as well as a spot where lovers meet.
The residents of Morioh are fond of it,
despite its unsettling appearance.
I have to admit... he's one crazy guy.
Gimme a break.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 3
The
Nijimura Brothers Part 1
Niji
mura Brothers Part 1