Once again, it's Morioh Radio!
We've got a great segment here for you today.
"Help Me! Midnight Discussions!"
Our first letter comes from a "Forever 21: Pretty Baby."
"Kai, I need to get this off my chest!
I was late to meet someone because of that stupid thing again!
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about!
That annoying railroad crossing that doesn't let you through!
Seriously, it just ding, ding, ding, dings, and never stops!"
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Seriously?
There's another Stand user at our school?
Episode 7:  Hazamada Toshikazu (Surface)
Yeah. His name is Hazamada Toshikazu. He's in class 3-C.
This Hazamada guy apparently got in an argument with his friend over some petty disagreement.
He insulted his favorite TV show or idol or something.
That same night, his friend gouged out his own eye with a mechanical pencil!
Isn't that just crazy?
Hazamada's friend could only recall one part of the incident.
"Before I knew what was happening,
I was staring at my gouged-out left eye in my hand."
So you're saying this guy gouged out
his friend's eye using some kind of Stand?
I'm not saying that's what happened, but I won't say it isn't, either.
Don't forget that normal people can't see Stands.
Something about your story seems off to me...
What was that?!
Josuke, you can't just call my info into question like that!
I've got a real job now and everything!
Huh? You found a job?
Of course, Master Koichi! I work in financing now!
Financing?
You didn't become a loan shark, did you?
Well... the place has a good reputation, at least!
Anyway, we can't just stand here and ignore this.
Wait up, Josuke!
M-Master Koichi!
Are you going with him?
Just let that idiot Josuke do his own thing.
There's something scary going on in this town...
If Morioh really is in danger,
then that means my parents, my sister...
...and everyone I care about will have to face it at some point.
Even if I'm scared, I have to do something!
H-
He's so tough!
I'd expect nothing less from a guy like him!
But...
Time for me to head home!
Stay safe, Master Koichi!
It looks like he's not in his classroom right now.
If that Hazamada guy seriously gouged out his friend's eye and came to school today acting like nothing was wrong...
...then he must be one messed up dude.
H-Hey, Josuke!
I'm gonna take a look inside his locker. Cover me, Koichi.
You could at least warn me before you do something like that!
For starters... His bag's still here.
Guess he's still at school. We need to be careful.
R-Right...
He's in the tennis club, and he likes comics.
This guy is hoarding way too much junk.
I doubt the bow and arrow is in here, but...
What's this piece of wood doing here?
A Sta-
N-No... This thing's an actual object.
Is this supposed to be one of those dolls they sell at art stores?
It almost gave me a heart attack...
Huh?!
What? Why?!
It turned into me after I touched it!
Now we know for sure...
Hazamada is a Stand user!
Great! You've got some nerve, making yourself look like me!
Note: A Japanese comic and animated TV series about a clumsy boy who becomes a superhero's apprentice.
You've heard of Perman, right?
I-It talked! It sounds exactly like him!
You know how there was that copy-robot thing in Perman?
Doesn't that sound super handy?
Wouldn't it be sweet having one of those?
Hey, Koichi. What is he talking about?
What the hell is Perman?
You've never heard of Perman?! Unbelievable!
And you call yourself Japanese?
Quit rambling! I'm the one asking questions here!
M-My arm!
Josuke!
The only difference between the copy-robot and me is that I can copy whoever I want!
Once I copy someone, they're forced to mimic my every move.
So I'm less like a puppet...
...and more like a puppet master!
K-Koichi! M-Move!
Koichi!
That's one of you taken care of.
Oh, but I can't take all the credit!
The one who really did it is you, his very own friend!
Shit like this...
...really pisses me off!
When people like you make others do their dirty work,
and never do anything themselves...
...it makes me wanna beat some sense into them!
Great! Tee-hee!
Dora!
Guess I'm outside your range.
If a user stays in one place, their Stand can only move so far.
Basically, by staying this far away from you, Josuke, you have no way of beating me!
Dora!
This Stand is called "Surface."
By possessing a doll, it gains physical form.
Because of that, even normal people can see it.
Hazamada! You asshole!
My goal is to beat the shit out of Kujo Jotaro so he stays out of this town for good.
That guy's a real piece of work!
Trying to dig up dirt on us as an outsider...
I hear Jotaro's Stand, Star Platinum,
can stop time for a second or two.
None of us stand a chance against a powerful Stand user like him.
But Josuke, this Surface copy of you has given us that chance!
I just need you to stay knocked out for a while!
You're the only thing standing in our way!
He collapsed, huh?
Now that's a sound I like to hear!
As long as he didn't slice a nerve,
he should still be able to see.
If he's lucky, anyway.
Looks like he won't be waking up for a while!
That was a piece of cake!
Hey! Pick up my bag.
We're going after Jotaro now.
Piece of cake...
I'm pretty sure the hotel Jotaro's staying at is called...
SFX: Gish!
...uh...
The Morioh Grand Hotel!
Yeah, that's the one!
Koichi!
J-Josuke, are you okay?
Th-Thanks for asking...
But man, that was a gutsy move.
Even though you're hurt, you still used your Stand to trick him.
What are you talking about?
The only reason I was able to do that is because
you healed my face with Crazy Diamond as I got hit...
Just one thing...
It would be nice if you could heal the injuries I got from slamming into the door, too.
O-Oh yeah!
Yes, this is the Morioh Grand Hotel.
Oh, uh, could you put me through to Kujo Jotaro in room 324?
One moment, please.
We're losing time!
We need to tell Mr. Jotaro about that Stand as soon as possible!
Thank you for waiting.
The line for Room 324 is currently in use.
Please wait until the current call is completed.
The line's in use?
Huh?!
Of course! It's gotta be my copy!
It must have called him before we did!
You sure, Josuke?
There's another Stand user at your school?
Yup! I'll fill you in at Morioh Station.
Meet me at the station plaza.
Should only take you fiften minutes to get there.
Got it. Front of the station in fifteen minutes.
Piece of cake!
N-No dice! He's not picking up!
He must have left already!
Mr. Jotaro was probably lured into meeting it somewhere!
Dammit! We're just gonna have to make a break for my copy!
To tell you the truth,
I couldn't really tell you and your copy apart!
Yeah. Seeing its face didn't really
creep me out, but its fingers sure did.
You see your fingers way more than your face, right?
I knew it was a perfect copy
just from how it copied my fingerprints.
Oh!
Josuke, that was quick!
Where's Master Koichi?
H-Hazamada?!
Why are you with him?
You're Kobayashi Tamami?
You really don't know why we're together?
I-I don't...
No idea at all?
I don't know! Why?!
Then...
...take this!
Step on it.
We've gotta hurry and catch up to Hazamada!
Otherwise Mr. Jotaro will be in deep shit!
Su
Sur
Surfa
Surface
Hazama
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Hazamada
Hazamada Toshi
Hazamada Toshikazu
9 Mi
9 Minu
9 Minutes
9 Minutes Le
9 Minutes Left
9 Minutes Left Un
9 Minutes Left Until
9 Minutes Left Until the
9 Minutes Left Until the M
9 Minutes Left Until the Mee
9 Minutes Left Until the Meet
9 Minutes Left Until the Meeting
It's gonna be really bad if your copy gets to Mr. Jotaro first!
Really, really bad!
Yeah!
I don't know how, but we need to catch up to it!
Bye-bye, Josuke!
See you tomorrow!
Bye!
Josuke!
Josuke, see you later!
Why the fuck do they only say goodbye to you?
Nobody ever says that to me!
All the girls in this school are fucking pigs, anyway!
Josuke...
Umm, will you read this?
L-Later!
Why the fuck did you take that?!
You don't deserve this!
Goddammit!
What makes you so special compared to me?
What the hell does it matter?
You don't have time to mess around, right?
Watch who you're fucking talking to!
Oww!
Did you scrape your hand?
That was pretty careless of you!
I'm made of wood, remember?
Shut the fuck up!
Keep your hands away from me!
Dammit, this is pissing me off.
Even though it's my Stand, this happens every time!
The other day, I had it copy the girl I had a crush on, Junko...
...but it kept doing shit to piss me off,
so it didn't go anywhere good!
Isn't there anyone in this world
who isn't a total mouth breather? Dammit!
That idiot Josuke!
First I need to get rid of Jotaro,
then I'm gonna smash him to bits!
It's gonna be awesome!
My bike!
He smudged it...
Dammit, is that idiot out of his mind? I'm gonna kill him!
Hey, I'm sure he didn't do it on purpose. He'll hear you.
Who cares? That's why I'm yelling!
Just look at him staggering around...
Seriously, he looks like a dying cricket!
That's a great metaphor! I like it!
You like it? Describes him pretty well, huh?
Hold him still, Surface.
I'm gonna gut him like a fish!
Wh-What are you doing?!
It's none of your fucking concern!
I'm just gonna make sure that mouth of yours
never spews bullshit ever again!
D-Don't!
A shard of glass?
H-Higashikata Josuke?!
Why? And he's got that midget with him, too!
Hazamada!
We finally caught up to you, asshole!
Did you already forget?
When you're within range of my Surface,
Josuke, you become my puppet!
Control him, Surface!
Are you sure about that?
Wha- That shape!
I wasn't trying to hit you with that glass shard!
I just needed it to be near you before I restored it!
M-My right hand!
It turned back into wood!
This sucks, Hazamada!
Calm down!
Just pretend you have your hand in your pocket!
No one will notice!
What we really need to worry about is that
Jotaro is gonna be at the station at any minute!
I'm still surprised Josuke wasn't hurt,
but we can't focus on beating him right now!
H-Hazamada! Wait for me!
I see...
They're meeting him in front of the station.
J-Josuke, we can't waste any more time!
They took the fastest possible route to the station!
No problem. That's why I have you, Koichi.
Looks like Josuke's not here yet.
You see Josuke anywhere around here?
Can't say I do!
But when I do, I'll take control of him again.
We've got this in the bag!
Hazamada! There's a train coming!
We're not gonna make it through!
Not unless we wait...
All right! Let's cut through the station building!
Even if Josuke catches up to us,
the train will definitely stall him!
Only one more minute!
I'm gonna get there first!
I did it!
Huh?
Isn't that Josuke?!
Wh-What happened to the train?!
Why's the crossing clear?!
Hazamada, look!
Wh-What the fuck kind of Stand is that?!
SFX: Ding Ding Ding Ding!
Great! Didn't I tell you?
That what I have you for, Koichi!
Ah! There he is!
M-Mr. Jotaro! It's me, Josuke!
Yo.
We made it!
We sure got Hazamada good, didn't we, Josuke?
Did something happen?
A copy?
A Stand copied you down to your fingerprints?
It sure did!
This could've ended badly if he had made it here before I did!
Now we have nothing to worry about!
The copy is missing his right hand, so this should be easy.
I was able to take it off myself.
That's how you can tell us apart.
Got it.
They should be here any second now.
Huh? What am I doing with this thing?
Why did I grab a pen from Mr. Jotaro's coat pocket?
I-I can't move!
My arm feels frozen in place...
O-On the other side of the glass...!
Th-That's...
Higashikata Josuke...
...I'm gonna have you stab Jotaro in the head
and kill him instantly for me!
After all, if he doesn't die instantly,
your Crazy Diamond can just heal him right up!
Josuke! This is your fault for
poking your nose where it doesn't belong!
My original plan was to beat him up just enough to convince him to leave this town on his own...
...but now I'm gonna make you kill him with your own hand!
It will be all your fault!
Do it! Let him have it, Surface!
M-Mr. Jotaro!
Asshole!
Something wrong, Josuke?
Huh? No...
Guess those guys finally found Hazamada.
You little shit!
You were right across the pedestrian bridge
at the station, just like that Josuke guy said!
Unlike you, he's actually a nice kid!
I don't know how,
but he healed our wounds and made us all better!
You're gonna pay for everything you did earlier!
Let's settle this behind the restroom!
That Stand is pretty terrifying if it copies you.
Anyway, guess I should take care of this doll.
Gotta release my pent-up rage somehow!
Dorararara!
Unknown to the others, Tamami was admitted to the hospital.
What a complete idiot!
Well, you got my condolences!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 8
Yamagishi
Yukako Falls in
Love
Part 1
Yu
Love
Yamagishi
kako Falls in
Part 1
Yu
Love