It's Morioh Radio!
Coming at you once again is yours truly, Kai Harada.
To get you up to speed, last week's topic was...
Check out how my spokes shine while they spin!
"The King of Terror is supposed to come from the sky this July.
What are the citizens of Morioh to do?"
I got this mountain bike as a gift for getting into high school!
Getting new stuff is always so exciting!
All right, let's get to the replies.
Guess this means I won't be taking the bus for a while!
O-Oww...
Wh-What was that?
Someone left a bag in the middle of the road...
N-No way! The thing inside that bag was a...
Wh-What am I gonna do?! I ran it over!
I-It was just an accident!
It was right in the middle of the road!
I couldn't help it!
Exactly!
That wasn't your fault.
It was just an unfortunate accident.
Whoever left that kitten inside a bag
in the middle of the road is to blame.
It's pretty horrific, huh?
W-We have to help it!
Too late.
You don't hear any crying, right?
It died.
What's your name?
My name's Kobayashi Tamami, and I just so happened to
graduate from the same school as you two years ago.
Nice bike you got there.
You a first-year?
Y-Yeah... My name is Hirose Koichi.
Man, that takes me back. High school was the best.
Things were great back then.
Anyway, have a seat, Hirose, my pal.
Huh? B-But...
C'mon, be quiet and have a seat!
So, I got a proposition for you.
I can bury that kitten for you,
but you'll have to give me a bit of cash in exchange. Sound good?
Hey! You listening to me?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
C'mon kid, quit yanking my chain.
I know this wasn't your fault...
...but are you really gonna do nothing about killing my cat?
Are you telling me that was your cat?
Sure was!
Y-You put your kitten in a place like that?
We're way past that, my friend!
I just wanna know if you really plan to do nothing about it.
After all, you're the one who killed it, kid!
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 6:  Hirose Koichi (Echoes)
So, you're probably feeling pretty guilty about this, am I right?
If spending a little cash would
free your heart from the shackles of guilt...
...you'd be stupid not to do it, right?
Right?
Wh-What's this lock-thing in my chest?!
It's so heavy!
Huh? You can see that?
Heh, then this should be quick, Hirose, my pal!
Th-This is a Stand!
There's a Stand lodged inside my chest!
Hey, Josuke...
Ain't that Koichi over there?
Yeah, it's definitely him.
He's always hanging around real shady-looking types.
Looks like he's havin' fun!
I'll have you know, I got my ability from a guy
named Nijimura Keicho just four months ago.
I couldn't tell you why it happened, but I've been happy ever since!
If I take advantage of my ability while I'm young,
I'll be set for the rest of my life!
Anyway...
Hurry and cough it up!
This lock isn't going anywhere until you pay up!
I-I'm all out...
...of money...
Huh? Did you really just look away from me?
W-Well...
I-It became heavier!
I'm gonna fall!
Tsk, tsk, tsk!
Lying like that isn't very nice of you!
You felt pretty guilty doing that, didn't you?
The guiltier you feel, the bigger my lock becomes.
It represents the weight of your sins.
It's automatic.
Even if I'm asleep, or really far away, it won't ever come off!
Get it? Now you'd best be coughing up your wallet.
Come on.
Are you for real?
You should have just given it to me in the first place!
You've even got seven thousand yen!
I-I need it to buy new sneakers for gym class today...
Sneakers?
Go barefoot!
What's going on over here?
J-Josuke and Okuyasu!
A grown man trying to threaten a high school kid for money?
How about you find a job and make your own money?
Hold it! Mind your own business, kiddos!
That ain't happening.
If there's trashy Stand users around,
abusing the power of their Stands...
...they need to be taken out with the rest of the garbage.
Hey...
This thing's really wedged in there!
Whoa, hold on... You guys can see it, too?
Just how many people around here can?
That's what I'd like to know.
But right now, it doesn't matter.
Will you please remove the lock from his chest?
Hey, you goddamn brats! Don't underestimate me!
I'm not messing around here!
Sinners have to pay for their sins! It's a rule of society!
How about this?
Why don't you two pay me in Koichi's stead?
I'll let him off the hook if you do.
Money is money, after all.
Oh? Tryin' t'pull a fast one?
Fuckin' try me!
Hold on a second! You already took seven thousand yen from me!
Consider it a fee for lying to my face, idiot!
You think seven thousand yen is enough
to make up for taking the life of my poor kitten?
That just won't do.
Five hundred thousand should be enough.
Five hundred thousand?!
Of course, five hun-
Shut the fuck up, stupid!
O-Okuyasu!
Hey, don't push it...
An' keep your fuckin' mouth shut, dumbass!
We toldja t'give his money back, so cough it up!
O-Oww! My front tooth!
H-Hey, whydja stumble around an' fall on purpose like that?
"On purpose"? You're awful!
How could you say something like that after hitting me?!
You knocked out my front tooth! You're the worst!
H-Hey, hold up, buddy... You okay?
W-Wait, Okuyasu...
Don't let him make you feel guilty for what you did!
H-He did it on purpose!
Repairing a front tooth is pretty expensive, you know!
Doesn't help that my insurance won't cover it!
Y-Ya no good...
Take it easy! Don't try anything funny with me!
If anyone with one of my locks attached to them tries to hurt me,
the damage gets sent right back!
D-Dickhead...
Hey. Is this supposed to be the cat Koichi ran over?
A-A stuffed animal?
Here, let me have a look.
I picked up your front tooth for you.
All better, now.
It's gone!
He did it! My chest feels so much lighter!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Hey, what about that seven thousand yen?
D-Don't worry about it! I'll give it back!
We got the money, so fuck off, stupid!
Y-You saved me... Huh?!
Th-The bills... H-He took them!
He took the bigger parts so the bank would exchange them!
Th-That asshole!
Fuckin' scumbag! An' it ain't even my money...
Crap! Only got away with seven thousand yen.
Don't think you've seen the last of me!
Just you wait!
Having such a rough start this morning really ruined my day...
I'm back, Police.
Hey, you alive? Woof, woof!
I'm home!
Oh, you wouldn't believe the wonderful things I've heard about you around town, ma'am!
They say you're the epitome of beauty, compassion, and elegance!
You must be joking!
I'm most certainly not!
Really?
Absolutely!
Wh-What is he doing inside my house
rubbing my mom's shoulders?!
The
The Lock
Koba
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Kobayashi
Kobayashi Tama
Kobayashi Tamami
Y-You!
What are you doing here?!
Oh, Munchkin, you're home! Hi!
D-Don't make me ask again! Wh-Why are you here?!
This kind man came here to return the money you dropped earlier.
Huh?!
You rushed home and lost seven thousand yen!
Th-This money... You told my mom you found it?
That's right.
You ran into Mr. Kobayashi on your bike today, didn't you?
Wha-
You should thank me for returning your money, Koichi, my pal.
Th-That's just common decency!
Munchkin, why are you acting so abrasive?
Ma'am, it's difficult for me to say this, but...
...when I ran into your son,
I seem to have dropped my own wallet in the process.
It looks exactly like this one.
To put it mildly, somehow we swapped wallets.
Do you get what I'm saying, ma'am?
Y-Yes, though that seems so unlike him...
But I suppose it's possible.
In that case, would you please ask your son
to return my wallet to me?
I had about five hundred thousand yen in it.
Please have him return it.
What?!
F-Five hundred thousand?!
So that's it!
I know what you're up to!
M-Munchkin...
Don't panic! He's a con artist!
Oh, that's right.
It's all lies!
I can prove that our wallets were switched around.
Last night, I got a hamburger combo at Jonny's... and...
Right! I also had an order of onion gratin soup.
So I believe the total on the receipt should be 1,833 yen...
It should be tucked away in the wallet with Koichi.
M-Munchkin!
N-No! Mom, you have to believe me!
He's trying to trick you!
You hid it there earlier, didn't you?!
Then you went out and bought a similar looking wallet!
I hate to break it to you, but your son seems to be going through a pretty despicable phase of his life!
Don't you feel guilty as his mother for raising a son like that?
Stop!
M-Mom!
I finally did it!
Now the weight of her guilt will keep her heart locked up.
I'm gonna take you for everything you've got!
I'll start by taking your house's land, title, and seal!
It's such a nice house, too!
Koichi, is something wrong?
Sis!
Wh-What?!
When she brought me my tea earlier,
I made her spill some of it on my hand!
Then I pretended like it really burned,
and she was all like "I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!"
It was pretty cute and sexy!
She's a third-year at an all-girls school, right?
R-Ripe for the picking!
F-F-Fantastic!
How dare you!
You won't get away with this! I won't let you!
What the hell?
What's up with that puny egg-thing?
What the hell is that?!
Mom, Sis, I need you to leave the room for a bit!
Munchkin, what's happening?!
This isn't the time for questions!
Hey! K-Keep that thing away from me!
Your mom and sister leaving the room
doesn't change the fact that th-they're my hostages!
I won't let you harm my mom or my sister!
J-Just try it, Koichi! Just try!
Remove their locks, now!
If your mom sees you beat the crap out of me,
it will only make her feel even guiltier!
I told you to remove them!
Don't underestimate Kobayashi Tamami, you annoying little shit!
L-Like hell I'll take them off!
SFX: Ka-crack!
Huh? What?
That didn't hurt.
Huh?
SFX: Thwack!
Whoa! What's this?
That's an impressive sound, but it's so weak!
What the hell is with your Stand?
This thing isn't really fast or strong, is it?
How dare you scare me like that, dumbass!
I'll show you!
Your Stand's strength is directly related to your mental strength!
SFX: Ka-crack!
Which means your mental strength is nothing!
I'm gonna make sure you pay dearly for this!
Something weird is going on with his cheek...
SFX: Ka-crack!
"Ka-crack"?
It looks like some kind of comic book sound effect!
SFX: Ka-crack!
Wh-What the hell? There's some weird ringing in my ear!
It's the same sound from when he hit me...
What the hell is this writing on my arm?!
SFX: Thwack!
I-It won't come off!
SFX: Ka-crack!
SFX: Thwack! Ka-crack!
W-Wait... Th-These sounds that I hear coming from inside me...
Your Stand did this?!
Goddammit! Get rid of these sounds!
SFX: Woosh... Boom!
SFX: Thwack! Ka-crack! Woosh... Boom!
It's sound!
My Stand is making sounds reverberate inside his body!
C-Come to think of it, it reminds me of that famous Matsuo Basho poem I learned at school...
"So quiet and still...
...the shrill of the cicadas...
...seeps into the rocks."
Dammit! I totally fell for it!
I'll only stop the sounds if you remove the locks from my mom and sister!
If you keep resisting,
even I don't know what will happen to your body!
Stop the sounds!
SFX: Ka-boom!
Quit being stubborn and remove the locks!
Dammit! How could you do something so horrible to me?!
I wouldn't threaten and con people
if I was afraid of little shitheads like you!
The "Tama" in my name means "ballsy"!
Let me show you how I live up to that name!
I'm not scared of some knife!
Don't take me lightly!
Prepare to see just how terrifying I can really be!
The true power of the locks!
Oww!
What?!
Oww, oww, oww, oww!
Make the cut shallow, and scream like hell!
Catch!
"Catch"?
Who was just screaming?!
What's wrong?
Munchkin?!
I-It's not what it looks like!
O-Oh no!
Yes!
M-Munchkin! How could you do something so horrific?!
No, Mom! It's not what it looks like!
No!
Sis!
I win! You lose!
Now hurry and get rid of these sounds, Koichi!
If you don't stop them now,
your mother won't be able to bear the weight of her guilt!
When people have more guilt than they can bear,
they start to think they'd be better off dead!
I-I can't take it... anymore!
Mom!
I've had enough of this world!
Enough of the tough guy act!
Hurry and stop the sounds before your mom kills herself!
No, I won't stop them!
I'll do the exact opposite and make more!
Believe me!
SFX: Believe me!
What?!
I need you to believe me, Mom!
Text: Believe me!
Believe me!
Mom!
Text: Believe me!
Believe me!
My ability affects a person's very spirit!
Like hell she'll believe you!
Mom...
He's right... If I, his own mother, won't believe in him...
...then who will?
Koichi has always been a good boy...
He would never hurt someone or try to take their money!
Yes!
Th-This is bad!
Mom!
G-Goddammit!
They never would have believed me...
My parents never would have believed me!
Gulp...
I was just joking around!
Munchkin, you gotta believe me
when I say this was all just a joke!
Remove my sister's lock, too!
It's already off!
Wouldn't want to do anything to ruin
her picturesque beauty, right?
I was only joking about taking your house!
I even gave back your seven thousand yen, didn't I?
Right? Right?
Please forgive me! I'll do anything for you, Master Koichi!
Huh? You'll do anything?
Yes, Master Koichi! Anything! I'll be your underling!
Good. In that case...
Bring me five hundred thousand yen by tomorrow!
I'm joking! It was just a joke!
Th-That didn't sound like a joke at all!
H-Hey, Okuyasu! What the hell is going on here?
Allow me to carry your bag to school!
You're seriously going to carry it?
Why, of course!
Master Koichi! You're a true man among men!
C'mon, cut it out!
Hey, Okuyasu!
Fuck if I know! I ain't so smart, remember?
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 7
Hazamada Toshikazu (Surface)
Hazama
da Toshikazu (Surface)