There it is... Gramps' ship, right on schedule.
Only about twenty minutes away.
I-Is Mr. Joseph Joestar the only passenger?
Yeah.
The crew is made up of men from the Speedwagon Foundation.
That Stand, Red Hot Chili Pepper,
can only move where there's electricity, but...
...it will resort to any means necessary
to get over the water to that ship.
If it beats us there, we lose.
It will kill Gramps.
Mr. Jotaro!
We got the boat all checked out.
I didn't see it in the battery.
Everything's good. We can get going.
Josuke, only Okuyasu and I are going to Gramps' ship.
Huh?
You and Koichi will stay here at the harbor.
Stay here?! Josuke and me?
How come?
Josuke, Chili Pepper's user is hiding
somewhere around here, watching us.
He's waiting for us to make our move.
He wants to know where the ship is.
I'm assuming he won't be taking a boat there himself.
All he needs is something with a battery
that can outrace a motorboat.
Just like it used the bike,
Chili Pepper will use something with a battery to fly there.
Fly? You mean it's going to fly there with something?
Yeah.
Chili Pepper is probably stealing
an RC airplane from somewhere as we speak.
An RC airplane?!
That could actually work!
RC airplanes can travel over
one hundred kilometers per hour!
That's even faster than the motorboat!
And since Chili Pepper is controlling it,
it can keep flying as long as it doesn't run out of fuel or electricity!
The range of the remote control won't matter!
So, Josuke, if you see anything flying around, look for the user in the harbor.
Koichi's Echoes has a range of fifty meters.
It can help find him.
If he makes his move before we do, Gramps is done for.
It's up to you to protect your dad from the shore. Got it, Josuke?
Yeah. We can't afford to waste any more time here.
surechigatteku kao no nai shisen
As I watch the indistinct faces passing me by
mune no ana ga kaetetta nichijou
The hole in my heart reminds me how much my life has changed
kyoukai nante nakutearu atarimae no kimyou, oh yeah!
Not setting limits is just me being my usual bizarre self, oh yeah!
(itsumodoori no asa ga) uwatsura de warau
With the dawn of each new day, I put on a fake smile
(shouhai fumei no mamani) hikareru mystery
Although unknown battles lie ahead, their mystery compels me
(hajimari mo iwazu) jitto hisonderu kono machi no dokoka
A hidden threat has awoken, lurking somewhere in this town
dakedo kyou mo jojo ni
But for today, we'll banter together
monku nanka iatte
just the same as we always have
nichijou wo odoru
as we dance our way through life
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
in this Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town!
Episode 12:  Red Hot Chili Pepper Part 2
Good luck, Okuyasu!
Thanks, Koichi...
We'll be arriving at Morioh harbor
in about twenty minutes, Mr. Joestar.
I see... Umm...
Have you seen my cane anywhere?
Huh? Isn't that it right in front of you?
Ah!
My dad, huh...
Josuke? What's wrong?
Knowing that my dad is some guy I've never even met is kinda...
How can I say it...
Well, none of that matters right now since he's in danger.
If I don't do my best to protect him, it'll haunt my dreams.
My mom will be a mess if she knows I let him die.
Shit! Jotaro figured it out!
Since he had you two idiots stay behind to find my user...
...it means he figured out my plan to use an RC airplane!
Red Hot Chili Pepper!
Yeah!
Kujo Jotaro is a pretty sharp guy.
He's the last person I want looking for me.
This remote control model Spitfire I stole
will reach Joseph Joestar in just five minutes.
That motorboat will take at least eight to ten minutes.
Which means that if I get rid of
both of you within three minutes...
...I'll have all the time I need to beat them there!
Y-You're Chili Pepper's user?
The name's Otoishi Akira; nineteen years old!
Oh, don't worry about my guitar.
My dream is to live hard and fast like Jimi Hendrix and Jeff Beck!
I'll be an ultra super guitarist just like them!
That's why I keep it on me at all times!
Someday soon, I'm gonna take my guitar...
...and give knock out performances all around the world!
Oh yeah!
I never expected the user to reveal himself like this!
He must be really confident that he can kill Josuke and me!
SFX: Yes!
To defeat your Crazy Diamond, I'll use only my pinky finger...
...just like I did against Okuyasu earlier.
Stay back, Koichi.
Let's rock, Higashikata Josuke!
Hold on...
Huh?
If you're making it a rule to only use your pinky,
I'm gonna make a rule of my own.
Rules? Get the fuck outta here!
A loser like you doesn't need any self-imposed rules!
What the fuck is wrong with you, asshole?!
You're the one who told me
I didn't need any self-imposed rules!
Didn't you say you were only gonna use your pinky finger?
So, what are you gonna do now, Mr. Otoishi?
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
You already said that!
Now you're just repeating yourself, dumbass!
This pain and agony...
How am I supposed to let it out?!
This rage building up inside me...
Who can I take it out on?!
Amazing...
Right-Hand Tapping
"I want... to kill... your Mamas!"
That was the truest expression of the feelings in my heart!
The ultimate expression of rage!
Let's do this, Otoishi!
Dorararara!
Wh-What the hell? The user just...
It makes sense that his Stand could move so quickly, but how was he himself able to do that?
Y-You're wrong, Josuke!
I saw exactly what happened from right here!
Otoishi isn't the one who moved...
It was you!
He moved you!
What?
He called out Chili Pepper and turned
Crazy Diamond around at super speed!
You're facing the ocean now, right?
He called out Chili Pepper?
Koichi! I didn't see Chili Pepper at all!
It's under the ground!
See all the drainage grates around you?
Its upper body popped out from one of them just now!
There must be electrical wires running everywhere underneath!
I'm at my strongest when I reflect on my actions.
Behind you and to your right! There it is!
Dora!
Now it's behind you!
Dorararara!
It keeps retreating into the electrical wires!
It's moving at the speed of light!
Mr. Jotaro is the only one who could keep up with it!
You don't have enough time to dig up the asphalt
and remove all the electrical wires, Higashikata Josuke.
And the more holes you make in the ground...
...the more places I can pop out of!
Josuke! To your right!
In front of you!
Behind you!
No, wait! Uh...
This is like a deadly game of whack-a-mole!
It's moving too fast for me to tell where it will pop up next!
Dora! Dora! Dora!
Blindly guessing where I'll pop up isn't gonna work!
Josuke...
I've still got two minutes left...
Plenty of time to finish you off.
Koichi, watch for where Chili Pepper
pops up next and tell me exactly where it is.
I'm too close to see where it is!
I-I can barely see it myself!
Every time I see it, it's gone again in an instant!
Just watch carefully, Koichi.
I'm sure you can tell what I'm thinking by now.
Huh? What do you mean?
I-It's all squishy!
The asphalt turned into coal tar...
...and the grates are completely covered in it!
Now I get it!
When he hit the ground earlier,
he restored the asphalt into a different form!
That means...
Behind you and to the left!
Dorararara!
Yeah! Bull's eye!
Bull's eye? That's a great one!
Do I get a prize if I keep hitting him?
R
Re
Red
Red H
Red Ho
Red Hot
Red Hot Chi
Red Hot Chil
Red Hot Chili
Red Hot Chili Pe
Red Hot Chili Pep
Red Hot Chili Peppe
Red Hot Chili Pepper
Oto
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Otoishi
Otoishi Akira
There's the ship! It's the Traffic!
W-We almost made it!
Don't let your guard down.
Huh?
Th-The hell is that?!
Josuke! Koichi!
I-It's so bright!
Up until now, Higashikata Josuke,
I was careless in how I fought you!
Guess I'm gonna have to do something about that, won't I?
I'm concentrating all of Morioh's electricity
into my Red Hot Chili Pepper!
I only waited until now to do this since it's gonna eat up all the power in the area, reducing my strength to zero!
But I don't give a fuck anymore!
Once I'm done with you two,
I'm gonna fly inside the RC airplane's battery and kill Joseph!
I-I can't see!
Asshole!
Dorararara!
I-It overpowered Josuke!
Josuke!
You get it now?
All of the electricity in this town is mine to control!
I'll make sure all the power I've eaten up gets put on your electricity meter!
You're finished, Josuke!
A-A tire?!
Little did you know, it was already too late to do anything.
You destroyed that tire on purpose, didn't you?!
You purposely did it so you could
trap my Stand inside the rubber!
That's right!
Since rubber is an insulator, it doesn't conduct electricity!
Chili Pepper can't use any electricity!
Dammit!
Yes! Now we just have to wait for Mr. Jotaro!
Gotcha!
Huh?
You think the rubber from that tire is strong enough?
Maybe if it was a meter thick!
Don't make me laugh!
This flimsy rubber isn't enough to contain my power!
Idiots!
It's curtains for you, Josuke!
Great. You would have gotten off easier...
...if you didn't have the power to break through that tire.
Th-The inside of the tire...!
It was completely full of air?!
N-Not the ocean! This is bad!
O-Oh yeah...
Salt water conducts electricity!
Since the ocean is so huge,
all that electricity will spread out in every direction!
I'm sorry! Please!
Get me outta here!
Earlier, it sounded like you were reflecting on your careless attitude toward fighting me...
Too bad being careless is ingrained in your character.
I-I'm dispersing...
Since his Stand dispersed through the water...
I-Is he dead?
Mr. Jotaro!
We defeated the user!
We defeated Chili Pepper's user!
Good job! That's a relief.
So this guy's Josuke's old man...
He's pretty big, but the guy's a serious geezer...
Excuse me, young man...
Can I have your name?
O-Okuyasu...
Okuyasu?
Me an' Josuke're neighbors, an' I'm also a Stand user.
Huh?
Stand user!
Sta-nd u-ser!
Ah, you also drive a Land Cruiser?
I said Stand user!
Oh, is that so? You're a Stand user?
That's awfully dangerous.
Come to think of it, Osomatsu, I seem to have misplaced my cane.
Have you seen it anywhere?
Note: A reference to the 1962 Japanese comic "Osomatsu-kun."
Ah!
How silly of me! I was holding it all along!
Is this old fart right in the head?
Mr. Joestar...
...I'm here to help carry your luggage.
By the way, Osomatsu, I have a question for you.
It's about Josuke...
Since I haven't seen the boy once in all these sixteen years,
would you mind telling me if he's ever mentioned me?
Far as I know, he ain't never said nothin' 'bout you.
I see... So he hasn't...
Yay! It's finally here!
Look, Josuke!
Yeah. That's nice, I guess.
To be honest...
...I'd be happier if he just turned around and went home.
Josuke...
I mean, I'm glad he wasn't killed by Otoishi.
Everything worked out in the end.
Still...
...I've never even met the guy before.
I can't see him as my dad.
This whole thing's gonna be awkward for both of us.
I don't have anything against him...
...but I need to think about my mom, too.
You get what I'm saying, Koichi?
O-Oh no...
Josuke, this is bad!
Th-The body!
Mr. Jotaro, we have trouble!
Otoishi Akira's body disappeared!
Somehow...
...he's still alive!
There's trouble! The enemy has boarded the ship!
Otoishi Akira is still alive!
You kiddin' me?
Take Mr. Joestar...
Who are you?
Huh? You say somethin'?
No, he...
I said that!
That man isn't from the Speedwagon Foundation!
Wh-What did you say?!
He's the enemy!
Seriously? Ya scumbag!
Hold on a second!
I'm the one who told you about the enemy!
Would the actual enemy do something like that?
He's the real enemy!
Ya got a good point!
But I was the first one to point out the enemy!
He came here to tell you so you'd let your guard down!
Y-Ya got a good point, too...
Wh-Which one of 'em is it?
It's him!
Urgh!
I gotta choose again?!
Fuck me!
Serves me right for leavin' this kinda stuff to my bro!
Okuyasu's not a problem for me.
And Jotaro still hasn't seen my face yet.
Once I kill Joseph...
...I'll escape!
I'll get as far away as possible!
Red Hot Chili Pepper!
Huh? Pop Pop Pigeon Popper?
I'm gonna kill you!
I know which one of you's the user now!
It's you!
There ain't nobody who fools Nijimura Okuyasu twice!
H-How did you know?
You wanna know?
How...?
I was ready t'punch the both of ya! I ain't too smart, y'know?
Watch it...
You need to be careful. You could fall into the ocean.
S-Sorry...
I would be fine if I had my cane...
...but now it's broken in two...
G-Guess there's nothing you can do about it...
Take my hand.
I just got a great idea!
Crazy Diamond can restore this thing!
Y-You don't get it, dummy!
Sometimes you're really dense, Okuyasu!
Huh? Why's that?
It's for the best if he doesn't try to restore it, don't you think?
Huh? Why?
Can'tcha tell me?
Now it's just a matter of finding the bow and arrow...
...to end the threat to this town.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 13
Picking Up Something Dangerous!
!
ous
Picking Up Something Danger
!
ous