Congratulations for receiving the winning ticket!
In spite of the fact you've chosen to make
your claim just before the expiration date...
...you are most certainly still entitled to the third place prize of five million yen.
With that said, here you go.
Your promissory note for five million yen.
As per the terms of the lottery,
this note will be available to cash in just three days.
One, ten, a hundred, a thousand...
Th-There's six zeros!
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 19:  Shigechi's Harvest Part 2
Pardon my prying, but...
Note: Reception Office
...from which vendor did you gentlemen purchase this ticket?
Sniff, sniff...
Wh-Which vendor?
Wh-Why do you wanna know that?
Oh, it's just a formality.
You impertinent brats!
You won five million yen?
This absolutely reeks of foul play!
As an experienced banking associate,
I smell something rotten here!
Is there any reason you won't answer my question?
W-Well, we got in it Morioh, of course!
Oh, really? How very bizarre...
As it so happens,
there isn't a single lottery vendor located in Morioh.
Th-That's right!
We must have gotten it while we were in S city!
We bought so many things that
it must have slipped my mind...
I-I-I-It was a long time ago, too!
You know, I just had a bizarre realization.
On the opposite side of the lottery ticket, there's a section where one may write in their name and telephone number, and it says...
Morishita Ichiro
...Morishita Ichiro.
Sirs, it would seem the name written here
doesn't match any of yours.
N-Name?!
Phone number?!
Who wrote dat dere?!
U-Umm...
My, my, my, this is truly bizarre!
This is your lottery ticket, isn't it?
Oh yeah! That's right! I remember now!
I used the backside to write down my friend's
phone number since I didn't have a memo pad on me!
Oh, my! Is that so?
So I suppose that means you're fine with me giving Mr. Morishita Ichiro a quick call, yes?
We're able to determine exactly where each
lottery ticket is purchased by checking the serial number.
If Mr. Morishita Ichiro was the one who purchased this ticket...
...and he correctly tells us where he bought it...
...we'll have to verify his signature...
...so we can figure out who rightfully owns this ticket.
Depending on what happens,
we may have to turn it over to the police.
The police?!
Hello? This is Morishita.
I'm calling on behalf of Budogaoka Bank...
I would like to know if a Mr. Morishita Ichiro
previously purchased a Great Year-End Lottery ticket.
Oh, I'm Morishita Ichiro, and I did buy one of those.
I'm sure I did.
I have you now, you impertinent brats!
My sense of smell was spot on!
There's not a chance in hell God would
grant stupid brats like you the winning ticket!
Dora!
Morishita Ichiro
Morishita
So you did! Can you confirm that for me once more?
Yeah, I did.
I got about ten of them at the same time,
and they were all losses.
I'm just gonna change the numbers a little bit!
You see, Mr. Kinoshita, your lottery ticket-
Kinoshita? But my name's Morishita!
Huh? I'm sure it said Mori before! Why, how strange...
Umm... your phone number is 1771-1281, correct, Mr. Kinoshita?
I already told you my name's not Kinoshita, idiot!
It's Morishita!
Why are you wasting my time with this?
I already threw out my tickets.
Why don't you try selling some winning tickets for once?
I-I'm so sorry!
J-Just wait, kids!
The number you are trying to reach is currently not in use.
Please confirm that the number is correct and try again.
Y-Ya believe us now?
I-I-I'm terribly sorry for my rudeness!
Yippee! We gots money!
I wons all five million yen!
Hey, ya promised halfa that t'us, Shigechi!
Did I do dat?
You seriously tryin' that again?!
Hey, Josuke! Why're ya stoppin' me?
We ain't letting him pull this shit again, are we?
No... I'm not holding back anymore!
I won't let you get away with it this time!
You tell him, Josuke!
I knew ya wouldn't back down!
Only makes sense!
Am I right in saying you don't wanna
split the money anymore, Shigechi?
You realize too much is at stake
for us to let this slide, don't you?
Here...
Dis's good 'nuff fer botha ya.
It ain't like ya dids mucha anythin'.
I jus' feels bad since we's buddies an' all.
Ya fuckin' pipsqueak!
Hey, Okuyasu!
Cough up the dough, dumbass!
Ya promised half, so ya better fuckin' hand it over!
Quit bein' such a greedy dipshit!
You're always so quick to hit people!
You need to calm down!
When fuckin' dipshits ain't got a clue what you're sayin',
ya gotta knock some sense into 'em!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry Okuyasu hit you all of a sudden.
But don't worry, Shigechi.
We're not trying to cause trouble for you.
We're just gonna hold onto the note for five million yen.
In three days, when we're able to cash it...
...we'll split it evenly in half, just like we agreed on.
Man, that kid's a real pain in the ass!
I'm done hangin' out with him.
You know, maybe we should take a hard look at ourselves
for thinking we could use him to earn some extra pocket money.
Don't be stupid!
Huh?
That ain't no way of thinkin' about it!
Only reason he even got five million is 'cause of us!
Bastard woulda been lucky to get a couple thousand.
Now he's gettin' 2.5 million.
2.5 million!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
You ain't havin' it.
You ain't havin' it!
I heards you guys, dammit!
I ain't gunna gives neither of ya a single yen!
My Harvest gots dat five million all by its lonesome!
Y'all won't never defeats my Harvest!
Wanna see why, huh?
Ya needs me t'shows ya, huh?!
I'll shows ya!
Oww!
Ya fucker!
Dammit!
The five million yen promissory note!
Don't take us lightly, ya fuckin' twerp!
If y'all trys chasin' me...
...I'll kills ya.
Shigechi...
Ya think you can kill us, ya greedy bastard?
Ya better be ready t'die if ya even think about attackin' us with your Stand, dammit!
W-W-W-Wait, Josuke...
What's wrong?
Somethin' feels all funny!
M-My legs're itchin' real bad!
Itching? At a time like this?
They're itchin' so bad!
My whole body itches!
Wh-What the fuck's goin' on?!
Pull up your pant legs, Okuyasu! Hurry!
What?!
They're inside my pants!
Dorararara!
Dora! Dora! Dora!
I-It's not working!
Defeating two or three of them
isn't enough to do any damage to him!
Goddammit!
He's gettin' away!
N-Now he's really pissed me off!
I'm way fuckin' past pissed off!
You're not getting away with all five million yen!
That greedy little fucker's got
the Okuyasu-Josuke duo t'deal with!
C
Cr
Cra
Craz
Crazy
Crazy D
Crazy Di
Crazy Dia
Crazy Diam
Crazy Diamo
Crazy Diamon
Crazy Diamond
Higashi
Higashikata
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Higashikata Jo
Higashikata Josuke
Shit! Ya gotta be real stupid t'make an enemy of Okuyasu!
He's really got it comin'!
He's definitely stupid if he thought
taking all five million was a good idea!
Ya fuckin' fatass!
Ya think ya can get away with all that fat weighin' ya down?
See? That's whatcha get, retard!
H-He keeps summonin' Harvest dudes
under himself like a conveyor belt...
...or some kinda bucket relay!
What the hell? He's moving ridiculously fast!
The kid's pretty stupid, but I gotta hand it to him!
Is he usin' his instincts?
Shit! We're losin' him!
Calm down.
All we gotta do...
...is use our Stands to lift each other up the same way he is, then corner him!
Hell yeah!
My five million...
Did you really think you could get away from us, Shigechi?
Bring it on! I'll pop your Harvest
like a buncha balloons, one at a time!
My Harvest is da bestest!
It'll gets anythin' fer me!
Even da nuts holdin' dis pipe together!
Da bolts, too!
If you think that's amazing,
you should get a load of my Crazy Diamond!
Dora Dora!
Ta-dah!
I'm still fuckin' pissed off, but I'm ready t'forgive ya.
Right after I get a couple good hits on ya!
Come on, give us the promissory note
for the five million, Shigechi.
I already toldja...
If y'all tried chasin' me...
...I'd kills ya.
Wh-What? M-My hands...
O-Ouch...
I can't get up!
Okuyasu, be careful!
He did something to me!
O-Okuyasu, you too?
Ya don'ts know what's goin' on?
I got botha y'all drunk!
A-Alcohol?!
My Harvest'll get whatever I wants!
I had it gets me some booze from da liquor store...
...an' inject it right into botha y'all!
Right into yer veins!
Wh-What?!
You bastard!
When ya gets booze in yer veins,
even a little'll getcha drunk!
N-Now that I think about it,
I remember hearing that alcohol can act like an anesthetic!
H-He may be smarter than I thought...
Or is this just his instincts?
I-I'm gonna fuckin' kill him!
Ain't no way I'm gonna lose 'cause of a little booze!
M-My eye!
Josuke, hurry up an' heal it!
W-Wait, Okuyasu!
Y'all had some real gumption,
callin' me a pain an' stuffs, didn'tcha?
I'm gunna gives ya a taste of
what happens when ya mess with me!
D-Dammit!
You have the nerve to get a big head
after blatantly breaking the promise you made?
I'm gonna get really mad soon!
Who knows what I'll do to you then!
Shut yer dumb mouth, Josuke!
Yer Stands can't do diddly!
Y'all're worthless!
Start orderin' me around once yer even
half as strong as Harvest!
Josuke, shut your eyes!
Josuke!
Darn, almost gotcha!
Closin' yer eyes ain't gonna helps fer much!
Harvest gets all the stuffs I want!
It'll rip your eyelids clean off an' pull out yer eyeballs!
Fine, Shigechi! That's enough!
Ya gotta forgive us! This's all our fault!
Oh? Y'all're sorry now?
Goddammit, you little asshole!
Oh? Okuyasu, looks t'me like Josuke ain't too sorry.
I-I'll talk some sense into him!
Please, ya just gotta forgive us!
Here's the rest of my money
an' the ten thousand yen ya gave us!
Please, just forgive us!
Who's gonna heal my eye if Josuke's dead?
O-Okuyasu...
Oh, yeah! I remember dat!
I was feelin' bad fer you fellers,
an' I gaves ya more'n ten thousand yen!
Here, just take it and forgive the both of us!
I get it, Okuyasu!
Just like baiting a raccoon dog with food and catching it,
you're trying to lure him over with cash to defeat him!
Your good pal Josuke always knows just what you're thinking!
Okuyasu, tellin' me da truth's real good of ya!
Good, good!
Hey, wait right dere!
Okuyasu, ya ain't tryin' t'hurt me with yer Stand by lurin' me overs with dat money, are ya?!
Ah! Ya are!
Didja really thinks I'd fall fer dat?!
Ya thoughts I was dat stupid?!
I ain't forgivin' ya no mores!
Ain't a problem if ya don't forgive us.
But you're too late!
Didn'tcha realize ya were already in The Hand's range?
I just gotta erase the space between us...
...and it'll teleport right over!
It's ours now!
Yours now?!
Wh-What're ya tryin' t'say?
I jus' gots t'take it back...
You still haven't realized, Shigechi...
...that any chance you had of winning just slipped away.
My five million!
What're ya doin'?!
No way! No way!
Stop dat!
Why wouldja do somethin' like dat?!
No way! No way! No way! No way!
Dat's five million yen!
Go ahead and try to hurt us if you want.
The only way this ticket is getting fixed is by my Crazy Diamond.
There's no way you can win here.
Oh... I see, yeah way!
And this should seal the deal!
H-Huh?! No way, no way, no way, no way!
What was dat for?!
Gather 'em all up, Harvest!
Guess you haven't realized it yet...
Sending away Harvest to pick up those pieces
just guaranteed your loss.
So tell me, whodya think's gonna
protect ya from our drunk asses?
Oh, yeah way...
Take that!
Now listen here, Shigechi...
Why don't we go over a few simple things together?
The one who collects all the pieces is your Harvest.
But whose Stand is gonna put them all back together?
Hmm?
Whose will it be?
Who will put them back together with their Crazy Diamond?
J-Josuke...
Josuke? Is that any way to refer to the likes of me?!
M-Mr. Josuke!
Yeah, that's Mr. Josuke to you!
And who was the one who took back
the promissory note from you?
Well? Say his name.
O-Okuyasu...
Mr. Okuyasu!
Good, good. That's what I like to hear.
Next, let's do a little bit of math.
What's the fairest way to split five million?
How can we do it so that nobody feels cheated?
H-Half's good fer me...
Half?!
Did you forget there's three of us here?!
Doesn't half seem a bit unfair?
It doesn't add up at all!
Hello?
I-It'd be a third...
D-Dat's right...
Alls I could do is gather 'em up!
Y-Y'all was right...
We gots the lottery ticket together!
Jus' one of us couldn'ta gots it alone!
I...
I gets it now... I-I gots blinded by greed...
We's gunna splits it up so nobody gets cheated!
We got it!
B-Bills!
F-Five million yen!
Please consider depositing your winnings into
Budogaoka Bank for complete peace of mind!
Sure thing!
We finally got it! And it ain't a dream!
Wait... We's splittin' it so nobody gets cheated, huh?
Huh? Dat's funny!
If we was splittin' it up evenly...
...ain't it not fair dat we don'ts include our Stands?
Since I gots 'bout five-hundreda my Harvest fellers,
dat means we should splits it five-hundred t'one an' one.
Ain't dat right?!
You greedy asshole!
You wanna fuckin' do this again?!
This shit never ends with you, stupid!
A-A third's good!
Higashikata Josuke – Money Currently in Possession – 1,666,666 yen
In spite of the unfortunate circumstances leading to
these impertinent teenagers coming upon so much money...
To be continued!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 20
Yamagishi
Yu
kako's Cinderella
Fan
tasy
Yu
Fan
Yamagishi
kako's Cinderella
tasy
Yu
Fan