I can't believe my good luck!
If that coffee hadn't spilled this morning...
How... How is that possible? I...
Damned brat... You even knew about Stray Cat!
It's useless.
As long as Bites the Dust remains active,
it will automatically continue protecting you.
I... I failed!
I-It's... It's almost time!
To think you made a try for my life
using Strat Cat's air bullets...
Hayato, that idea never would have occurred to you
had you not repeated this morning three... no, four times now.
Because you've returned here for a fourth time...
...Bites the Dust must be fated to blow up not just Rohan,
but one or more of his friends, as well.
You must have told someone other than Rohan of my existence.
Or perhaps they questioned you about me.
Who did you kill? Hmm?
Was it that puny Koichi kid?
Or maybe Kujo Jotaro?
His death would make me very happy.
I-It's all over!
Allowing you to repeat this morning would be far too risky.
You would undoubtedly attack me again.
I'll undo Bites the Dust once anyone after Rohan dies.
No one can rival my Bites the Dust!
Luck is on the side of I, Kira Yoshikage!
That name... That name you just said...
Oh, did I let my real name slip?
Yes, my real name is Kira Yoshikage.
You can tell that to whomever you like.
By the way, what time is it right now?
I...
I haven't said anything about you!
Since this whole thing started,
I haven't told a single person about you!
All I did was make a phone call!
I met a guy who told me he was late from oversleeping,
so this time I found his number and woke him up!
All I did was call his house this morning!
You're the one who said it!
Just now, you said it yourself!
All I had to do was wait!
I've been waiting for him to get here without oversleeping!
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
Let the joy of love give you an answer!
Wakare no toki sae kudakenuishi de
With a meaning which is unbreakable even when we're apart
1999 Bizarre Summer
Kawasu yuki ga umu sanka
Our shared courage will give rise to a song of praise
Great Days!
Episode 37:  Crazy Diamond is Unbreakable Part 1
Hey, Josuke!
Looks like we still got here on time!
Hold it, Okuyasu!
I don't know if it's fate or just a huge coincidence,
but I can't believe the name I just heard come out of that guy's mouth!
I-I-Impossible!
You just yelled out the name Kira Yoshikage, didn't you?
Huh? What?!
H-How could such a coincidence...?
It's not a coincidence!
It wasn't fate, either! It was a gamble!
I made a gamble!
And I won!
I'm sure I just heard you say that!
You definitely just said that name!
It can't be...
Asshole!
Dora!
If you somehow happen to have the same name as him, I can instantly heal your wounds.
Th-This guy's Kira Yoshikage?!
Th-This can't be happening!
This is all your fault, you brat!
H-How has it come to this?
I need to undo Bites the Dust and keep myself protected!
Dorararara!
Return, Killer Queen!
It's so cold.
I can feel the rain running down my back.
Would it kill this kid to show up on time?
Oh?
It's Koichi and Mr. Jotaro.
I did it! I made it in time! I beat fate!
I have no desire for overwhelming happiness.
Nor will I accept a life of utter despair.
Like a plant that grows unperturbed in the sunlight,
I want to live out my life in peace.
You've finally shown your face!
I'll see to it that you're never at peace again!
Guess Rohan hit the fuckin' jackpot with this photo!
I don't think the two of us
running into him was a coincidence, Okuyasu.
I don't know what's going on, but the fact that
he said his real name to Kawajiri Hayato just now...
...makes me think we got here right in the nick of time!
Just to make sure there isn't a misunderstanding here,
I never ran away from you.
I could have killed you at any time had I so desired.
I only refrained because I detest direct conflict.
Direct conflict is completely at odds
with the peaceful life I yearn for.
Winning a single battle is easy,
but it creates stress from anticipating subsequent fights.
It's utterly foolish.
Fighting against others is a sad and endless cycle.
Half the reason we started looking for you
is because you killed Shigechi, dumbass!
A murderin' pig fucker like you ain't got no right
t'choose what he is or ain't gonna do, ya dumb fuck!
Careful, Josuke!
Don't touch Killer Queen's dirty fuckin' hand!
That's the only reason I haven't eliminated you all.
You three are currently the only obstacles standing between me and lifelong peace.
I have no choice but to fight you for uncovering my identity.
Hey, Kawajiri Hayato! Get behind us!
Crazy Diamond has an effective range of one to two meters.
Its ability is to restore things which have been damaged.
I won't need to use its ability against you.
I just gotta kick your ass!
Josuke!
Dora!
He's strong...
All right! I can't see what's going on, b-but he's amazing!
He made Kira spit blood and go flying!
You're way too slow for me, Killer Queen!
Trying to live a peaceful life has made you super lazy.
Your Stand just isn't cut out for one-on-one battles!
Josuke, don't underestimate him just 'cause he's slow!
Since we gotta fight him without touchin' him, The Hand'll take care of him no problem!
Bring it!
So he can teleport things by erasing space?
The direction of my attack is no longer aimed at Josuke.
It's aimed at you.
I-Inside my backpack...!
What?!
Well, this works, too.
I managed to hit him with this attack on my first try.
H-He didn't touch me...
I didn't see him touch me...
The air... The air breathed fire!
Okuyasu!
Th-The air... breathed fire?!
The air!
I've been keeping this plant around
in case something like this happened.
Now I can combine Stray Cat's ability to control air
with Killer Queen's ability to create explosions.
Hayato, I have you to thank for bringing it to me!
Invisible air bubbles combined with unstoppable explosions!
Could two things be any more compatible than that?
That's why he's been keeping it!
It's all my fault for bringing it here!
I already told you that luck is on my side, didn't I?
The characters in the word fate mean "luck" and "life."
How fitting!
Th
The
The Ha
The Han
The Hand
Niji
Nijimura
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Nijimura Oku
Nijimura Okuyasu
Is something wrong, Mr. Jotaro?
No, it's nothing.
I thought I heard Josuke's voice over the rain for a second.
That useless layabout probably overslept.
If they aren't here in five minutes...
...I'm going to head to Kawajiri Hayato's school without them.
I'm coming to heal you, Okuyasu!
I can't let you do that!
Before you get to him, I'm going to blow you away!
It shot out air like a bullet!
And... he turned it into a bomb!
It's coming! You have to run away!
Can't you see it?!
It's that weird distorted thing!
I-It's gonna hit you!
Dorara!
Heal?
He's trying to use his ability to heal Okuyasu!
The ability to restore damaged things...
I'm impressed you were able to create a wall
from the broken slate so quickly.
I-It's shooting again!
I-It's coming!
Dorarara!
There's nothing worse than assuming something to be true.
Especially when you have delusions of possessing great strength or abilities.
I-It's coming through the crack!
Even though it touched something, it didn't explode!
Hmph. I thought that was going to blow his head off, but...
...the explosion must not have been
triggered close enough to him.
Killer Queen's bombs don't
automatically detonate on contact.
That was an inaccurate assumption.
They can be triggered at any distance.
No matter where you hide,
or how quickly you protect yourself with a wall or metal plate...
...my bombs will pass through and explode right on top of you!
You have nowhere left to run.
Die!
It's too late! There's no way he'll dodge it!
I have nowhere left to run?
I never planned to run away in the first place...
...and I'm sure as hell not running away now!
I'm not leaving here until I heal Okuyasu!
He's running toward it?!
I-It passed by him!
You can trigger your bombs at any distance?
Looks like that's not quite true!
If you set off an explosion while I'm close to you, Kira, you'll get caught in the blast yourself!
All right, Okuyasu! I can heal you now!
Don't touch him!
I mean, I think...
He could have just turned Okuyasu's body into a...!
Damn! Hayato, you brat.
No... way...
I never saw Killer Queen touch Okuyasu...
How do you know that, Kawajiri Hayato?!
You're not a Stand user!
I can tell!
I've been living in the same house as him!
His expression totally gives him away!
It touched him while you weren't looking!
I'm sure!
He turned Okuyasu's body into a bomb!
Kira Yoshikage!
Oh, who am I to say?
With you charging toward me,
I'm not sure if I actually managed to touch Okuyasu or not.
It happened much too quickly.
Should I trigger the switch and find out?
Don't do it, Kira Yoshikage!
Go ahead and shoot me with another air bullet!
Hurry up and attack me already, dammit!
I have no reason to recklessly attack you right now.
Higashikata Josuke, I have the advantage of deciding
whether to attack you or not based on the movements you make.
It's very possible that I failed at turning Okuyasu into a bomb.
You may still be able to heal him with Crazy Diamond.
Perhaps I'm revealing too much,
but there's only one way for you to save Okuyasu's life in this situation.
You have to touch and heal him.
You'll likely explode if I succeeded at turning him into a bomb,
but your Crazy Diamond should be able to heal him before you die.
It's worth it to heal your best friend's
wounds by sacrificing yourself, isn't it?
D-Don't touch him!
I'll wait until you make your decision.
Decide now whether you'll touch
your best friend and heal him, or if you'll come after me.
I'll wait as long as it takes for you to make your decision,
but I doubt you'll choose to touch him.
Even though he is your best friend.
I have proof he turned him into a bomb!
I'm positive he can't control more than one bomb at a time!
Once he's used his ability to make a bomb,
he can't create another one until the first goes off!
He would be shooting a bunch of them at once if he could,
but he's only doing one at a time!
He turned Okuyasu into a bomb, so now he can't shoot!
What are you trying to say?
I'm telling you that there's a way to save Okuyasu's life!
And that's...
Killer Queen, trigger the switch!
...if I'm the one who touches him!
What?!
H-Hayato, you...!
I get it! Crazy Diamond!
Dorararara!
You're insane, Kawajiri Hayato!
You've got guts!
Are you really just a grade-schooler, kid?
If I didn't know that you could heal people,
I never would have done that!
Besides, you of all people can't die!
He'll kill me if you die, and then he'll be free!
He'll kill my mom, too!
Then even more people in our town!
No, he has to die.
To think that your ability is powerful enough to restore something I blew up instantaneously...
I realize now that your ability is a perfect counter to mine.
Killer Queen!
Josuke, he's firing!
I'm going to detonate it on impact,
so you can't guard against it.
However, since there's a chance you'll try to avoid it,
I made it small and difficult to see.
I wonder if you can dodge it while carrying Okuyasu and dealing with the debris lodged in your wounds.
Hurry up and run away, Josuke!
If his next explosion even barely touches you, you'll die!
Okuyasu! Your wounds are healed!
Wake up already, Okuyasu!
Hurry up and move! He's gonna get you!
Eight meters until impact.
Come on, you have to wake up now!
You aren't hurt anymore, Okuyasu!
Josuke!
Seven more meters.
Just open your eyes, Okuyasu! Hey!
Hey, Okuyasu!
Hurry up and open your eyes already!
Come on!
Let's fight together like we always do and kick his ass!
Josuke...
With the same precision as Joe Montana throwing a touchdown pass,
I'm going send the bomb right under his nose...
...then detonate it in his face.
Four meters until impact.
L-Let go!
It's gonna hit you if you don't run away!
Okuyasu's... Okuyasu's already-
Shut the hell up!
You're the one who needs to run away, kid!
Two more meters until impact.
The explosion will cover approximately a three-meter radius.
I can see it! It's about two meters in front of you!
Hurry up and run away!
Okuyasu's... Okuyasu's already dead!
He isn't dead!
Okuyasu is healed!
I'm sure he'll open his eyes!
I'll trigger the switch in one more meter!
Josuke!
Dora!
H-He split the air with a knife made of blood!
Did Josuke somehow shoot a powerful stream of blood out of his body to cut it in half like a knife?
That's right! It's just like when I used a needle to stab the air bubble
when I was first attacked by that stupid cat plant!
He used the blood from his wound
like a water jet cutter... Hmph.
...to cut right through it.
I wonder if that stopped it, though.
It didn't deflate! It's headed right for you!
The air bullets I've turned into bombs
are kept stable by Killer Queen's ability.
That's why it won't pop!
Whether you cut it into pieces,
or try to crush it beneath your feet, my bomb ability will never go away!
As soon as it touches you, I'll make it explode!
Finally, impact!
Huh? H-His body...
...is floating?
Detonate!
No, it isn't floating!
I can't heal my own wounds with Crazy Diamond's ability...
...but since debris from the pavement got stuck in my wounds after the first explosion...
...I was able to restore them!
Th-The piece of road inside his body dragged him away!
I have no choice!
I don't know whose house this is,
but we're breaking inside, Hayato!
Y-You need to leave Okuyasu behind!
If you don't leave him and run, you'll be killed!
He'll catch up to us and kill you!
Could you shut the hell up about that, Hayato?
Okuyasu and I are like brothers.
He's my best friend!
You don't understand what I'm saying!
By the time you healed Okuyasu's wounds, he was already dea-
Stop it!
Stop! Don't even think of finishing that sentence!
You need to focus on defeating him!
I don't like this...
If not for his ability to restore things,
my bombs would be unrivaled.
The most terrifying person standing in the way
of me obtaining peace of mind isn't Jotaro...
It's him!
Higashikata Josuke!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 38
Crazy
D
iamond is
Un
breakable Part 2
D
Un
Crazy
iamond is
breakable Part 2
D
Un