Josuke, we're going hunting.
Huh?
Let's go.
H-Hold on a second, Mr. Jotaro!
Did you just say hunting?
Are you trying to tell me...
...we're about to go hunting for babes with nice bodies?!
I'm the type of guy who's all about true love,
so this is pretty new to me!
I hope I can do it...
Otoishi Akira finally talked yesterday.
He did?!
We learned that before we brought him into custody,
he had been using the bow and arrow.
He told us he shot a rat with it.
A rat?!
But the rat didn't die after it was shot.
It writhed in pain until it freed itself from the arrow, then ran away.
Even though it's just a rat,
the fact that it survived means it obtained a Stand ability.
We have no way of knowing what kind of Stand it is,
but we need to hunt it down before it causes any harm.
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 16:  Let's Go Hunting!
Whoa, far out!
Getting your Stand within range of
a small, skittish rat will be difficult...
...but if you use these ball bearings to attack it,
your range will increase to twenty meters.
This may be obvious, but you can't hit a Stand with these.
They're only good for defeating the user.
Your turn.
Huh? I have to do it, too?
I dunno about this...
Ball-shaped things give me weird thoughts...
I was so close!
Yeah, not bad. I'd give you eighty-five points.
Let me make something clear before we start hunting this thing.
When your target is a living creature,
you need to focus on accuracy over speed.
If you're within range of the rat and miss your shot...
...it will never let you get close to it again.
Don't shoot until you're sure you'll hit it.
I'm not trying to put you under pressure, but remember that.
I'm definitely feeling the pressure now...
Otoishi Akira shot the rat near this irrigation canal.
Given the area, it was probably a brown rat.
Brown rats can swim, eat anything, and live anywhere.
They can grow as large as twenty to thirty centimeters long.
Their maximum weight is about a kilogram.
They're able to jump two meters high.
Found a lead.
Aren't those bird tracks?
The front paws have four digits, and the back ones five.
The S-shaped trail means it was dragging something.
The line is from its tail.
It's about twenty centimeters long.
There could be more, but at least one rat was here.
There's a tick on this leaf.
This means multiple rats are
definitely going through this area.
There's probably a nest deep inside that drainage pipe.
For now, we'll lay a trap and record anything that goes through it with this video camera.
That's one of those cameras that lets you
watch what you're filming, right?
You're not using cheese for the trap?
It's a tempura crumb.
Cheese is too extravagant for rats.
There sure are a lot of flies around here...
Mr. Jotaro!
I-I found...
Rat corpses?
No doubt about it!
They look like they're trapped in stewed fish jelly!
Why the hell are you poking it?
It's flesh.
Their flesh melted together, then solidified.
The flesh melting under their skin is what killed them.
How the hell did their corpses end up like that?
Hard to say.
It's hard to say, but I can only assume the rat is responsible.
It used its Stand?
It killed its friends and claimed their territory as its own.
Which means...
...it's definitely making a nest at the end of that drainage pipe.
We need to find out if this thing is keeping to itself or not.
Looks like the drainage pipe leads to that farm.
We may be too late already.
R-Really?
There's a chicken coop, but I don't see any chickens inside.
I don't see any signs of life around their house, either.
It doesn't look like they left, but their front door is wide open.
The rat is there.
It's unfortunate...
...but the people living there are probably dead by now.
Let's go. We're checking it out.
The rat shouldn't run away if we get close to it...
...since it thinks no human is fast enough to catch it.
It won't expect anyone to shoot ball bearings at it.
We'll get as close as we can and take it out in one shot.
Found something.
Rat droppings.
They aren't composed of grass or grain.
It's meat.
They went toward this room.
Let's check it out.
Got it.
What's that noise?
Is it the fridge's compressor?
What the hell?
Does their refrigerator door open by itself or something?
Or maybe the door's magnet is weak?
What?! There it is!
Shit, it's right here!
That's what opened the refrigerator just now!
Is it even possible for a rat to do that?!
There's no way...
Whoever lives here must have just left it open.
Am I actually oblivious enough to believe that, though?
This rat is a Stand user!
Jo-
Mr. Jotaro's not here!
He's still in the other room!
Great... We locked eyes...
I-Is that...?
Did the rat do this?!
Th-They're still alive...
Did that rat really use its Stand to turn these people
into a pile of goop, then store them in the fridge?
Now it's eating them!
Damn... Mr. Jotaro isn't coming back!
I'll just have to kill this thing myself!
He said I needed to put accuracy ahead of speed
since we're dealing with a living creature, didn't he?
If I miss even once, it will know what my range is.
Am I remembering that right? Damn...
Talk about pressure!
From this angle, the table and chair are in my way...
I'll make sure I shoot the ball bearing right into its forehead!
Just stay right there...
Crap! It stopped eating!
It could run away if I make any sudden moves!
I have no choice!
It's risky, but I have to shoot it from here!
It's moving! Now!
Yes!
That didn't kill it!
There it is!
That must be its Stand!
You gonna try to attack me?
Don't underestimate me!
I'll get you for sure with this next shot!
Crap! It's escaping under the table!
Get back here!
Mr. Jotaro, what's the hold up?!
The rat's right here!
That shape...
Shit! It's a projectile shooting Stand!
Dora!
What should I do?
Slap it away with my bare hands?
That doesn't sound too appealing...
What happened?
Did I just hit it or not?!
You bastard!
Yes! I got it!
I missed its forehead, but I still won!
That was a close one...
Mr. Jotaro, I'm in here!
I got the rat! We're done!
Man, what were you doing?
That was a bad time to go missing!
I had to defeat it by myself.
I got pretty lucky, though...
...since the ball bearing barely hit it!
I swear I wasn't trying to make a pun with "barely" there!
Its Stand looked like it was shooting needles or something.
I bet your flesh would melt off if it hit you.
The people who live here got hit, but they're still alive.
I can heal them with Crazy Diamond.
If we don't finish this by sunset, it's gonna be a problem.
Huh?
There's another one. It just attacked me.
Mr. Jotaro! Y-Your hand!
It got me in the other room.
I should have dodged it, but...
...I wanted to see what effect it would have if it hit me.
Even with just the slightest touch, some kind of Stand poison starts melting your flesh, and it affects Stands, too.
Five or six hits would reduce a person to a pile of mush.
Good thing I avoided it!
I'm lucky we don't have similar personalities!
The rat escaped outside afterward.
It realized you killed its friend in the kitchen.
Not to be pushy, but I really need to be healed.
O-Oh, right!
Damn...
Why did there have to be two of them?!
S
Sta
Star
Star P
Star Pla
Star Plati
Star Platinum
Ku
Kujo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: A
Kujo Jo
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
Hello, this is the Speedwagon Foundation research team.
Hey, it's Kujo Jotaro.
Mr. Jotaro!
We've tried several times to get in contact with you!
I was in pursuit, so I turned my ringer off.
Is there something new from Otoishi?
Yes. Otoishi Akira was hiding the fact that he shot two rats.
So confirm this for me...
There's just two of them, and no more?
Yes. We're certain now.
Otoishi Akira, gimme a break...
He's really done it now.
It kills everything in its territory, be it humans or its own kind.
It only cares for itself.
A creature like this can't be allowed to live.
Mr. Jotaro, wait up!
How are we gonna find a puny little rat in this gigantic field?
E.T. Seton, the author of Seton Animal Chronicles, once said...
"There is no animal that cannot be tracked."
Rats tend to only take paths familiar to them.
In other words, we can assume it went back to the irrigation pipe.
If rats aren't constantly eating...
...they'll die from starvation in just ten hours.
Look. These are fresh bite marks.
Yes! That's awesome!
We've got this thing cornered!
Look at this...
It didn't even touch the bait in our traps.
We caught it on video.
Its ear looks like a bug-eaten leaf.
We'll call him "Bug-Eaten" from now on.
Look at how cautious he is...
Unlike earlier...
...we can safely assume Bug-Eaten
won't let us get within twenty meters of himself.
These are rifle rounds.
I brought four of them with me in case we needed them.
A-Actual rounds?!
Because of air resistance, the ball bearings
fly off course when they're shot over twenty meters.
Since these rounds are aerodynamic,
they'll shoot straight for up to seventy meters.
Am I gonna shoot them with my Stand, too?
I'm not really feeling this plan...
Of course you're not. Guess I'll do it myself.
Hang on a sec...
Why'd you have to phrase it like that?
That kinda pisses me off!
That first one would still be alive if it wasn't for me!
I mean, yeah, it wasn't a perfect shot...
Good point. Take two of them.
Huh?
P-Pressure...
Watch your step. There's leeches in the water.
Impossible...
What's up?
Be careful, Josuke.
His trail suddenly ends here.
How is that possible?!
How can the trail just disappear?!
That's it! He's hiding in the dirt!
He dug a hole and covered himself in dirt!
No!
He's backtracking...
I didn't know rats knew how to do that.
Backtracking?
Backtracking is an instinctual behavior seen in some wild animals
that allows them to evade predators by retracing their steps.
In Japan, this behavior has been observed in brown bears, weasels, and rabbits.
Rats, however, have never been observed backtracking!
So if I'm understanding this right...
the rat pulled a fast one on us?
Our situation may have just been reversed.
With this terrain...
...we may be the ones being hunted now.
It feels like something is staring at us...
We need to take cover!
Move slowly...
The attack from Bug-Eaten's Stand
is slow enough that we should see it coming.
Pay close attention to where it comes from.
If we can figure out where he's hiding,
we can shoot him before he shoots us.
What the hell is this?!
Wha-
The rat used our own trap against us?!
Star Platinum: The World!
Gimme a break...
Don't worry, I removed the needle before the poison spread...
...along with the flesh that it pierced.
Slap a bandage over it.
I also figured out where he's hiding.
Halfway up the hill, near that cluster of rocks.
Amazing! You and this rat are something else!
Does this mean I'm the only dumb one here?
He's sixty meters away.
It doesn't look like he's gonna shoot more needles at us.
He knows he'll expose his location if he shoots again.
He's a smart son of a bitch.
Why are you complimenting him?
We need to do something!
I agree, Josuke.
If we don't give this our all...
...Bug-Eaten's gonna get us.
I want you to take all four rounds with you.
From this distance, your shot will go slightly upwards, so aim about one centimeter below him.
Mr. Jotaro? What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna expose myself so he'll fire his needles at me.
It'll be up to you to figure out where he is, Josuke.
When your chance arrives, shoot him.
I-Is he serious?!
You're the only one who can do this!
Even if I get hit by one or two needles...
...your Crazy Diamond can heal me up.
Don't forget, Josuke. You can't heal yourself.
I need you to give this your all, Josuke!
I-I need time to mentally prepare!
Star Platinum: The World!
Did you find him?
N-No... He moved right after he fired!
I'll try to make my way up the hill to get closer to him.
Watch carefully for the moment he fires.
The moment he fires...
P-Pressure!
There! I see him!
What?!
Did the little bastard aim its needles at the rock since it knew I would dodge?
Was I hit by the ricochet?
Mr. Jotaro!
Don't focus on me, Josuke!
Aim for the rat!
Get him right when he's about to attack!
This is bad!
I have four rounds, but this is my only chance!
If I waste any more time...
I'm trying again, Josuke!
There! He's in the same spot as before!
But his body is partially blocked by the rock...
Shit! If only he were looking over here!
I can't screw this up!
I'm just gonna have to hit a smaller target!
I'm starting to feel confident.
You're finished, you little asshole!
Josuke missed...
I'm glad you looked my way.
I figured you would look in my direction if I missed you.
Now I can hit you for sure!
I guess I wasn't the dumb one after all!
You can call me the man who
excels under pressure: Higashikata Josuke!
Those rats with Stands that Otoishi Akira created...
When I compare what they've done to the destruction humans have caused, I feel conflicted...
I'm glad Josuke is someone I can rely on.
But gimme a break. It's about time we get to relax a little.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 17
Kishibe
Ro
han's
Ad
venture
Ro
Ad
Kishibe
han's
venture
Ro
Ad