There's nothing here... Both pockets are empty.
There's just this piece of paper...
The scent isn't coming from her pocket anymore... Could it be...?
It's just a plain, white piece of paper.
What?!
Jo... Josuke!
July 15th (Thursday) 12:42 PM
You've really done it now!
How dangerous!
You really should have watched where you were going!
I did warn you that the floor up here
was burned in places, didn't I?!
I don't see anything unusual.
His back is perfectly normal...
I-It's over... I... I'm finished...
I don't know why, but it's been my fear that if someone
were to catch even a glimpse of my back, it would all be over!
H-Hey...
I'm done for!
C-Calm down!
I'm sorry, okay?
I just couldn't contain my curiosity...
What?!
That was a Stand attack!
There was a Stand on his back?!
If there were, even if I read him again with Heaven's Door...
Now I see why nothing was written inside him!
He was already attacked before he entered my house!
This architect was the victim of an enemy Stand attack,
and now that attack is going to be directed at me!
Gimme a ride...
It's here! The enemy Stand is here!
Gimme a ride... 'kay?
Gimme a ride...
Gimme... Gimme a ride, 'kay?
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
July 15th (Thursday) 1:39 PM
Here's the list of every person
who has gone missing in Morioh, including runaways.
Episode 33:  July 15th (Thursday) Part 3
These all come from after Kira disappeared, so there aren't many.
So Kira's victims may be among them, is that right?
I'm not sure, but it's possible.
Right now, we can't afford to miss a single move he makes.
If you hold your breath for too long,
your body will eventually gasp for air.
I'm sure of it.
July 15th (Thursday) 12:55 PM
Gimme a ride, 'kay?
Gimme a ride!
Heaven's Door!
Gimme a ride...
...'kay?
Gimme a ride!
What?! I-It can't be...
Has it possessed my back?
Did it transfer itself to me after I saw the architect's back?
Damn!
Burn the photos...
...'kay? Burn the photos...
Photos?
Burn 'em, 'kay? Burn the photos...
What are you talking about?
Those photos I took...
Is it possible that among the ones I've saved,
there lies evidence that could lead us to Kira Yoshikage...
...and you were sent here to get rid of it?
Just burn 'em all up... 'kay?
Burn 'em up good, 'kay?
Shut your annoying mouth!
Heaven's Door!
Let's see...
It's time to figure out what you are and give you some orders!
Oww!
What?!
I'm a Stand born from the arrow
which pierced Kinoto Masazo's back: Cheap Trick!
But now... my new user, Kishibe Rohan... is you!
You're my new user!
Wha-
Get it?
You pretty much just used your Stand to attack yourself!
We're up to speed now, 'kay?
I'm a Stand who does what it wants.
Even though I was created by Kinoto Masazo,
he couldn't become a true Stand user capable of controlling me.
All he knew of my existence
were the things I whispered to him...
...and the innate fear that he shouldn't ever let anyone look at his back, 'kay?
Get it, 'kay? You get it now?
Get it? 'Kay?
My only ability is to whisper to people.
'Kay? Now go burn those photos!
You freak! Get off of me!
Dammit! You little...!
How can I get this thing off?!
That's easy. Just show your back to someone else.
If someone else sees your back...
'Kay? If they do, I'll transfer to them.
Just show someone!
Afternoon, Mr. Rohan!
I'm a big fan of your comics!
Can you put a nude in the next chapter?
Make it real sexy!
Bye!
Burn the photos, 'kay?
July 15th (Thursday) 12:47 PM
Josuke!
H-He caught it!
Y-You asshole!
Crazy Diamond, huh?
Well, I guess this means what I heard is true,
so I won't be needing this useless gun anymore.
Wasn't that terrifying?
Now bite it, Higashikata Josuke.
Bite your lower lip!
Will he do it?!
Bite it! Come on, just bite it and reveal your sign to me!
So this is his Stand?
Looks just as shitty as the Stand the old guy from the photo has!
He isn't going to bite it yet, I see...
He's covering up his fear with anger.
I have no choice. I'll have to reveal myself to him.
You have some nerve, asshole!
There it is again... This creepy feeling...
Why is he showing himself now after hiding this whole time?
He did it on purpose.
He revealed himself so you would attack him!
He's dangerous... He's way too dangerous, Josuke!
My Stand's ability may be shitty as you put it...
But if you must know exactly what it does...
...it allows me to file away various things
by turning them into paper.
This piece of paper here is Hirose Koichi.
Asshole! So that's where you've been hiding Koichi!
That's Koichi's scent!
He didn't have something of Koichi's on him...
He had Koichi himself!
He's still alive, unfortunately.
After all, my Stand's ability is shitty.
I have neither the ability nor the strength to kill someone.
Though this ceases to be true if the piece of paper containing someone happens to tear like the one I just demonstrated.
I'll go easy on you and just kick your ass,
but you need to bring back Koichi right now!
Go ahead and do it yourself...
...if you can.
Dora!
Note: Hirose Koichi
Koichi!
After all, my Stand's ability is shitty.
I have neither the ability nor the strength to kill someone.
Though this ceases to be true if the piece of paper
containing someone happens to tear.
It's a trap!
I wouldn't go after that paper if I were you!
Josuke, ignore it!
You bit it! You finally bit it!
My Enigma has eagerly awaited this moment, Higashikata Josuke!
It waited this entire time just for you to bite your lower lip!
Dorararara!
Dammit, you asshole!
You've shown me the sign of your fear!
No matter how hard you resist,
you're powerless before Enigma once you've given in to your fear!
I feel bad for Josuke, but I'm glad I didn't help him...
If I had helped him, that asshole probably would have
gotten rid of me first since I can track people by scent.
I hope now you see there isn't a force in the world capable of stopping Enigma.
Wh-What?
He's restoring the metal rod!
He's using his power to get out!
That piece of paper probably wasn't the one Koichi's trapped in...
I'm guessing you wrote "Hirose Koichi" on it to trick me...
I say this because the only way you would be confident enough to show yourself is if you held Koichi hostage...
...and kept him alive so you could use him to threaten me.
That piece of paper was a trap.
I knew the whole time!
I'm right, aren't I?
Still, I had to try saving that piece of paper
since there was a chance it really was Koichi!
Even if there was only a 1% chance that it was Koichi...
...I had no choice but to try and save him!
Enigma, you win.
This is the limit of Crazy Diamond's power.
But here's a warning before I go!
Once I've turned into paper,
you better instantly tear me apart.
If I live through this, I swear I'll kill you!
H-He sure talks big!
Taking care of him was a breeze.
Note: Hirose Koichi
Fungami Yuya, huh?
It was wise of you not to assist Josuke.
Eliminating you would have been simple.
The sign of your fear is when
you touch your fingers to your chin!
Anyway, the old man in the photo didn't say anything about getting rid of you, so I won't even try.
It's the only choice that makes sense.
Would you like to know something interesting about my paper?
Anyone can remove the contents by unfolding it.
It's incredibly easy, but surprisingly difficult if you're afraid.
To the Morioh Grand Hotel.
Finally! I've rid us of Hirose Koichi and Higashikata Josuke!
And right about now, Kishibe Rohan should be...
July 15th (Thursday) 2:21 PM
Which is it?
Which of these photos is of Kira Yoshikage?
Which one of these is
the old man in the photo trying to get rid of?
Burn 'em, 'kay? Do it.
It's no use...
I don't have enough clues to know.
Just burn 'em already, 'kay?
Shut up! You talk too much!
Damn! I need to tell someone...
I have to let someone know about this thing...
En
Enig
Enigm
Enigma
Miya
Miyamoto
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: C
Growth Potential: C
Miyamoto Teru
Miyamoto Terunosu
Miyamoto Terunosuke
July 15th (Thursday) 1:20 PM
Uh, you said the Morioh Grand Hotel, right?
Yes, that's right.
You spending the night there?
No, I just have business to take care of...
Business, indeed.
No...
I'm not letting you reach the Morioh Grand Hotel.
Josuke, you prick! Way to play it cool...
As stupid as it sounds, if one of my girls
were turned into a piece of paper like that...
...if it were any one of them...
...I would have done the same!
Letting you or Kira Yoshikage
continue to live in this town would be lame as hell!
Give me Koichi!
You're making a very big mistake right now.
Do you really want to fight me?
Do you really wish to make Kira's father your enemy?
Very well!
Sixty-three, sixty-four, sixty-five kilometers...
It may not be strong, but my Highway Star never quits!
The taxi stopped...
But it isn't at the hotel yet...
No one has gotten out yet...
His scent coming from the car is still strong...
But where is he? Where is he hiding?
The scent of this paper...
I'm sure now!
That piece of paper smells like Koichi and Josuke!
Wait, Highway Star! Don't open the door yet.
That nutjob is underestimating me.
This must be another trap.
Trying to lure me in, huh?
Fine, I accept!
I said I would do it!
He's after my fear.
How's he gonna try to scare me?
I need to figure that out.
What? What the fuck?
He stuck a piece of paper inside the door?
Underestimated again! And this scent...
This piece of paper is a trap!
At least I figured it out.
Open the door, Highway Star.
So he can turn fire into paper, too...
Too bad I saw right through his trap!
Josuke, Koichi, I'm here to rescue you!
But... I can smell something
other than Josuke and Koichi in here...
It's probably not a good idea to open this thing...
Huh?
There's a weird scent I've never
smelled before moving around inside.
I can kinda smell it inside the paper...
What?!
Shit! Highway Star!
Wh-What is this liquid?
I-Is it some kind of chemical?
Fuck, things just keep coming!
W-Wait...
I can smell iron in there!
C-Calm down! He's trying to scare me!
If he's able to scare me, he wins!
Iron...
What is it? A machine?
Fuck!
I just have to open it!
Josuke! Koichi!
Note: Higashikata Josuke, Hirose Koichi
I-It's an electrical current!
Somehow he put electricity inside the paper!
That machine-like scent I could smell
coming from the paper was a...
...a...
...a shredder!
It won't turn off!
Josuke and Koichi are getting pulled in!
Fuck! Highway Star!
I-It's hopeless...
Highway Star isn't powerful enough to destroy this thing!
Josuke! Koichi!
You finally touched it, Fungami Yuya!
You finally became scared and touched your chin...
You're totally uncool!
Scaring you was far too easy, Fungami Yuya!
There's nobody in this world whom
Enigma can't turn into paper!
It can easily do it to anyone!
Easily? That's why it's so great!
It turns anyone into paper instantly!
How great!
I lost. You sure did scare me.
But I'll happily accept defeat...
Turning into a thin piece of paper is exactly what I needed to fit my hand inside the shredder!
What did you just pull out?!
Don't you dare open up that piece of paper!
Dora!
I'll happily turn into a piece of paper...
Fungami Yuya...
I gotta admit... you're actually a pretty cool guy, after all!
Higashikata Josuke... Hirose Koichi...
S-Stay back, Josuke! Look at this piece of paper!
I-I'll tear it to shreds!
Fungami Yuya is inside this piece of paper!
Act 3! 3 Freeze!
S-So heavy...
You know, I just realized...
There was something I said I was gonna do to your earlier...
Oh yeah, that's right.
I said I was gonna kill you.
Yep, I definitely said that.
I also said I could never forgive a guy like you, didn't I?
Assholes like you who take hostages
and threaten people by scaring them piss me off!
W-Wait a minute!
I just like observing people when they're scared!
I only got my Stand just recently and it made me cocky!
I-I'm sorry! I feel really bad about this!
I just realized something while watching you...
You have a habit of closing one eye
when you get scared, don't you?
Well? That's your habit, right?
But...
When you're really scared, you close both.
Dorararara!
Dora!
You like observing things?
Then you better get used to it.
Because you're gonna be doing a lot of observing without saying a single word!
I-I'm a book...
The Enigma boy, Miyamoto Terunosuke,
became a book and has been rendered unable to fight!
Josuke never bothered reading the contents of the book,
and it now resides at the Morioh Public Library.
If you ask the librarian for a book called Enigma,
they will only allow you to read it inside the library.
While reading this book,
some claim to hear a voice coming from it.
Well, that's all she wrote!
But not really, I guess...
Maybe this means we're finally
getting closer to finding Kira Yoshikage!
We still know nothing, though...
Curses... Those persistent fools!
July 15th (Thursday) 4:10 PM
Nobody will come to help you!
Just burn those photos, 'kay?
July 15th (Thursday) 4:30 PM
All right, I'm going out for a bit.
Where are you going?
If I wanna get to the bottom of this as quickly as possible,
I need to investigate the places where these people went missing.
Nobody is capable of escaping the fate they were born into...
He's definitely made a move.
July 15th (Thursday) 4:52 PM
I'm going to film it...
I'll film proof that my Papa isn't my Papa!
No matter what!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 34
July 15th (
Thursday
) Part 4
July 15th (
Thursday