Good morning.
This is Kawajiri Kosaku.
I understand this is incredibly selfish of me,
but I'm going to be fifteen minutes late to the office today.
Yes. My son is misbehaving, and I have to discipline him.
Yes, Sir. I completely understand that
anyone else would find my excuse trivial at best. Yes.
I'm terribly sorry.
Yes, the moment I'm done.
Yes, I'll head directly to the office.
Yes.
Yes. Please excuse me, Sir.
Damn that spineless Kawajiri Kosaku...
Was climbing the corporate ladder that important to him?
Acting like that is so stressful.
Josuke escaped inside this house since he knew
forcing us to fight in close quarters would give him the advantage.
I must agree, unfortunately.
It's in my best interest to avoid
a close-quarters fight with Crazy Diamond.
If I can figure out Josuke's exact location,
I can shoot him from here with an air bullet. But...
Hey, you there!
Just what do you think you're doing on this property?
Oh, is that how it is?
Trying to tell me you're not on this property?
Don't get technical with me, Mr. Nice Guy!
Is this your house?
How long have you been watching?
Hey, I'm the one asking questions here!
I'll have you know I live next door!
I was hoping I'd get to sleep past noon today,
but I got woken up by a loud noise outside.
You're a suspicious guy!
The cute girl who lives here, Rio,
is always telling me about how her panties get stolen!
And since nobody is normally around here at this time...
I envy you.
Huh?
To have so much free time...
Hey, you running away from me?!
Shit! He's got some nerve, going after Rio!
It pisses me off!
So he is a panty thief!
These panties...
Th-These are Rio's...
...p-p-pan...
Yippee! I'm so lucky!
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
Episode 38:  Crazy Diamond is Unbreakable Part 2
I-It's no use! The phone's not working!
Okuyasu is dead...
I'm gonna beat the hell out of Kira Yoshikage
with Crazy Diamond until he can't move a muscle.
In a few minutes, this will all be over.
Hayato...
Stay back against the wall.
Otherwise, Kira will see you.
But where exactly...
...is he gonna come in?
Huh?!
Wh-
Wh-What?
J-Josuke!
It's an air bullet!
There's one headed right for you!
It's the same size as the one from earlier!
B-But that's impossible!
There's no way he can know where you are from outside!
How does he know?!
Great...
I know how far away you are, Higashikata Josuke.
I know right where you are.
Three meters until impact...
I-It's visible!
The ball of air is visible now!
Yes!
Now he can dodge it!
No matter how many are sent after him,
he'll be able to dodge... them...
What's going on?
I-It's going after Josuke!
Kira Yoshikage somehow knows exactly where I am!
Where is he? How can he see me?
There weren't any windows in that room!
All of the curtains are drawn, too!
There's no way he can see you from outside!
It's automatic! It must be automatically chasing you!
No, you're wrong.
Sheer Heart Attack is the only ability of Killer Queen's that automatically goes after heat sources.
This thing is completely ignoring the lit cigarette!
Besides, there's no way the bullet could be automatically homing in on me after going through a solid wall...
...and Kira definitely wants to trigger
the final detonation that finishes me off himself!
I don't know how, but he knows exactly where I am!
It's getting faster!
Find Kira for me!
Figure out how he's watching me!
I-I see him!
H-He's right outside the gate!
Two meters until impact...
He's outside?
I have no idea how he's tracking you from there, Josuke!
Hurry up and run away!
You asshole!
I have no idea how you're watching me...
One more meter!
...but I have no intention of trying to hide from you!
Crazy Diamond!
Good, it's going to hit Josuke!
Detonate!
Yes! It was a direct hit!
Killer Queen!
My, my, that was close.
Good thing I was on guard.
I'm impressed that you had the willpower
to deal one final, desperate blow.
This is why I refuse to get
anywhere near you, Higashikata Josuke.
J-Josuke!
H-He's alive!
Hmph. It was a direct hit,
but it didn't blow him away.
Detonating by hand is slightly
less accurate than doing it automatically...
...but he can't undo the damage he's received.
My next shot will finish him for sure!
W-We...
We have to get away from here!
Y-You're pulling me in the wrong direction...
Go the other way...
Not that way... Go the other way!
I'm gonna kill him!
I need you to drag me towards Kira Yoshikage!
My Crazy Diamond...
...can't heal my own wounds...
But once my blood has left my body,
it becomes like any other object.
It stops being part of me!
I can gather it up and stick it onto other objects!
That's why I put some of it inside a shard of glass!
Now that the rain stopped,
the blood stain he got on his jacket earlier...
...should have dried up by now!
That's my automatic homing attack!
C
Cr
Cra
Craz
Crazy
Crazy D
Crazy Di
Crazy Dia
Crazy Diam
Crazy Diamo
Crazy Diamon
Crazy Diamond
Higashi
Higashikata
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Higashikata Jo
Higashikata Josuke
The shard of glass I just guarded myself from...
He must have used the blood stain...
The stain must have led the glass shard right to me!
Y-You hit him dead on!
It's deep inside Kira's back now!
That's...
Higashikata Josuke and his damned Crazy Diamond...
I can't predict the actions of him or his Stand...
Still, Josuke has sustained much more damage than I have!
Just one more shot!
One more shot and I, Kira Yoshikage, will be victorious!
I-It's coming!
H-He sent one big enough to see from here!
No doubt about it...
That's his final shot!
This will be mine, too!
I-I don't think the same attack will work on Kira twice!
He'll guard it!
Well... I had to try just to know for sure!
Oh yeah, Hayato. Sorry to ask you this,
but there's a lighter in my pocket that I used earlier.
Can you grab it for me?
I don't think I'll be able to grab it myself with this piece of wood sticking out of my stomach...
The smoke is useless now!
You can see this air bullet without it!
I'm not using the lighter to see the air bullet.
I need it to look at something else. Grab it.
Let's figure out how he can see me once and for all.
Don't move, Hayato.
J-Josuke? Wh-What are you...?
Hold still, Hayato.
He may not be watching us after all...
I think he's listening.
Kira was holding a cell phone.
Is that just a coincidence? No!
But who was he talking to?
Was it his boss from the office?
No, not him.
There's only one person Kira would be
calling at a time like this...
I almost completely forgot about you,
old man in the photo!
You've been trying to protect
Kira Yoshikage this entire time!
I have no idea when he got inside my pocket, but...
This was our answer!
Th-The air bullet passed through the window!
Get back!
It hit!
Josuke... is running away three meters ahead.
D-Dammit!
I-It passed him!
Now, he's moving diagonally right and up three meters...
He doesn't realize that it's just
Josuke talking to him in a raspy voice!
Now, he's running away, one meter to the left...
What?! How could you do this to me, you thug?!
Right there! Detonate!
Yoshikage!
I did it! Josuke was completely blown away, wasn't he?
Yeah, he went out in a blaze of glory.
My directions sent him straight to Hell!
Then again, he was just a ghost,
so I guess you could say he crossed over.
Josuke...!
J-Josuke!
Th-This must be some kind of... mistake...
Something this horrific...
...should never have happened... during my life...
All I asked for was to live a life of peace, like a plant!
However, at times like these...
something I shouldn't forget... during such bad situations...
...such horrible situations like this...
...is that there's always a chance for victory.
My past has taught me that!
As long as I think things through rationally,
despite being backed into a corner, my chance to win will surely come!
I just need to do the same as I,
Kira Yoshikage, have always done!
There isn't any kind of trouble I'm incapable of overcoming!
None!
You're finally within my range...
...Kira Yoshikage!
H-He's close to him!
H-He finally got close to him!
Since it's a close-quarters fight, it'll be over in an instant!
Josuke's ability is stronger,
b-but if Kira touches him, he'll be turned into a bomb!
N-Not to mention,
Josuke still has wounds on his legs and torso from that blast...
Josuke, it's a miracle you can even stand right now!
Higashikata Josuke!
Bring out... your Killer Queen!
Killer Queen!
Dora!
H-He's so strong...
I'm finished...
I, Kira Yoshikage, am going to be utterly defeated!
Dorararara!
N-No way... There's no way...
We were so close!
Josuke is so much stronger than him!
Is fate really on the side of that serial killer?
M-My fists didn't connect!
These are air bubbles!
They cushioned the blows!
B-But I wasn't trying to guard myself...
I had no time to consider that!
Stray Cat!
That's it! Stray Cat thought it was being attacked,
so it instinctively blocked his attacks!
My chance! I've found my chance!
A chance finally presented itself at this horrible time!
Killer Queen!
Change that air bullet into a bomb!
I win!
I changed it into a contact bomb!
Anyone who touches it will explode!
Josuke, with all of the damage you've sustained,
you won't have the strength to dodge this!
Kira Yoshikage!
It's a contact bomb?!
Josuke! It doesn't matter if you use glass or even wood!
Hit it with something and take cover!
I win! Something like this always happens
after life deals me a bad hand!
Luck truly is on the side of Kira Yoshikage!
Wh-What?!
Th-The air bullet is going off course!
Th-That's...!
Is that...?
You're...
...O-Okuyasu!
Y'know, I always wondered...
Where's all the stuff that gets erased by The Hand go?
I ain't too bright, an' it gives me
headaches thinkin' about it too much.
There!
What?!
I-I can't believe it! I-It's Okuyasu!
But his heart stopped, and he wasn't breathing...
I was just havin' a funny dream...
I was walkin' in the dark or somethin', an' I saw a light.
My dead big bro was there.
My big bro, Keicho.
He says to me "Where're you goin', Okuyasu?"
An' I said "I'm just followin' you, big bro."
Only made sense since
I could always count on my big bro.
He ain't never made a bad choice,
so I wasn't worried.
But then he says to me:
"Ya gotta choose where you're goin' for yourself.
Okuyasu, you're the one who's gotta
decide where you're gonna go."
I thought about it real hard...
...an' I told him I was goin'
back t'Morioh, then I woke up.
Made me feel real sad...
Okuyasu...
...y-you're really pushing it, dreaming at a time like this!
Ya don't gotta be like that!
You're actually lookin' pretty good for all the beatin' you got!
Shut the hell up!
You should have woken up sooner
if you weren't really dead, dammit!
I-Impossible...
Fate was supposed to be on the side of I, Kira Yoshikage...
This was supposed to be my chance!
Stray Cat! Shoot another bullet!
Wh-What?!
Wh-Wh-Whoa! Whoa, there!
Y-Yes! Now Kira won't be able to
use his air bullet bombs anymore!
Th-Th-There's never...
There's never been any trouble that I, Kira Yoshikage,
couldn't overcome with enough effort!
Look, Mr. Jotaro!
The loud noise we heard must have come from that house!
What do you think happened? A gas explosion?
L-Look over there! That man is injured!
Josuke and Okuyasu are there, too!
That child is Kawajiri Hayato!
And the man is Kawajiri Kosaku.
Looks like everything is finally coming together.
Any fate that would side with you...
Any chance that would come your way...
They're nothing compared to
the spirit of justice that's here right now!
It's definitely here! There's no doubt about it!
Compared to that spirit, you're nothing!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 39
Farewell,
Morioh:
Town of Golden
Hearts
Morioh:
Farewell,
Town of Golden
Morioh:
Hearts