Hello, Kawajiri residence.
July 16th (Friday) 7:57 AM
Huh? No, it's not.
I see. Well done, Hayato.
You protected me from that meddlesome Rohan.
Listen, you have the wrong number.
Bye.
So, now that we've covered that...
They had the wrong number.
...I suppose it's about time I headed to work to keep my wonderful family happy.
Before I go, could I give you a goodbye kiss?
Huh?
Why did you do that?! My precious teapot...
How could you do such an awful thing?!
I have no idea what's gotten into you!
You never answer me when I call! Why?!
I swear...
Mama, he isn't human!
If I let anyone know anything about him,
they'll be blown up, and this morning will reset.
If I keep letting him do whatever he wants...
...it may not happen right away,
but eventually he'll kill Mama and me!
K-Kishibe Rohan!
He's the only person I know other than Kira with an ability!
I have to do something about Kishibe Rohan!
Only someone with an ability like Kishibe Rohan's
stands a chance of defeating Kira and saving Mama and me!
Th-There he is! It's Rohan!
If I try talking to Rohan, he'll blow up and die.
Then this morning will repeat again...
I have to let Rohan know about Kira without talking to him!
I have to change fate!
Wh-What's going on?!
Note: [WARNING] Do not read any further.
This is the ability Rohan used on me last time!
Dammit!
I'm not anywhere near Rohan right now!
He hasn't even seen me!
Once fate has been set in motion, it can't be stopped...
...Hayato!
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
Let the joy of love give you an answer!
Wakare no toki sae kudakenuishi de
With a meaning which is unbreakable even when we're apart
1999 Bizarre Summer
Kawasu yuki ga umu sanka
Our shared courage will give rise to a song of praise
Great Days!
July 16th (Friday) 8:27 AM
Damn, the weather forecast didn't say it would rain!
Episode 36:  Another One Bites the Dust Part 2
You must be under the impression that you
purposely broke that teapot earlier, but you're wrong.
Anything that happened in
a previous cycle will happen again.
It will because it has to.
It's fated to be so.
If you were turned into a book during a previous cycle,
you'll turn into a book again, no matter what.
That is what makes Killer Queen: Bites the Dust unrivaled.
It erases any evidence of my identity
and puts everything else back as it should.
Which means that before I head off to work, I'll get to witness Rohan being blown to bits.
Note: It rained. → At 8:27 AM, lightning struck above the Pepsi sign.
I can't let Rohan die here!
I can't let Rohan be killed by him!
Ah, poor Kishibe Rohan.
Watch closely.
Right now, he has no idea he's
about to meet his utter demise.
I wonder if he realizes that he'll never
be able to draw comics ever again.
R-Rohan...
I-It can't be!
Hayato, the fact you ever encountered Rohan will soon
completely disappear, and the morning will continue on.
If I undid Bites the Dust right now,
Rohan's death would become permanent and never repeat again.
I won't do that for now, though.
A few of his friends intend to show up here.
You're going to automatically defeat them for me, too.
Just like an undetectable landmine.
But don't worry. Bites the Dust won't harm you in any way,
so you're free to relax and live your life as a normal young man.
Well, Papa has to head to the station.
Study hard and do your best.
It's all my fault... Because he met me...
Because he met me, Kishibe Rohan died!
Is there any way I can beat him?
Excuse me, can I ask you something quickly?
Do you know what time it is?
I think my watch is busted.
Hello? Did you hear me?
It's 8:33...
Huh? Have I seen you somewhere around town?
Where was it?
Do I look familiar to you?
No...
I see... Guess I was wrong.
Sorry for asking something so weird.
So it's 8:33, huh? Thanks!
Mr. Jotaro! It really is past 8:30.
But that's strange... Where did Mr. Rohan go?
Th-These are Kishibe Rohan's friends!
They were supposed to meet with him!
He left the car door wide open with the key still in the ignition.
They probably have abilities like he does...
Th-They came here to ask me about Kira Yoshikage, too!
This isn't like Mr. Rohan at all...
Oh no! It will be really bad if they figure out
I'm Kawajiri Hayato and ask me about my Papa!
That's Mr. Rohan's earring!
Crap, sorry kid.
I overslept and now I'm late to meet my friends.
Huh? You look real familiar...
Where've I seen ya before?
Ah, Josuke and Okuyasu!
'Sup!
Yo, Koichi!
Mornin', Mr. Jotaro!
What, so Rohan's the only one not here yet?
Th-There's two more of them...
When he said his friends were coming...
We'll never find Kawajiri Hayato's house since that bastard has the address.
...he must have been talking about them!
I totally forgot I grabbed this from you.
Here. Your hat.
Th-Thanks...
His face at this angle...
Something about this angle...
I'm sure I've seen him somewhere before...
Where was it?
It must have been somewhere...
Koichi. Look at the name on his backpack.
Huh?
Kawajiri Hayato?!
What?!
Th-They found me out!
Wake up
The weather forecast begins
Kira leaves the house
Hayato encounters Rohan
Lightning strikes the Pepsi sign
Kishibe Rohan dies from explosion
Wake up
The weather forecast begins
Kira leaves the house
Hayato encounters Rohan
Lightning strikes the Pepsi sign
Kishibe Rohan dies from explosion
Wake up
The weather forecast begins
Kira leaves the house
Hayato encounters Rohan
Lightning strikes the Pepsi sign
Kishibe Rohan dies from explosion
July 16th (Friday) 8:34 AM
Kawajiri Hayato...
What's he doin' here?
Is this a coincidence?
D-Does this have something to do with
Mr. Rohan not being here?
If these guys start asking me about Papa...
...they'll all get blown up!
D-Don't do it! Don't ask me anything!
If all of you die, then who's gonna beat him?!
Even if I have to trick them...
...I can't let these guys die, no matter what!
I'd like to ask you about this photo.
I want you to tell me why you were filming here.
Why were you recording footage of your da-
M-My nose!
I need a doctor! My nose is gushing blood!
I-I... Later!
Hold up.
Your nose is bleeding? Let me see it.
So, what happened?
I gotta go... Bye...
You don't need to see a doctor.
Your nose isn't bleeding anymore.
Huh?
Huh?!
The name's Higashikata Josuke.
That guy is a relative of mine, Mr. Kujo Jotaro...
...the guy with the scary face is Nijimura Okuyasu...
...and finally, this friendly-looking guy is Hirose Koichi.
You go to Budogaoka Elementary, right?
You're not gonna be late.
We have just a few questions for you...
...about this photo here.
If you weren't up to anything, then don't worry about it.
I-I was up to something!
Don't ask me about it!
You can't ask me anything!
Is this guy in the photo...
...your da-
Stop! Don't say another word!
I-It's no use...
Now they're gonna ask me even more questions...
What do you mean "Don't say another word?"
...one after another...
What are we not supposed to say?
I can't stop it anymore!
Are you talking about your dad?
They're gonna explode!
They're all gonna explode!
You suddenly shouted "Stop!"
Don't say another word?
But we ain't asked ya nothin' yet!
Is it possible...
...that the act of asking you a question is a bad idea?
They're gonna explode... Explode... Explode...
I know!
I-If I kill myself, then no one else will have to die!
Since I'm the bomb, I just need to kill myself!
If I die, I'm sure these people will be able to
beat him and save my Mama!
Come on, just ask him about Kawajiri Kosaku already!
Wait, Josuke. Something's wrong.
What are you bending over for?
I-It isn't working!
I can't cut my throat with the box cutter!
That's...!
That Stand!
Ain't no doubt about it!
Killer Queen!
Orara!
To be more precise,
it's Killer Queen's tertiary bomb, Bites the Dust!
Retaliation is futile.
If you can see me,
then I'm already inside your eye.
It doesn't matter how many of you
there are, because all at once...
...you tried discovering my identity!
Wow, you're already awake?
I'm happy you finally answered me for once,
but there's no need to yell.
Breakfast is ready, so come eat.
I couldn't prevent it...
The rest of them were attacked, too...
It's no use... No matter how hard I try...
...in an hour, fate will eliminate those guys, too...
I can't even kill myself...
My death would probably be bad for him,
so he made Bites the Dust automatically protect me...
He's too strong...
Kira Yoshikage is a complete monster!
Either he has to die,
or he has to undo Bites the Dust for some reason...
...otherwise, those guys will die for sure!
Either he has to die, or he has to undo Bites the Dust...
For as long as I've lived,
I never thought I would have to kill someone...
I didn't think an eleven year-old boy like me
stood a chance of killing a monster like him...
But there's one way I can!
A way for an eleven-year-old like me to kill him...
Just one...
And it's sleeping quietly in the attic,
like a gun resting in an armory...
For the first time in my life,
I prayed to God from the bottom of my heart.
"God, please help me kill this man."
I was right!
The cat-like plant starts moving when sunlight hits it,
then attacks by shooting air bullets!
Even with just a little sunlight in the room, it's so strong!
This behavior...
I can take advantage of this behavior
and have it shoot him at point blank range!
Point blank range...
But when can I do it, and how?
I can't do it anywhere near the house...
Mama is here.
That's right, my hat!
He'll try to put the hat on my head!
That will be my chance!
I'll be at point blank range when he comes up behind me!
That's when I have to get him!
Huh?! You're kidding! We're already on air?
Uh, well... It is currently 7:55...
Papa said he wanted another cup of coffee.
Yes, hello?
No, wrong number.
The Sakurais don't live here.
Here, darling! Thanks for waiting!
Your freshly brewed cup of coffee!
Right...
It's a lovely morning.
I suppose another cup before work couldn't hurt.
Fate doesn't change with Bites the Dust, right?
Something that was destroyed once
will be destroyed again, no matter how much you fight it!
That's what you said, right?
My precious tea set!
Serves you right!
Okay Mama, I'm going to school!
I'll always be here for you!
I'll protect you forever, Mama!
I can't believe it...
I can never tell what that boy is thinking, but...
...maybe he's a good kid after all.
Oh, don't worry! I'll clean this up.
Not much we can do now that it's broken.
More importantly, were you burnt?
No... I'm fine...
He's still not here...
H-He's not here... He's still not here yet!
S-Something's wrong! He should have been here by now!
Why isn't he here?
Damn, the weather forecast didn't say it would rain!
I-It's starting to rain!
Did leaving the house before him change fate?
No, that's impossible!
If he's coming here to put the hat on my head,
he should be approaching from behind!
L-Lightning struck the Pepsi sign!
Calm down! Calm down! I have two minutes left!
I have more than two minutes before
Kishibe Rohan is automatically blown up!
I have to believe in fate...
H-He's... already standing by the tree!
He's already right here!
What a lovely morning, indeed.
And yet, Hayato was acting strangely...
Why?
I have a nagging suspicion...
We must have repeated this morning
at least... three... no, four times now.
I-Is he just that smart?
I'm running out of time!
I'll have to attack him from here!
I-Is he staying away from me because he knows
I have the cat plant, and that I could attack him up close?
No... He's too close to know that.
But... I still have to defeat him with just one shot!
If I miss, Rohan will explode, then he'll undo
Bites the Dust after the rest of them are eliminated!
He'll win if that happens!
There's no more time... Crap...
Move one more step to the left!
If he steps out from behind that dirty-looking tree, I can get him!
What?! H-He's hiding himself even more!
The look in Hayato's eyes when he left the house...
He seemed awfully determined.
He gave me the same look that horrible
Hirose Koichi and that shit stain Josuke did before.
My instincts are telling me to cautiously observe him.
Not that there's much Hayato can do to stop me.
It's too late!
Once it's a few seconds past 8:29,
the attack on Kishibe Rohan will start!
The poor brat is shaking.
His eyes look like cesspools full of drowning rats.
I must have imagined seeing that determination.
His eyes are those of someone who has given up hope.
He moved!
I came here to bring you your hat, Hayato.
If there is a God, I thank you!
And I thank fate for making this serial killer
move out from behind the tree!
I feel a fighting spirit burning inside me!
Take this, Kira Yoshikage!
What?!
I... I did it!
I hit him dead-on! I... I did it!
Kawajiri Hayato isn't coming...
He must have taken a different route to school.
You're finished, serial killer!
Wh-Wh-What?!
Recently...
Impossible!
...with how quickly my nails have been growing...
...I thought my luck had turned completely rotten, but...
...I had something in my pocket.
My luck finally seems to have
taken a turn for the better since last night.
Remember when Mama's precious
tea cup shattered this morning?
The coffee spilled and burned my hand and wrist,
so I took off my watch and put it inside my chest pocket.
I can't believe my good luck!
If that coffee hadn't spilled this morning...
How... How is that possible? I...
I... I failed!
I-It's... It's almost time!
Episode 37
Crazy
D
iamond is
Un
breakable Part 1
D
Un
Crazy
iamond is
breakable Part 1
D
Un