Keep your hands off those dice, Higashikata Josuke!
Stay right where you are.
What is he doing?
If he figures out I've been using the space alien to cheat...
Knowing Rohan, a simple apology won't cut it...
What are you checking for?
It may be my imagination,
but I feel as though these dice are staring at me.
Gulp!
Ba-bump, ba-bump...
Hmph. Well, it seems fine.
Let's continue the game.
Rohan... Adds 30 New Chips.
I-I'm gonna go easy this time and bet two...
You get what I want from you now, space alien?
I just barely wanna win.
All I want you to do is put me a tiny bit ahead!
All right, go!
H-He still doesn't get it!
I suppose twice in a row can become three in a row.
It's certainly within the realm of possibility.
An omen multiplies your bet by five, correct?
Here you go.
It can't be helped that you rolled it again.
No kidding! I guess a lucky roll like that really can happen three times in a row!
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichini mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days
Episode 28:  Highway Star Part 1
Wh-Wh-Wha...
What did you do that for?!
I don't know how, but I'm certain you're cheating.
I won't forgive you...
And I won't forgive myself unless I figure it out!
Dude, you're insane!
And you're infuriating.
I've held back the anger I feel toward you for the sake of
Mr. Joestar and Koichi up until now, but...
...I refuse to sit here and do nothing
while you make a complete fool of me!
The thought of you laughing on the inside
at my expense is unbearable!
Give me your hand!
My Crazy Diamond can heal it for you!
Shut up!
Do you understand why I mutilated my pinky finger?
I did it to ensure that you won't
forfeit this game, Higashikata Josuke!
I won't let a simpleton like you
underestimate someone of my caliber!
We're going to play one more game!
While we play, I swear I will find out how you're cheating!
If I haven't figured out how you're cheating by the game's end...
...this two million yen is yours to take.
Consider it payment for healing
my pinky with your Crazy Diamond.
However, if I figure out how you're cheating...
...your pinky will belong to me, Higashikata Josuke.
Hey, looks like you boys are having fun!
Yo, it's me!
Josuke, long time no see!
I've been stuck in the hospital for over a month!
I don't really know how, but somehow I got
hit on the head while standing by the side of the road!
Tamami?
What are you doing here?
I called him earlier to ask if he could act as an overseer.
Overseer?
Kobayashi Tamami, at your service.
I'm here to ensure that your promise
is surely and promptly upheld...
...using this lock that I'll attach to your heart.
No matter who wins or loses, I'll fairly judge the results.
My rate is 20%, or 400,000 yen; whichever sum is larger.
You plan on playing one more time
to figure out how he's cheating, correct?
Yeah.
What?!
However, it's possible you may choose to stop cheating...
...so I need to ensure that won't happen.
In the event that you attempt to win without cheating...
...I've put a rule in place so that
Tamami's lock will automatically attack you.
This is really bad... but I have to do it!
I need to keep cheating until the end and get through this!
All right, I'll go first.
How do you like that?!
A four!
A pair of three's and a four!
Yes! You're finally rolling normal numbers!
He'll never figure it out now!
N-Now it's my turn, right?
Hmph. You look awfully relieved.
I sense that something you asked someone to do went well.
Don't panic... Rohan hasn't figured it out...
I just gotta keep playing!
H-He threw up?!
C-Crap! He's getting dizzy!
Rohan shook him around way too much!
Josuke! Quit hiding the dice behind your hand.
Huh?
I can't see them.
You need to throw the dice while I can see them.
Huh? Is there a fire somewhere?
Wh-What? Sirens?!
H-He's allergic to sirens!
Crap! He's gonna change back!
What are you doing? You're acting suspicious!
Show me what you have in your hand!
Sorry for yelling all of a sudden!
I just needed to pump myself up!
I'm rolling now!
Go! Do it!
It's a six-six-six omen!
The lock didn't move! Josuke is cheating!
Well? Did you figure it out, Mr. Rohan?
Mr. Rohan, are you admitting defeat?
I guess Rohan can't see the rash from his side.
Hang in there!
You either figured it out or you didn't!
I'm screwed...
That's...! I can't believe it!
I'm done for!
I can't believe it! There's a fire!
Huh?!
Mr. Rohan, your house is on fire!
It was the magnifying glass!
The magnifying glass caused the fire!
We were too busy paying attention to the game to notice!
Shut up! I don't care if my house burns down!
The only thing that matters right now
is figuring out how Josuke cheated!
Are you serious right now?!
You need to take your two million and get the hell out of here!
W-Well, guess I'll go now...
Wait, Josuke!
Before I go, I'm gonna heal your pinky!
I didn't ask you to do that!
Josuke, wait! You son of a bitch!
That was close...
I guess I'm the type of guy people love to hate, huh?
Who knew...
You appear to be in low spirits.
Was I of assistance to you?
Sh-Shut your mouth, jeez!
Kishibe Rohan's house: Received 7,000,000 yen's worth of fire damage.
Josuke: Though not losing anything in particular,
managed to make Rohan's grudge against him even worse.
Kishibe Rohan's house: Received 7,000,000 yen's worth of fire damage.
Josuke: Though not losing anything in particular,
managed to make Rohan's grudge against him even worse.
Kawajiri
Kosaku
Shinobu
Hayato
To all you drivers out there,
be sure to drive as safely as possible.
Yesterday, someone on a motorcycle crashed at the entrance to Twin Forest Tunnel...
...and was badly injured as a result.
Police later discovered that...
Recently, Mama's been acting weird.
She's dressing up, buying new lipstick, and actually seems happy.
Did something happen?
Mama's getting naked in front of Papa...
Haven't seen that in a while.
Was I a child born to loving parents after all?
What is he doing?
Higashikata Josuke... and that Kujo Jotaro...
It's their fault I'm in this mess.
Oh, Josuke. Thank you for yesterday.
Where did you go to eat and sleep
after what happened yesterday?
Mikitaka! Mikitaka!
I told you to stay right behind me!
We just moved here, and we still have so much to do.
All right, Mother. I will be with you shortly.
Huh? Huh?!
Don't tell me you're trying to prank people
into thinking you're an alien again!
If he told you that, please just ignore him.
At his old school in Tokyo,
he caused so much trouble when people took him seriously.
Anyway, if you'll excuse us...
Huh? Huh?!
I brainwashed her. She believes me to be her son.
I've elected to take the name Hazekura Mikitaka here on Earth.
Be seeing you!
Mikitaka! Come here this instant!
Hazekura Mikitaka... Alien or Stand User??
H-Huh? Huh?!
What the hell just happened?
What is with that kid?
Was he a space alien or wasn't he?!
Did he become a Stand user when I struck him with the arrow?
The way he created a divide between
Josuke and Kishibe Rohan was effective, but...
Still!
Next time, the Stand Highway Star
will surely defeat anyone who goes after my son!
Why are you avoiding eye contact with me?
Am I undeserving of a proper greeting?
You know very well that I'm your elder, Higashikata Josuke.
Sorry about yesterday...
D-Dealing with that fire must have sucked...
It did. About 2,500,000 yen's worth of my furniture
was burned to crisp, just like in the film Pretty Woman.
Not that it matters to me in the slightest.
Something wrong? Take a seat.
Someday, I'll have my revenge for yesterday's dice game.
What?
Was that...?
Josuke, did you see that?
I saw the door to a house in the tunnel wall!
There was someone inside!
It has a window, too!
There really is a room in the tunnel wall!
And someone is living inside of it!
Now a man is with her!
But I can't see their faces...
What is he doing?
Josuke, are you seeing this right now?
Shut the hell up, Kishibe Rohan!
I'm not gonna let you mess with me like this!
Can no one else see it?
That house...
Could there be a new Stand user?
The man who cut off that woman's hand... Could he be...
...Kira Yoshikage?!
Morioh Landmark #8
Twin Forest Tunnel
- Completed in year five
of the Kaei Era (1852).
- Rennovated in year twenty-eight
of the Showa Period (1953).
- 450 meters in length.
- Connects the road between
S city and Morioh.
Because it curves inside, the exit is
not visible from the entrance. Due to
the lack of light, many accidents have
occurred inside. As a result,
young people commonly believe
it to be haunted.
Note: Twin Forest Tunnel
You saw a room inside the tunnel?!
You're not fooling anyone!
You really wanna get back at me with a bullshit lie like that?
You of all people don't believe me, Higashikata Josuke?
Even after lying about cheating while we played dice...
...and never doing what you claim you will,
you have the gall to accuse me of lying?
You and I will clearly never get along.
I suppose nothing good could come of you joining me, anyway.
All right, time to check it out.
There's the exit.
There's nothing here.
The only thing here is the wall of the tunnel.
Perhaps I was just seeing things.
What?!
Th-This...
...i-is the room I saw from the bus...
It appeared out of nowhere!
The man and woman from earlier aren't here...
Damn! There's someone there!
This room was a trap!
It's coming... Something is after me!
I can't see it, but something is coming after me!
What was that just now?
I couldn't see it, but it was headed right for me.
It definitely wasn't human...
That room was a trap.
That man resembling Kira was nothing more than an illusion.
That room was created by a Stand.
I can't face it alone. Should I tell Mr. Joestar about this?
What? It's chasing me!
What are these things?!
They're... They're shaped like footprints...
Are they a Stand?
Sixty kilometers per hour!
I sped past them.
It seems like they can't go faster than sixty kilometers per hour.
Are they being remotely controlled?
What?!
Damn! They caught up to me!
I barely even slowed down!
These things...
I'll turn them into a book and control them!
Heaven's Door!
Damn... They're sapping all my strength...
I don't really want to see Rohan's face ever again, but here I am.
I guess I really am a hopeless liar.
What?!
W-Wait... I-Is this...?
Rohan's motorcycle? But where is he?!
Th-This thing...
Give me nutrients...
I need you to give me your nutrients!
Heaven's Door!
"Stand name: Highway Star.
That room is a trap.
If a curious passer-by enters that room,
they will be tracked down the same as a hunting dog tracks a scent...
...until they're finally caught and had all of their nutrients sapped from their body.
Once the victim has been touched by Highway Star, its weakness...
Its weakness...
...g-goes away?"
I-It's no use... I have no more strength...
I can't keep reading...
M-My strength grows weaker by the second...
I can't even order it to do something...
I... can't...
Rohan!
Hey, you in here, Rohan?!
Josuke! He came back for me...
An ally of his...
Your name is Rohan?
Hey, Rohan! Answer me! Where are you?
Rohan!
Th-That's...
R-Rohan?!
Go on, Rohan... Ask him to save you.
Where the hell did this room come from?!
Are you okay?!
Call out for help.
I've left you with just enough nutrients to call out to him.
If you ask him to help you, I'll let you live.
I'll take his nutrients instead of yours.
Now... Help me lure him into this room.
It's the only way you'll come out of this alive. Call him, now.
Why is this room here?
It looks like somebody lives here or something!
Hurry up and call to him!
Look! He's too suspicious to come any closer.
You're not in love with him or something, are you?
Just ask him for help and get it over with.
Do you want to die?
I-If I lure him in here...
If I let you take his nutrients instead of mine...
...w-will you really...
...let me live?
Of course, it's a promise!
It's a give-and-take deal for his nutrients.
Call to him. Hurry up and call him!
I refuse!
What?!
If there's one thing I enjoy more than anything else,
it's saying "no" to those who enjoy flaunting their power over others.
Run away, Josuke!
You won't stand a chance if you enter this room!
It'll kill you!
You bastard!
You really think I'd run away
just because a guy like you told me to?
I'm gonna give it an ass-kicking!
Where is it?
Where's that asshole hiding?
Wh-
Why would you do this, Higashikata Josuke?
Even after I warned you that it was dangerous...
You always do the exact opposite
of what I expect you to do.
And that's why I hate your guts!
That's why you infuriate me beyond belief!
It's going to attack you!
It has your scent now!
Yes! I got him!
Heaven's Door!
Note: My body will fly backwards at seventy kilometers per hour!
Josuke, Highway Star will follow you anywhere you go,
up to sixty kilometers per hour!
Find the user!
The only way you'll survive is to defeat the user!
Quit talking, you moron!
Rohan!
Kishibe Rohan...
I can't believe you actually saved me...
It's... It's hard to believe, but I feel weirdly moved!
All right, Rohan...
I just gotta find its user, right?
Once I find its user, I'll kick his ass!
Hang in there for me, Rohan!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 29
High
way
St
ar Part 2
way
St
High
ar Part 2
way
St