July 15th (Thursday) 10:43 AM
Who is this? I've never seen him before.
Greetings! I'm Kinoto, the architect you
most graciously requested on the telephone!
I'm here to appraise the cost of
the renovation and repairs you mentioned!
Oh, that's right. I forgot I had called for an appraisal.
Heaven's Door!
I apologize for doing that so suddenly,
but I've been trying to be more cautious lately.
Note: "Yay! I got work! Gonna make some money! Kishibe Rohan seems rich, so I'm gonna make bank off him. Hopefully I can overcharge him a bit."
Born in 1970 and considered a first-class architect.
His name is Kinoto Masazo.
I see.
He appears to be who he claims he is.
He's neither a Stand user nor an enemy.
Hmm?
Note: "I don't like anyone looking at my back."
Note: "I won't let anyone see my back. I don't have acne, scars, or a tattoo,
but I never want anyone to see my back! I wish I had a girlfriend. What should I do?!
I'm unsure of what to make of this,
but I suppose we all have our own strange fears and concerns.
At the very least,
I see no reason to bar him from entering my home.
Though perhaps I should know better from that Rock, Paper, Scissors kid incident...
To be safe, I'll write into him that he cannot attack me.
Huh? Was I spacing out just now?
No. But please, come in. Let's get to business.
Is something the matter?
The room that caught fire is the one facing the yard.
We can't discuss this until you come inside.
Oh, don't mind me! I'll follow behind you!
Huh?
Please, go on ahead!
July 15th (Thursday) 9:06 AM
Of course I'll get away! It's simple.
Episode 32:  July 15th (Thursday) Part 2
It's not like you guys have found Kira Yoshikage yet, am I right?
You haven't even seen my real face, either.
Note: His name is a reference to the transmission tower
Didn't you notice how fake-sounding my name was?
What kind of name is Kanedaichi Toyohiro?
Wh-What the fuck?
Are you wearing some kind of mask?!
I didn't waste my time thinking about leaving here without coming up with a solid getaway plan!
Anyway, I guess this is goodbye forever.
Y-You asshole!
Please do not come in, Josuke!
I have decided to remain inside this transmission tower.
What?! What the hell are you talking about?
This entire ordeal arose from
my discovery of the transmission tower...
...and it was my idea to put
myself at risk by transforming into the wire.
I knew I could be of use to you two.
I did it so that you would be proud of me.
Despite Okuyasu's insistence that I stay out of it...
I brought this upon myself.
Do not fear for my well-being.
Compared to living in a spaceship,
it is quite spacious in here.
You're a weird guy, but I respect you.
Honestly though, I don't really care who stays here.
It's all the same as long as it's not me.
You can work out who stays here amongst yoursel-
No, you're the one who's staying here!
There's only one "goodbye" happening here!
And it's the one we'll say to you once the three of us leave!
J-Josuke!
Y-You bastard!
Since you cut the wire,
I was able to restore it and climb right up!
Impossible...
Mikitaka, think you can hold on for another ten seconds?
Once I'm finished beating this asshole
back into the transmission tower, I'll heal you right up!
Don't fall, Josuke!
Ain't happening!
I called what you did impossible earlier, but I was wrong...
I should have said it was impossibly stupid!
I just wanted to finally leave this transmission tower...
I never planned on killing anyone...
But now I'm gonna have to send you crashing back down
to the ground so I can get away, you impossibly stupid idiot!
Shut the hell up!
Dora!
Dorararara!
Crazy Diamond...
Your Stand looks pretty strong up close, however...
...do you think you stand a chance of laying even a single finger on me when I can get around this transmission tower with my eyes closed?
I'm guessing its effective range is no more than two meters.
Shit!
What was that for? Quit screwing around!
Josuke, move from that spot!
He already used his knife!
He cut into the transmission tower!
Dora!
That was a dirty trick.
Good thing my Crazy Diamond is fast enough to defend itself from your attacks.
What's with the smirk, asshole?
You happy I'm about to beat that smile off your face?
I know this transmission tower like the back of my hand!
I know exactly how to cut it to make
the energy fly in whichever direction I want!
Like someone who has played
billiards way too much, I know all too well!
Billiards?
Jo-
Josuke!
You said your Crazy Diamond was fast enough to defend itself from my attacks, right?
But can you tell which direction they'll even come from?
I wonder how many shots I've fired off!
They're bouncing off the tower's beams!
Here they come!
Dora!
Josuke!
From behind!
That's why I called you impossibly stupid!
That space alien or whatever was ready to stay here
in the transmission tower forever. You should have let him!
Then you wouldn't have needed to die!
B-Both of his arms?
He has no chance of defending himself
from the next attack like that!
Here it comes! This energy will finish you off!
It's going right for your...
By the way, Okuyasu...
Did you see how many of his shots
I was able to block with Crazy Diamond?
Huh? Yeah, I saw!
I think ya got four of 'em!
Huh? Did you just say "by the way?"
Four, huh? Well, that should work.
Four shots should be plenty.
What are you two talking about?
Earlier you said they were bouncing off the beams!
You said your Stand's energy was bouncing around like billiard balls to attack me.
What are you trying to say, Josuke?!
My Stand is Crazy Diamond!
I'm sure the old man from the photo already told you,
but its ability is to restore damaged objects and energy!
Restore? It can restore things?
What exactly did it restore?
Are you trying to imply you had
the chance to restore something just now?
You idiot!
He restored the deflected energy
and returned them to where they originated from!
Josuke, I believed you to be defeated, but your victory was assured all along.
I-Impossible...
I guess you really meant it was impossible after all!
I'm so sorry!
I decided to live on the transmission tower since I couldn't stand other people!
But the old guy in the photo convinced me that if I could trap even a single Stand user here...
...he would look after me in the outside world,
which is why I went along with it...
Please! Will you let me stay here in the transmission tower?
I never want to leave here ever again!
I want to stay here forever!
I'll never think of leaving the transmission tower ever again!
New Morioh Landmark: The Man Living on the Transmission Tower.
Morioh Landmark #9
The Man Living on the Transmission Tower
Bringing him salt or snacks will make him more than happy to take pictures with you, despite his preference to remain in solitude.
He's a bit shy, which is why he wears
a mask and keeps his real name a secret.
Anyway, that old guy in the photo...
Did he say anything else to you?
Like where his son, Kira Yoshikage, is?
Or maybe something else?
Is there a Stand user named Koichi living here in Morioh?
What did he say about Koichi?!
Listen, the old guy in the photo just randomly mentioned him while he was talking to me.
I didn't ask many questions,
and he didn't go into detail.
Who cares?! What'd he say about Koichi?!
He said he was eliminated!
What did you say?!
It sounded like the old photo guy
finally figured out where his son, Kira Yoshikage, is.
He said this wasn't about protecting his son anymore,
and that he was preparing to attack.
Then he mentioned this morning that
a new Stand user eliminated another Stand user named Koichi...
And that's it.
July 15th (Thursday) 10:58 AM
Hmm... This is rather...
Whoa! Th-This door will cost at least 800,000 yen!
Its design is highly reminiscent of doors
made during the Victorian and Edwardian eras!
The material appears to have come from England, as well!
This certainly won't be cheap...
I know he doesn't want anyone to see his back...
...but was he doing this the entire way to my house?
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Drink before it gets cold.
Oh, don't worry about me!
July 15th (Thursday) 11:16 AM
I must remain in control...
Now isn't the time...
C
Cr
Cra
Craz
Crazy
Crazy D
Crazy Di
Crazy Dia
Crazy Diam
Crazy Diamo
Crazy Diamon
Crazy Diamond
Higashi
Higashikata
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Higashikata Jo
Higashikata Josuke
July 15th (Thursday) 10:20 AM
Poor Koichi... I hope they find him safe and sound...
July 15th (Thursday) 11:37 AM
Fuck, he's gone!
He ain't at home or at school! He ain't anywhere!
Koichi! Koichi!
Where are ya, Koichi?!
I ain't givin' up that easy!
I'll find ya no matter what, Koichi!
And that's why we need you!
We need your incredible sense of smell
and tracking abilities to help us find Koichi...
...Fungami Yuya!
In exchange, I'll heal your injuries. It's a fair trade.
A fair trade?
Don't fuck with me, Josuke!
You underestimate me!
I won't forgive you for doing this to me!
I have too much pride to even think about helping you!
I'll take that as a no.
I guess it was pointless to ask you, anyway.
Well, see you around.
Can't waste any more time.
Wait, huh? You're giving up that easily?
H-Hold on a sec, jeez!
I'm sure we can work something out!
Okay, fine! I'll help you out!
You're a tough one to bargain with, damn!
I'm the only one losing out here if I let
my tough guy act keep me from getting outta this hospital!
I can't show my girls any love like this,
and it's starting to make me feel worried and alone!
I'm pretty much where I was after I got in the accident,
so I can't really hold it against you!
So can'tcha just hurry up and heal me?
These injuries are driving me crazy!
I just finished healing you with Crazy Diamond.
Huh?
I gotta say...
...I am one devilishly handsome man!
To say I resemble a Michelangelo sculpture would be a huge understatement!
But looking closer,
I think my eyes are a bit droopier than before...
Did your Stand really heal me up 100%?
Don't even start with me!
More importantly, just how good is your sense of smell?
Good question...
I mean, I don't want you to think of me like some hunting dog, but...
To give you an idea,
I can smell three girls walking down the hall right now.
Smells like Reiko, Akemi, and Yoshie.
They're my groupies!
I can even tell that they came here from the pachinko parlor.
Yutie Pie, how do you feel?
Ah, Yutie Pie! Our Yutie Pie is out of bed!
Yo!
Are you all better, Yutie Pie?
Yutie Pie!
Take it easy there, my lovely ladies.
It's Josuke!
What the hell are you doing back here?
Looking to get your ass kicked?
Cut it out! Josuke and I are cool now.
But more to the point,
you three were just playing pachinko, right?
Huh?
How did you know?
I can smell the ass sweat on your skirts!
The only reason I can think of for all three of you to
be sitting on your asses for that long is to play pachinko.
Akemi, you got chocolate on you?
You won at pachinko, huh?
You're right! You're so smart, Yutie Pie!
Here, they're for you!
As you can tell...
I'm the man I am today because of these girls.
You healed my injuries, so I'll help you out.
You don't want me to think of you like a hunting dog?
You're way better than that, Fungami Yuya!
July 15th (Thursday) 12:05 PM
Is something wrong?
The floor upstairs is also burnt, correct?
I'll appraise it as well, so please go on ahead!
What is with this man?
Why is he going to such lengths to hide his back?
What will he do if I see it?
I-I want to see it!
All the trouble he's gone through to hide it
makes me want to see it even more!
I'll trick him into showing me...
Oh, my back... It's so itchy...
I just can't quite reach the spot.
I apologize for asking this so soon after meeting you, but can you please scratch my back for me?
Well... I guess so.
July 15th (Thursday) 12:38 PM
It was here.
This is where we found Koichi's bag lying on the ground.
Koichi's house is less than two minutes away from here.
How did this new Stand user manage to attack Koichi and take him away on his way to school?
Nobody even saw him...
Josuke...
This deal of ours...
It doesn't involve me fighting, does it?
I just needed to track his scent, right?
You don't expect me to fight any enemies, right, Josuke?
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
You're being followed...
...by that man over there.
I can smell Koichi's scent coming from him!
He has something of Koichi's on him!
What? That guy over there?
Wait! Get back here!
You asshole! What did you do with Koichi?!
M-Mom?
Mom!
This is definitely my mom!
She's unconscious, but still alive!
Even watching from here, I couldn't tell what just happened!
When did he change into Josuke's mom?
I heard that Jotaro can stop time for two seconds,
but this is nothing like that!
Jotaro couldn't just swap places
with a random person out of nowhere!
If he had targeted me directly,
I would have been satisfied just knocking him out...
...but that asshole went after my mom!
I can't forgive him for that!
Playing a trick like this is too low!
Yuya! Where did he go?!
Where did that asshole disappear to?
If you were touching him when he disappeared, how do you think I would know?
B-But... He's definitely still here, Josuke!
He's close! His scent is still strong!
Hmm... Fungami Yuya, huh?
I'm surprised his sense of smell is this good.
I expected to get caught once I started following him, anyway.
I had every intention of bringing out Josuke's mother...
...so that I could observe him in person.
Observe...
My Stand, Enigma, excels at observation.
Luckily, Enigma has already observed
Hirose Koichi, as well as Josuke's mother.
July 15th (Thursday) 7:37 AM
Sometimes he really pisses me off...
I guess he won't mind if I eat his pudding, then!
Josuke! You really were still at home!
You're here, aren't you?
Note: "Your panties"
Every human being feels fear.
There's no use trying to hide it from me.
The fear that lies deep within one's heart can never be erased...
...no matter how hard they try.
Wh-Who are you? How did you get in here?!
I've already figured it out in this short time watching you.
When you're afraid, you have a habit of swallowing your saliva, don't you?
Everyone has a subconscious sign
which reveals when they're afraid.
A habit that only shows itself in the face of fear...
Did you not realize it until now?
Tell me who you are!
I won't give you any money!
Get the hell out of my house!
Do I look like a burglar to you?
I don't want your money.
In fact, I should be paying you.
Because right now, I'm having way too much fun.
I just love how much attention you're giving me.
The attention you're giving me out of fear, that is.
Oh? You swallowed again, didn't you?
See? You did it again!
It's a sure sign that you're afraid!
Once the sign of your fear is known,
my Enigma can complete its unavoidable attack!
I turned Higashikata Tomoko and
Hirose Koichi into paper without a problem!
Note: Higashikata Tomoko, Hirose Koichi
When I startled Koichi on his way to school,
he revealed his sign in the form of blinking twice.
I recognized it immediately.
Yuya! I need you to tell me where his scent is coming from!
As tough as Higashikata Josuke is, I expected him to be afraid the moment his mother appeared out of nowhere.
But just like that, I know Josuke's sign!
Josuke bites his lower lip when he's afraid!
Next time Josuke is afraid and shows that sign, my Enigma will eliminate him from this world!
Yuya, you keep looking toward my mom...
It couldn't be...
Is it her jacket? Is there something inside her pocket?
I don't know what kind of Stand he has,
but could it be in her pocket?
Oh? Is he going to bite his lower lip?!
Come on, bite it!
Yuya, answer me! Is he in here?!
Damn! He isn't afraid enough yet.
Josuke, I never promised to help you fight...
I only promised to track down your friend...
It's too dangerous for me to help more than that!
I accepted your deal since you healed my injuries,
but only an idiot would put himself in danger for no reason!
I'm sorry man, but that guy is too fucking creepy!
I'll just have to see for myself!
There's nothing here... Both pockets are empty.
Except for this piece of paper...
The scent isn't coming from her pocket anymore... Could it be...?
Don't do it! Whatever you do,
do not unfold that piece of paper!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 33
July 15th (
Thursday
) Part 3
July 15th (
Thursday