Killer Queen! This is the name I've chosen for it.
I'm going to completely eliminate you...
...so that my sleep will go undisturbed tonight.
I toldja nots t'move!
Don't takes my Harvest lightly!
Die!
You have this many?
Crushing just three or four of them
hardly seems to damage you.
If ya moves even a lil',
I'll cut yer whatchamacallit artery or whatevers!
Oh yeah! It's da carotid artery!
I swear I'll cuts it!
Dere ain't nobody dat can beats my Harvest!
Looks t'me like ya gots a power-type Stand dat can't go very far!
It only gots a one or two meter range, right?
If ya wants t'die, den jus' try'n move!
I see... So each individual user has a unique power?
A Stand? Hmm... Stands, huh?
By the way, my Killer Queen
possesses a special power of its own...
He gots somethin'... Geddit!
Huh? Dis's jus' a 100 yen coin...
What're ya doin' with dis?
Nothing much.
I just wanted to show you my Killer Queen's special power...
...seeing as how you're as good as dead.
Killer Queen's special power...
...is that it can turn anything it touches into a bomb.
Literally anything...
For example, a 100 yen coin.
Get rid of dat 100 yen coin, Harvest!
With that out of the way, I can finally rest well tonight.
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 22:  Kira Yoshikage Wants a Quiet Life Part 2
Did you hear about that salon that helps you find your true love?
Huh? Seriously? That's so dumb!
It's true! One of the high school girls did it!
It seems one blast wasn't enough to finish the job...
Wh-What's goin' on? What...
What da...
What happened t'me?!
I already told you.
My Killer Queen can turn anything it touches into a bomb.
I turned this 100 yen coin into a bomb.
I can trigger the switch whenever I want,
blowing my opponent to bits from the inside out.
Though in your case, Shigechi...
...half of your face blew into your head...
...and about a third of your brain
got mixed in with the flesh of your face.
Before I finish you off with this next blow,
there's something I would like to ask you.
These abilities you call Stands...
Do your friends, Josuke and Okuyasu, also have them?
S-Somebody help me...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You won't be leaving here alive.
I can't leave any living witnesses.
No one can know the true identity of I, Kira Yoshikage.
However, I'm interested in knowing of other Stand users.
I can easily investigate who they are myself,
but I figured it wouldn't hurt to ask you first.
Josuke, Okuyasu...
Can you give me any other names?
How many more of them live in this town?
What powers do they have?
I-I dunno...
Don't tell me that you don't know.
Listen, if you aren't willing to tell me...
...I'll have to eliminate your parents, too.
Wha...
...What'd ya say?
M-My Papa and Mama?!
Hurry up and tell me.
If you do, nothing will happen to them.
We may be discovered if you take too long to decide.
Just give me their names. Come on, make it quick.
E-Everyone was lookin' fer a serial killer here in town!
A serial killer... Dey was talkin' 'bout you!
Yer da one who killed Sugimoto Reimi!
What? Sugimoto Reimi?!
He can still use his Stand?
Killer Queen!
That brat...
He was so torn up, too.
I... I gots t'find... Josuke...
Josuke's Crazy Diamond...
...can heals me up...
I... I gots t'save Papa an' Mama!
I gots t'save Papa an' Mama from dat bad man!
Dat no good, nasty man...
...can't be livin' in da same town with Papa an' Mama!
High School Ahead. No middle school students beyond this point.
—Middle School Principal
I gots t'find him...
I gots t'find Mr. Josuke...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, are you okay?
I gots t'find him...
He looks hurt...
Is he from the middle school?
Th-There's something wrong with him...
We should get a teacher...
No, leave him alone. He's creepy...
Let's go...
J-Josuke!
You said everyone was looking for me?
Do you mean to tell me someone in this town
knows the nature of Sugimoto Reimi's death?
I can't allow anyone to pursue me.
No one else knows the identity of I, Kira Yoshikage.
Which is why I need you gone for good.
I gots t'keep my Papa an' Mama safe!
Killer Queen already touched that doorknob.
Josuke!
This is the power of Killer Queen.
He's been eliminated without a trace.
Was someone just calling my name?
Yeah, I heard it too.
Whoa! H-Hey, Josuke, look!
Got... cha!
Sh-Shigechi?!
Shigechi!
Th-This ain't good, Josuke!
Harvest was gushin' blood after it disappeared!
That ain't how Stands're supposed to disappear!
Why do ya think one of those
Harvest dudes showed up right in fronta us?
Let's go to the middle school.
We have to find Shigechi!
Damn... When did that fall off?
Well, it can't be helped.
Hopefully my usual tailor has the same button.
How awful...
He struck again... It was him...
The soul of another one of his victims is flying away...
That boy must have run into him!
Shigechi...
I'm sure of it.
This boy is dead.
Poor Shigekiyo ran into him, then was murdered.
I'm certain.
I don't know under what circumstances
the two of them met or how he killed that boy...
...but I'm sure it was him.
I know it was him since he killed me, too.
I looked for Shigechi everywhere, but I couldn't find him...
He disappeared less than five minutes
after Okuyasu and I left.
All of Shigechi's books and school supplies were left behind.
His parents have the police searching for him.
This probably means...
D-Do you mean... the killer is a Stand user?
I know most of you probably don't know much about Shigechi...
...but it's hard for me to imagine anyone
who could beat Harvest in a direct confrontation.
This guy killed Shigechi in less than five minutes,
then somehow hid his body somewhere inside the school.
Jotaro, since we're almost certainly
dealing with a Stand user here...
...we have no choice but to lend our assistance.
Josuke...
I heard you picked up a button.
Yeah... Harvest brought it to me.
Here.
This is Shigechi's final message.
It's possible Harvest may have ripped it
from the serial killer's clothes just to bring it to you.
I'm gonna hold on to this.
I need to investigate.
Y-You can find that guy using a button
that could have come from anywhere?
Possibly.
We may be able to figure out the brand of clothing
he was wearing and where it came from.
I see...
I-If we're done here, I'm gonna go home...
I-I ain't feelin' so good...
I-I'm gettin' all pissed off...
Let's go home, Dad.
There's something wrong with Okuyasu...
Yeah... Shigechi was a greedy, annoying little jerk...
...but he was the type of guy you just couldn't help but like.
It's hard to believe that he's gone.
I'm not totally sure, but I think Okuyasu is upset since he doesn't know whether to feel sad or angry right now...
I'm going through the same thing...
...but it's probably even worse for Okuyasu...
Fuck...
It seems terrible things were happening that I didn't notice...
I must be warning each of my customers who dine at my restaurant of this...
I don't believe he'll come to my place, but just in case...
Even though Stand users are drawn to other Stand users...
...I never wanna meet that asshole.
So everyone here plans to take action, huh?
Oh?
That was Josuke just now...
Okuyasu was with him, too.
Hey, get a load of this...
Last Friday was my birthday, right?
That guy I've been going out with
gave me this stupid ring as a present.
Look at this thing! Why would I want this?
I still did the whole "I love it so much!" thing for him.
I'm only dating him since his dad is super rich, because otherwise he's a complete loser.
This ring is so gaudy! How much was it?
Probably around 150,000 yen.
I can just pawn it off for some money.
I wouldn't be caught dead with this thing on my finger!
That woman has an ugly heart, but...
...her hands and face are so soft and beautiful...
By dating me, her soul will be cleansed of its filth.
I have to go now. See you later!
Okay, bye-bye!
I'm afraid that's it for us.
I'm glad it was a clean farewell.
Yangu Shigekiyo has died
(Stand: Harvest)
Ki
Kill
Killer
Killer Qu
Killer Que
Killer Quee
Killer Queen
Ki
Power: A
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: A
Kira
Kira Yoshi
Kira Yoshikage
Greetings, all. It's Morioh Radio!
Coming at you once again is yours truly, Kai Harada.
How has the beginning of the week been treating you all so far?
There's just a few short days left in June now.
Now, let's eat.
And come July... That's right, it's vacation time!
Oh, that's right...
I have some errands to run today,
so I would like you to stay home.
What kind of plans do you lovely listeners have?
I'm so excited!
Coming up, the perfect song for this sunny day happening in the middle of the rainy season!
We'll eat dinner together when I get back.
Please, enjoy!
I'm so happy they still had the Parisian Special!
You're so lucky!
Let's hurry to Yohee Station!
Wait, Asuka isn't here yet!
Really? What's taking her so long?
It's been four days since the incident with Shigechi...
Nothing much has happened since then, but...
...now we have undeniable proof that
a serial killer is still running rampant in our town.
To tell you the truth,
when I look at the faces of people passing by...
...I can't even tell if they look innocent or not.
Oh! H-How are you doing, Mr. Jotaro?
Umm, have you learned anything new since I last saw you?
You know, like about the serial killer's button or something?
Unfortunately, no.
Don't have any leads yet.
I-I see...
Umm, where are you going?
Nowhere, really.
Just over there.
Ah...
This is rough...
It's hard to hold up a conversation with him
when he hardly talks...
Unlike Mr. Rohan's overbearing personality,
it's Jotaro's silent demeanor that makes him scary...
What can I talk to him about? Uh...
That's a nice coat you're wearing!
Sign: Centipede Shoes
Looks like this is a shoe store.
Huh? Oh, yeah, it is a shoe store.
Is something wrong?
We also
do simple
tailoring!
We also
do simple
tailoring!
Even though it's just a shoe store, they do some simple stuff, too,
like adjusting the waist measurements on skirts, and hemming pants.
There's even an electronics shop around here that sells flowers.
Is that what's wrong?
I checked out all of the tailors around Morioh, but...
...I didn't bother looking into places like this.
You having a problem with this button?
No. If you've never seen it before, then don't worry about it.
I just forgot what it was originally attached to.
Kid, you want an animal cracker?
I like eating the camel last,
so pick any of the others that you like.
No thanks, I'm fine.
Oh, okay...
Anyway, not only have I seen that button before...
...I actually just got finished repairing the suit it came off of.
A customer came in yesterday
asking me for this exact same button.
See? It's the same button.
Mr. Jotaro!
Gimme a break. We actually found it, Koichi.
Found it?
Oh, n-nothing!
B-But more importantly, what did the customer look like?
Do you know his name?
His name?
Of course I know his name.
Do you take me for a fool?
I haven't forgotten the name of a single one of my customers.
That's just common courtesy when you deal with
the same customers, even if you have hundreds or thousands!
Seriously?
Yes! That's amazing!
Can you tell us his name?
Well, the jacket should have an order tag attached to it.
I mean, I remember his name,
even though I've had hundreds of customers...
...but it will be faster to just look at the tag.
Let's see...
Note: Kira
His surname is... How do you read this?
I think it's...
Wh-What is it? C-Can you show me?
Umm... Umm...
Look over here.
Wh-What the hell?! My hand!
Look over here!
M-Mr. Jotaro! L-Look!
Be careful, Koichi! Don't get any closer to it!
Hey, I told you to look over here!
Is that his Stand?
M-Mr. Jotaro!
H-He's here! He's trying to take the jacket!
I didn't suspect anyone would actually investigate the button that fell off my jacket...
Did they see my name?
Why have these things been happening to me lately?
Gimme a break...
I can't believe he chose now to pick up his suit...
Regardless, I will make them disappear... using my Killer Queen's Secondary Bomb.
Just like that brat, Shigechi...
It's still moving!
That jacket is important evidence!
Wait!
Don't make any hasty decisions without thinking.
The way he's tugging on it is suspicious.
Something about this Stand...
...seems really dangerous!
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 23
Sh
eer Heart
Att
ack Part 1
Sh
Att
eer Heart
ack Part 1
Sh
Att