July 12th (Monday) 5:05 PM
Yoshikage... My son...
Where have you gone?
I'm sure you've hidden yourself
and changed your face and name by now...
How unfortunate... And yet...
Right. We need to look into everyone who's gone missing recently.
Including runaways.
Kira is probably still in hiding.
Do you think he would attempt to
commit murder while in hiding?
It's not easy for serial killers like him to control their impulses.
He'll strike again.
Do we really not have to do anything?
We still don't have any clue where Kira could be...
I was thinking the same thing.
Mr. Jotaro said it was fine, though.
He said we should keep going to school
like normal students until he has more information.
Be better t'keep looking for Kira than wastin' time studyin'!
It'll be a piece of cake this time
since we already got him cornered once, won't it?
Yes. As long as I'm repairing my house,
I'd like to have some renovations done, as well.
Damn him! He's taken pictures of all those businessmen in an attempt to find my son!
Could you send someone over to give me an estimate?
Jotaro and all those other Stand users
are doing as they please...
I need to make more Stand users
to deal with these meddlesome troublemakers!
Is that...?
There's no mistaking it!
Even though his appearance has changed,
our father-son bond has drawn us together!
I know my son when I see him!
I've finally found you, Yoshikage!
I need to figure out...
...who this guy disguised as my Papa really is.
It can't be...!
At this rate, those damned Stand users will...
I won't allow it!
I won't allow that to happen!
I swear I will protect Yoshikage!
Shining justice mebaete
Shining justice takes bloom
Brand-new bed town kosasuru ibuki
Brand-new bed town feels like a breath of fresh air
misaki kara shiokaze, tonneru nukete tou e
The cape creates a salty breeze, through the tunnel past the tower's beams
hikareai komichi ni mayoikomu
Until it's finally drawn in and fades into the town's streets
kokoro ni (kokoro ni)
Within our hearts (Within our hearts)
tokekomu kage
Lurks a hidden shadow
terasu ougon no spirits
The golden spirits will illuminate the way
sore wa mamori nuku hikari
Toward that light we must protect
Let the voice of love take you higher!
atsumaru chikara de tokisae koete
Our powers combined will help us surpass even time
1999 Bizarre Summer
meguru yuuki de ikiru machi
Living in this town surrounded by courage
Great Days!
July 15th (Thursday) 7:50 AM
See you later!
I'm gonna be late! And I have class duties today!
Episode 31:  July 15th (Thursday) Part 1
July 15th (Thursday) 8:02 AM
Man, I was up way too late last night...
I feel fuckin' fantastic after all the sleep I got last night!
Look at that, Josuke...
Those're binoculars!
They're just sittin' there!
You really can't help but
get distracted by things on the ground, huh?
They're probably super dirty.
Huh? Really?
I most certainly am not dirty!
Hello Josuke and Okuyasu.
Th-That was you?
Mikitaka, you can't just scare us like that!
Nearly gave me a fuckin' heart attack, dammit!
Oh, that's quite enough!
Quit acting bashful.
It wasn't a compliment.
But hey, good timin'!
I wanted t'ask ya somethin'.
I wantcha t'be totally straight with me.
That alien stuff is all bullshit, ain't it?
You're just a Stand user who thinks
he's an alien or somethin', ain'tcha?
Just fuckin' say if ya are or not!
I have been truthful with you from the beginning.
I am a space alien.
Why're ya suddenly talkin' like that?
C'mon, cut it out.
Anyway, why were you sitting there in the middle
of the road transformed into a pair of binoculars?
Oh, that's right. I was waiting here so that I could show you both that structure in the distance.
That thing?
That structure is a transmission tower.
Transmission tower?
Oh yeah, it doesn't do anything anymore.
They put it out of commission and disconnected all the cables.
Once Morioh began developing residential areas, they retired the transmission tower and started putting all the cables underground.
So what's the deal with it?
You trying to establish contact
with another planet or something?
There is smoke coming from its center, is there not?
Huh?
Y-You're right...
Please use me to take a closer look.
Wh-Whoa, hey! It's a kettle!
What?! What's that doin' up there?!
It's twenty meters off the ground!
Would you please look about five meters higher?
What is all that stuff?
I-I wanna see, too!
Unbelievable! Un-fuckin'-believable!
There's a guy up there!
He's cookin' somethin'!
What?! Let me see!
He must be livin' on the transmission tower!
He's got all the stuff he needs there!
He's up there catchin' fish an' growin' cucumbers!
He's got it made!
That's amazing!
He's completely self-sufficient up there!
The people of your planet seem to relish in odd behavior.
Be careful!
H-He's...
He's a new Stand user!
Yeah! He started flyin'!
But what is a Stand user doing living up there?
I suppose it is in your best interest
to learn more of this man.
I finally see them. About time.
Have they taken an interest in me?
Make yourselves at home.
It's been a long time since I last spoke to another person.
Look... He saw us now, too.
Wanna check it out?
Yeah, but we need to be careful.
We can't be sure if this new Stand user
is an enemy or a friend.
July 15th (Thursday) 8:05 AM
Huh? C-Can I help you?
I'm in a bit of a hurry right... now...
Huh? Huh?!
July 15th (Thursday) 8:11 AM
Gettin' close to this thing, it's a lot bigger than I thought.
You two, stop right there!
Don't come any closer to this transmission tower!
Huh?
You need to step further away!
I just finished using the toilet,
so you better step back if you know what's best for you.
What is he talking about?
Don't fuckin' tell me this's...!
Can't say I didn't warn you!
Not my fault you got covered in my feces and urine.
Th-That's disgusting!
Disgusting? How rude!
I set it up to spray like that so I could fertilize the wildflowers down below!
I like to recycle as much as I can.
To your right I have Asiatic dayflowers,
mountain udo, and watercress.
They're all edible wildflowers!
And best of all, with all these wildflowers around,
I can catch and eat any rabbits who try to eat them!
Do you actually live up there?
Doesn't this transmission tower
belong to the electric company?
Who told you that?
I bought this place with my own hard-earned money.
I got this abandoned transmission tower for just one-hundred
thousand yen and turned it into my own self-sufficient dwelling!
Ya bought it?
For one-hundred thousand yen?
Yup! Just one-hundred thousand yen.
Since I'm self-sufficient,
I don't have to work anywhere anymore.
And even if I never left, I get all the exercise I need just by moving around the transmission tower.
Get a load of the amazing view I have!
Huh? H-Hold on a minute!
Even if you never left?
Just how long have you been staying here?
Let's see... About three years now?
Th-
Three years?!
I don't think I've touched the ground for at least a month!
Yo, Josuke...
I ain't never knew a guy this fuckin' stupid lived here in Morioh...
He's a fuckin' nutcase!
An' he sure as shit ain't our enemy!
Ain't no way he's gonna attack us.
Maybe...
For now, I guess we should
head back and report this to Mr. Jotaro.
Still...
Something about this seems off to me...
July 15th (Thursday) 10:15 AM
What was this boy doing?
I see no issue with him recording video footage, but...
The way he's hiding behind that pillar suggests he's gathering evidence like I am.
He must be following someone
and recording their actions.
Could he be recording one of these men?
Kawajiri Hayato, huh?
There's something very strange...
...about this boy.
July 15th (Thursday) 7:33 AM
I'm home!
That's strange...
Josuke, did you leave for school yet?
Josuke!
Ah, I'm starving!
Josuke, you little shit! I can't believe you!
The nerve of him to take a bite out of my Kamakura Custar,
then put it back in the fridge half-eaten!
Not to mention there should still be two in here!
Sometimes he really pisses me off...
July 15th (Thursday) 8:14 AM
Hey, buddy! Something just fell out of your pocket!
Is that a photo or something?
Can you two please leave now?
Don't feel like you have to pick it up! I can do it!
Looks like a polaroid photo. What's he panicking for?
Seriously, it's fine! Just leave!
What?! That's...!
Hey! J-J-Josuke!
That's... Kira's dad!
I knew his dad's ghost was involved with this!
You finally stepped inside! I've been waiting for that!
You never would have stepped inside
if I had asked you to!
But by telling you not to come in,
you got angry and came in anyway!
You've finally stepped into Superfly, Higashikata Josuke!
Wh-What?!
Well done, Kanedaichi Toyohiro!
You've done well to lure that idiotic Josuke into your Superfly!
Good work!
Somethin' ain't right! Get back here, Josuke!
I can't! Kira's dad is right here!
He has the arrow with him!
You asshole!
Get back here!
What?!
Once someone has entered the transmission tower,
they can't leave until another person comes in and takes their place.
If you try to force your way out,
you become part of the transmission tower itself!
That's the power of my Stand, Superfly!
You completely fell for it, Higashikata Josuke!
Make sure he never escapes, Kanedaichi Toyohiro!
Josuke!
S
Su
Sup
Supe
Super
Superf
Superfly
Kane
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: n/a
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Kaneda
Kanedaichi
Kanedaichi Toyo
Kanedaichi Toyohiro
Josuke!
Sh-Shit...
Even though it's my Stand,
I have no direct control over Superfly itself.
You could call it an independent Stand.
I can finally leave now that you showed up!
Even I, its user, was held captive by my Superfly.
Well, good luck living here in my stead!
That motherfucker!
He musta been workin' with
that old geezer from the photo!
Okuyasu, can I be of assistance in any way?
You'd just get hurt, so stay out of it.
You've done enough already.
Maybe if ya could turn into dynamite instead of just dice or binoculars or whatever, then maybe ya could help us.
I cannot do that.
I cannot exert strength beyond my own, and I certainly
cannot transform into something as complex as dynamite.
But I believe I could be of use.
Shut the fuck up!
I just finished tellin' ya there ain't nothin' you can do!
Leave the dangerous shit t'us!
That fucker's tryin' t'get away since he thinks he's got him trapped in there...
...but he ain't never met the likes of us!
Hey... You thinking what I'm thinking, Okuyasu?
You bet I am!
Ain't nothin' special about a stupid ol' transmission tower!
Let's fuck it up, Josuke!
Yeah! I'll have no problem getting out after we destroy it!
Dorarara!
Cut it out!
What the hell? How are they so strong?!
This thing's pretty tough!
So long as we keep at it, we'll snap the thing in two!
An' look up there! He's about t'fall off!
Y-You idiots! How could you commit such a heinous act?
I knew this was a possibility, though.
Didn't you notice something?
The transmission tower absorbed the power from your attacks and is redistributing the force throughout the entire structure.
Huh? What the fuck's this retard talkin' about?
Josuke, just a little more an' you'll be outta there!
Let's do it!
Hold on, Okuyasu! Listen!
Something isn't right... What's that weird noise?
It's the force from your attacks
moving inside the transmission tower!
What?
Consider this fact for a second.
You know all about the conservation of energy and all that, right?
That stored power has to escape from somewhere.
Where do you think it's all gonna end up?
No way...
Duck, Okuyasu!
What?!
You can attack it all you like, but any damage you do
to the transmission tower will come straight back to you!
Hit it and get hit back. Cut it and get cut back!
Consider the implications here!
No matter what ability anyone who
tries to help you happens to have...
...they can't ever destroy the transmission tower!
Okuyasu!
Th-This ain't good, Josuke...
The thing hit me...
I got a hole in my side...
I suppose I should have warned you beforehand.
Now I bet you're thinking that if you defeat me,
the user, you'll be able to get out of there.
But that won't work, either.
Like I said earlier,
this transmission tower is an independent Stand.
Even if I died, this transmission tower would probably
keep trapping people inside of it for all of eternity.
That's the power of Superfly!
Josuke...
All of eternity?
But don't feel too down about it.
You just need to lure someone else inside, Higashikata Josuke.
One comes in, one comes out.
Just lure a sucker into taking your place and make a run for it!
It's just like the card game Old Maid.
Society works pretty much the same way.
All you have to do is pass the old maid off to someone else.
Isn't that right?
You are correct in stating that if Josuke were to lure someone else inside, he could get out.
Huh?
What?
But you will be the one to take his place
inside the transmission tower.
In you go.
Y-You...!
Mikitaka! When did you...?
Who the hell are you?
Why were you an electric cable?
When did you get there?!
What's up with your ability?!
Thank you for asking!
For you see, I am a space alien.
Huh?
Y-You really can be useful!
This is your chance!
Please step outside, Josuke!
Y-You bastard!
I really gotta hand it to ya, Mikitaka!
Josuke, hurry an' get outta there!
Get outta the transmission tower!
R-Right!
I did it!
You bastard! What the hell?!
The old fart in the photo
never told me Josuke had a friend like you!
Being a space alien, I am unfamiliar with this game of Old Maid.
However, for you to deceive Josuke
and tell him that he cannot leave...
...is akin to an adult beating a small child
at a game they had no hope of winning, is it not?
That is why it is you who should
remain in the transmission tower.
You will be the one to remain here.
After living here for so long,
I developed thick calluses all over my hands.
I can hide things underneath them.
Take this!
You appear to be under the impression that you have
cut a part of my body, but that is incorrect.
What you have cut is not me...
...but the cable from the transmission tower
which you clung to earlier.
He did it!
Good job!
Now reach the top and get out of there, Mikitaka!
I've waited so long for someone like you to step inside this transmission tower!
Did you really think I would let you escape?
I've thought of nothing else but
getting out of here every single day!
Did you forget already?
The transmission tower returns any damage done to it!
That cable is part of the tower!
I cut the cable at just the right angle
to send the force back to you.
H-Have I been defeated?
M-Mikitaka! Hurry up and get out of there!
I can heal that wound for you!
I won't let that happen!
I'm the only one leaving here!
Perfect angle and direction!
Once struck, it strikes back!
Mikitaka!
Y-You asshole!
You really put me through the wringer
trying to get out of here, but now I'm in the clear!
It's really gonna hurt when you
pull those things out, but...
...you'll have plenty of time to treat those wounds.
You can use the medicinal plants
I've been growing down there.
Asshole! Do you really think you'll
get away with this just because you got out?
I'll chase you to the ends of the earth, dammit!
Of course I'll get away! It's simple.
It's not like you guys have found
Kira Yoshikage yet, am I right?
July 15th (Thursday) 10:42 AM
Who is this? I've never seen him before.
July 15th (Thursday) 8:14 AM
July 15th (Thursday) 10:38 AM
I'll expose him... no matter what.
Any time I need to see your face, I just close my eyes
And I am taken to a place where your crystal mind
And magenta feelings take up shelter in the base of my spine
Sweet like a chic-a-cherry cola
I don't need to try to explain, I just hold on tight
And if it happens again, I might move so slightly
To the arms and the lips and the face of the human cannonball
That I need to, I want to
Come stand a little bit closer
Breathe in and get a bit higher
You'll never know what hit you
When I get to you
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need you, but...
Ooh, I'd die to find out
Ooh, I would die to find out
Episode 32
July 15th (
Thursday
) Part 2
July 15th (
Thursday