Doing things that bring attention to myself...
This is what I, Kira Yoshikage, hate the most.
To think that I'm experiencing such humiliation
in front of complete strangers...
I can't believe my invincible, remotely controlled
Sheer Heart Attack was caught...
Damn... I have to free myself of this somehow...
Hey, mister, you okay?
Feeling sick or something?
You want us to call your mommy for you?
It's nothing. Get lost.
Hey, hey, hey, you hear that?
You having some funky daydreams
after a good day of drinking too much, mister?
Having fun? Feeling good right now?
You got a real nice suit!
We're a bit low on funds after getting fired.
No girl wants to fuck a guy with no money.
Seeing guys like you just pisses me off!
At least try to put up a fight!
Mister, looks like your shoelaces are untied!
I'll tie 'em up for you!
A square knot! You're too kind, man!
H-Hey, what's wrong?
Killer Queen: Primary Bomb.
Anything it touches turns into a bomb.
G-Get a doctor! I need a doctor!
What a horrible day...
Get me a fucking doctor!
I just want to live out my life in peace,
yet I've been forced to deal with thugs on a day like this...
taisetsu na mono ubawaresou
Something important is being taken from me
nichijou ni magirekonda akuma
By a demon that's thrust itself into my life
heion na toki kuzuresatteru
Everything is crumbling around me
nanigenai soshite sarigenai
Living my life as if everything was fine
kizu ga nai uchi ni ubawareteita
Until suddenly it was stolen away without warning
torikaeshi ni iku nara ima sa
This is my only chance to take it back
tsuranuita ya no youna surudosa de
Those who fight with a heart pierced by the arrow
butsukeau kokoro wa utsukushii
Are a beautiful sight to behold
doko mademo chase you
Anywhere you go I'll chase you
itsumo chase you
I'll always chase you
ore wa chase you
I will chase you
nigeba wa nai
You can't escape me
hashiridase chase you
Run faster as I chase you
asu mo chase you
Even tomorrow I'll chase you
tataki tsukete yaru no sa
Until I finally pummel you
shouhai wo wakeru nowa shuunen sa
My perseverance will propel me forward to achieve victory
dakara I Chase You
Which is why I chase you
Episode 24:  Sheer Heart Attack Part 2
Hey, Josuke...
The hell's goin' on at Centipede Shoes?
I'm not sure yet, but it can't be good!
Hurry up! We can make it there in five minutes!
Look at all those cracks!
The bomb Stand's user should be hurt from it too, right?
Please remain within a short distance from me.
No more than five meters at most.
Act 3 has a five meter range.
You and I have grown.
Our power has increased tremendously.
Do not lament the fact that my range
is shorter than that of Act 2.
Gravity
5 Meters
If you were to move more than five meters away from that thing,
the weight afflicting it would disappear...
Gravity
5 Meters
...and it would rush straight for us unhindered,
much like a bitch in heat.
Conversely, the closer you are to it...
5 Meters
Gravity
...the heavier it will become.
Will you get closer to it?
N-No... This is close enough.
I just hope Josuke gets here soon...
Apparently, there's a gym opening up
near Budogaoka High School soon.
I really wanted to get a membership there...
I need to improve my stamina.
Although perhaps I would have lifted the same dumbbells used by
disgusting men who touch their genitals after not bathing for a week...
...or maybe even swam in the same pool as them.
It took me three minutes to get here.
I really felt my lack of stamina
as I was using that crosswalk earlier.
By the way, who else is coming here?
I'm going to assume you've called someone for help already.
Since Higashikata Josuke and
Nijimura Okuyasu live nearest to here...
...and it's been five minutes,
they should be here in two minutes, right?
The three of you are friends, aren't you?
Yamagishi Yukako and that woman running Salon Cinderella
are also what you would call Stand users, correct?
You wouldn't call a woman to your aid, would you?
H-He's...
I left my jacket with the button behind.
I'll retrieve it later...
...after I've eliminated you.
H-He's... right in front of me!
This man...
For years and years... he's taken countless lives...
...including Reimi and Shigechi's!
Let him have it, Act 3!
Killer Queen!
Why does he have two Stands?
I thought a user could only have one Stand!
Sheer Heart Attack is a homing bomb that
Killer Queen can launch from its left hand.
That's why only my left hand took damage.
I must warn you, Master Koichi...
You have exceeded the five meter range.
The weight afflicting that bomb Stand is disappearing.
S-H-I-T! I must attack it once again with 3 Freeze.
I see... Range, eh?
Which target would you like me to hit?
The user, or his shitty bomb Stand?
3 Freeze cannot afflict more than one target at a time.
Even if we make the user heavier,
his bomb Stand won't stop since it works on auto-pilot!
But if I make the bomb heavier, the user will get me!
Which do you choose?
I await your command.
Which target would you like me to hit?
S-Stop the bomb!
3 Freeze!
It seems no matter which you had chosen to attack,
fate decided you would lose.
Regardless, even though I thought my Sheer Heart Attack
had no weakness, it still ended up failing me.
I had to pay for damages at the café,
then got into a minor scuffle with some thugs.
I feel like I've been had.
I've never felt so cornered in all my life.
I can't help but feel a bit defeated.
Really, though. I have to hand it to you.
You're an impressive young man.
By the way, do you have any tissues in your pocket?
A handkerchief would work, too.
Hmm? I'm trying to be respectful.
The least you could do is answer me.
I don't... have any...
Here, use one of mine.
That's a lot of blood coming from your nose, isn't it?
You can use those to wipe it away.
I'm going to beat you to death now.
In just over a minute, your friends should be arriving here.
If I don't do this, I won't be able to accept
having faced such horrific public humiliation.
Now, now, you don't need to scream like that.
I endured just as much pain on my way here,
and not once did I scream.
You're a man, aren't you?
You should follow my example!
Look at this. You really need tissues now, don't you?
I'll help wipe you off.
They say your brain slows down
when your nose is stuffed up.
You know, I was lying on the ground
a little while ago too, just like you are.
I'll blow you to smithereens
with Killer Queen in about a minute.
You need to endure the pain like I did until then.
You need to be more like me!
Y-Your name...
...is Kira Yoshikage...
Kira Yoshikage... is your real name...
My driver's license!
When did you take it out of my wallet?
You goddamned brat!
You said you had to pay for damages at the café earlier, right?
That's what gave me the idea!
So what?
What do you gain from knowing my name?
I'm about to eliminate you.
Yeah, I've accepted that you'll kill me.
But even so, I figured out what your name is.
You're nothing special.
You may get away for now, but how does it feel?
A goddamned brat like me figured out who you are!
Let me say it again!
A goddamned brat figured out who you are!
You're a complete idiot!
I can't wait to kick your ass in the next world!
Damn you!
Goddammit! Why do I feel like I've been bested?
E
Ech
Echo
Echoes
Echoes A
Echoes Ac
Echoes Act
Echoes Act 3
Hiro
Hirose
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: A
Hirose Ko
Hirose Koichi
What an annoying brat.
Josuke and Okuyasu should be here in one minute,
which is more than enough time for me to finish this.
The only reason I beat him was to calm myself down.
His sock is inside out...
Doesn't that bother him?
Ugh, I can't stand it!
Not that way, Okuyasu!
But Centipede Shoes is over here!
We'll get there faster if we go this way! Hurry!
Wear your socks properly!
That's better...
Now I can finally blow you to bits!
Killer Queen!
Anything that touches the tip of its finger turns into a bomb!
In your case, I'll be turning your student badge into a bomb.
Primary Bomb!
Koichi, you were the true winner of that fight
the moment you got into his head.
What?!
What a surprise.
I didn't think you could move with those wounds.
Unfortunately, you would have been
better off if that had been true.
I can practically see through your gaping wounds.
Nice watch you got there.
That face is gonna get really fucked up once I'm through with it.
And by "that face", I mean yours.
You're a very interesting man.
Although I'd love to know your name
and a bit more about you, I'm afraid I have to leave.
I have only twenty seconds left.
I have no time for idle chit-chat.
Just now, I felt barely any power coming from your Stand.
I blocked your attack more easily than catching a pop fly.
Do you really think you stand a chance
against my Killer Queen with such meager power?
Ora!
Wh-
H-He's fast!
H-How can he move like that?!
Now that I'm looking closer...
Gimme a break. Talk about ugly.
But you won't have to worry about that anymore...
...since I'm about to make your face...
...even uglier.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
What kind of Stand is this?
It's moving like it stopped time itself!
Ora!
Koichi, if it weren't for you, I'd be dead right now.
You did a good job holding your own against him.
You have my respect, Koichi.
You've really grown.
Hey, Koichi!
Koichi!
Wh-What the fuck happened here?!
K-Koichi! Mr. Jotaro!
Be careful, Okuyasu!
What the fuck's goin' on here?!
Mr. Jotaro! Koichi!
Calm down for a sec!
I need to figure out if Koichi is still alive!
I can heal him with Crazy Diamond if he's still alive!
Yes! Mr. Jotaro is alive! Just barely, though...
K-Koichi's alive, too! But he ain't breathin'!
Hurry! Hurry an' heal him, Josuke!
Hey, he ain't wakin' up!
But I already healed him!
This is terrible... Josuke and Okuyasu are here...
He's hurt really bad!
It could take a while for him to wake up.
What a day... This is the worst day of my entire life...
I, Kira Yoshikage, have always seen myself through in a pinch...
I'll make it through this, no matter what!
What are you doing?
Looks like this guy's awake.
Hey, don't try anything funny, pal.
Turn around real slowly! Show us your face!
Be careful! Don't go anywhere near Centipede Shoes!
There was a huge explosion there earlier!
The owner was blown right out of the building!
So were those guys!
An explosion?
H-Hey, calm down... Were you caught in the blast?
I'm just an office employee...
But... now I'm going to die! Look at all of this blood!
I-It's so painful!
H-Hey, calm down. Everything's fine now.
I can heal your wounds.
Where were you hurt?
I think one of my ribs may have punctured my lung...
P-Please hurry and heal me!
Hurry?
Oh? No matter how you slice it,
I look like an average high schooler...
...so why are you asking me to heal you?
It's hard enough for me to get into pachinko parlors...
...yet you think I look old enough to be a doctor
that graduated from medical school?
Huh?
You're a complete sucker.
You've seen my Crazy Diamond, haven't you?
Damn! I got ahead of myself!
That means you're our enemy...
...and this battle was a draw.
Th-This guy's the killer?!
I suppose this means I've lost...
Yes, I'm the man you've been looking for.
My face has been revealed, my Stand has been revealed...
...and even my name has been revealed.
I suppose I won't be getting a good night's sleep...
...but only for tonight!
Killer Queen!
What the hell are you doing?!
Just what it looks like. I cut it off!
I-It hurts... It's so painful, and I'm bleeding everywhere...
I've even started tearing up...
But winning or losing means nothing to me.
I'm going to survive!
I'm going to survive in peace!
Even though it's my fate to be unable to fight the urge to kill...
...I'll still live a happy life!
Sheer Heart Attack, I've set you free!
Take care of them for me.
You have to protect me!
What the hell is this beat-up looking thing?
Josuke, that's a bomb Stand that goes after body heat!
You can't break it!
It's gonna explode once it senses your body heat!
Dorararara!
It ain't gonna break?
Dora!
Break?
I was thinking the opposite. I healed it.
Since that asshole left it behind...
It's kinda gross,
but that hand will lead us to the serial killer!
Follow it!
Yeah!
You're not getting away that easily, dumbass!
H-Hey, what's going on?
Finally... I'll be able to sleep... without trouble...
K-Kira? Why is your face covered in blood?
Hello, everyone. Is it already time to head home?
I'm in a hurry, so I'll be seeing you.
The killer's name is Kira Yoshikage!
His address is Morioh Kotodai 1-128!
He's thirty-three years old!
His Stand is a short-ranged bomb Stand, Killer Queen!
Hey, where's that guy goin'?!
I don't care where he's going! He's done for!
He's in this building!
Hey, wait... This is...
Salon Cinderella!
What is he doing here?!
D-Dr. Aya! Are you here?
Dr. Tsuji Aya!
D-Dr. Aya's...
Dr. Aya's...
What the hell? What the fuck's goin' on?!
He's dead... Why is Kira Yoshikage dead?
Dr. Aya!
Th-This is...
What the hell happened here?
Wait! That man isn't Kira Yoshikage! He has his left hand!
Huh?
He d-doesn't have a face!
Huh?!
He ain't got fingerprints on his right hand, neither.
Who is this guy?
That man...
He's wearing the same suit that man was...
He brought him into my salon...
and killed him before my eyes...
He's more terrifying than I imagined...
He forced me to switch their faces with Cinderella...
Along with his hair and fingerprints...
So he looks like someone else now?
Yes...
H-His face...
Crazy Diamond!
H-His...
Josuke, don't touch her! Get away from there!
His face...
Dr. Aya!
On the other side of the door!
You're not getting away, asshole!
I-Is it...?
I-It's rush hour...
Th-There's too many...
Wh-Which one is he?
Which one is Kira Yoshikage?!
Kira Yoshikage! Quit being a coward! Show yourself!
He got away...
He won't be quivering in fear or hiding for his life...
He probably won't even leave Morioh.
He'll keep living in this town like he always has.
Tsuji Aya has died.
Tsuji
Tsuji Aya
Tsuji Aya has
Tsuji Aya has died.
Ki
Kira
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a new identity after changing his name, face, and address.
Kira Yoshi
Kira Yoshikage
Kira Yoshikage has
Kira Yoshikage has ass
Kira Yoshikage has assumed
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a new
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a new identity
after
after changing
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a new identity
after changing his
after changing his name,
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a new identity
after changing his name, face
after changing his name, face, and
Kira Yoshikage has assumed a new identity
after changing his name, face, and address.
Episode 25
A
to
m Hea
rt
Father
to
rt
A
m Hea
Father
to
rt