Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
Get out. We're going home.
Get lost.
Nobody asked you to be here.
You think you'll help me?
This is my friend of three years from Egypt...
Abdul!
Red Bind!
This is...
I'll tell you the truth!
Despite appearances, it is not an evil spirit!
Jotaro, what you believed was an evil spirit is actually a being created from your life energy; a kind of powerful vision!
Because it stands beside you, we have a special name for this vision!
A Stand!
It's a one-hundred-year-old coffin, pulled up from
the Atlantic Ocean off the coast of Africa four years ago.
Coffin?
I did some research after it came into my possession...
I discovered that four generations before you, my grandfather,
Jonathan Joestar, died on the ship where this coffin was hidden.
Apparently it was empty by the time they discovered it.
But I know exactly what was inside!
Abdul and I are trying to discover where he is.
Because he is evil incarnate!
His name is Dio!
He has awoken from his hundred-year sleep.
It is our fate to do battle with him!
And on the back of his neck...
From this asshole's neck down...
...is the body of my grandfather, Jonathan Joestar,
which he's doing hell knows what with!
Kujo
Jotaro! Wait, honey!
You almost forgot something!
Goodness...
Here, a goodbye kiss.
Smooch.
Dammit, woman...
Kujo
Quit clinging to me like I'm some kid.
Okay! Have a good day!
Gimme a break...
It's Jojo!
What? Jojo?
You're right! It's Jojo!
Jojo!
Good morning, Jojo.
Jojo, what were you doing during
those days you were absent from school?
Hey, you!
Quit clinging to Jojo's arm like that!
You're getting too close! Back off!
What the hell, ugly?
Shut it, tiny tits.
Ugly.
Tiny tits.
Tiny tits, tiny tits, tiny tits...
Ugly, ugly, ugly...
Shut the hell up! You're fucking annoying!
He totally just talked to me!
No, that was for me!
Jojo, wait!
Wait for us!
Jojo!
What the-?!
The tree branches...
Jojo!
Oh, no!
Jojo fell down the stairs!
Oh, but he's moving.
The tree branches must have broken his fall!
Did the tree branches cut my leg?
No, it couldn't be...
Something cut it before I fell.
That's why I fell down the stairs. It must be.
But...
Jojo!
Are you okay?
Oh?
His Stand appears to be very powerful.
I see...
No wonder he wants me to get rid of him.
Even so...
He'll be no match for my Stand.
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 2: Who Will Be the Judge?!
That was scary!
Jojo, are you okay?
You're really lucky.
If you were like fifteen centimeters off,
you'd totally have hit the cement!
There are always accidents happening on these steps.
From now on, you should hold my hand when you go down, Jojo.
You there...
It looks like you cut your leg.
Use this handkerchief to wrap it up.
Are you all right?
Yeah. It's only a scratch.
Hold it.
Thanks.
We've never met before. Do you go to our school?
Kakyoin Noriaki.
I just transferred here yesterday.
Pleasure meeting you.
That was Kakyoin. He's not so bad.
Really?
I still like Jojo better.
Me, too.
What?
What are you talking about?
Give it up.
I'm the best for Jojo!
During that time, I was weakened...
...by being reduced to a head.
If I hadn't stolen Jonathan Joestar's body...
Without that energy, despite how little it was...
...I never could have survived at the bottom
of the ocean for those one hundred years.
However, this body acts as a bond between parent and child,
connecting Jonathan to his descendants.
They are aware of my existence.
By obtaining Jonathan's body, I have acquired a new power...
A Stand!
This Stand is also affecting the bodies of his descendants.
Advantages and disadvantages come hand in hand, that is inevitable.
I must eliminate them...
I must eradicate Jonathan's family.
What's up with this cramped room?
This is why I can't stand Japan!
Abdul, how do you deal with it?
It is quite fascinating...
This thing they call "the tea ceremony."
Who cares about some tea ceremony?!
Instant coffee is plenty good!
By the way, about Dio...
Mr. Joestar, now that we are cognizant of his existence,
would it not be fair to assume he knows of ours as well?
But we still don't know what he's going to do,
or what kind of power he has.
Japanese coffee tastes terrible!
That is American.
Jojo, how did you get this cut?
Nurse's Office
You didn't get into another scuffle, did you?
And take off that hat!
It's poor manners!
Honestly...
Nurse, when has Jojo ever gotten hurt in a fight?
That'd never happen!
He's right!
Can't argue with that.
Well, I guess I'll have to believe you fell, Mr. Scatterbrain.
Hey, hold it.
What are you doing?
I'm cutting your pants.
Like hell you are.
Well, I can't treat you through them.
I'll take them off.
It's a waste.
Aren't you stingy?
Now then, while Jojo is taking off his pants...
...I'll take your temperatures and prove you're just pretending to be sick.
But we really do have colds!
Yeah, he's right! Let us go home early!
No way!
Oops.
What is this?
Kujo Jotaro, today I will murder you with my Stand!
—Kakyoin Noriaki
K-Kakyoin?
H-Hey... Nurse!
What are you doing?!
What's it look like?
I'm shaking the thermometer so the mercury goes down!
Th-Thermometer? Nurse...
That's a pen!
A pen? Did you say a pen?!
Does this look like a fucking pen to you?
How... How stupid can you be?!
This thermometer looks like a pen to you idiots?!
Then take a...
...closer...
...look!
She's...
Ka
Kakyo
Kakyoin
Kakyoin Nori
Kakyoin Noriaki
My eye! My eye!
Jojo...
Don't tell me you also think this looks like a pen... okay?!
What is this strength?
What kind of woman is this strong?!
I saw something strange crawling up from the floor earlier...
Was it a Stand?
Kakyoin Noriaki...
Was he the one who cut my leg on the stairs?
Indeed it was!
Y-You're...
Hey, you again.
That nurse of yours is being controlled by my Stand.
Attacking my Stand will mean hurting her, Jojo.
You bastard! Who the fuck are you?
I told you earlier. Kakyoin Noriaki.
My Stand's name is Hierophant Green.
I am only a human, but my loyalty lies with him...
Therefore...
I will murder you!
I'm not going to hurt her.
Now that I've dragged it out... I understand...
It's just a lame Stand that's so pathetic it can only possess people.
Kakyoin, is that the best your Stand can do?
It's all green and striped, like a shiny melon.
You're going to regret dragging that out of her, Jojo!
Quit acting tough.
I can see my finger marks on your forehead.
If I decide to crush your Stand's head like a melon,
it looks like your head will be crushed, too.
I'm gonna keep a grip on you for a while.
We're gonna go see Gramps.
I'm sure he'll love to meet you.
As for me, I want to know more about Dio.
W-What?
What is this green fluid coming out of his Stand's hands?
As I said, Jojo...
You're going to regret this.
Take this! My Stand, Hierophant Green!
Don't make any weird moves!
Emerald Splash!
How's that?
Emerald Splash...
My Stand, Hierophant Green excreted what appeared to be bodily fluids, which in reality was a vision of destructive energy!
It pierced right through your Stand's chest.
As a result, your insides have been torn to shreds.
And so have hers!
W-What?
I'm positive I got that Stand out of her...
As I said...
Attacking my Hierophant Green would mean having to hurt her.
My Stand can reach further than yours, but it doesn't like open spaces.
It prefers to hide within something.
If you drag it out, it gets angry.
That's why, when you wrenched it from her throat, she was harmed.
It's all your fault!
Jojo, you're responsible for this!
Jojo, this is on you alone!
You did this!
If you had let me kill you in the first place,
this nurse wouldn't have been hurt.
Trying to get up?
How depressing...
If I could draw a comparison here,
it would be to a boxer in front of a sandbag.
You stand up only to be knocked back down.
I, Kujo Jotaro, have always been labeled a punk.
I tend to get a bit rough fighting my opponents,
to the point that some are still in the hospital.
There was one dumbass teacher who was all talk,
so I taught him a lesson, and he never came back to school.
At restaurants that serve me shitty food, I leave without paying the bill.
However...
Even I...
...know true evil when I see it.
Evil is when you use the weak for your own gain,
then crush them under your foot!
Especially if it's a woman!
This is what you're guilty of!
Your Stand isn't visible to the victim or the law.
Therefore...
I shall be the judge!
Evil?
You've got it wrong.
Evil refers to the person who loses.
The victor decides what justice is.
They shall be the last man standing!
How it's done doesn't matter!
The loser is the evil one.
And now, the final blow!
What? The loser is evil?
Emerald Splash!
Well, in that case...
What?!
Impossible! He shrugged off the Emerald Splash?!
...you're the evil one after all!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
TN: Ora is a verbalized battle cry used during an attack.
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
The one to judge you... is my Stand!
What a powerful Stand...
You only caught it by surprise and hurt its chest a bit.
I'm lucky my Stand isn't a weakling,
but I get the feeling it will become more violent.
That was close.
She'll be fine once her wounds are treated.
What was that? A gas explosion?
It came from the nurse's office!
None of you leave the classroom!
I'll leave the rest to them.
I'm ditching school today.
I have to get him to tell me what he knows about Dio.
H
Hi
Hie
Hiero
Hieroph
Hieropha
Hierophan
Hierophant
Hierophant G
Hierophant Gre
Hierophant Gree
Ka
Hierophant Green
Kakyo
Kakyoin
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: D
Kakyoin Nori
Kakyoin Noriaki
Jotaro's totally thinking about me at school right now!
I feel like my son and I just had a connection right now!
I'm not thinking about you.
J-Jotaro!
W-What about school? And who is that?
H-He's covered in blood!
D-Don't tell me... Did you do that?
It's got nothing to do with you.
I'm looking for Gramps.
It sucks having to find him in such a huge house.
I think your grandfather's in the tea room with Mr. Abdul.
Oh, Jotaro, you never tell me anything...
Even though I... I...
I worry so much about you.
But I know that deep down you're a sweet boy.
Hey.
Yes?
You look a little pale this morning. You all right?
Yay! Fine, thank you!
I knew it.
Well, this is no good. He's done for.
He's not going to make it.
He'll be dead in a matter of days.
Jotaro, it's not your fault.
Look, the reason that this man
swore loyalty to Dio and came to kill you...
...is right here!
What... is that?!
Next Episode
This is very bad... At this rate...
Sometimes having a cold isn't so bad.
I don't really know.
This is the one thing I feared most!
Now, what will we do?
Episode 3
Dio's Curse