Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
Here he is!
The man himself, Abdul, is alive!
After my head and back were injured in India,
Mr. Joestar and Jotaro tended to my wounds.
I also had Abdul do some shopping for me.
We're heading to Egypt in this bad boy!
N-No way! You seriously bought this?!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 23: High Priestess Part 1
The Red Sea.
Ask any diver, and they will tell you
it is the most beautiful sea in the world.
The sea is surrounded on both sides by red desert shorelines,
and so it was named the Red Sea.
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
Egypt
Saudi Arabia
Sudan
There is no pollution to be found here
since there are no nearby cities, nor connecting rivers.
It is an unsullied sea.
Hey, you know how to drive this thing, Abdul?
No problem. You need not worry.
I can drive it, too!
But you're not gonna.
I'm not getting in another crash because of you.
My grandson sure is harsh.
A submarine, huh?
This is the first time I've ridden in one.
It isn't as cramped as I expected.
Yeah. Normally you'd see a vessel like this being used by rich people for pleasure.
As you see, it even has-
Whoa! Nice!
I love this kind of stuff!
If only I had a cute girl to see it with...
It would seem you truly have not changed, Polnareff.
We did not come all this way for pleasure.
Oh, what's this?
It's a sonar.
It detects reflected sound waves underwater, kind of like a radar.
All clear. Nothing is in our way.
If an enemy tries to attack from any direction,
we'll be able to see them.
But if we're attacked in here, we're shit out of luck.
We're sixty meters below sea level.
I guess I should have expected this in a luxury sub for the wealthy.
A refrigerator, coffee maker...
...and the latest satellite phone.
Can you get me something to drink, Kakyoin?
I'm parched!
And for me, as well.
Sure.
Is cola okay?
Hey, Gramps...
You've barely moved. What's up?
Guys, quiet down.
I need to make a call.
A phone call? To where?
To go through the trouble of making a phone call from here,
it must be something important.
Yeah. This is important and very delicate.
Guys, quiet down.
Oh, I don't know... Which one should I pick?
I really like the design of the sparkly one,
but I need something for the charity event tomorrow...
Perhaps something in a refreshing white would be better...
What do you think, Roses?
You will look lovely in either, Madam.
Coming!
Yes, hello?
Oh, Joseph! It's you!
It's been so long.
By the way, where are you?
I'm having trouble hearing you.
Y-Yeah... I'm at a hotel.
Sorry, but work is keeping me from coming back any time soon.
Oh, goodness. Sounds difficult.
Going on a business trip in another country
straight from visiting Japan...
It's been nearly a month now, hasn't it?
Y-Yeah... Sorry.
By the way, Suzi...
Have you talked to Holly lately?
Yes, I spoke to her on the phone yesterday.
She said she caught a cold that
started developing into a bit of pneumonia.
She said it wasn't serious, but I'd like to go check up on her.
No, you shouldn't bother. She'll be fine soon enough.
You're such a worrywart...
He calls this an important conversation?
Yes. Madam Joestar is quite sprightly,
so he must check in with her now and then...
Yeah, I'll check up on that myself.
...to ensure she will not visit
Ms. Holly in Japan, and discover the truth.
Right.
Does that mean she doesn't...
Of course.
Of course, no one has spoken a word to her about it.
She would be needlessly worried.
It's all right. There's nothing to worry about.
Well...
I see. All right.
I'll just visit Japan some other time.
Oh yes, Joseph! I simply must ask you something.
I just can't decide between a white dress and a purple one...
Uh-huh... Suzi, could you let me talk to Roses?
Madam!
Have you considered the blue dress?
I believe it's somewhere in the back of the closet.
You're right. I'll go take a peek.
Hello, it's me, Master Joseph.
Where's Suzi?
She left the room...
She won't be able to hear us now.
I see...
Right now, I'm calling you from the submarine I mentioned before.
Ah, so you managed to safely meet up with Master Abdul?
Tell me, how is Holly doing?
Have you gotten a hold of the doctors
from the Speedwagon Foundation?
Yes, well...
Ms. Holly tells us over the phone that she's
suffering from nothing more than a cold.
She is quite insistent...
But her condition grows worse by the day!
Master Joseph!
Perhaps it's in our best interest to tell Madam Joestar?
No.
There's no need for that.
We're gonna put an end to this soon.
It's better that she just sticks to her daily routine.
Under no circumstances should you tell Suzi anything.
I'll keep in touch.
As you wish. I pray for your safe return.
Oh, Roses, you already hung up?
I wasn't finished speaking with him!
Madam...
Oh, never mind. Let's have some tea.
You'll have some, right, Roses?
Oh?
M-Madam!
Please have a seat! Allow me to serve the tea!
Really?
You have my sympathy, Mr. Joestar.
Don't worry about it! We're here for you.
We're right at Egypt's door!
We must defeat Dio posthaste, in order to save Ms. Holly.
It is for this reason that I have returned.
Yeah. Thank you, guys.
This isn't so hard!
Now I see why you were so good at steering earlier, Abdul.
I swear...
Hey, watch yourself.
The sea is full of obstacles!
I know that! All right! Let's speed this baby u-
Polnareff!
I didn't do that!
So sleepy.... We there yet?
One, two, three, four, five...
Oh, there are exactly five cups.
Hey!
Hurry up with the coffee! I'm thirsty!
Then make it yourself!
Look. the coast of Africa is visible!
Our arrival is imminent!
Near this coral reef, there is an underwater tunnel formed by erosion.
The exit is two hundred meters inland.
We will surface there.
We finally made it to Egypt...
Yeah, finally.
Egypt, huh?
Yes, finally.
Is something wrong?
Nah, I'm just really happy.
It's been a long time since the five of us were together.
Hey, Kakyoin...
Why six cups? There's five of us.
That's odd. I guess I wasn't paying attention.
I could have sworn I grabbed five...
Wh-
What?!
Gramps!
Mr. Joestar!
No way!
A Stand! A Stand somehow made its way into our submarine!
Ora!
I-It disappeared!
No, you're wrong!
It transformed!
It transformed into one of the gauges!
Just as it transformed into a coffee cup!
Seriously?
We're at the coral reef!
We were only a few hundred meters from surfacing in Egypt!
Mr. Joestar...
He's unconscious, but his wounds aren't bad.
He just lost his prosthetic hand.
Th-The phone?!
Who's calling at a time like this?!
Ignore it, Polnareff!
Don't get distracted!
This is High Priestess!
Our enemy's Stand is represented by the High Priestess.
You've heard of it?
I certainly have.
We are dealing with the Stand user, Midler.
Her Stand can be controlled across vast distances, so she is likely on the surface.
Its powers?
It is able to turn into metal, glass, or any kind of mineral.
This includes plastic and vinyl, of course.
Even if we manage to touch it,
unless it is attacking us, we will have no way of seeing it.
B-But, how the hell did it get in here?
I see... That'll do it.
How quaint... It made a hole to get in?
It damaged the surfacing system!
We have begun to sink faster!
We're already running out of oxygen!
It's impossible to navigate!
Jesus! Enough already! Who the fuck is calling?!
Jotaro?!
Hey! Do not needlessly touch-
Hi! Joseph, it's me again!
I hadn't finished speaking to you,
so I had Roses give me your number.
Why aren't you talking?
You sound like you're in a rowdy hotel.
Is that a siren I'm hearing in the background?
And is there water overflowing from the bathtub?
Sorry, but Gramps isn't available right now.
That voice... It can't be...
Jotaro?! Where is Joseph?
You should be in Japan!
Why are you with your grandfather?
Answer me, Jotaro!
There's nothing to worry about, Grandma Suzi.
I'm with Grandpa.
Later. We'll call you back once things cool off.
Jotaro!
Hold on! We are about to hit the sea floor!
Oh my god!
I knew this would happen!
Every vehicle we ride in gets destroyed!
Never again will I ride in a submarine...
Hi
High
High P
High Pri
High Prie
High Priest
High Prieste
High Priestess
Mi
Midl
Midle
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Midler
How strange...
I was getting through until a moment ago...
It seems the line went dead.
But...
Why was Jotaro...?
H-Hey, we're losing oxygen in here...
Kakyoin...
Did you see which gauge the Stand turned into?
I... I'm pretty sure it turned into that one.
No! Jotaro! It has moved!
Now it is behind Kakyoin!
Hierophant Green!
Kakyoin!
Ora!
Everyone, get to the door!
It is escaping by disguising itself as part of the hull!
Easier said than done...
If we stay here any longer, we could sustain serious damage!
Kakyoin, are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
Everyone, head for the next room!
We shall seal this room behind us!
I-Inconceivable!
It was able to transform into a handwheel so quickly...
I-I must move my hands!
Its nails tore off Mr. Joestar's prosthetic hand!
What?!
Yes! We got it!
That was close...
I guess this thing isn't faster than Star Platinum.
What'll we do with it?
Jotaro, you can't hesitate!
Show no mercy! Hurry and rip its head off! Hurry!
Aye aye, sir.
F-Fucker...
It turned into a razor!
I-Impossible...
Such power!
I can't believe it landed an attack on Jotaro...
What an enemy...
W-What's the situation?
I'm not sure what's happening, but are we in trouble?
Shut the fuck up, Gramps.
It will attack us if we touch it...
So, we shall avoid just that!
Magician's Red!
Silver Chariot!
Too hard!
Chariot's blade can't pierce it!
We have to strike while we can see it!
Everyone, stand back!
Th-There's still oxygen in here!
Even so, we don't have much time!
Are you all right?
Yeah!
Leave it, Jotaro! It will transform again.
Since we are sinking, we must trap it in here!
Only then shall we find a way to defeat it!
I, Kujo Jotaro, will personally beat you to death.
What the hell?!
Jotaro, you answered a phone call from Suzi?!
Seriously... You shouldn't have done that!
Well, whatever. We'll talk once we're through with this.
Just leave it to me!
You got a plan?
Yeah, and it's brilliant, too!
I, Joseph Joestar, have dealt with situations like this before!
Why was Jotaro with Joseph?
Have you heard anything?
N-No...
Still, it made me so happy to hear that boy's voice after so long.
I heard he's become rather wild lately...
But deep down, he's a sweet child who deeply cares for his family.
I'm sure he's helping Joseph out as best he can.
Yes, Madam. Master Jotaro and Master Joseph are likely fighting an enemy together this very moment...
Ms. Holly is in danger, and they continue to
fight for her safety, despite the risk involved...
What do we do now?
I can't tell if it's us or the Stand that's trapped anymore!
Sooner or later, it'll claw its way out of that room and get to us!
We are at a massive disadvantage
in this closed space filled with machinery!
This submarine is done for!
We must abandon it and escape!
We must surface in Egypt!
But we're forty meters below sea level!
It's not that deep, but how are we gonna get to the surface?
So now we gotta scuba dive?
I've never done this before...
Hurry up! Step on it!
Gimme a break.
I can't make the necessary preparations to dive without my hand...
Lend me a hand, Jotaro.
Do it yourself.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Above all, never panic.
The sea floor is so beautiful...
When everything's fine, we'll use this...
When things aren't good, signal this.
I would like to see your face just once.
Episode 24
High Priestess Part 2