Just now... I felt my son die!
I sense a terrible misfortune has befallen my son,
J. Geil, through our kindred connection.
My precious son...
So you died covered with these wounds...
I feel the same pain you felt...
You were absolutely magnificent
while you fought for Lord Dio, J. Geil!
But...
To kill someone like you, with a soul so pure...
Surely they used some form of underhanded trickery!
Curses!
Those heathens!
I'll have you make them pay a terrifying price, Empress Card!
Move!
The time to act is nigh!
That Stand will surely bring them all a slow and painful death!
What horrible sadness!
Die for what you've done!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Jojo and company have taken a bus to the sacred city, Varanasi.
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Varanasi
Calcutta
Episode 12: Empress
Look, I don't normally lecture people...
But seriously, the reason stupid people are so stupid is because
they can't even understand you after you keep repeating yourself.
You ever meet guys like that?
Complete dumbasses who just don't get it.
But you know... uh...
Err... I didn't catch your name...
Nena.
Nena! Nice name!
You're the daughter of some
wealthy family in Varanasi though, right?
You're beautiful, and obviously a pretty smart girl.
I'm pretty good at reading people, so hear me out.
Hol Horse is a horrible, lying bastard.
He tricked you! Your parents would be upset if they knew.
Now listen closely...
You can't let people take advantage of you like that!
Even though it's easy when you're in love...
But you can't think of it like that!
Be rational, and have a broad outlook.
Hey. It's coming into view.
The city of Varanasi.
The holy river, the Ganges.
Saints, the old, the sickly, children, cows, dogs, monkeys, food, excrement, burning corpses...
This river gently embraces all these things as it flows.
Everything from birth to death is laid bare here.
It is said that people can spend months here
in the sacred city of Varanasi without getting bored.
This is likely because the scenery one sees
in this city reflects the scenery of one's soul.
Man... it's getting worse.
What's wrong? Gramps, you feeling okay?
It looks like my bug bite is getting infected.
It's definitely swollen.
You should get that checked before it gets worse.
You know, doesn't that kind of look like a face?
Hey, don't joke like that, Polnareff.
Just kidding!
Want me to tag along to the hospital?
No! Quit treating me like an old fart.
I take off now.
Huh? What was that?!
Is very infected.
Poison will spread if we no take off.
Hey, hey, hey...
Can't you just give me some medicine and slap a bandage on it?
No worry. I numb it. You feel no pain.
No problem. You gonna be okay.
Now, lie down please.
I study medicine in England.
I also do the appendectomy.
Uh-oh. Is a bit rusty.
Well, no problem.
All right.
Let's go with the chopping.
Oh, man...
I don't want to see you slice it off.
No problem!
Hey, what's the holdup?
Is it over?
What?!
Hey, Doctor!
Tryin' to cut me? You're pretty dumb, you fucking moron!
W-What the hell are you?!
I'm Empress, as in the Empress card, Old Man Joseph!
And now, I'm gonna bloody you up good!
When did you get on me, you freak?!
It has teeth! It stopped the scalpel!
It's so strong!
It grabbed the scalpel!
Oh no!
Th-Thank goodness it was my prosthetic hand...
You fucker! Plan on cutting yourself?
We share the same body now, Old Man Joseph.
You're not getting away from me now, honey!
Now, how about I guess what you're thinking?
Well, let me fill you in...
Only Stands can defeat other Stands.
Your Stand, Hermit Purple, uses the power of
remote viewing to see things far away.
Is that enough to fight me?
Can you really defeat something that's fused to your arm?
No way!
Where's your user?
Where was I when you latched on to me?
Dumbass! Like I'd tell you!
Damn you!
Gonna go cry to your friends?
I bet that'll go just great!
Doctor, your next patient is wait... ing...
D-Doctor!
H-Hey! Don't get the wrong idea!
I didn't—
I am responsible!
I am Joseph Joestar! An American!
I'm staying at Hotel Clarks!
What?!
By the way, baby, I've got a thing for
smoking hot nurses like yourself!
What?!
Murderer!
Wait! It's not me!
Oh no...
Can't go back to the hotel now!
Now there's nothing stopping me from killing you!
Y-You pest!
I'll smash you to a pulp!
What?
Hey, this is your arm.
Take care of it, you senile old fucker.
It grew arms! Will it keep growing?
H-Hey! Let go!
What are you holding on to? Let go!
No way!
Officer! I've found the culprit!
He's right here!
It's been a while, but let's give it a try...
You there! What are you doing?
Overdrive!
You shithead!
This is your arm!
You think your Ripple would work against your own body?
Halt! Don't move!
In that case, Hermit Purple!
I-It's squeezing me...
I can use Hermit Purple this way, too!
I told you not to move!
Halt! Stop!
Shit!
What the hell? It's dark in here!
What is going on?
H
He
Her
Herm
Hermit
Hermit P
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purpl
J
Hermit Purple
Jo
Jose
Josep
Joseph
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Joseph Joes
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Joseph Joest
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
So to sum it up, Nena...
Real men don't talk big.
That's how you separate the honest ones from the liars.
In order to avoid the police,
I had to run in the opposite direction of the hotel.
If I had known this would happen,
I'd have taken Polnareff with me.
Instead of a petty guy like Hol Horse...
How about me? Aren't I your type?
I don't dwell on the past.
I don't even care who you were dating before.
What's important is the future...
...and that we understand each other's feelings.
Ah, look over there!
That place is a hotel run by a Japanese woman named Kumiko.
She manages it with her Indian husband.
Look out, coming through.
We can probably get a cheap room there.
Oh, really?
But what about our hotel?
Wha-
What are you doing?
I'm chowing down, Joestar.
Gotta get bigger!
You stole those at the market! You speedy little bastard!
W-Why, you...
Now I'm this big!
You might say I'm mooching off my parent,
but I guess it's really just your arm, Papa.
You ugly bitch!
I'll show you that I, Joseph Joestar,
have way more experience fighting than you do!
That said, what the hell am I gonna do?
Shit...
Anyway, Hermit Purple!
Father, thank you for raising me.
But it isn't nice to tie your children down like this.
You must raise your children to be free!
Oh no!
I-It's no use...
I need to use Hermit Purple's remote viewing
to find the user, but I don't have a camera!
W-What should I do?
At this rate... will not only my arm...
...but my entire body become a part of it?
Now I've grown big enough to kill you!
See? My hand can reach your neck.
If I bust the artery in your neck, you'll die for sure!
Oh no!
What's up with him?
You bitch!
What on earth is that?!
L-Look!
That guy's got a huge, nasty growth on his arm!
Shit! Where's its Stand user?
Polnareff, sir...
I'm just a useless woman who can't survive without a reliable man!
I love you... because you're so reliable and kind...
H-Hey, where's all this coming from?
I-Is this for real?
I'm totally falling for her!
Lucky!
Hey, Joseph Joestar.
You fucking retard!
You keep getting further and further from Jotaro and the others.
Do you think I'm running around...
...just to wear myself out?!
I'm running so I can kill you!
My goal was...
...to dunk you in this!
You dense old fucker!
A nail?!
I picked it up earlier!
I just happened to find it while we were rolling on the ground earlier!
So now I can cut your neck open!
Did you really think I'd suffocate if you stuck me in there?
Now die!
I have a physical form, but I'm not a living organism.
Did you already forget that?
Only Stands can defeat Stands!
Hey big guy, weren't you going to
show me our difference in fighting experience?
Where's that "experience" you ranted about?
You're just a pathetic geezer who's too old for his own good!
M-My prosthetic fingers...
They almost broke from that attack earlier...
And now they're out of strength...
Just one more push, now...
Your life as a leeching invalid is about to end!
There's not a single way you can defeat m—
Not a single way...!
Huh?
Not a single... what now?
My hearing isn't what it used to be.
Why don't you run that by me again?
Coal tar!
You stuck me in coal tar!
It wasn't to suffocate me, but to solidify me!
B-But...
How did you know there was coal tar in there?!
With my Stand, Hermit Purple, and its incredible power!
H-Hey, everyone, look...
What is this?
In the ashes that foreigner spilled everywhere...
They formed a map of the city!
Y-You used spirit photography?!
So that's how you found the coal tar!
You used the ashes to make a spirit photo!
Well, I think now you should be able to see
a huge difference in our fighting experience.
When your opponent flaunts their victory early, they've already lost.
That's how Joseph Joestar gets things done!
Seems like I only get better with age!
By the way...
A Stand can tear away another Stand!
Now you'll say, "Stop, anything but that!"
Stop, anything but that!
No can do. It pains me, as well.
Children can't depend on their parents forever.
You have to live on your own once you've grown big!
Question is... where's the Stand user?
W-Well, then, Nena...
Let's seal our love with a kiss.
What? What? What?!
W-What's wrong, Nena?!
So that's Empress's Stand user...
That hideous woman...
She attached her Stand to me as a tumor with a human face,
and camouflaged herself as a beautiful woman.
That was pretty careless...
She really got you, Polnareff.
E
Em
Empr
Empre
Empress
Ne
Nen
Power: C
Speed: E
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Nena
And here I thought we'd finally be able to sleep in a bed.
Maybe we would be if gramps hadn't
fucked up and got the cops chasing him.
It's all taken care of.
We're taking this car.
Polnareff, your turn to drive.
Hey, are you still in shock?
I'm the one who got attacked by the Stand.
I think I would have preferred that...
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
We'll be saying farewell to India.
I mean, I am a girl after all.
Did you see his face?
We don't need to get ourselves into trouble right now.
A truck? No way!
By the way, do you like sumo?
Episode 13
Wheel of Fortune