Right under your chin, Polnareff?
What?!
It's me, you fool. The user of the Anubis Stand!
W-What should I do?
Die!
I'll shave your chin right off!
W-Who the hell are you?
Aren't you the owner of this place?
C-Could it be that the katana...
The katana is actually a Stand,
and it can control whoever wields it?
Was that guy in Kom Ombo not the real user?
Polnareff!
No matter how hard you try, you're no match for me!
Th-This power...
After our last battle,
I memorized Chariot's powers and strengths!
I've never lost to anyone I fought before!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
C'mon, c'mon!
Episode 29: Divine Anubis Part 2
Come on, you almost got it!
Polnareff and Jotaro seem to be taking their time.
Polnareff! Who the fuck is this guy?
Stay back, Jotaro!
Th-The sword is a Stand!
It's way too dangerous for your Star Platinum to fight it bare-handed!
And this guy isn't the user! He's just a puppet!
N-Not to mention the Stand... is getting stronger!
Asshole!
Whoa, there!
Does it sting?
I've memorized how much punishment you can take.
It will be interesting to see if you can
withstand this next attack, Polnareff.
Polnareff!
H-He's getting stronger... with every strike!
I-I can't take it!
I-I can't hold him back!
Now!
Take this!
What?!
I have your attack patterns memorized.
After I've fought an opponent,
even if the person wielding me changes...
No matter what, no matter what, no matter what, no matter what...
...I won't lose!
I-It's no use... My sword is useless now...
C-Crap! Jotaro, help me out here!
Star Platinum!
Ora!
D-Did we beat him?
No, I barely scratched him.
It took all I had to land that punch.
Hey, Khan... are you okay?
Fuck... This thing is strong.
This is the first offensive Stand we've seen
in a while that doesn't use tricks or special abilities.
As expected of Star Platinum. It's as fast as I was told.
But now, I have that memorized, too.
W-What's the matter, Khan?
Stay back!
He's been possessed!
If you don't want to be cut open, get inside and hide!
Th-This is bad, Jotaro...
The more we fight it, the faster it gets...
H-His next attack... It's going to be the fastest,
strongest, and most intense we've seen yet!
Move it, Polnareff!
He's aiming for me!
Run, Jotaro!
Die!
Ora!
H-He caught it?!
Impossible... He caught my blade...
I understand now. Star Platinum's strength
doesn't come from its speed and precision alone...
It also comes from Jotaro's ability to stay cool under pressure.
I'll keep that memorized...
Is he dead?
No, he's just unconscious!
Jotaro, don't touch the sword!
Even now, that Stand's evil power could still be active.
Anyone who touches the drawn blade falls under its control.
We'll sheathe it, but without touching it.
So what now?
We'll be in big trouble if it gets drawn again.
This thing has our powers memorized.
I'm not sure we'll be able to beat it again.
Why don't we let it nap in the Nile for eternity?
For eternity, huh? That's a good idea!
Hold it! Police!
Oh, good timing! Could you get this guy to a hospital?
I got a report someone was fighting, and here you guys are!
Why are you holding a katana?!
Hand it over immediately!
Hey, quit it!
Don't unsheathe it!
Polnareff!
No way...
Polnareff's eyes...
Did that cursed sword get him?
You there! You drew the katana!
Did I?
Hey, officer. Don't lie to my face.
Aren't you supposed to uphold the law?
H-Hey, what are you doing?
Aren't you the one who drew it?!
I don't know where the real Stand user is,
but Polnareff is definitely under his control.
I never thought I would have to fight Polnareff...
I can't hold back if I'm fighting Chariot.
Even if I won, it would mean killing Polnareff.
Don't forget that I, Divine Anubis,
have memorized all of Star Platinum's moves.
Anyone I've fought before will never
stand a chance of defeating me!
Ora!
Whoa, there!
H-His speed... Shit!
He's getting faster. I-I can't take it...
I have to stop the sword!
I'll catch it again!
It sped up!
Your head is mine!
Wha-
Ora!
What speed and power...
I've never faced a Stand that could move at this speed.
I-I'm not gonna be able to win...
If I don't fight Polnareff using all my strength, he'll kill me.
To think you'd use a headbutt
to escape from a failed blade-catch...
I just about had you. Too bad.
However...
I have that memorized now, too.
Jotaro...
Right now you're thinking that if you don't kill Polnareff, you'll die.
How naïve of you. Naïve, naïve!
So without further ado, allow me to show you
just how I'll finish you off for good.
Can you...
...beat this...
...Jotaro?!
Silver Chariot plus Divine Anubis! Dual wielding!
Di
Divi
Divine
Divine Anu
Divine Anubis
Kh
Kha
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Khan
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
This is bad...
Since he has the katana, if he gets any faster...
...even my Star Platinum...
What's the matter? Am I putting you to sleep, Jotaro?
I have to stop him before he kills me!
Star Finger!
All that did was make my arm feel lighter.
I see. I guess that's one way of doing it.
You look surprised!
Here I go! Without armor!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
You idiot! Your "Ora Ora" can't possibly stop two Stands who are experts at dual wielding!
Your chest is open!
I got you!
I did it! I won!
Lord Dio! Jotaro is defeated!
I, Divine Anubis, have defeated Jotaro!
Yes!
You're a fool if you think you can stop the blade or pull it out!
The cursed sword I reside in has memorized each of
your Star Platinum's powers, surpassing it in strength!
Just a bit further...
A-Are you serious?
Yes, of course!
I certainly am! Lord Dio will be pleased!
S-Stop... Don't push it any further...
I-I can't take any more...
I refuse to stop! I'll keep pushing until I tear your guts to shreds!
Ora!
W-What?!
I-I'm going to snap! I-I have to pull free!
Stop!
Ora!
So, what was that about tearing me to shreds?
I told him if he kept pushing it in, I wouldn't take any more.
Since the katana wasn't moving, it was an easy target.
Still, he was a tough enemy...
I barely pulled off that last move...
It took all the strength I had left...
I'm just glad that finished him before he could memorize it...
I've never been so drained from a fight before...
I need to find Gramps and Abdul quick...
W-What happened to me?
D-Don't tell me that cursed sword was controlling me...
Yeah... But it's over now.
Sorry...
Polnareff, go get Gramps and the others.
I'm too tired to walk.
It's shining...
I've memorized it...
The true user of Divine Anubis was the blacksmith
who forged this sword over five hundred years ago.
Now only his Stand remains, making me a Stand with no user.
Lord Dio pulled me from the darkness of a museum storeroom.
Lord Dio's Stand, The World,
is a Stand so powerful, I could never hope to defeat it.
This is why I have sworn my loyalty to him.
Jotaro, no matter what, I'll kill you!
I know all of your powers now.
You'll never see...
Here's a bandage.
...my ultimate speed coming!
Don't need it.
I'll stab you in the back!
Die, Jotaro!
W-What?!
Curses, I missed! I tripped over that dog!
Where did that dog come from?!
Oh, it's Iggy.
What's up with you? Eating candy now?
And right off the ground, too... you disgusting dog.
Th-That river...
It's the Nile!
N-No way, it can't be!
I'm gonna fall in the river at this rate!
I'm done for if I fall in the river! I'll rust away!
Someone stop me!
Yes! If I keep going in this direction, the wall will stop me!
Lucky!
What?!
Curses! I was so panicked, I accidentally phased through the wall!
I'm going to fall!
Yes! A boat appeared! I'm saved!
If I get stuck in the boat,
the boatman will be curious and try to pull me out!
Then I can take possession of him!
Once I control the boatman, I'll begin my counterattack on Jotaro!
There was a cow on board!
H-Hold on! Stop struggling! Hey!
Calm down, you dumb cow!
That's it! I'll possess the cow!
And then...
I won't make it in time!
Hey, look at that! That cow is freaking out about something.
Gimme a break. Who the fuck cares? Just go and get Gramps.
Help!
H-Hey, fishies. Come here for a moment!
Come on, please touch me!
Ah, wait! Where are you going?
Oh, Mr. Crab!
Please, just take me to the surface!
I'll get you something yummy to eat!
W-Wait! Don't leave me, Mr. Crab!
I'll rust over in a matter of days!
H-Help me!
Don't leave me!
I'm all alone!
Divine Anubis
Retires
Dumb dog.
What are you looking at?
There's nothing to eat over there.
Wha-
S-Shit!
What the hell are you eating to make your farts smell like that?!
Polnareff...
To think we missed all of that...
The Divine Anubis Stand, huh?
Must've been a rough one, Jotaro.
Yeah...
I'm never going out alone with him again.
Stop! Get off of me!
Cut it out already, you dumb dog!
S
Sta
Star
Star Pl
Star Plat
Star Platin
Ku
Star Platinum
Kujo
Kujo Jo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: A
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
Though these people may appear to be tourists,
this is only because there are several races living in Egypt.
This man is a typical Egyptian.
He's wearing the traditional jellabiya garment.
This man is a Nubian.
This is a man of the desert, a Bedouin.
And this man is Indian, having no relation to the rest.
Finally, this doesn't have much to do with race, but...
Hey! That chick's got some smokin' legs! What a babe!
I can't stop staring at her!
Like, bam! They just invite you to stare!
Next Episode
Mr. Joestar, what's wrong?
Something strange is going on...
What the hell are you doing, you dirty old man?!
Something really strange!
Men seem to enjoy touching things...
My body!
...even when they really shouldn't.
Episode 30
Mariah's Divine Bastet Part 1
This is it!