Th-This is bad!
Stay calm.
It's times like these when a man has to stay calm and collected.
It's a pain in the ass getting this stuff on
without my prosthetic hand.
Which of you have gone scuba diving before?
Nope.
I haven't.
High Priestess is still attacking from the next room!
Quickly, teach us how to scuba dive!
Don't panic, Abdul.
Above all, never panic.
That's the most important part of scuba diving.
When you're underwater, for every ten meters you go
below the surface, the pressure increases by one atmosphere.
There's one atmosphere of pressure on the surface.
We're forty meters below the surface right now,
so we'll endure five atmospheres of pressure.
If we try to surface right away,
our lungs and blood vessels will burst.
We'll have to ascend slowly to adjust.
We're near the Egyptian coast, so we'll go up along the sea floor.
Now...
...I'm gonna let the water in.
This is a regulator.
There's a valve inside that only lets in
air from the tank when you inhale.
When you exhale, your breath will come out of the left side.
What about our spit?
What happens if we get spit or phlegm in our mouths?
All of that will come out of the other side.
By the way, this should be obvious, but we can't talk underwater.
We'll use hand signals instead.
Let's keep things simple and use two.
When everything's fine, we'll use this to signal we're okay.
When things aren't good, signal this.
Mr. Joestar, given our abilities,
could we not simply use our Stands to speak underwater?
Good point...
Damn, I had the perfect hand signal I wanted to use.
Pantsu Maru Mie
I can see your underpants?
Yeah!
We're under attack and could die at any moment!
Quit messing around and let's go!
Soon this room will be filled with water.
Put on your mask and regulator.
P-Polnareff!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 24: High Priestess Part 2
W-When did it...
I-It transformed into a regulator!
A-Asshole...
That thing's gonna tear him apart from inside!
This is bad!
Hurry and drain the room!
It is too late for that!
It must have been waiting for this moment!
Ora!
F-Fuck!
It went inside Polnareff!
He will be torn to shreds!
W-What now?
Hierophant Green!
Hermit Purple!
H-Hey...
I caught it before it went down his throat, Kakyoin!
Likewise!
Let's force it out before it transforms!
We did it!
All right, keep it restrained.
Look! It is transforming once again!
A speargun! It transformed into a speargun!
Emerald Splash!
Silver Chariot!
Now!
It's reloading!
This is bad!
H-Hurry!
Gramps, hurry up!
I know, I know!
Th-That was close...
Don't relax just yet.
That freak knows how to hit us where it hurts.
Polnareff, are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
Everything's okay. You guys saved me.
Merci beaucoup.
The sea floor is so beautiful...
It would be nice to spend some leisure time here.
This is no time to be taking it easy.
We have to surface before we run out of oxygen.
Will it come after us?
I do not foresee that happening.
High Priestess can transform into metal and glass,
but it cannot become fish, water, nor sea foam.
Keep your eyes peeled.
If it follows us, it'll probably transform into a screw on our gear or something.
Watch out for moving stones and pebbles, too.
Look, a sea tunnel!
Our depth is seven meters.
We are finally at the Egyptian shore!
Swim along the rocks to the surface!
What?!
Th-This is...
The Stand! It was disguised as the seabed!
It is enormous!
W-We're being sucked into its mouth!
N-No way!
How is it so enormous?!
How is this thing so fucking huge?!
What kind of Stand power is this?!
It was so small earlier!
You boys are so slow!
Since rocks are made of minerals,
shouldn't it be obvious the seabed is made of minerals, too?
Her Stand is way more powerful now that it's near its user!
She must be close!
Correct!
I'm seven meters above, on the shore!
However, my High Priestess will grind you to a pulp,
so you'll never see my face. Never!
I-I wonder where inside the Stand we are...
We're still in the mouth.
It didn't suck us down its throat.
Hey, Jotaro!
Jotaro, you're just my type, so this is really hard on me.
It's too bad my Stand, High Priestess, has to digest you.
If only we had met under better circumstances. A pity.
Then again, Lord Dio will praise me if I kill you.
No hard feelings.
Gimme a break. Do I have to?
Say it! Come on, just hurry up and say it!
Say what?
I see...
Midler...
I would like to see your face just once.
You could be my type, too.
I might even fall for you.
I-I bet she's a real babe!
I can tell just from the sound of her voice!
Indeed. I envision her being an elegant woman.
I say this as a fortune teller.
Doesn't she sound like that actress, Audrey Hepburn?
If only I were thirty years younger...
You liars! You don't mean any of that!
I'll kill you!
Holy shit!
Everyone, look!
W-What is that?
I-It's a tongue!
It's the Stand's tongue! Look out! Be careful!
Jotaro!
She sent him flying!
T-Teeth! The molars!
Jotaro! Run!
You'll be crushed!
You wish to pit your strength against mine?
S-So strong...
Jotaro! These teeth are as hard as diamonds!
You'll never break them!
I'll kill you first!
Save Jotaro!
Stay out of my way!
It's the tongue again!
Magician's Red!
Th-This is bad!
Pull him out!
Jotaro!
Hi
High
High P
High Pri
High Prie
High Priest
High Prieste
High Priestess
Mi
Midl
Midle
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Midler
Jotaro!
J-Jotaro was crushed by its teeth...
J-Jotaro...
Is it too late?
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
No, wait. I can hear something.
It sounds rather distant...
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
It's getting closer...
Th-That voice...
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
The teeth! It's coming from inside the teeth!
Everyone, brace yourselves!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Even though they're as hard as diamonds, he broke out!
Oh my God!
He's not done!
He's smashing the other teeth!
Talk about overkill.
As usual, his Stand demonstrates immense power!
Hey, we're getting the hell outta here.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Gimme a break.
Well, it had hard teeth, but breaking them was a snap.
Looks like your diamonds were a little low on calcium.
That was awful...
Hey, there's a woman passed out over there.
It would appear to be High Priestess' user, Midler.
What should we do? Is she incapacitated?
Let's see if she really is a babe!
I like her style.
Let's see...
Well? Polnareff?
N-No comment...
Stop! Don't look!
Her teeth are fucked up! There's no reason to look!
Anyway, we have finally arrived in Egypt.
Indeed. In a jet, this trip would've taken twenty hours...
...but it took us thirty days.
We visited so many places.
Inside a brain, and then inside a dream.
A dream? What are you talking about, Kakyoin?
Hey, now, it's morning. Wake up already.
Oh, right. You guys don't know about that.
Well, whatever. Let's go.
Stands...
Mysterious, spiritual powers, symbolized by the Tarot.
"Around the World in 80 Days."
Tojirare teta toki ni
Within the confines of time
Joseph Joestar once described their journey in that way.
Traveling from Tokyo to Hong Kong,
they encountered Tower of Gray.
Hi no hikari abiseru no wa dareda
The light of the sun shines upon them
On their way to Singapore by sea,
they encountered Dark Blue Moon and Strength.
Mirai nokosu kibou
They carry with them hope for the future
In Singapore, they encountered Ebony Devil and Yellow Temperance.
Nagareru boshi no Crusaders
The Starlight Crusaders
In Calcutta, India, it was Hanged Man and Emperor.
In Varanasi, India, Empress.
Kakeru no wa inochi
They would wager their lives
Near the Pakistani border, Wheel of Fortune.
Mamorubeki ai to
To protect those that they love
Card wa kuba rareta
Using the Tarot cards they were dealt
In the mountains of Pakistan, Justice.
In Karachi, Pakistan, Lovers.
In the deserts of the United Arab Emirates, Sun.
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up tachihadakaru
Stand up, stand up, stand up, to those that stand in your way
In Saudi Arabia, Death 13.
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now teki wo taoshi
All right now, all right now, all right now, show them no mercy
On a small island in the Red Sea, Judgement.
And now, on the floor of the Red Sea, High Priestess.
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down michi wo hiraku
Break you down, break you down, break you down, carve out your own path
After defeating many of Dio's assassins,
they have finally arrived in Egypt!
Tamashi no Vision Stand Proud!
May your spirit's vision Stand Proud!
Only two of the Tarot Cards remain.
However, Jojo and company are still unaware of the dangers that await them.
That's...
One, two, three... nine.
Nine of them? Men and women...
Huh?
What... was that?
Have the flies swarming nearby been eliminated?
The Speedwagon Foundation...
I can't let my guard down for even a moment. I swear...
I've grown quite used to this body.
Do you feel it, Jonathan?
Your descendants are approaching.
It's so very cruel...
This world of ours...
Oh, is that so? So Jotaro is helping you with work?
How marvelous!
This kid's still got a long way to go.
So, is your work that important?
Yeah. This is a really important job.
There's no room for error.
But if we're working together, we'll get it done.
Say, Joseph... Could I speak to Jotaro?
Sure, but what about?
Not much.
Is it so wrong that I want to hear my darling grandson's voice?
N-No...
Jotaro...
It's me.
I have high hopes for you, Jotaro!
Do your best. Take care of your grandfather for me.
Sure.
I'm sure if you Joestar men work together,
you can overcome any hardship.
I'm absolutely sure of it.
Grandma Suzi, you...
Hmm? What's the matter?
You sound so serious all of a sudden.
Never mind.
All right, I'm hanging up.
I look forward to hearing good news. Ciao!
Madam...
It has been thirty years now that I've worked for the Joestar family.
B-But this is the first time something like this has...
Oh, you're overreacting.
It's just a business trip, isn't it?
W-Well...
It's so troublesome when men act selfish.
But I'm used to it by now.
The Joestar family has been like this for a century.
I'm sure she'd agree, and laugh it off.
What's the matter, Jotaro?
It's nothing.
All right, let's go!
The ties our family has held to Dio for a century...
...will finally be brought to an end by us Joestars!
It won't be just us.
Hey, Mr. Joestar!
We got a dune buggy!
Let's get a move on!
We need to leave before it gets dark!
Gramps...
For sure, we're pretty lucky.
If you don't hurry up, we'll leave you behind!
All right, we're coming!
Egypt, a nation composed of 97% desert.
But, thanks to the blessings of the Nile,
beautiful, fertile green spreads all the way down its river banks.
It is a country fabricated from ancient Egyptian civilization,
together with Persian, Greek, Roman, Islamic, and Arabian cultures.
What adventures await Jotaro and company on their journey through this eternal land?
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Egypt Arc