W-What the hell happened here?
It looks like someone went through this room
with a giant hole punch...
W-Why?
The destruction goes on into the next room.
Abdul and the others must have encountered an enemy.
Jotaro! Bust the door down!
Sure.
Ora!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
So long, Iggy.
Episode 44: The Desolate Void: Vanilla Ice Part 3
Polnareff... It is not by your hand that I bleed...
It is Abdul's.
Earlier, I was ready to eradicate you and Abdul at once...
...but he knocked you out of the way.
Abdul betrayed his instincts, protecting you rather than himself.
That is why I bleed...
Despite my grave injuries, I am in no immediate danger of dying.
I swear I will destroy the remains of Joestar's group!
I will eradicate them, without fail!
Iggy... didn't I tell you not to use your Stand...
...and to quit it with the tough guy act?
How many times... do I have to say it?
Polnareff!
Vanilla Ice proclaimed that a mere dog could possess neither resolve...
...nor a proud soul.
However, a Stand is the manifestation of one's soul!
Iggy's soul moved of its own accord!
There was no choice to be made!
I-I can feel it in the sand...
Why is this happening? Dammit!
It's an empty shell. The empty shell of a Stand...
This cold feeling can only mean one thing...
Dammit! Why couldn't it have been me?
I-
Iggy!
Too slow, Vanilla Ice!
But you were right earlier...
My friendships never end well.
I was supposed to save Iggy, but he saved me instead.
Goddammit...
Why did this happen?
I was even starting to like him a little...
This happens every time...
It never hits me until it's too late...
I thought you were just a stubborn fucking dog...
...but I respected your tenacity, even though you were never friendly.
At first I thought it was because you felt superior to everyone else,
but it was really just your pride keeping you from showing any affection.
I told you not to save me...
Dammit! If it weren't for your stubbornness...
I knew it. Vanilla Ice, you bastard...
I knew something was up.
You're immortal.
Did Dio do this to you?
W-What's... happening?!
Didn't you notice the changes happening in your body?
You received his blood.
You're just like the monsters I used to read about.
You're just like Dio.
A soulless fucking vampire!
You wretch!
It seems like you started to transform
right around when I stabbed you in the throat.
Come on!
Let's see how determined you are now!
Are you still determined to protect Dio?
Come at me! I'm right here!
What's wrong, Vanilla Ice? Come on!
You will not...
Go to hell.
A-Abdul! I-Iggy!
A-Am I seeing things?
Or was that...
Either way, I need to climb these stairs...
...and finally face Dio.
This is no time to be shedding tears of sorrow.
Abdul and Iggy have died
Th
The
The F
The Foo
The Fool
I
Ig
Power: B
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: D
Growth Potential: C
Iggy
Japan!
Forty-three days have passed since Jojo and company first departed.
Please pull over, Roses.
You can stop the car here.
Soba
Soba Midokoro
Please, Madam... Must we really stop for a soba stand?
Of course!
I haven't been to Japan in ages!
I need a little something to eat before visiting my daughter!
Would you be a darling and hold Turtlekins for me?
You mustn't, Madam!
Because this place caters to men, Japanese customs dictate that a lady such as you must not eat here!
It simply isn't the place for you.
Enough of that!
I'm taking a commemorative video to mark the occasion!
Yes, yes!
This poverty-stricken atmosphere is simply marvelous!
No Vomiting
or Urinating
Mr. Roses...
Have you told the Madam of Ms. Holly's condition yet?
Come on, Roses! Come, come!
I-I'll be right there...
I... I have not.
She came to Japan under the impression that
Ms. Holly only has mild pneumonia.
I've served the Joestar family these past thirty years...
Ever since Ms. Holly was in grade school...
I know I should have told her the truth...
But... I lack the courage.
We arrived in Japan before I had the chance to tell her...
Ms. Holly is at her limit.
She will only survive a few more days at best.
I can tell the Madam if you like.
N-No... I've been lying to the Madam about Ms. Holly for too long.
I must tell her myself.
Is it true that she may be cured
if that man named Dio is defeated?
Yes, if he is defeated.
Ms. Holly's body is reacting to an energy
few can perceive known as a Stand, and it is overwhelming her.
This malicious energy is coming from a man known as Dio.
The Madam cannot see Stands...
...but when she encounters the shadow of death, she will sense it.
You must tell Madam Joestar at once.
Sh-Shadow of death?
Hey, Roses! What are you doing?
You simply must try this curry udon!
M-Madam, there is something you must know...
Oh! I simply must film this
vending machine that serves peculiar drinks!
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
Family
Planning
Premium Condoms
It's simply marvelous! Care to try one, Roses?
M-Madam, please stop! Those are not drinks!
P-Please listen, Madam!
Huh? What is it?
Th-The truth is, Ms. Holly...
This Japanese man is so cool!
Simply marvelous!
Hello! Hello! Give me smile!
What the fuck?
Who the fuck said you could film me?
Madam, get back in the car!
Yay!
Come back, you bitch! Don't fuck with me!
Gimme that camera!
Who the hell do you think you are, you worthless hag?
Do I gotta make you bleed, ya dusty hag? Well?!
Hey, that's enough!
Don't you dare lay a finger on the Madam!
Madam, you must remember the customs of Japan!
Fine...
I... I still haven't the heart to tell her
Ms. Holly only has a few days left...
I can't bear to see the Madam miserable and in shock...
We've come all this way, yet I still cannot tell her...
We're almost at the Kujo household...
I must tell her now...
I must be the one to tell her!
Roses, I can tell you've been trying to tell me something...
I know what's been troubling you this entire time.
My daughter's life is in peril, isn't it?
When I called from New York, she sounded so cheerful and strong.
She told me it was just a mild cold...
Joseph also insisted he was doing fine, and that he was just busier than usual.
Yet somehow I knew...
My husband and daughter were in peril.
I've lived with the man for fifty years,
and bore him his daughter.
I was terrified...
Terrified to learn the truth...
I wanted to visit my daughter so badly,
but I was frightened to actually see her once I got to Japan.
Since this is out in the open, allow me to elaborate.
Ms. Holly's survival greatly depends on the next several days.
Mr. Joestar and the others went to Egypt
to address the source of her illness, but...
...we have yet to hear back from them.
Please forgive me for not telling you, Madam...
There was nothing we could do for Ms. Holly, and it hurts...
It's too cruel!
What kind of nonsense are you prattling on about, Roses?
There's only one thing we can do for Holly right now.
Holly...
Mom...
Roses, listen carefully...
The only thing that will help my daughter now is having faith.
I don't know all of the details, but I have faith.
If Joseph and Jotaro are doing their best to save my daughter,
then I have complete faith in them.
Ever since I met that man in Italy fifty years ago,
he hasn't let me down once.
Once his mind is made up,
he will follow through, no matter what.
Have faith in Jotaro and Joseph.
Get better, and we can be a family together again.
Mom...
Madam... Ms. Holly...
S
Sta
Star
Star Pl
Star Plat
Star Platin
Ku
Star Platinum
Kujo
Kujo Jo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: A
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
Vanilla Ice, Kenny G., D'Arby the younger...
The three of you were so stupid!
It makes me laugh knowing those jerks
got what was coming to them!
Calling me "Nimrod" like I'm some moron...
At least I didn't get myself killed!
Nimrod, it is impossible for you to defeat Joestar and the others with your powers.
Stay here.
H-Hey... Let me in on the action, too!
You are nothing more than a vampire.
Just try and interfere! We'll kill you if you do!
Don't go anywhere, Nimrod.
I'll be the one to finish off Jotaro!
Wait! There's something up ahead!
It's a woman...
P-Please spare me!
Don't drink my blood! Please don't drink my blood!
I'll do whatever you want! So please, spare my life!
H-Hey, wait a second... Calm down.
I promise I won't run away again! So please... spare my life!
Calm down!
We're not Dio's minions, and we're definitely not vampires!
We're friends! We'll help you, so calm down already!
Friends?
Friends? A-Are you really my friends?
You're really going to help me?
Sure. We're friends...
Friends of justice, that is.
That's right, we'll help you!
Help you find your way to hell!
Right, Kakyoin?
I-Impossible! W-Why? Why?!
How did they figure it out?!
My power is infallible!
Your "infallible power" is having the face of a woman on the back of your head?
You could have turned your hands around at the very least.
Th-That's right!
I didn't realize... Dammit!
Hey, nimrod.
Where's Dio's room? Tell me.
Jotaro, don't knock him out. He can guide us there.
Why, you...
You called me "Nimrod!" Don't mess with me!
I'll kill you!
I am immortal, for the blood of Lord Dio flows within my body!
Oh? Are you telling me I can't kill you?
I guess you're a vampire like Dio.
So, let's see how immortal you really are.
Oh my God!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Neat, so it's true.
But even a vampire can be cut to pieces.
Come on, you're leading us to Dio. The sun's going down.
Okay... But I have a question for you...
How did you know those guys called me "Nimrod"?
Gimme a break...
These curtains are made of pretty nice cloth...
This should make it easier for me to move and jump around.
It still hurts like hell,
but I can't give up or think about the pain.
Polnareff... I've been waiting.
Dio.
It's about time.
Next Episode
It's about time, Dio!
He brings back nothing but bad memories.
I have no regrets.
I-I'll tell you exactly what happened!
We're in trouble... We're in big trouble!
When did he call out his Stand?
You have one more chance.
Episode 45
Dio's World Part 1