Before we start the game, I'd like to test something.
Shuffle up those cards.
They're shuffled.
What now?
It doesn't matter which one...
...but choose a card and memorize it.
Don't show it to me.
I've chosen.
Let me guess, six of hearts?
Now I'll tell you every card from the top.
Five of spades, queen of diamonds, jack of spades, ace of hearts...
...seven of diamonds, six of clubs, king of clubs, two of diamonds.
He knew them all!
But D'Arby was the one who shuffled the cards!
How did you know?
I could keep going and tell you every card from top to bottom.
My Star Platinum kept track of
how he ordered the cards as he shuffled.
What an interesting development.
However, so long as I avoid letting your Star Platinum
watch me shuffle the cards, nothing will come of it.
Don't you get it?
You need to be smarter about cheating against me.
Consider this your only warning.
Good.
Episode 35: D'Arby the Gambler Part 2
The security seal.
An unbroken security seal proves that
a pack of cards has never been tampered with.
Just one joker.
All the cards are in order.
They're normal playing cards.
I've passed page 538...
I'm at page 540- No... Page 556.
I'm at the top of my game today.
I know which page I'm at from the feel alone.
Jotaro's Star Platinum may have impressive eyes...
...but they are no match for my nimble fingers.
Even once I've shuffled, I can tell where each card is located.
Okay, open the game!
Ten of hearts.
Seven of clubs.
Then it's my deal.
Star Platinum shouldn't be able to see me shuffle from this angle...
Go ahead and cut.
Time to deal.
One for Jotaro...
...and me.
W-What is this? What happened?
Jotaro, his finger!
Your Star Platinum broke D'Arby's finger!
Like I said...
He has to be smarter if he wants to cheat against me.
Cheating? When? He was just dealing the cards!
He did not make any suspicious movements!
You're wrong.
Give the cards in his hand a good look.
The second card is sticking out!
He was just about to deal me that card.
He started off dealing them in order,
then tried to give me the second card from the top.
In effect...
...he wanted to deal himself the card on top.
That card would have given him three tens!
This technique is known as "second dealing."
It takes advantage of the assumption
that a deck of cards will be dealt from the top.
In short, this advanced technique allows for
the dealer to deal the second card from the top.
When pulled off by the nimble fingers of a professional,
it is nearly impossible for a normal person to notice.
And needless to say, this is D'Arby,
a man capable of memorizing the position of each card!
You violent brute! My finger...
No, I was too gentle. You're lucky I didn't tear it off.
Gimme a break. I can't even trust you to shuffle cards.
Let's get someone else to deal.
That kid on the hill can do it.
Good.
Abdul, can you go get him?
Certainly.
I'm impressed...
A good cheater knows to take advantage
of psychological blind spots.
Impressive eyes aren't enough to catch me cheating.
I underestimated your ability
to see through my second dealing.
My broken finger will serve as a reminder of this...
I will do everything in my power
to defeat you at this game, Jotaro.
This happens to be my biggest game since May 17th, 1986.
On that day, I won eight properties from a Japanese man
named Mayama Shozo, along with his pitiful soul.
He was a rich man, and a skilled gambler.
I am not competing against you for the sake of Lord Dio!
I am competing against you because I was born to gamble!
W-What are you doing with
Mr. Joestar and Polnareff's souls?!
I've divided their souls into six chips each.
If you believe your cards are no match
for your opponent's in poker, you may fold.
However, you must be able to ante up enough chips to participate in a hand, and two will not be enough.
Once you have collected six identical chips, they will make up a complete soul.
Sound good?
With that said, Jotaro...
I will give you your six chips if you still wish to bet, but...
...I must hear you utter those magic words.
Fine, I'll bet my soul.
Good!
Jotaro...
These snow-white chips will represent your soul.
Once I have taken those six chips from you...
...your soul will be mine.
Div
Divine
Divine Os
Divine Osir
D
Divine Osiris
Da
Dani
Danie
Daniel
Daniel J
Daniel J.
Daniel J. D'
Power: E
Speed: D
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Daniel J. D'A
Daniel J. D'Ar
Daniel J. D'Arby
My opening ante will be a single Polnareff chip.
Let's begin!
Poker!
Once every player has been dealt five cards, they each get
one chance to exchange them to help strengthen their hand.
With high stakes added to the mix,
it can become quite a fierce psychological battle!
I'm going to exchange two cards.
Jotaro, your soul is represented by a mere six chips.
I would advise you to consider your next moves carefully.
Boy, do not worry if you are unable to understand what is going on right now.
Everything is fine.
Shuffle and deal as you normally would.
I'm exchanging three cards.
My, my, that's quite a frightening glare!
Did you manage to get a good hand?
Should I play it safe and bet only one Polnareff chip?
Call.
If neither of them folds,
they will need to play at least three chips each...
Good. Show your hand, Jotaro!
Two pair, nines over eights.
How unfortunate.
Two pair, queens over jacks.
What a close call! I nearly lost that one.
Now if you don't mind...
O-Only three chips remain...
J-Jotaro...
Next game. Deal.
Not only will this be our next game, it will also be our last.
I'm exchanging one card.
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Look at your cards and decide if you will exchange any of them!
Jotaro?
These cards...
...are good enough.
Um... What did you just say?
I must be going deaf.
I couldn't have heard you say they are good enough.
You heard right. They're good enough.
I'm going with these cards.
I heard you the first time!
What I really want to know is why you are using those cards without even looking at them!
They're good enough.
Quit fooling around! Answer me!
Why would you use cards
you haven't so much as glanced at?!
By the way, Abdul, I need a favor from you.
Favor?
I-I understand what you mean,
b-but why have you chosen not to look at your cards?
I said answer me, Jotaro!
In addition to my last three chips...
...I'll raise you Abdul's soul!
Wh-
What?!
D'Arby, you are a man who naturally keeps his cool.
Each and every move you make is calculated.
It is why you are such a powerful opponent
without resorting to violence.
I am not a man suited for gambling,
as my emotions tend to cloud my judgement.
I would surely lose against you.
However, I believe in Jotaro!
Although I am unsure what these unseen cards hold,
I will allow Jotaro to gamble my soul since I believe in him!
Even if it means my soul is at stake!
How about that...
The two of you have clearly become
overwhelmed by the tension in the air.
Boy!
I told you I'm exchanging one card! Make it quick!
O-Okay...
Mr. D'Arby, I did what you told me to...
I gave the Japanese guy
worthless cards he can't do anything with.
My technique always works.
You'll beat him. I know you will.
I'm sure Jotaro still believes this boy is nothing more
than an innocent bystander who has no stake in this, but...
...not only is everyone in this café working for me,
so is everyone within eyeshot of it.
Including the owner and all of these men.
I will win no matter who deals!
As per my instructions, Jotaro's cards are worthless.
When I realized he was so audacious as to
not even look at his cards, I began to panic...
But it's a bluff! How dare he try bluffing against me.
Does he think I'll fold? What a fool.
Very well.
I'll call with my three chips of yours and all six Polnareff chips.
But in addition...
...I'll raise you all six of Joestar's chips!
That brings the total to fifteen!
W-What did you say? Wait just a moment!
Jotaro has no more chips left to gamble with!
Oh, really? I believe he does.
What do you mean?
I merely require his legally binding
consent in case he happens to lose.
My Stand will take care of the rest.
What do you mean by this?!
You have the soul of the hospitalized Kakyoin, do you not?
What?!
Yes, feel the anxiety! Let it consume your morale!
I want to see his cool facade crumble before my eyes!
How dare you try to bluff the great D'Arby!
I won't be satisfied until I see
your poker face contort with sheer terror!
Fine.
I'll bet Kakyoin's soul, too.
J-Jotaro!
You cannot gamble his soul before he has agreed to it!
Have I gone too far?
Hey, Jotaro! What was that just now?
What was what? What the hell are you talking about?
You just lit a cig-
Something wrong? Don't feel good?
Th-This man...
His confidence! Could it be...
Did he use his Star Platinum
to switch out his cards while I wasn't looking?
I, Kujo Jotaro, bet the soul of my friend,
Kakyoin Noriaki, and will relinquish it if I lose. - Kujo Jotaro
Y-You stupid brat!
Don't cast that worried look in my direction!
If they figure out I hired you,
you won't live to see another day!
Dammit!
I have four kings in my hand...
The only hands able to beat mine are four aces,
a straight flush, and five of a kind with the joker.
Four Aces
Straight Flush
Five of a Kind
There is only one way Jotaro could have one of those hands,
and that is if he switched all five of his cards...
Star Platinum may be fast, but could it really have switched out
not just one, but all five of his cards under my watchful eye?
Of course not! How absurd!
I refuse to believe he could switch out
all of his cards under my watchful eye!
Fine, Jotaro! How about we finally finish this?
How dare you try to pull a bluff on me with that cigarette!
N-N-Now you have a drink?! When did you...
Y-You cur! How dare you!
Very well, I'll show you my hand!
My cards-
Hold it.
I haven't raised you yet.
Wha-
Raise?! You have nothing left to be-
I'll raise you my mother's soul.
What?!
Your mother?! Jotaro, Ms. Holly's soul?!
The reason I came to Egypt in the first place
was to save my mother's soul.
If she knew I needed to bet her soul to save her,
she wouldn't hesitate.
But D'Arby, this means you need to bet
something of equal value in return.
And that's...
...revealing the secret of Dio's Stand!
His reaction... It must mean...
...he knows the secret of Dio's Stand!
But anyone who betrays Dio will perish...
If he says so much as a word about it,
D'Arby's life will be in grave danger.
Jotaro... Your confidence comes from
knowing you will win for sure, yes?
Can I really trust you?
Are your cards actually good enough, Jotaro?!
Well? Call or fold? Call or fucking fold?
What's it gonna be, D'Arby?
I have to say it!
I have to!
I'm the greatest gambler in the world!
I'll take the bet! I'll call!
Call... Call... Call... Call...
I'm going to call!
Ca-
I-I can't! I'm petrified with fear! I can't speak!
I'm so frightened, I c-c-can't even speak!
I-I can't... I can't breathe...
He... p-passed out!
He passed out standing up!
He got so nervous, he passed out.
Mr. Joestar and Polnareff's souls are returning!
You saved them!
He knew deep down he had lost.
That's why he finally admitted defeat and released their souls.
F-Four of a kind!
H-He had four of a kind with kings!
J-Jotaro, was your hand actually that good?
I-I knew it...
The cards I dealt him were worthless!
Even Star Platinum couldn't cheat against someone like D'Arby.
Good thing I scared him into folding...
...because that hand was fucking worthless.
Gimme a break.
Knowing that would have scared the shit out of me.
S-Scared you?
Jotaro, did you really gamble our souls
with such worthless cards?!
It looks as though the rest of his collection has also been freed.
Come on, guys! Let's play mahjong together!
Backgammon and dice games are also pretty thrilling!
Too bad I'll beat you all!
D'Arby and Divine Osiris retire
D'Arby and Divine Osiris retire!
It appears we will not be able to divulge Dio's secret from him...
Yeah. He was pretty tough, though.
Nearly beat the four of us by himself.
He really was something.
He truly was a terrifying man.
Ugh... What the hell happened?
We really got gypped this time...
Next Episode
My daughter's condition has gotten worse.
When I said, "And?", I was asking to hear about you...
Yer too weak to fight 'em yerself? Bullshit!
Fate will not allow it, indeed.
You saved my life!
Boingo an' Hol Horse, the invincible duo!
Episode 36
Hol Horse and Boingo Part 1