— 1983: The Canary Islands, Off the Northwest African Coast —
W-We did it!
We finally got it!
It's been lost for a hundred years, but now the treasure is ours!
All right, careful now!
Keep calm! Just bring it this way...
I got it! I got it!
Up we go.
Isn't it a bit long for a treasure chest?
Hey! You're lifting it too high!
Okay, I'm setting it down!
One, two, three!
Yes! Pry it open, quick!
Wait. How bizarre...
This box is locked from the inside.
Who gives a shit? Bust it open!
H-Hold on! There's something engraved here.
D-I-O... Dio.
Is it a name?
Do you think anyone gives a damn?!
The sun is about to set!
Once it gets dark, it'll be impossible to see how to get it open!
Yeah, good point!
Right! Let me go grab the blowtorch!
Get ready to say hello to treasure!
One day, an unmanned cruiser was sighted.
The boat was in perfect working order,
and there was no indication of an attack.
However, the only signs of life on board
were three half-full cups of coffee...
And...
An acetylene blowtorch.
It had been used to open the steel box on deck.
The box was empty, but it is believed to have
sheltered something inside its two compartments.
Some believed it contained treasure,
but after a few months, it was entirely forgotten.
Kujo Jotaro, Seventeen years old.
Height: 195 centimeters.
His father is a Japanese jazz musician.
— 1987: Japan —
He's currently on tour.
His mother is an American of British descent.
That's him. Jotaro is my son.
Apparently his friends at school took the "Jo" from Kujo...
...and the "Jo" from Jotaro to nickname him Jojo.
What a riot!
S-So...
How many people did Jotaro kill?!
Don't tell me! I don't want to hear it! No!
Uh, who told you he killed anyone?
He just got into a little scrap.
Actually, the thugs he faced were armed with nunchucks and knives.
There were four of them, including a former boxer,
and your son managed to break fifteen bones between them all.
Their balls were crushed and...
...Pardon my language...
They were sent to the hospital.
Ma'am, please make sure he learns his lesson!
Okay!
But the real problem is what happened after.
Could you copy this and pass it around?
Yes, sir.
Your son is quite the oddball.
Come in. We'll show you the way.
I'm grateful.
Well, anyway, please take him home.
What? He's being released already?
We can't keep him forever.
By the way, ma'am, your Japanese is very good.
How long have you lived in Japan?
Twenty years.
Ah, no wonder.
Good work.
We've had our hands full lately.
There's even a waiting list for our cells.
Your son is just up ahead.
Jotaro!
Jotaro, throw the ball to Mama!
Very good!
Do your best at the sports meet tomorrow!
Okay!
Jotaro...
We should celebrate.
What would you like to eat today?
Mom, all I want is to eat your cooking.
Jotaro... Jotaro...
Jotaro!
Shut the hell up!
Don't be such a pain, woman!
Okay!
He's actually a very sweet child!
Episode 1: The Man Possessed by an Evil Spirit
He would never do something so awful!
Hey! Don't fall asleep, Kujo!
You're being released. Get out!
What part of "go home" don't you understand?!
Mom, go home.
I'll be hanging out here for a while.
I've been possessed by an evil spirit.
I have no idea what it could make me do.
Even during that fight, it took all I had to stop it.
So you better not let me out of this cell...
For crying out loud, Ma'am! Do you see what I mean?
We're trying to release him, but he refuses to leave.
Forgive my asking, but is your son well in the head?
This isn't some hotel!
Please! Let us change cells!
He's telling the truth!
There really is an evil spirit possessing him!
It's terrifying!
We'll never do bad things again!
That's enough! Quiet down!
W-What is that?
You're behind bars!
How the hell did you get that?
I already told you.
It's the evil spirit.
The evil spirit brings things to me.
H-He's reading Shounen Jump while listening to his boombox!
H-How?! Th-This ain't good!
This isn't good at all!
Hold it!
I doubt this will be enough to stop you from releasing me.
I'll show you just how frightening the evil spirit can be.
Then maybe you'll understand why it's such a bad idea to let me loose.
H-He took my gun!
W-We've got trouble!
Hey officers, did you finally see it? That's the evil spirit.
If you didn't, then...
J-Jotaro!
There's something behind me...
It must have just recently possessed me.
His grandfather, Joseph, has strange powers, too...
W-What's happening to my son?
Ku
Kujo
Kujo Jo
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
Papa!
Over here, Papa! Over here!
Holly! Hey, move it!
Papa!
I'm so glad you came!
If my only daughter needs my help...
I can be anywhere in the world within 24 hours!
Where's Mama?
She complained...
But I told Suzi it was a business trip
for the Joestar real estate agency.
Papa...
Holly... Holly...
Hey, Holly! Get off me already!
No! It's been forever since you last held me!
Look, you...
How can a 45 year-old woman talk like that?
Oh, now you've done it! It's tickling time!
Hey! Cut it out!
What the hell are you people gawking at?!
Mama...
Don't look!
I'll take your bag.
By the way, Holly, about Jotaro...
You're certain he said "evil spirit"?
What's happened to you, Jotaro?
That's right. The policemen said they couldn't see it, but I saw it clearly.
I saw a separate arm...
And it grabbed the gun!
The others couldn't see it, but you could?
Yes...
So Jotaro says that he's been possessed recently,
but nothing strange has happened to you?
Not to me. But Jotaro says he won't leave the cell
until he knows what's going on.
Papa, what should I do?
There, there, my beloved daughter.
There's nothing to worry about when Joseph Joestar is here!
Yeah.
Let's hurry up and see him...
My grandson, Jotaro!
H-How terrifying!
That thing brought him even more stuff...
And it's violent...
That thing possessing him is horrifying.
I-If the general public caught wind of this,
I'd lose my job in a heartbeat!
Don't worry. I'll be taking my grandson home.
"Grandson"?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
I told you, this is as far as you'll go!
Convince him from over here! It's dangerous!
It's fine, now move it! Leave him to me.
We can't be held responsible for this! Y-You...
Hey, outta the way!
Jotaro! It's your grandfather!
I'm sure he'll be able to help you!
Please come out with your grandfather!
Get out. We're going home.
Get lost.
Nobody asked you to be here.
You think you'll help me? What the hell can you do?
Sorry you got dragged here all the way from New York,
but you won't be able to help me.
Th-The pinky from my prosthetic hand!
When did he take it?
You see? Do you finally get it?
It's the evil spirit.
Don't get too close.
You'll only shorten the little life you have left.
H-How can this be? I don't believe it...
It was able to deceive me right off the bat...
Yes... I know exactly what Jotaro's evil spirit is.
But rather than explaining it with words,
if I make him experience the truth himself...
...he'll get a better grasp of it.
No, the real reason he needs to physically understand it...
...is to face the dangers that lie ahead for him!
Abdul, you're up.
This is my friend of three years from Egypt...
Abdul!
Force my grandson Jotaro out of this cell.
Don't even try.
He looks strong, but do you really think I'd let
someone force me out of here just because you said so?
No way in hell.
I'll just want to stay even longer if he tries to force me out.
This will require a bit of violence.
Soon enough he will be in such pain,
he will squeal, "Please get me out of here."
Whatever it takes.
Papa, what are you doing?
H-Hey, you can't-
Be quiet!
Yes, sir!
That's...
Yes, Abdul also has a so-called "evil spirit."
An evil spirit he can freely control!
The evil spirit's name is...
Magician's Red!
I-It's hot! The fire! I'm burning!
My arms are burning!
W-What is this evil spirit?
Kujo's thrown himself against the wall and won't move!
This doesn't make sense!
A-And isn't it getting a bit...
How is it that hot?!
That's insane! It's way too hot!
Oh, there it is! It's finally revealed itself!
And the fact that it's so clearly visible means it's very powerful!
Why you...
I cannot believe he is able to manifest it so vividly!
I'm surprised you got an evil spirit, too.
And Gramps, the identity of the evil spirit...
I know of it.
Mr. Joestar, you asked me to get your grandson out of the cell.
I was planning on holding back...
...but we are in grave danger from how strong it is.
Shall I stop?
If you continue to insist I get him out, it will require using enough force to send your grandson to the hospital.
So be it. Give it a shot.
Yes, sir!
Red Bind!
This is...
There's so much heat!
I don't have a clue what's happening!
Papa! What are you doing to Jotaro?!
Holly, be a good girl and keep quiet.
Okay?
I-I can't breathe...
The evil spirit's withdrawing.
If your breathing is restricted, your evil spirit will weaken.
I'll tell you the truth!
Despite appearances, it is not an evil spirit!
Jotaro, what you believed was an evil spirit is actually a being created from your life energy; a kind of powerful vision!
Because it stands beside you, we have a special name for this vision!
A Stand!
A Stand?
As it is told in Aesop's Fables...
The cold wind only made the traveler pull his coat on tight,
but the heat made him admit defeat.
Do you want to come out of your cell now, Jojo?
Enough of this shit.
The reason I refuse to leave is because
I keep harming others without realizing it.
It's interesting you got an evil spirit, too.
But if you keep doing this shit...
...I'll kill you.
He smashed the toilet!
Th-That's destruction of property!
I warned you.
Bastard!
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Hey!
Why'd you suddenly turn your back on me?
Turn and face me!
Mr. Joestar...
As you can see, I have forced him from the cell, but...
Are you saying you let me win?
Not exactly.
It truly was my intent to send you to the hospital,
but I did not expect you to be so strong.
If I hadn't stopped this steel rod, what would you have done?
My Stand is Magician's Red.
It could melt a steel rod like this in midair with ease.
Abdul has the same power as you.
You don't need to stay in that cell to
research your evil spirit any longer.
Ma
Magi
Magic
Magici
Magician
Magician's
Magician's R
Magician's Re
Mo
Magician's Red
Moha
Moham
Mohamme
Mohammed
Mohammed A
Mohammed Ab
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: D
Mohammed Abd
Mohammed Abdu
Mohammed Abdul
Oh, thank goodness!
Jotaro finally came out of his cell!
You're such a pain, woman.
Okay!
Hey, you punk!
How dare you speak to your mother like that!
And Holly, don't smile after he insults you!
Okay!
Gramps, just one thing...
There's just one thing I don't understand.
Why did you know about my evil spirit...
no... my Stand or whatever it's called?
That's what I don't understand.
Very well.
I came here from New York to let you know what's happening.
But to properly explain it, I must start from the beginning.
It has to do with the Joestar family.
Take a look at these pictures.
What is this?
It's a one-hundred-year-old coffin, pulled up from
the Atlantic Ocean off the coast of Africa four years ago.
Coffin?
I did some research after it came into my possession...
I discovered that four generations before you, my grandfather,
Jonathan Joestar, died on the ship where this coffin was hidden.
Apparently it was empty by the time they discovered it.
But I know exactly what was inside!
Abdul and I are trying to discover where he is.
He? Hold on...
"He" makes it sound like you're talking about a living person.
How could something lost at sea for a hundred years be alive?
Because he is evil incarnate!
His name is Dio!
He has awoken from his hundred-year sleep.
It is our fate to do battle with him!
The hell was that, Jotaro?!
Don't give me that face like this has nothing to do with you!
This face means,
"That was so stupid, I don't know what to say," old timer.
O-Old timer?!
Abdul, was it?
We just met, but you act like you're above me.
And Gramps...
Do you expect me to eat up an unbelievable story like that?
But would you not have found that our evil spirits are equally as unbelievable?
Well, whatever.
Sooner or later, you'll have to believe me.
If you're curious how I know of Dio's existence...
...and why exactly I'm going after him...
I'll show you!
Actually, about a year ago, I also suddenly obtained an evil spirit, or rather, the power of a Stand!
What was that?
Gramps, what did you-
I'll show you! My Stand's...
...powerful ability!
Did you see?
The thorns that came from my hand? That was my Stand!
It has the powerful ability to take spirit photos of visions I've captured from far away places!
Though every time I do it, I have to destroy a 30,000 yen camera in the process!
Good sir, is something the matter?
It is fine. Please leave.
Right...
The vision that will appear in this picture, Jotaro...
...will be what determines your fate!
What?
Jotaro, Holly... Have either of you ever taken a close look at the back of your necks?
What are you getting at?
I doubt you've ever bothered to look closely...
...but right around the base of my neck,
there is a star-shaped birthmark.
Again, what the fuck are you getting at?
I asked my mother about it, and she said that my father,
who died when I was young, also had it.
Apparently those belonging to the Joestar bloodline
all have this star-shaped birthmark.
Hey, Gramps...
What the hell is gonna show up on that film?
This is our undiscovered destiny!
Dammit, just show me what the hell is on it already!
Papa...
Dio!
He has consistently shown up on all of my spirit photos!
And on the back of his neck...
From this asshole's neck down...
...is the body of my grandfather, Jonathan Joestar,
which he's doing hell knows what with!
A hundred years ago,
there was an incident on the Atlantic.
My grandmother Erina is the one who told me about it.
But needless to say, Dio took possession of my grandfather's body and survived!
And there's one thing I'm certain of...
That son of bitch is hiding somewhere around the world, plotting something!
It was four years ago that he returned.
The reason my spirit photos and your evil spirit
began to manifest this past year... is most certainly related to Dio!
In the wider world, our gifts are considered psychic powers.
My Stand has been with me since birth...
...but your powers are linked to Dio's body.
So in effect, you are linked to Jonathan's body by invisible threads.
All that we know for certain is that it was Dio's existence that brought forth this dormant power within you.
Abdul, can you tell where he is from this photo?
I cannot. The background is hardly discernible.
As I thought...
I shall give it a closer look.
I'm counting on-
Oh, Holly.
I'm sorry I had to bring this up all at once.
Now, let's go home.
Y-Yes...
I'm gonna be visiting Japan for a while now.
I'll be staying at your place.
Yes, Papa.
Jotaro, let's go.
This again...
Just now, it felt as if something was observing me again.
Is it Jonathan's descendants, after all?
This body must be sending out some kind of message through his soul to his descendants.
Very well. Is this what they call "fate"?
It is a fate I must be rid of.
A destiny I must erase.
I have already made my move.
Next Episode
Jotaro!
Here, a goodbye kiss.
Dammit, woman...
Kakyoin Noriaki.
I just transferred here yesterday.
Does this look like a fucking pen to you?
The loser is the evil one.
Episode 2
Who Will Be the Judge?!
The one to judge you...