Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
What?
I'm a kid?!
Little boy, are you okay?
I'll wash and treat your wounds for you.
N-No way!
Chariot!
There's no way I can overpower him!
She's gone...
Where'd she go?
She was here just a minute ago...
I didn't hear a scream or anything...
...so what happened?!
Where'd she go?!
Polnareff...
You said the shampoo was stinging your eyes, yes?
If it stings so badly...
...then let's wash it all out!
Very thoroughly!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Because I'm a kid, my arms... c-can't reach!
Episode 33: Alessi's Divine Set Part 2
If I had my old arms, I could poke his eyes out and get away!
Pulled the plug, eh? Shit!
But here's the thing...
You still won't be able to breathe
if the tub takes too long to drain!
Will it drain in five minutes? Or maybe ten?
Do you feel despair?
Then I'll make this quick!
This is what true despair feels like, Polnareff!
W-What the hell is this?
That shape... and that color! It couldn't be...
You couldn't have!
N-No adult would ever be shameless enough to do that!
That smell... It's...
Disgusting! You actually did it!
Even though I couldn't use my arms or legs, I could still let one loose!
H-How could you be so cruel?!
D-Don't you have even a shred of decency?!
If you were the main character,
that wouldn't have even crossed your mind!
That's very bad! Very bad!
Where's that lady?
What did you do to her?
Where is she?!
Lady! Where are you? Lady!
Lady!
What do you think I did?
Whoa, there!
We should both tread carefully, Polnareff.
We could accidentally crush her.
I-It can't be...
I-Is this... You can't be serious...
L-Lady...
Anyone who touches the shadow of my Stand, Divine Set, will rapidly grow younger!
Polnareff, you noticed my attack quickly, so you only became around eight years old once you dodged out of the way!
But she was touching my shadow for several seconds!
And now she's a fetus!
She's fine for now, but without the protection of a mother's womb, she'll definitely die!
The only reason this happened is because she tried taking care of you!
What a dumbass!
Y-You dirtbag!
D-Darn! I just...
You touched it again!
You'll become even younger this time!
About four years old if I'm not mistaken, Polnareff!
Darn it!
I-If I don't...
If I don't beat him fast enough, the lady will...
At this rate, she won't live more than a few minutes!
I have to beat that
perverted creep as soon as possible!
She treated my wounds and was so nice to me...
I have to...
I have to do something, fast!
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Why are you so concerned with protecting that dying fetus?
You're gonna end up just like her before long, anyway!
D-Darn! I touched the shadow again!
I-I'm shrinking...
Yes! Victory is finally mine!
Polnareff, you should be about three years old now!
And even better, your mind should be on par
with a three-year-old's, too!
Locking the door won't do you any good!
Crud! Th-The bars are too close together!
Even as a little kid, there's no way I can make it through!
Crud!
Th-They won't break...
Looks like your precious Chariot
has also become a three-year-old!
It can't cut through those bars, and it's far too slow!
Now, then, here I come!
Here I am, Polnareff!
H-He's gone!
What?
He's not here! That insufferable brat...
Did he squeeze through the bars and escape outside?!
Whoa, he almost got me!
That sneaky Polnareff is trying to trick me!
He wants me to think he escaped through the bars.
In reality, he's probably hiding somewhere inside
in hopes of getting the drop on me!
Not bad.
Pretty impressive for a brat!
But where are you hiding?
With such a small body, he could have hid in the drawer.
I'm guessing he's either in the bucket or the drawer...
Or maybe he's hiding in the stuffed animal...
Which one could it be? I have a one-in-three chance of finding him.
Let's see if I can get it first try!
I want to split your brain open with my axe as soon as possible!
That stuffed animal looks really suspicious!
But that's just what you want me to think,
so I'll take a swing at this clock instead!
M-My bad!
Then...
The bucket is the obvious choice!
Huh?
So it is the stuffed animal!
Th-Th-The drawer, then!
H-He's gone!
He's gone! He's gone! He's gone! He's gone!
I-Impossible! He's gone!
H-How... It can't be!
The walls and ceiling are made of stone! Chariot couldn't
dig through them even if they were one centimeter thick!
And I know for sure he couldn't have cut through those bars!
Impossible! Where is he? Where did he go?
Are you really gonna lose to a kid in a battle of wits...
Gulp!
...Old Man Alessi?
I-Impossible!
One of the goldfish disappeared...
Div
Divine
Divine Set
A
Al
Ale
Power: D
Speed: D
Range: E
Durability: C
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Ales
Alessi
I was hiding in the goldfish tank, behind this mirror!
Even a kid could figure out a simple trick like this!
Mirror
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Ball
Take
Mirror
Off
Wall
Mirror
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Ball
Take
Mirror
Off
Wall
Mirror
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Ball
Hide
In
Tank
Mirror
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Ball
Hide
In
Tank
Mirror
Lady
Ball
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Mirror
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Mirror
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Good job falling for it, retard!
Mirror
Ball
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Ball
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Ball
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Mirror
Ball
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Mirror
Ball
Lady
Goldfish Tank
Hide
In
Tank
Old Man Alessi, you perverted creep!
Even as a two-year-old, Chariot can still slice your face up!
Very bad! Very bad!
H-Hey, wait!
I won't stop attacking him with my Stand
until it's too young to fight!
Very bad! Very bad!
This is very, very bad!
That creep! He escaped out the window!
Very bad... Very bad...
Jotaro!
Shit, he'll kill me!
Why Jotaro? Why is he here?!
Pretty strange that you fell out the window
already covered in blood.
Calm down... I just gotta calm down.
I need to stay calm if I want to win here!
Jotaro must still be looking for adult Polnareff, and he probably doesn't know who I am yet.
I'll play dumb like I usually do,
and when the time is ripe... I'll attack!
The fine owner of this house will be so angry with me!
I was only cleaning the window and I slipped!
What will I do? What will I do?
They'll be furious!
Hold it, you cruddy geezer!
Mister...
Who were you again? Who were you...? Um, um...
Now! I knew I'd get my chance when Polnareff showed his face!
You're wide open, Jotaro!
Watch out for his shadow!
Yes! I touched it! I touched Jotaro's shadow!
No!
Jotaro! Now you too have succumbed to the power of my Divine Set!
H-He... Wha-
Th-This is..
O-Oh no!
That guy's gonna to turn into a kid, too!
Jotaro!
I heard that you were only recently able
to use your Stand, Star Platinum!
That means you didn't have your Stand as a child!
Now you'll turn into a normal boy again!
He's growing so small...
He turned into a seven-year-old!
I won!
Lord Dio, I will be the one who kills Jotaro!
You'll have to pay me a fortune for this!
Die, Jotaro!
Whoa! He punched him! With those tiny fists!
Gimme a break.
Don't underestimate me just because I'm a kid.
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
E-Even as a child, when Jotaro's serious...
...he's really serious! So strong!
Mmmf, hmmf, gmmf... Huh?
Not good enough. Time to make doubly sure he's finished!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Very good!
The God of Destruction and Storms, the Stand Divine Set.
Alessi, aged thirty-eight and single...
...as he flies off into the distance... retires!
Was that just a dream?
This earring belonged to that boy...
It really did happen.
For some reason, I couldn't move my body...
That's right! I couldn't move a muscle, but I remember now!
That boy was trying his best to protect me...
He was fighting an older man.
Where did that strong, brave boy go?
Where is my little knight?
Where are you? Where did you go?
She was such a sweet and loving woman...
And so genuinely kind...
That was a close one...
I turned back to normal, but I wonder if she's okay.
Um, pardon me...
Did you happen to see a little boy leave my house?
He has silver hair, just like yours...
Pardon me for asking, but have we met before?
N-No... I d-didn't see any kid...
L-Let's bail, Jotaro.
Come on, right now!
W-Wait!
Could you be...
That earring...
I've never seen you before.
We couldn't have met before.
My friend and I are travelers.
This is my first time visiting here,
and I'm already moving on to the next town.
Maybe it really was a dream...
Don't say it, Jotaro.
Don't say a word.
Oh! It's Jotaro and Polnareff!
Where have you guys been?
Ah, it's Mr. Joestar and Abdul!
I keep saying again and again to not wander off on your own!
Look who's talking! You're the ones who disappeared!
Now, now. Let us finally get something to eat.
Iggy! Where the hell were you?
Woof!
S
Sil
Silve
Silver
Silver Ch
Silver Cha
Silver Char
Silver Chari
J
Silver Chario
Je
Silver Chariot
Jea
Jean
Jean Pi
Jean Pie
Jean Pier
Jean Pierr
Jean Pierre
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Jean Pierre P
Jean Pierre Pol
Jean Pierre Polna
Jean Pierre Polnare
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Allow me to clear this away.
Ah, thanks.
It's about time we caught a break...
What should have been breakfast has turned into lunch...
Yeah...
We'll reach Cairo before long.
We have to figure out where Dio is hiding.
Oh, a spirit photo!
Will it show up?
I'm not sure.
But we're much closer, so it should work.
Now, here goes!
Good sir, is something the matter?
It is fine. Please leave.
Right...
Gramps, what's up? Can you see it?
Just a bit longer...
Almost done...
There!
This is the place we have to find!
Next Episode
The only reason you feel cheated is because...
You're really pissing me off!
Gambling is much like a relationship.
At the first sign of anything unusual...
Go home if you're too afraid...
I'll bet my soul!
Episode 34
D'Arby the Gambler Part 1
Good!