Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 20: Death 13 Part 2
Saudi Arabia...
Roughly 8,800 kilometers from Japan...
It's been about four weeks since we left.
If we don't hurry, things will only get worse.
Kakyoin...
Hey, Jotaro...
What's the deal with Kakyoin?
He's been like this since his episode on the plane earlier.
He even went after the baby.
He's a danger to himself. I think he's losing it.
He may have to sit out the rest of our journey.
I was afraid he figured out my secret for a second...
...but now, Kakyoin is even doubting himself.
We're in the middle of the desert.
I just need to wait until they fall asleep.
If nobody's there to wake them up...
Something smells good! Whatcha making?
Baby food.
It's milk, egg yolks, bananas, and bread all stewed together.
Here. Want a taste?
Delicious!
Now that's the stuff! Gimme more! More!
Hold on! This food is for the baby!
You jerk! Don't eat my food!
I'm hungry! Hurry and feed me!
A... A scorpion!
Th-This is bad!
That was close...
D-Darn! Kakyoin saw that!
He killed the scorpion...
Th-That baby really is...
C-Crud!
You've had enough!
Mr. Joestar, Polnareff, did you see that?
Huh?
That baby really isn't normal!
He just killed a scorpion!
It happened so fast! He stabbed it with a safety pin!
Kakyoin, calm down. What are you saying?
This is no ordinary baby!
He's not even a year old, yet he knew what a scorpion was...
He killed it with his own tiny hands!
A scorpion?
Where?!
In here!
The dead scorpion should be in here...
I-It's not here...
I-I'm telling the truth!
Where are you hiding it?!
Is it in your clothes?!
We get it, Kakyoin! That's enough! Stop!
Mr. Joestar!
I told you this earlier, but you're exhausted.
We'll discuss this tomorrow, once you've calmed down.
Now, open wide! It's yummy!
Oh? Dat's weird! You wook pwetty hungwy, but you're not gonna eat?
Say "ah."
E-Enough already!
There's a reason I can't eat right now!
Mr. Joestar! I'm convinced now!
I don't know where he hid the scorpion,
but he has to be a Stand user!
I have all the proof I need right here!
Look! Read what it says on my arm!
It's a warning!
I must have gotten this wound in my sleep!
Oh my God!
Kakyoin, did you do that to yourself?
K-Kakyoin, you really...
Oh my God!
You big idiot!
Wasn't it obvious that if you showed them that,
they'd think you went insane?
D-Did I just make things even worse?
A-At this rate... I won't have a choice...
I'll have to use force!
Hierophant Green!
It's no use. He's lost his fucking mind...
N-No way... I-I'm certain, Jotaro...
His Stand was the one in our dream, Polnareff...
We can't go to sleep, Mr. Joestar...
Believe me... Everyone, if we fall asleep, we'll be killed!
Believe me... Please, believe me...
Yes! I got away without being found out!
You guys lose!
You lost to your own disbelief in your friend!
Victory is mine, dummies!
How could this happen?
Does this mean Kakyoin won't be able to travel with us anymore?
We'll figure out what to do with him in the morning.
Time for bed.
Polnareff, help me move Kakyoin.
Sure thing.
Jotaro, get out the sleeping bags.
Sure.
You say something?
Nope. He's just heavy.
I'm gonna slice you all up, then scatter what's left across the desert!
Why are we sleeping in the middle of
an amusement park like a bunch of morons?
I remember now!
Th-This is...
Jotaro! Mr. Joestar! Be careful!
I-It's coming back to me now...
W-We're inside a dream...
It's horrifying.
This is a world of nightmares!
What, it's just a dream? Guess I can relax now.
Don't react like I did!
Listen! What Kakyoin said is true!
Baby... Stand...
This is the enemy's territory!
I know it's unbelievable, but the Stand user is that baby!
Nobody will wake you now.
You'll never escape the world of Death 13.
Now I can finish you all for good!
Since I knocked Kakyoin out earlier...
...he should be somewhere in this world!
We have to find him!
Where are you, Kakyoin?
I need to tell him I'm sorry!
P-Polnareff, what's with your hairstyle?
Did you mess up styling it?
Polnareff!
What?
M-My...
My prosthetic hand!
Holy shit!
How are we supposed to fight this?
How?!
A-Anything can happen here...
There's no rhyme or reason to it!
We're at his mercy in this world!
Wait. There is one rule...
The one to slice us into pieces...
...will be his Stand...
...and it alone!
Rally-ho!
D
De
Dea
Deat
Death
Death 1
M
Death 13
Man
Manni
Mannis
Mannish
Mannish B
Power: C
Speed: C
Range: E
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: B
Mannish Bo
Mannish Boy
Rally-ho!
Star...
It's no use, Jotaro!
We can't call out our Stands in the dream world!
...Platinum!
Th-That's funny... His Stand appeared...
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Rally-ho! I'm an imposter!
This overwhelming power! This absolute fear!
It's so exciting!
Stands are made up of spiritual energy.
And while you dream, your spirit is at its most vulnerable!
Death 13 has trapped your spirits in the state they were in
when you fell asleep, and that's why you can't summon your Stands!
Although...
If you had summoned your Stands before you fell asleep...
...you could have brought them with you, like your clothes, the sleeping bags, and that prosthetic hand.
Death 13 will never have to fight other Stands!
And since only a Stand is capable of
defeating another Stand, I can never lose!
Now...
...let me hear it!
I want your screams to signify how
pleased I am for taking this easy victory!
Rally... ho?
Rally-ho!
Oh, are you that imposter I made earlier?
W-What?!
Impossible!
This one's the real thing!
It really is Hierophant!
They're normal again!
It's Kakyoin!
Kakyoin's over there!
When I was knocked unconscious earlier,
did you forget my Hierophant was out?
I had Hierophant hide underground before I fell asleep.
Help me!
Now, it's time for your punishment, baby.
C-Crud!
Let go!
Quit it, Death 13!
It will never leave your blind spot.
If you keep resisting...
...even if you are just a baby, it will break your neck.
Kakyoin!
Kakyoin, we really owe you one!
I thought you had really lost it!
I didn't believe you...
You fought this battle by yourself...
I'm sorry...
No, Polnareff. There's nothing you could have done.
At first I had no clue how to bring my Stand into the dream,
but after you hit me, it gave me the idea.
I should really be thanking you.
N-No kidding?
T-Talk about conflicted feelings!
I'm a bit embarrassed...
He's holding back because I'm a baby!
Kakyoin, your stupidity will cost you your life!
You're still inside my nightmare world!
Hey, what's with the clouds?
The clouds are moving together for some bizarre reason!
Don't try anything funny, Death 13!
Kakyoin! Get Hierophant away from his back!
What?
I'll chop you in half!
I-Impossible!
He chopped himself...
...i-in half.
Kakyoin!
Rally-ho!
Didn't you know?
Death 13's body is actually hollow!
Death 13 is nothing but a head, arms, and giant scythe!
You big dummy!
Let's see...
Kakyoin's body should be split in two
inside his sleeping bag right now.
Just kidding!
Kakyoin!
A-Are you okay?
Take a closer look.
My Hierophant isn't so careless as to stay on his back forever.
He's not chopped in half!
He turned himself into string, and now he's crawling into my ear!
M-My arm is moving on its own...
It's going in...
Like I said...
He was on your back, so the scythe couldn't touch him!
Now, if you're not happy with being torn up from the inside...
...why don't you heal the wound on my arm?
Anything is possible in a dream,
so you should be able to heal my cuts, right?
Y-Yeah...
All right, everyone. Up and at 'em!
Polnareff, wake up! Breakfast is ready!
I feel like I just had an awful nightmare...
Same here.
I can't remember, but it must have been a really bad dream.
Kakyoin!
A-Are you all right?
What do you mean?
W-What do I mean?!
You were off your rocker last night!
You even carved letters into your arm...
H-Huh?
Your wound is gone?
Well, I think it's about time to change the baby's diaper.
Huh?
Come on, it's morning.
I guess he's finally getting along with the baby.
Could all of that have been a dream?
So... Did you sleep well?
Well, whatever!
Everyone forgot.
A Stand whose existence can be completely forgotten...
What a unique Stand.
But I remember.
I'm the only one who brought their Stand into the dream.
Listen. Because you're a baby, I won't kill you, or even injure you.
We'll take you to a nearby town.
You need to go back to your mother.
But don't you dare come near us again.
If you do, I'll punish you.
Just like this...
M-My poop?
Oh, Kakyoin.
You whipped up some baby food?
Yeah.
Come on... You must be hungry by now.
Hey, no... You wouldn't...
Come on, it's yummy! Open wide!
Oh, this again? What does he have against this stuff?
If this keeps up, I'll have to force feed him.
Don't!
Hey, hey, Mr. Joestar...
He'll only hate it if you force him.
For situations like this...
See? Isn't it yummy?
Ba-dum tsh!
H
Hi
Hie
Hiero
Hieroph
Hieropha
Hierophan
Hierophant
Hierophant G
Hierophant Gre
Hierophant Gree
Ka
Hierophant Green
Kakyo
Kakyoin
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: B
Precision: C
Growth Potential: D
Kakyoin Nori
Kakyoin Noriaki
Sea
Red
Arabian Sea
Cairo
Saudi Arabia
Egypt
Having traveled through the Arabian Peninsula,
Joestar and company are about to enter Egypt via the Red Sea.
However!
Hey, Gramps... something's up.
You're going the wrong way.
Shouldn't we be going west, directly to Egypt?
You're on a course for that island.
Yeah, that's right.
I have my reasons for not mentioning it earlier, but...
...before we enter Egypt,
we need to take this detour to meet someone.
He's a man of great importance to our journey.
A man of great importance?
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
But at the cost of Abdul's life...
There's nothing I can do...
You have my thanks for freeing me from that lamp.
It's real, gold treasure!
Tell me the three things you desire!
Can you... bring someone back...
Episode 21
Judgement Part 1