Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 3: Dio's Curse
He's done for.
He's not going to make it.
He'll be dead in a matter of days.
Jotaro, it's not your fault.
Look, the reason that this man
swore loyalty to Dio and came to kill you...
...is right here!
What the hell is that spider-like thing on his head?
Is this why he swore himself to Dio?
This flesh bud was formed from Dio's own cells...
...and is connected to his brain.
It was implanted in his brain to control his thoughts.
Simply put, the flesh bud is able to bring forth
certain feelings within him... like a controller.
Charisma!
This is a quality that will make
a soldier unquestionably obey a dictator!
That will make true believers follow a cult leader!
This young man admired Dio and swore loyalty to him!
Dio is very charismatic...
...which allows him to easily
sway others with his overwhelming charm.
This was how he was able to order Kakyoin to kill us.
Can't we remove it?
The brain is too delicate.
If he moved even a little during the extraction,
it could cause permanent brain damage.
Jojo...
The story I am about to tell you happened four months ago.
I was in Cairo, Egypt...
...when I met Dio!
I am a fortune teller by trade.
My shop is located in the souq Khan el-Khalili.
It was the night of the full moon...
He...
I saw him standing quietly on the stairs leading up to the second floor of my shop...
He gave me a cold gaze that felt
as if it would pierce through my heart...
His golden hair...
His nearly transparent alabaster skin...
...and his overwhelming presence
made him seem unlike any normal man!
I knew immediately from Mr. Joestar's description who it was, for it was unmistakably Dio!
I understand you have a power most mortals do not.
It would make me very happy if you let me see it.
It was at this moment that I realized how truly terrifying he could be!
His words brought such peace to my soul...
They had a dangerous sweetness to them...
Which was exactly what made him so terrifying!
Come, Abdul...
I ran for my life.
I dared not even consider fighting him.
I was incredibly fortunate...
Because I realized it was Dio, I was able to
quickly escape by jumping from the closest window.
I knew the winding streets of the souq below
like the back of my hand, and so I was able to escape.
I may have ended up like this young man...
Forced to be one of his followers by a flesh bud...
And then you would have died a few years later,
your brain completely devoured.
Died?
Wait just a minute...
Kakyoin here...
...isn't dead yet!
I'll get it out with my Stand!
Wait, Jotaro!
Gramps, stand back!
I can pull it out without doing any damage.
My Stand has the precision to grab a moving bullet.
Stop! That flesh bud is still alive!
Don't you realize why part of the bud is on the outside?!
It's why not even the best surgeon can extract it!
Shit!
The flesh bud stabbed him with its tentacle!
This is bad! Let go, Jojo!
It will attempt to enter the brain of anyone who tries to extract it!
Why... you...
Stay still, Kakyoin. Your brain is done for if you move.
Let go, Jojo! It is already at your face!
Hold on, Abdul!
My grandson is a strong man.
He's completely calm despite it entering his body.
He isn't even trembling. Nor is his Stand!
He can move with more strength and precision than I expected.
He did it!
Overdrive!
Wh-
Why?
Why did you risk your life to save me?
Who knows?
If there even is a reason, I couldn't say.
Your Mama sees right through you, Jotaro.
Right, all done.
Thank you... very much.
Kakyoin, was it?
You should rest for a while.
You can stay the night.
Papa, get his futon ready.
Why me?!
I never liked sleeping on the floor in the first place!
Holly, replace my futon with a real bed!
Papa, while in Japan, you must do as the Japanese do.
Oh, and my name is Seiko now.
Huh?!
Holly comes from the word "Holy," which is "Seinaru" in Japanese.
So all my friends call me Seiko!
What kind of name is that?!
"Holly" is the name I gave to my beaut-
I won't answer if you don't call me Seiko.
Holly!
Does it still hurt, Kakyoin?
I-It's fine.
Holly!
Gimme a break...
All right, Kakyoin, give me your uniform.
Come on, now.
Holly!
Hmph!
Holly! Hey, Holly!
Hey, where are you?
Look at this, you gave me Jotaro's pants!
Where are mine?
They fit fine, but I can't wear these!
Hey, Holly!
Oh, maybe I need to call for Seiko to have her answer...
No, the only daughter I know is Holly. Holly! Answer me!
I'm actually going to go to school today for once.
That's odd...
Here, a goodbye kiss.
Smooch.
That's usually how this goes...
M-
Ms. Holly!
Ms. Holly! Ms. Holly!
S-She has a high fever...
Is she sick?
Th-This... it cannot be!
S-Sorry...
H-How can this be?
Incorporeal...
This is a Stand!
Ms. Holly has manifested a Stand!
He
Her
Herm
Hermi
Hermit
Hermit Pu
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purp
J
Hermit Purple
Jo
Jose
Josep
Joseph
Joseph J
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Joseph Joes
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
Ms. Holly now has a Stand...
A-And... the Stand has given her a high fever!
We thought that only Jojo and Mr. Joestar
were being affected by Dio's body...
It was a relief to us that Ms. Holly was unaffected by it...
No, we merely wanted to be relieved.
She could not have gone unaffected.
Anyone with Joestar blood coursing through their veins...
...will be affected by Dio's curse.
That is why...
Stands are controlled by the user's mental strength,
and move using their fighting instincts.
Ms. Holly is a very gentle and peaceful person,
and so she lacks the strength to withstand Dio's curse!
She is powerless to control her Stand!
This is why her Stand is harming her!
This is very bad... At this rate...
She will die!
It will kill her!
A Stand...
Holly...
This... This is the one thing I feared most!
M-My daughter has manifested a Stand...
I knew she wouldn't have the power to withstand it...
I even knew she wouldn't have the power to deny the curse from Dio's soul!
Now, what will we do?
Just one thing...
We must find Dio!
We need to kill Dio and lift the curse! That's all we can do!
However...
No matter how many times I try, he stays obscured by the darkness.
The background is dark in every spirit photo I take.
It's impossible to find where he is with these.
We have used various different ways to analyze them,
but the darkness has caused them all to fail.
Hey. You should have said that sooner.
Maybe I'll find something...
...hiding in that darkness!
What do you see behind Dio?
My Stand is so accurate it could remove
a flesh bud from someone's brain...
And move with enough precision to catch a bullet.
It'll make a sketch.
A fly! There was a fly there!
But a fly's not gonna help us...
Wait a moment!
I know this fly!
What?!
Jojo, do you have an encyclopedia?
We've got a library.
Give me the memo.
I will investigate at once!
Holly!
Papa, I...
Just take it easy... Jotaro, get some water.
You appear to be doing well.
Sorry, but I am busy at the moment.
Is it actually possible for your own Stand to kill you?
It is. In the past, I have seen many people suffer this fate.
Right now, it is only her back. But eventually, that Stand,
growing like a fern, will slowly bind Ms. Holly's entire body.
She will suffer from a high fever and various illnesses,
and then eventually, she will fall into a coma.
She will die.
It will appear to most people she is dying from an unknown illness,
and not even the most skilled doctor will be able to cure her.
No one, not even you nor I, can do anything about it.
But there is still hope.
It will take about fifty days for her to reach this point.
We must find and defeat Dio before then.
If we are able to destroy the connection
with Dio's Stand, we can save her!
Thank you, Jotaro.
Really, I wonder what's wrong with me...
I can't believe I got a fever and passed out.
But...
She doesn't know what's happening since it's coming from her back...
You gave me quite the scare, Holly.
Come now. You need to brush your teeth now that you're up.
Say, "ahh."
Don't forget your face.
Your hair is a mess, too.
And your nails!
Papa, can you also help me change my underwear?
Just kidding! I was only joking!
Now then, Jotaro, what would you like for dinner?
Don't move! Just stay in bed!
Y-You shouldn't do anything until your fever is down...
Just shut up and get better.
Holly, come on...
All right.
You've all been so kind to me since I got sick.
Sometimes having a cold isn't so bad.
H-Holly!
Sh-She lost consciousness again...
She was acting cheerful, yet she's burning up!
The way she's been acting confirms it.
Although she hasn't said anything,
my daughter knows she has a Stand!
She's been trying to hide it from us...
She didn't want us to worry...
My daughter is that kind of person.
Mr. Joestar, I have found it.
That fly...
...is here.
The Nile Ue Ue Fly.
It can only be found in the Egyptian Nile River Basin.
The ones with stripes on their legs are known as Aswan Ue Ue Flies.
Egypt!
We have narrowed its location down to the city of Aswan.
There we will find Dio!
You're going to Egypt, huh?
Kakyoin.
What do you mean?
That flesh bud was implanted in my brain three months ago.
While my family and I were at the Nile River during our vacation in Egypt, I met Dio.
Egypt
Cairo
You were also in Egypt?
It appears Dio wants to stay put in Egypt for some reason.
When will you leave?
I'll go with you.
Go with us? Why would you?
To tell you the truth...
As for why I suddenly want to go with you... I don't really know.
I guess it's because you brought me to my senses.
That's all.
Holly... we'll save you, no matter what.
Don't worry.
There's nothing to worry about...
We'll make you better.
Just take it easy...
Jojo's mother, Ms. Holly, is a woman capable of calming the hearts of others.
People feel at ease while around her.
This may sound awkward...
...but if I were to fall in love,
I'd like it to be with someone like her.
I would give my all to protect her.
And I would want to always see her warm, happy smile.
We're wasting time! We leave immediately!
These are the most trustworthy doctors
from the Speedwagon Foundation.
They'll take care of Holly around the clock.
Jojo, before we leave, I shall name your Stand for you.
Name it?
Using the cards of fate, the Tarot.
Blindly choose a card and it shall be decided.
This will suggest your fate, as well as your Stand's power.
The Star! The Star card!
So I shall name your Stand...
Star Platinum!
Kujo Jotaro
Kujo Jotaro. Stand name: Star Platinum!
Star Platinum
Kujo Jotaro
Power: Precise movements and superhuman strength!
Star Platinum
Kujo Jotaro
Joseph Joestar. Stand name: Hermit Purple!
Joseph Joestar
Hermit Purple
Power: Spirit photos!
Joseph Joestar
Hermit Purple
Mohammed Abdul. Stand name: Magician's Red!
Mohammed Abdul
Magician's Red
Power: Fire and heat!
Mohammed Abdul
Magician's Red
Kakyoin Noriaki. Stand name: Hierophant Green!
Kakyoin Noriaki
Hierophant Green
Power: Long distance manipulation and Emerald Splash!
Kakyoin Noriaki
Hierophant Green
All right, we're off!
Let's go!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
As I anticipated...
They have discovered my location.
Will you find me here in Egypt...
Joseph and Jotaro?
He saw us.
I definitely felt Dio looking at us just now!
Yeah.
Be careful.
A Stand user may already be on this plane.
Next Episode
Could we already be encountering another Stand user?
Unbelievable! It is faster than Star Platinum!
What?
It will shudder all right...
Wow! He's gorgeous.
Excuse me, do you have a moment?
Episode 4
Tower of Gray