Just as I thought...
Joseph's blood worked...
It worked perfectly!
I can feel my power growing like never before!
It worked...
It really worked!
Although this body once belonged to
Jonathan Joestar a mere one hundred years ago...
...it is now imbued with the blood of his grandson, Joseph...
...and the one who made this possible
by allowing me to escape, Jotaro, is you!
The Joestar bloodline was mere dog feces
lying in the road to my destiny!
In the end, you Joestars were nothing more than tools for me to use as I pleased!
G-Gramps...
G-Gramps!
No matter what...
No matter what, even if Dio does something to my body...
...you can't let your rage get the better of you, Jotaro.
You don't need to concern yourself with me anymore.
This happened because it had to.
Is this... Gramps'... soul?
Kakyoin solved the mystery of Dio's Stand.
And I relayed his final message to you.
Had we all fought Dio at once,
he would have wiped us out instantly.
I've seen that you can move a bit while time is stopped.
For about two or three seconds.
Use that time wisely.
No matter what Dio does next, don't lose your cool.
If you attack him with blind rage,
you'll put yourself in a bad situation.
Jotaro...
This was a pretty great trip, huh?
A lot has happened to us.
I swear...
We've had such a fun fifty days...
Was that real?
Hey!
What are you gawking at, Jotaro?!
M-Motherfucker!
Now he is an empty shell!
Gramps told me not to lose my cool...
...but I can't help it!
I can't stay calm after seeing what he just did!
This is the final round!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
The World!
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Ora!
Episode 48: A Long Journey's End, and a Farewell to Friends
The World! Time Stop!
Wryyyy!
One second has passed! Two seconds have passed!
Three seconds have passed! Four seconds...
Ora!
Wryyyy!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Five seconds have passed.
Six seconds have passed.
Seven seconds have passed!
I still feel the power surging within me!
I can stop time for even longer!
By the way, Jotaro...
You should no longer be able to move.
You likely assumed you would be able to move
two seconds before I resumed time, but...
...you have made a fatal error!
This is a truly magnificent feeling!
I feel as though I could begin singing!
Eight seconds have passed!
I first attained immortality one hundred years ago, but...
...it never felt nearly as good as the feeling I have right now!
The blood of a Joestar is just what I needed!
This is an amazing high!
G-Gramps... you were right...
Losing my cool got me into trouble...
Still, this isn't fucking over!
I have some rage I need to let out!
Nine seconds have passed!
Time has stopped for nine seconds!
However, nine seconds seems to be my current limit.
Y-You bastard...
Wryyyy!
Prepare to meet the full power of my Stand!
Jotaro! Earlier you mentioned being unable to keep calm...
...but your fury has clearly reached its limit!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Muda!
Prepare yourself for my final attack!
This is it! My final Time Stop!
Using the nine seconds during which I can move while time is stopped, I will emerge victorious!
The World!
One second has passed.
Two seconds have passed.
Three seconds have passed.
Dio, for reasons unknown, disappeared while time was stopped.
Four seconds have passed.
Still, Jotaro had no time to think.
Dio was up to something, so while time was stopped, for the
two seconds Jotaro could move, no matter what attack he may face...
...for those two seconds, the only thing
he could do is retaliate with Star Platinum!
Five seconds have passed.
If there's one thing I know for sure, Dio,
it's that the instant you show your ugly face, I'll beat it to a pulp!
Six seconds have passed.
Bring it on, Dio!
Seven seconds have passed.
Road roller!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Time is up! There is no escape!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Eight seconds have passed!
Wryyyy!
I shall smash you into the ground!
Ora!
Nine seconds have passed.
I've done it.
Victory is mine.
Star Platinum has finally been defeated by The World!
Immortality! Eternal life...
...and Stand power!
Here lies proof that none shall surpass the mighty Dio!
Pathetic humans! I will rule you all!
Bow before my knowledge and might!
Ten seconds have passed!
My ability to stop time has reached ten seconds!
Now, then...
...I shall find Jotaro's lifeless body and drink his blood!
If he has any left, that is!
W-What?
My body... i-is slowing down...
N-No... it isn't slowing down...
I-I cannot move! I-Impossible!
M-My body is frozen in place...
Dio!
It's been eleven seconds.
I guess that's your limit.
What?!
I stopped time at the nine second mark.
That's how I escaped.
Gimme a break...
And now...
...I'll use my last second to defeat you for good!
J-Jotaro!
Th
The
The W
The Wo
The Worl
The World
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
I-Impossible! You stopped time?
Somehow... you did it right as I reached my nine second limit...
How does it feel, Dio?
Having someone come at you from behind while you can't move a muscle...
In a way, it's like if you were holding your breath underwater,
and just as you came up for air...
...someone suddenly grabbed you,
dragging you right back down into the depths below.
Sound familiar?
But I can't say I feel sorry for you.
Ora!
Time has begun to move again.
There's not even a shred of sympathy for you in my body.
Don't expect any pity from me.
Still, if I finished you off by beating you to death...
...it would leave a bad taste in my mouth.
How many seconds until your legs recover?
Three seconds? Four seconds?
I'll let Star Platinum loose on you the second you heal!
Bring it on!
If I were a gunman from a Western, I'd say...
"Draw. Let's see who's got the fastest gun in the West,"
or something like that.
He's mocking me!
But... But, Jotaro...
You may have made it this far,
but you are still just a mere human!
With such precious little time to live,
you think just as every other human does!
You worry about living a life free of regret,
and doing things that would leave a "bad taste" in your mouth...
But that kind of reasoning is as compelling as rat feces left in a bathroom, and will only lead to your demise!
The mighty Dio has no such thoughts!
I have just one simple thought on my mind!
Only one!
To be victorious and reign supreme! Nothing else!
That alone will satisfy me.
And just how I reach that end...
...matters not!
How does it feel to be blinded by my blood?!
I win!
Die!
Ora!
What?!
I-Impossible... I-I am Dio...
I am the mighty Dio!
You'll be dust once the sun comes up.
In the end, you lost for just one reason, Dio.
Just one simple reason.
You pissed me the fuck off.
D
Di
Dio
Dio.
Dio..
Dio...
Dio... and
Dio... and The
Dio... and The World
Dio... and The World...
Suffer
Suffering
Suffering Utter
Suffering Utter De
Suffering Utter Defeat
Suffering Utter Defeat.
Suffering Utter Defeat..
Suffering Utter Defeat...
Suffering Utter Defeat... Have
Suffering Utter Defeat... Have Died.
S
Sta
Star
Star Pl
Star Plat
Star Platin
Ku
Star Platinum
Kujo
Kujo Jo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: A
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
Speedwagon car #2 reporting.
We're heading north on el-Nil Street.
Dio's body has been retrieved.
I repeat, Dio's body has been retrieved.
Dio's body will live until it's exposed to sunlight.
Proceed with caution!
Don't let your guard down.
Roger.
Kakyoin Noriaki is dead.
We're transporting his body by helicopter.
Jean Pierre Polnareff is unconscious.
He's being treated in car #1.
Roger.
By the way, I have a question for you.
Why did you put Dio and Joseph Joestar's bodies in the same car?
This isn't over.
Dio took something...
...and I'm gonna take it back.
What are you talking about?
Is it possible to transfuse blood from one corpse to another?
I-Impossible! Are you suggesting we transfuse Dio's blood into Mr. Joestar's lifeless body?
Are you trying to bring Mr. Joestar back to life?
Dio sucked his blood out just a few minutes ago.
Even though Dio's upper body is destroyed, he needs to return what he has left.
You think we have enough time?
There's your answer. Do you read? Over.
R-Roger...
I-It's impossible! He has no pulse!
His heart is stopped,
which means it's impossible for blood to pump through his body!
Impossible?
Our journey has been full of impossibilities.
I'm sick and tired of hearing that things are
"impossible" or "futile." It means nothing to us.
You said his heart has to be pumping, right?
How fortunate.
I've had some experience with
stopping and starting hearts thanks to Dio.
Ora!
There's a pulse!
His heart's moving!
Hurry! Extract the blood from
Dio's body and perform the transfusion!
This just might work!
L-Look!
His shriveled skin is already regaining color!
His flesh is softening and stretching!
Brainwaves! I'm detecting brainwaves!
I can't believe it! He has a regular heartbeat!
His eyes! He opened his eyes!
We did it! He's come back to life!
Gramps?
Jotaro, you fool!
Y-You asshole! It can't be...
I live again thanks to you!
You!
W-Wait, Jotaro! I'm kidding! Kidding! I'm just kidding!
It's just a joke! A joke!
I'm sorry! I just wanted to mess with you a little.
It's definitely me!
I'm Joseph Joestar. I was born September 27th, 1920.
My wife's name is Suzi Q! I like collecting comic books!
Which actress plays the female lead
in the 1981 film, Tarzan, the Ape Man?
Bo Derek.
Who sang the parody of "Beat It," called "Eat It"?
Al Yankovic.
Gimme a break.
Only someone like you would know pointless shit like that.
Car #2 reporting! It's a miracle!
Mr. Joestar has woken up!
Mr. Joestar came back from the dead!
Hooray! Over!
Now you've returned what you took from us, Dio.
It's over now.
Too many people have given up something to Dio.
For the last one-hundred years,
there have been so many people...
...who have given things up to him.
Most of it will never be returned.
Yeah, he took so much. Way too much...
What we've lost to him
may be even greater than the earth itself.
Still, because of those we lost...
Because of them, we're alive right now.
Kakyoin...
Iggy...
Abdul...
It's over.
Are you really going back to France, Polnareff?
You don't have any more family there, do you?
Why don't you come to New York with me?
Mr. Joestar, even though my family is gone,
France is still my homeland.
I have good memories of my hometown.
I have to go back no matter where my travels take me.
But give me a call if you ever need me!
No matter where you are in the world, I'll come running!
It'll be lonely without you.
Even though we've gone through a lot...
...I still had a lot of fun!
It was a fun journey with you guys there!
Yeah, it really was fun.
I believe that from the bottom of my heart.
Passengers on France International Airlines Flight 92,
bound for Paris, please head to Gate 18.
See ya later, you shit-stained geezer!
I hope you live forever!
And you, his stubborn grandson!
Don't you dare forget me!
We'll meet again!
Even if you're sick of my face, you jackass!
I couldn't forget a guy like you if I tried.
Take care.
See ya.
Yeah...
Holly...
Why are you sitting up all of a sudden?
I... feel a lot better for some reason!
And I just felt something in my heart...
What?
They're both coming home, Mama!
Holly!
Papa and Jotaro!
They're coming home!
The End