Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
Hey, Gramps... something's up.
You're going the wrong way.
You're on a course for that island.
...before we enter Egypt,
we need to take this detour to meet someone.
He's a man of great importance to our journey.
A man of great importance?
Hold it, someone is living here?
This island is puny, and it looks deserted.
I agree.
Mr. Joestar, does anyone actually live here?
Someone does, in fact.
They told me so back in India.
Huh? Who is "they?"
What? Did someone say buffet?
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 21: Judgement Part 1
Hey, someone's watching us from the grass over there.
He's running away!
That looks like...
Yeah. I would recognize him anywhere!
Stop! Please stop!
C'mon now, aren't ya hungry, Michael? Prince?
I made it nice 'n' good by addin' them tasty clams ya enjoy!
I got plenty here for ya.
Eat up 'n' become a round 'n' tasty chicken fer me, Lionel!
That man... It can't be...
It can't be...
Wait!
Let me talk to him. You guys wait here.
My name is Joseph Joestar.
I'm traveling to Egypt with these three-
Get lost! I ain't hearin' it!
That voice...
D-Don't ya dare speak to me!
Nobody tells me good news no more!
It's always gotta be somethin' wrong! I ain't hearin' it!
Get lost!
Mr. Abdul!
Abdul...
Get lost!
I-It can't be!
That's Abdul's...
...father.
His father?
He abandoned society to live alone on this island.
I wanted to tell you guys about this place sooner, but if Dio found out we were stopping here...
...the peace Abdul's father has here may have been compromised.
I couldn't let that happen.
Still... Telling him that his son is dead...
...isn't going to be easy.
Polnareff!
Abdul's death wasn't your fault.
No, but it is my responsibility.
I'm left to carry this burden.
Is his father also a Stand user?
Yeah, but I'm not sure what kind of Stand he has.
Considering his reaction earlier, it's hard to imagine he'll help us.
Leave it to me.
I'll try to reason with him.
I finally got revenge for the murder of my sister,
but at the cost of Abdul's life.
There's nothing I can do... I'll never make it up to his father...
How depressing...
This is neat.
Did it come from a sunken ship or something?
It's covered in barnacles.
Looks like it's made of gold, but...
...it's got some weird face carved onto it...
Maybe it's worth something...
Let's see if I can rub these barnacles off.
W-What the hell?!
I-It's gone!
W-What the hell was that?
Did the air trapped inside suddenly burst out?
Not like it's Aladdin's magic lamp or something...
That gave me a good scare.
Three!
Just three!
I'll grant your wishes!
Tell me the three things you desire!
W-What the hell is this?!
My name is Cameo.
You have my thanks for freeing me from that lamp.
Now tell me your three wishes.
Are you a Stand user?!
Silver Chariot!
N-Not bad...
He's pretty strong...
Hey, pal!
You're pretty strong, which means your Stand user is nearby!
Who is it?!
Is the answer to that question your first wish?
Will you really be satisfied making such a mundane wish?
Don't "I'll grant you three wishes" me!
Are you telling me you can make me super rich right now?
Is that your first wish?
Just try it if you can! And quit fucking with me, dammit!
Very well. It is yours.
Hail 2 U!
( Fortune be with you! )
Wha-
What the hell was that?
Could it have been an enemy Stand?
What a freak...
He didn't attack, and he asked me to make three wishes.
I don't know what's going on, but I need to be careful.
There's something on this island...
I need to tell Mr. Joestar what just happened as soon as I can.
It may have something to do with Abdul's father.
What's that?
There's a weird clinking sound...
Th-This is... It can't be!
Th-This is Napoleonic era gold!
This isn't an illusion or a dream!
It's the real thing. It's real, gold treasure!
A-Are you mocking me?!
N-No... If he wanted to mock me,
he would have needed to bury this beforehand.
He didn't have time to bury it after I made my wish.
How did he bring this here?
Tell me your second wish.
It shall be granted.
Y-You bastard! What kind of stunt are you trying to pull?!
You can't fool me with this!
If you're my enemy, act like it and fight me!
I'll take this treasure if you don't...
Is the answer to that question your second wish?
Do you really want to make such a boring wish?
As thanks for freeing me of my lamp, I will grant you any wish.
Y-You asshole!
F-Fine... In that case, make me...
...a cartoonist!
It's been my childhood dream!
I wanna be bigger than Disney! Not just some nobody!
I'll build a Polnareffland!
W-Wait, hold it...
Hold on for a sec...
Wait, just wait...
Actually, a girlfriend would be sweet!
More than wealth and fame...
...I want love!
I want her to be cute, and for us to be bound by the red string of fate!
I need a girl who feels exactly like I do!
Do it now if you think you can, asshole!
A girl, eh? Very well.
N-No, wait. Actually, I'm having second thoughts...
Can you...
...bring someone back... from the dead?
Is the answer to that question your second wi-
Enough already!
Bring my dead sister back to life!
Then I want you to bring Abdul back to life!
I bet you can't do that for me!
Very well.
I'll grant your wish.
W-What?
Si
Silv
Silve
Silver
Silver C
Silver Ch
Silver Cha
Silver Chari
J
Silver Chario
Je
Silver Chariot
Jea
Jean
Jean Pi
Jean Pie
Jean Pier
Jean Pierr
Jean Pierre
Jean Pierre Po
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Jean Pierre Poln
Jean Pierre Polnar
Jean Pierre Polnaref
Jean Pierre Polnareff
You'll... grant it?
Sure. But you made two wishes, so I gotta do them one at a time.
I'll start with the second wish, your sister.
Hail 2 U!
W-Wait! What the hell are you?!
Why would you-
W-What was that?
That sound I just heard...
I-It sounded like someone digging...
There it is again!
W-What is that sound?!
I-It can't be!
A-A crying woman?
Who the hell is there?!
Th-That's...
H-Hair...
A woman's hair...
A woman's footprints...
N-No way!
It can't be... It can't... be...
My little sister is buried back at home in France...
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Stay... away...
I'm in pain...
My body still isn't ready...
That voice...
Cherie!
Where the hell did Polnareff wander off to?
Not up there.
It's pretty dark out now. Where could he have gone?
It couldn't be an enemy, could it?
Ch-Cherie...
I-Is it really you?
It's you, right?
W-Where are you going?
Where are you going, Cherie?!
It's me! Please wait!
Why are you running away, Cherie?!
Where are you? Please, let me see you!
Please wait, Cherie!
One more time... Let me see your face...
Big brother!
Big brother! Higher, higher! Lift me up higher!
Yay! Now spin around!
Oh, how nice! I've been meaning to get a new umbrella.
Thank you, big brother.
I'll be back soon!
Cherie! Cherie!
Are those... dead birds?
It looks like something chewed them apart...
Cherie!
Are you there? Why are you running?
It's me, your older brother!
Because... I'm covered in dirt...
And my hair is all messed up...
Don't worry about that, Cherie!
I'll love you no matter how dirty you are!
Why are you crying?
Why are you sad, Cherie?
Cherie...
No.
No, you can't!
Don't come near me!
B-But why? What is this about?
Because...
...you'll hate me.
Hate you? Have I ever once said I hated you?
You have...
When we were children...
...I gave your tropical fish to the cat...
You were really angry and said you hated me.
Yeah, I was angry then, but I've always loved you!
Even right now!
Really?
You've always loved me?
Of course I have!
You'll love me, no matter what?
I'll always love you, no matter what.
Cherie... I can't believe it's really you.
You'll never know how much I missed you...
Yeah.
I feel the same, big brother.
Cherie, please look at me.
Please show me your face.
Why are you crying? Why are you sad?
Sad?
No, big brother.
I'm not crying because I'm sad...
Huh? Then...
Because...
...big Brother...
...I'm happy to finally get a taste of you!
Ch-Chariot!
Che... rie...
I'm sorry for biting you, big brother.
My body still isn't ready yet.
But if I eat your flesh, I'll return to normal.
You're fine with me eating you, right?
You always did everything I asked of you.
C-Cameo!
What now?
Y-You son of a bitch!
What? Gotta problem?
I granted your wish.
My only power is to grant wishes. The rest is up to you.
Th-Then, I'll tell you my third wish!
M-Make my sister...
Make my sister...
Make my sister disappear!
Return her to the earth!
Nuh-uh!
What?!
You still don't get it, Polnareff?
I'm a Stand!
I'm the Stand represented by the Judgement card!
My power is to grant the deepest desires in your heart
by giving them form from dirt.
You made your own sister, with a wish from your own heart!
Y-You...
Anything you've created, I cannot unmake.
This battle is mine!
By the way...
You mentioned a third wish,
but you've already made it, haven't you?
Y-
You can't mean...
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
People expose their greatest weaknesses
when they wish from the heart!
Because of you, I...
Abdul, I...
I didn't think you would be this hurt...
I'll get better if I eat, right?
...and the third wish alone...
Episode 22
Judgement Part 2