What the fuck is that?
Why didn't Abdul's flames detect it?
Where are you, Abdul?!
Abdul...
...has been disintegrated to death.
The two of you are next.
I will obliterate any foolish notions you have of defeating Lord Dio!
Bit by bit... One after another...
I, Vanilla Ice, will scatter you throughout my dimension of darkness.
You're lying...
Abdul isn't really dead!
Don't fucking lie to me!
W-What?
I didn't realize Polnareff's Stand was so fast,
nor that it could attack from this distance.
Look at me! You son of a bitch!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 43: The Desolate Void: Vanilla Ice Part 2
What's that?
The effects of the illusion should be gone,
but it felt like a wall just collapsed somewhere in the mansion.
Could it be Abdul and Polnareff?
Fuck! I'm sure I hit him, but he's still alive...
He shrank and disappeared into that dimension...
Both him and his Stand!
Abdul... Goddammit...
You're... You're the one who told us...
Polnareff! Iggy! Look out!
You told us to put ourselves first if anything happened...
You said you wouldn't save us...
You lied!
Ever since we reached India,
you've been making everyone's problems your own!
Abdul! Why didn't you just leave me to die?!
If I hadn't crouched just now, I'd be dead...
Is this fate telling me to live?
Is Abdul trying to tell me to keep fighting?
We have to get out of here!
Let's move, Iggy!
Up there, Iggy!
Let's go upstairs! This way!
An exit!
That's the door we entered from!
But we can't turn back now!
Abdul sacrificed himself so we wouldn't have to die!
He entrusted us to defeat Dio...
And I'm not about to betray his trust!
We can't run away with our tails between our legs!
I'm done running away!
The only place I'm running to is where that asshole, Dio, is!
Let's go get him!
And here I thought they would attempt to flee...
So close...
It's quite impressive that he managed to injure me, Vanilla Ice.
He must possess a strong will to conquer fear in the face of danger.
I will find and kill them without fail. Without fail...
My Stand is far stronger than theirs.
His Stand's mouth leads to a dimension of darkness?
I don't know what that dimension is like,
but now I understand how he got so close without giving off signs of life!
Still...
How the hell can we beat this guy?
H-He cut us off!
He's here!
He must be close!
Iggy, watch my back!
I'll watch yours!
There's no way he can get in here without making a hole in the wall!
If there's one thing I'm sure of...
...it's that once he shows his face from his
dimension of darkness, I'll get my chance to kill him!
Come at me, goddammit! I'll cut you in half!
My Chariot is even faster than it was earlier!
I'm gonna kill you for murdering Abdul!
What?! He got in through the crack under my foot!
Chario-
My foot!
Now that I have taken your foot, you cannot escape from me!
Motherfucker!
Almost.
Mr. Joestar, it sounds like a battle!
Yeah, it sure does.
Abdul and the others must be fighting around here somewhere.
Hurry! We have to find them!
So you've managed to hide amidst the confusion, Polnareff.
How useless.
You cannot have gone far on that foot.
I presume you are hiding under the rubble.
You are powerless before the great Vanilla Ice.
I will defeat you without fail.
Now, where are you hiding, Polnareff?
Why must you be so noisy, Vanilla Ice?
L-Lord Dio!
Please be careful!
Polnareff and that mutt are hiding somewhere.
Please leave this to me.
You needn't trouble yourself over this.
The Fool's fake Dio tricked him!
Normally I'd feel guilty about attacking someone from behind...
...but since that's how you killed Abdul,
I don't mind returning the favor!
This is what you deserve!
Do it, Iggy!
C
Cre
Crea
V
Cream
Va
Van
Vanil
Vanilla
Vanilla I
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: C
Growth Potential: D
Vanilla Ic
Vanilla Ice
Do it, Iggy!
Break through his shoulder, then split him open like a mackerel!
No! Dammit!
He figured it out!
Light from the sun is streaming into this room.
The real Lord Dio would never...
...leave his room to enter this place!
Iggy!
The real Lord Dio trusted me to handle this situation!
Under no circumstances would he descend to this floor right now!
Fuck! He's gonna kill Iggy!
He's gonna swallow Iggy in his dimension of darkness!
How dare you, you disgusting mutt!
You compelled me to destroy an image of Lord Dio!
W-What the hell? He punched him!
He didn't use his dimension of darkness!
He just punched Iggy across the room!
Of all the things you could do...
Even though it was a fake image of Lord Dio, how dare you compel me to strike it!
I shall kick you to death, heathen!
I could swallow you in my
dimension of darkness at this very moment!
But that would not placate my anger!
This is all your fault! Yours!
You have provoked my wrath!
This is all your fault!
Repent for your sin!
How does it feel?! Repent for your sin!
How does it feel? How does it feel?!
S-Stop...
This Vanilla Ice guy is fucking insane...
He's blind with rage...
Did attacking that image of Dio really make him this angry?
His mind itself is a dimension of darkness!
A desolate void that rips everything apart!
Lord Dio told me that we must
never underestimate the resolve of mankind!
But you are nothing more than a pathetic mutt!
You do not possess resolve, a proud soul, or anything of the sort!
Stop it...
How does it feel? How does it feel?!
How does it feel?! How does it feel?!
Stop it, Vanilla Ice!
Let us end this, Polnareff!
Shit!
He disappeared!
But...
Iggy!
Your fake Dio made of sand may have failed, but it gave me an idea!
I know how to figure out where he is!
There he is!
I can see where he's going!
You're finished! I've got you!
You shithead!
Whenever you're moving in your dimension of darkness, you swallow up everything in your path.
So swallow this!
Swallow this sand and get closer, motherfucker!
Once your gross, disgusting mouth appears...
...that's when I'm gonna strike!
I stabbed him head-on! Serves you right, asshole!
I know your other weakness, Vanilla Ice!
If you want to see where I am...
...you have to poke your head out of your
dimension of darkness, or you can't see what's outside!
Eat this!
Eat my sword and go to hell!
You motherfucker!
Y-You're...
I pierced your brainstem through your throat, dammit!
Hurry up and die! That injury is fatal!
Die already!
Fucking die already, Vanilla Ice!
I refuse!
I cannot die now.
I will kill you at all costs!
Then I will swallow Iggy at all costs,
and Joestar and the others soon after!
Then I may die!
You bastard!
A wise move, pulling your sword free.
This time, I'll send you straight to hell!
Is this the arm that stabbed me?
You son of a bitch!
Fuck! I had no choice but to shove him away!
Shit!
You're not getting away!
I got him! B-But this is bad!
Dammit, he got my leg! I can't move...
But I have no time to worry about the pain!
I was so close to finally finishing him off!
This guy...
...is really determined!
He's crazy, and determined to serve Dio at all costs!
I won't let his determination get the best of me!
He's not the only one who refuses to die until the other is dead!
The bastard! Here he comes!
Take this!
I-It's no use... He swallowed the tip of my sword as I cut him!
It's impossible to attack him while he's in his dimension of darkness!
I'll just end up getting swallowed!
He's swallowing up everything in his path! Goddammit!
The bastard... Now that he knows I can attack him,
he's guessing where I am and randomly attacking all over the place!
He's got good instincts!
He'll hit me for sure if this keeps up!
I'll call Chariot back for now.
D-Damn...
Iggy's lost a lot of blood...
And his broken bones are piercing his lungs...
Talk about reckless... He's eating away at the walls!
W-Wait! I was wrong!
These aren't instincts! He has a plan!
Not only is he looping around, he's starting to close in on me!
He's moving like a mosquito coil, or maybe a cyclone!
And he's closing in on me!
Even if he doesn't show his face to see where I am, he'll still hit me!
I'm caught in his trap!
W-Will I be able to dodge with this leg?
The only way I'm getting out of here is through the floor!
It's hopeless... I don't have enough time!
He's coming for me!
Somehow I dodged him...
But he's gonna keep closing in on me, like a needle on a record.
He'll reach me in about five more loops...
Now, here's the question...
How will I dodge him with this hole in my leg?
Pi
Pick
Pick one
Pick one of
Pick one of the
Pick one of the th
Pick one of the three
Pick one of the three fol
Pick one of the three follow
Pick one of the three following
Pick one of the three following opt
Pick one of the three following optio
Pick one of the three following options:
Opt
Option
Option #1:
Option #1: The
Option #1: The ha
Option #1: The hand
Option #1: The handso
Option #1: The handsome
Option #1: The handsome Po
Option #1: The handsome Pol
Option #1: The handsome Polna
Option #1: The handsome Polnare
Option #1: The handsome Polnaref
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
su
sudd
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
sudden
suddenly
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
suddenly th
suddenly thi
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thin
suddenly think
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks
suddenly thinks of
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a
suddenly thinks of a coun
Option #1: The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a counter
suddenly thinks of a counterattack.
Opt
Option
Option #2:
Option #2: His
Option #2: His fri
Option #2: His frien
Option #2: His friends
Option #2: His friends wi
Option #2: His friends will
Option #2: His friends will co
Option #2: His friends will come
Option #2: His friends will come sa
Option #2: His friends will come save
Option #2: His friends will come save him.
Opt
Option
Option #3:
Re
Real
Option #3:
Reality
Reality is
Option #3:
Reality is cru
Reality is cruel.
Option #3:
He
Reality is cruel.
He won't
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be ab
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be able
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be able to
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be able to dod
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be able to dodge
Option #3:
Reality is cruel.
He won't be able to dodge.
I'd like to choose option #2, but I can't count on it.
There's no way Mr. Joestar and the others,
who entered the mansion just ten minutes earlier...
...would show up in the next couple of seconds
like American comic book heroes yelling "Ta-dah!"...
...and save me at the last minute.
Mr. Joestar and the others could be struggling in a battle of their own for all I know.
Looks like #1 is my only option!
Chariot! Pull me out of the circle as hard as you can!
Goddammit! Pull harder!
I-It's no use!
Despair! The only answer left is #3!
Reality is a harsh mistress!
My Silver Chariot is a Stand that excels in swordplay...
But now, it's not even strong enough to pull my own weight...
Fuck...
You're still injured! Stay still, stupid!
If you move or use any of your Stand's power,
the broken bones piercing your lungs will kill you!
Hey, what's with the tough guy act, stupid?
Are you trying to save me so both of us die?
I'm the one who has to look cool and save you!
You have to live to tell
Mr. Joestar and the others about this guy!
Did you forget why we're here?!
Abdul died to save me, but that doesn't mean you should, too!
If both of us die, it's over!
He'll get me for sure on the next loop...
It's gonna be #3...
Reality can be cruel.
Looks like his determination...
...won out after all.
So long, Iggy.
Next Episode
It is not by your hand that I bleed...
It is Abdul's.
I don't know all of the details...
My friendships never end well.
You will not...
This happens every time... It never hits me until it's too late...
Episode 44
The Desolate Void: Vanilla Ice Part 3