It's about time.
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 25: Iggy's The Fool and N'Doul's Divine Geb Part 1
W-Who is that?!
They're here.
It's a helicopter!
No kidding, we can see it.
That's a Speedwagon Foundation helicopter.
They're looking for a place to land.
Speedwagon Foundation?
Are they the guys taking care of Mom back in Japan?
Those friends of yours?
Yeah, that's them.
Don't tell me we're going for a helicopter joyride.
Nope. As much as I'd like to, the crew aren't Stand users.
If we were attacked, they would be at risk.
Then why is it here?
They brought us some backup.
What's that? Backup?
He has a few personality issues, so it took a while to get him here.
Mr. Joestar!
Him joining us on this trip is inconceivable!
He could never be of use to us!
You know him, Abdul?
Yes, quite well.
Hold on.
If he's our backup, then that means he's a Stand user, right?
His Stand represents the The Fool card.
The Fool?
He must be pretty stupid with a card name like that.
It is most fortunate he is not our enemy.
You would lose to him.
What's that, you son of a bitch?
Better watch your mouth.
It is the truth.
Why so forceful? That hurts.
Trying to sound like you know everything...
Cut it out already.
It's landing.
Mr. Joestar, I see you're well.
Thanks for flying out here. I appreciate it.
So...
Which one of you is the Stand user?
Who is it?
You?
No, it's neither of us.
He's in the back seat.
The back seat...
There's nothing there.
No, he's there...
Hey, hey, hey!
So he's there, but where is he?
Is he some kind of midget?
Come on out here! Come on!
B-Be careful!
What the hell is this sticky crap?
Please, be careful!
He's in a terrible mood from the helicopter ride!
Stay back!
I told you he has personality issues!
Polnareff, you will not win.
I'm just wondering where the hell he-
H-H-H-He's...
...a dog!
Don't tell me this dog....
Yes! He's the user of The Fool.
His name is Iggy!
One of his favorite pastimes is
tearing out human hair by the mouthful!
We don't know where he was born...
...but when the dog catchers in New York weren't able to catch him...
...Abdul finally had to do it for them.
Oh, that's right, now I remember...
While he's ripping out hair, he likes to...
...fart in their face. He's a vulgar one.
Goddammit! I'll make you pay!
Damn you...
Chariot!
Th-That's...
Is that really The Fool?
I know we met an orangutan Stand user
off the coast of Singapore, but...
What kind of stupid mutt do you think you are?!
I'll cut you in half!
It's turning into sand...
I-I can't cut it!
It became solid and swallowed up my sword!
That's...
Simply put, it is a Stand composed of sand.
Right... The simple ones are strong.
I don't think I could beat it.
Hey! Help me! Do something about this dog!
Sorry, Polnareff, but I'm not going to let my hair get ripped out.
You monster!
Do you have his treats?
If we didn't, we never would have made it here.
Stop! Help me!
What an incredible sense of smell!
What's that?
Coffee-flavored chewing gum.
It is Iggy's favorite treat. He would die for it.
Mr. Abdul! Keep the box hidden from-
Curses! He snatched the entire box!
He loves coffee-flavored chewing gum,
but he still won't let down his guard for anyone.
You could at least remove the paper...
There's no way this guy can help us.
Gimme a break.
Fuck...
My beautiful hair has been ruined...
You asshole!
While he's eating the gum, he won't be a problem.
Let's go grab the supplies.
Here's some food and water for your trip.
Oh, thank you.
There are medical supplies and a change of clothes as well.
Also, a new camera for taking spirit photos.
Those TVs we've been using
just aren't the same for spirit photography.
Oh, I know.
Hey, you guys.
I see. This should make a nice memory.
Abdul! Hurry up with the gum!
Why bother when you two have
become inseparable friends, Polnareff?
Mr. Joestar, we're heading out now.
I have one last question for you.
It's about my daughter...
How is Holly doing?
Give it to me straight.
Right... I hate to say it, but I'm afraid she isn't doing well.
Her energy levels have gone down, and her life is still in danger.
According to the doctors from the Speedwagon Foundation...
...she'll be lucky if she survives another two weeks.
There's no time.
Shit...
Also, there's something else we must tell you.
According to a report from two days ago...
Nine mysterious men and women gathered at a building Dio was rumored to be hiding in.
They departed together shortly after.
Dio and nine others?
Right now their identities are a mystery.
The person who reported this was murdered, and the building was found empty.
We were unable to locate any of them.
Any further investigation is impossible for us,
due to the fact that we aren't Stand users.
Could they be new Stand users?
Wait, hold on.
Of the Stands that suggest Tarot cards we've encountered so far,
excluding Hol Horse's Emperor, only The World is left.
I thought The World card was Dio's Stand, but...
Abdul?
I-I do not know.
I never knew. Nine of them?
Apparently Dio hasn't gotten used to his new body yet.
Dio has too much pride. He would never flee from Cairo.
It looks like he's trying to stop us from getting there.
Gimme a break. There's only two weeks left, and nine of them to face...
This may be a bit tiring.
Well, we should get going.
Please have a safe trip.
Thank you. Take care of Holly.
That mutt...
It noticed the presence of the great N'Doul, eh?
Damn. So close.
I almost had it there.
I must be out of practice.
The Aswan Ue Ue Fly, huh?
It's because of this fly that Joestar
and the others were able to pursue Lord Dio...
Th
The
The F
The Foo
The Fool
I
Ig
Power: B
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: D
Growth Potential: C
Iggy
Mr. Joestar, can't you do something about him?!
Why is this fucking dog taking up
an entire seat while we're stuck in the back?
My back is starting to ache!
You'll have to wait for the flavor of his coffee gum to fade.
He'll move once he sees the new piece of gum...
...then you can switch seats.
All right, all right. Calm down! Jesus...
W-What the hell?!
L-Look! Over there!
Th-That's...
The helicopter!
The Speedwagon Foundation helicopter
from earlier crashed in the sand!
It shows no outward sign of attack...
It's as if it fell right to the ground...
There's no way!
Be careful!
We may end up being attacked by an enemy Stand!
Look! It's the pilot!
He's dead...
There are marks where he clawed the side...
What a mess...
Approach carefully.
Something could be hiding.
It's water.
All of that water...
It's coming from the pilot's mouth... No, his lungs.
Even a fish came out...
He drowned, right in the middle of the desert!
But how?
H-Hey...
The other guy's over here!
He's alive!
Are you all right? Get a hold of yourself!
What the hell happened?
Wa...
Wa... ter...
What? You want water?
Polnareff, hand me that canteen.
Okay...
Here, hang in there. Have some water.
Drink slowly.
No! The water's gonna kill me!
What?!
I-It's the enemy Stand!
The enemy Stand is inside the canteen!
D-Dammit!
The Speedwagon Foundation crew wasn't even involved in this, and they still got attacked!
Abdul, did you see what kind of Stand it was?
I saw only a hand.
It is still inside the canteen!
I did not see it leave.
Who could it be?
They mentioned Dio gathered nine men and women...
Might one of them be the attacker?
Jotaro, find the enemy user's location.
I already am.
But...
There's nobody in sight.
I even looked for a mirror like that idiot with Sun had.
It looks like the enemy is controlling it from far away.
Polnareff, attack the canteen.
Me?
Th-The pilot's head was
completely sucked into that tiny little canteen...
So if I start poking holes in that thing...
Hell no!
Kakyoin! You're closer anyway!
Why can't you just hit it with an Emerald Splash?
I don't want to.
Don't make me do something you won't do yourself!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
No means no.
Well, then maybe I don't wanna do it either!
Th-That's...
K-Kakyoin!
It's the water!
It poured out of the canteen mixed with the blood!
The Stand was not inside the canteen with the water...
The water is the Stand!
It got Kakyoin!
I-It got Kakyoin's eyes!
Polnareff! Quit panicking!
Bring out Chariot and defend yourself!
This is bad! It's gonna get Polnareff!
What's going on? It attacked the pilot's corpse!
No, not that. It wasn't the corpse. The watch...
It attacked the watch's alarm.
Sound! It attacks by detecting sound!
Sound?
Shit! Polnareff!
It's coming for you!
Run for the buggy!
I-It's fast!
Hurry, Polnareff!
I-I'm hit!
Hermit Purple!
It receded into the ground...
The enemy can detect sound through vibrations in the ground.
It can move undetected beneath the ground, and when we least suspect it...
...it will attack us from behind, or through the bottoms of our feet.
Its user can keep a huge distance from us...
They retreated to the top of their vehicle.
They must have realized that I, N'Doul,
was targeting them through sound.
A shame this fact won't do them any good.
H-How's Kakyoin?
Not well.
He may have been blinded.
Let us make haste.
We must get him to a doctor immediately.
But if we move, we'll be attacked!
We can't be careless.
What?!
These footsteps... It's the dog.
That mutt...
It exited the car before I could strike.
It anticipated my Stand's attack.
It seems that dog is going to be a problem after all.
The tires are in the water! Fuck!
It's no use! We're being pulled in!
We cannot hold on!
Move further back!
Backup, c'mon, dammit! Back us up already! Hey!
That accursed mutt...
It must have deduced that I'm only four kilometers to the west.
What should I do...?
I must take care of the mutt first!
How careless can you be?!
You dumb dog!
No, I'll leave the mutt alone.
It appears Joestar and the others haven't tamed it.
If it's just going to sleep, it's harmless.
Now, without further ado!
It's so sharp! It sliced through the front tires!
Now it's throwing us back!
S-So that's what it's trying to do... Shit! Everyone hang on!
Next Episode
I hear you, I hear you.
Do not make a sound!
You can sense the enemy's location by scent, can't you?
Now the water is chasing after Jotaro!
If we can find the user, our chances of
defeating this powerful Stand are good.
That's Iggy.
Episode 26
Iggy's The Fool and
N'Doul's Divine Geb
Part 2