Oh, a new page...
It's coming in...
Oingo and Boingo, the best bros,
took the bus that came four hours later.
They avoided the accident!
What exciting future adventure awaits these best bros?
Suddenly, as they entered the city of Aswan...
"Oh! There they are!"
"The five meanie bad guys are here!"
The three of them were blabbing at each other.
They seemed a bit worried...
It's them.
Then they drank some black tea with poison in it. Gulp!
B-Big bro...
So all we gotta do is poison 'em.
Little bro, we're invincible together!
With your comic Stand that predicts the future...
And my Stand...
...which transforms my face...
They'll be dead meat!
Our cards are the God of Knowledge, Thoth,
and the God of Creation, Khnum!
We're the Oingo Boingo Brothers!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 27:
Oingo's Divine Khnum and Boingo's Divine Thoth
It's definitely at this café...
...and at this table...
...where they'll drink the poisoned black tea.
Th-The predictions made by my Stand,
the God of Knowledge, Thoth, always come true.
How are they doing?
Abdul's neck wound wasn't anything serious, so he's being released tomorrow, but...
...Kakyoin wasn't as fortunate.
He could go blind.
That's not good...
It's unfortunate, but Kakyoin could be out for the rest of our journey.
Hey, there's a bunch of cafés around here!
Let's get a drink and relax.
Good idea. Which one?
My cigarette says that one.
Welcome.
What can I get for you?
Let's see... I'll have some black tea.
Same.
So, three black teas?
No, it's better we don't.
Listen. Egypt is enemy territory.
More enemies are lurking around us than ever before, and we don't know where or when they'll attack.
We have to be careful about poisoned goods.
From now on, only drink from bottles or cans.
What? Seriously?
Seriously.
Hey, forget the black tea and bring us cola.
Cola?!
Yeah. Is there a problem?
N-No. Right. Cola, yes?
Three colas coming up...
Oh, and we'll take the caps off ourselves at the table.
Also, make it the third, fourth, and fifth colas from the right.
C-Cola with the caps on?
I won't be able to poison them...
Was the prediction wrong?
N-No, little bro's comic is always right!
J-Just believe! I gotta believe in my little bro!
If I, his big brother, don't give my all to
fulfill our destiny, we'll never defeat them!
Big bro, the predictions are absolute!
Hey, Manager! This cola is warm!
You think you can get away with serving warm cola?
You can't make me pay, jackass!
Wait, the cola isn't cold?
Th-The refrigerator is broken...
You're way too paranoid!
Even if that guy's our enemy,
and he was really trying to poison us...
...how the hell would he know we came here?
This city has loads of cafés,
and we just randomly decided on this one.
There's no way they tracked us down here.
All I'm saying is that it doesn't hurt to be careful.
If you're that concerned, we can go somewhere else.
Let's head to the place across the street.
Fire!
My café is on fire!
Some asshole left their cigarette in the road,
and it spread to the trash!
Hey, Manager. We'll have those three black teas after all.
W-We did it...
Man, for someone to leave a lit cigarette near the trash...
This world is full of terrible people.
They're drinking it... They're drinking it!
D-D-D-Drink it all down...
Th-They drank it!
That dog took my cake!
Who the hell let a dog in here?
Iggy!
Whose dog is this?!
Hey! Get this mutt out of here!
Dammit, Iggy!
Stop, you fucking dog!
Blast it! It was right in their mouths!
Goddammit! What's supposed to happen next?
I-It doesn't say yet...
B-But... the prediction wasn't wrong.
Thoth can only see the very near future.
This time...
This time, we'll take full advantage
of your prediction and kill them for sure!
Yes... We're...
The Oingo Boingo Brothers!
"That mutt! Curses! We failed!"
"And we were so close!"
Big bro Oingo and little bro Boingo were so frustrated.
But after they pulled themselves together,
Oingo and Boingo chased after those three guys and their dog.
As they chased them, though this isn't really important,
the bros saw a guy with a super annoying face.
The bros really hated this type of guy!
I bet he did something horrible in a past life...
It's got me pissed all of a sudden. I'll punch him!
Even though he didn't do anything wrong,
Oingo pointlessly punched him in the face!
The guy with the annoying face freaked out!
He accidentally dropped his wallet stuffed with money.
"Hooray! We're rich!"
The bros sure are lucky! Peace!
What a moron.
W-We hit the jackpot, big bro.
Ah! B-Big bro, it's coming in.
They continued to chase Joestar and the others.
Joestar and his friends got in a car
and headed to the hospital to see Kakyoin and Abdul.
Oingo planted a bomb shaped like an orange in their car.
Jotaro exploded!
His head split into two bloody halves,
and that was game over for him!
Th-Th-Th-This prediction is so detailed...
Yes!
Div
Divine
Divine Kh
Divine Khnum
O
Oi
Oin
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Oingo
M-M-My Stand, Thoth, can only see the near future.
But once it prints a prediction,
there's no way to change it. At all!
Jotaro will definitely explode!
I rigged the bomb to detonate three seconds after someone digs their finger into the peel!
It can't fail!
His fate...
...is decided!
Who's there?
What are you doing in our car?
That's not Jotaro?
No way! Jotaro said he was going right to the hospital.
Be careful!
C-Crap...
Don't let him get away!
C-Crap! It's Joestar and Polnareff!
Yeah, I know!
Hey, don't hide in there!
Who the hell are you? Get out!
We said get out, dammit!
Hurry it up!
Hey, hey, why the panic?
Polnareff, it's just me.
Oh, it's just Jotaro.
My Stand, Divine Khnum, is a transforming Stand.
I can change my height, weight, and even smell, to whatever I want.
I made the hat by transforming my hair!
But what's the deal?
Didn't you say you were heading straight for the hospital?
I forgot a thing in the car, so I came back for it.
My wallet, that's what I forgot!
Give me a break.
Jotaro, what happened to your school jacket?
S-School jacket?
W-What? What? School jacket?
This isn't very fashionable for you.
Ah... Right, school jacket...
I-It's at the cleaners!
I brought it to the cleaners, but I was all outta dough.
Th-That was a good answer. Yeah!
Huh... I see...
Then hurry up and get in the car. We're leaving.
Huh?
Huh? In the car?
N-No way...
No way... No way...
The Jotaro that gets his head blown in half...
I-It can't be the real Jotaro!
That means... I-I-I-It's going to be me!
Impossible!
Nah, a-actually, I-I think I'll go for a stroll...
What the hell are you talking about, Jotaro?
It'll be much faster to take a car from here.
Big bro Oingo!
C-Crap...
I have to get out of this Jotaro disguise quickly!
O-Otherwise I'll be the one that gets blown up!
I-I know! I'll throw the orange away!
I just need to get rid of the bomb, then put it back in the car later.
That way the real Jotaro will blow up instead!
Yes!
What a relief... I'm safe!
Hey, it's Iggy!
He must have jumped in the car while we were moving.
He's got an orange in his mouth!
Did you steal that, Iggy?
That could make a nice gift for Kakyoin.
Wha-?!
Holy cow!
Holy cow?
Since when did you start yelling weird things like that?
N-No... Holy cow... Like, cow...
I-I just saw a cow in front of us.
Jotaro, you're acting really weird today.
You look scared shitless.
You aren't...
...an imposter, right?
G-Give me a break.
What the fuck are you talking about, Polnareff?
Have we reached the hospital yet?
Say, Jotaro. Do that special trick of yours.
Special... trick?
What is he talking about?!
You taught it to me.
You know, like this!
Whoa, not half bad!
R-Right, that's what you mean.
I'm saved! If that's all there is to it,
I can do it in spite of how dangerous it is!
Hell yeah! I'll do it. Piece of cake.
All right!
Do the one where you have five in your mouth at once, Jotaro!
F-Five?!
Just hurry up and do it. I wanna see it again!
S-Shit. What kind of weird habit does Jotaro have?!
I-If I can't do it...
...they'll become even more suspicious,
and I'm acting strange enough already!
Polnareff looks like he might start
peeling the orange bomb at any time!
A-All right, dammit!
I'll do it!
F-Five, right? Five...
Hurry up and do it!
I can do this! I'm gonna do this!
I'm really gonna do this, right?!
All right! My secret talent!
Hot, hot!
H-Hot... Hot...
I did it! Goddamn, I did it!
There! How was that? I did it!
You can do anything when your life depends on it!
Here.
Last time you drank some juice while the cigarettes were still lit.
You can do it!
Aw, you failed!
Jotaro, are you okay?
Oh my God!
Little bro! Little bro, Boingo!
Make this prediction go away!
Get rid of that page!
Big bro Oingo! The prediction is absolute!
Hurry and release that transformation!
If you undo the transformation,
then the real Jotaro will blow up instead!
You can do it!
Jotaro, you're acting really weird today.
I-I just... f-feel a bit shitty...
C-Confound it!
Knowing these guys,
once they get suspicious, they'll keep prodding me!
If I undo the transformation, they'll kill me.
But if I don't, then the bomb will instead!
Th-That's it! I can use feeling sick as an excuse!
If I tell them I have a stomach ache, they'll let me out of the car!
Jotaro, the way your hands are put together...
You have your left thumb on top!
C-Cripes! Does the real Jotaro always put his right thumb on top?!
Crap! What do I do?
H-H-H-How can I fool them now?!
The way you put your hands together
proves you were a woman in a past life!
My fortune said that since I put my
right thumb on top, I was a man in a past life!
Huh, really? I always put my left thumb on top.
Mr. Joestar, that means you were definitely a lady in a past life!
What do you mean, definitely?
How the hell would you prove that?!
That's bullshit!
M-My stomach is really starting to hurt...
Staying with these guys is going to kill me...
A-All right... I'll tell them about the stomach ache!
Jotaro, let's see who can eat a whole orange faster!
What?!
H-H-H-Hey...
Don't, dumbass!
Whoa! What the hell, Jotaro?
W-What's wrong, Jotaro?
Uh, it's nothing.
You really are acting weird.
Uh, that orange i-i-i-is probably spoiled now...
Huh? How?
W-Well, you know... That's the one Iggy picked up...
It could've been floating in the gutter...
Have a different one.
It isn't dirty or bruised. Looks fine to me.
Whatever. I'll have this one, and you can have one of the others.
God, it hurts!
H-Hey...
My stomach hurts!
My stomach is fucking killing me!
S-Stop the car! Hurry!
Your stomach hurts?
I can't stand it anymore! Lemme out! Lemme out!
I'll do it behind a rock!
But the hospital's just over there!
Just go ahead without me. Seriously, just go ahead!
Hold it, Jotaro!
Take some toilet paper.
I...
I did it!
I actually got away, goddammit!
I finally got away! Eat it!
I can finally undo my transformation behind that rock!
So Iggy picked this orange up off the ground, huh?
Maybe it really was in the gutter.
What should I do?
Throw it away?
Hooray! I can finally use
Divine Khnum's power to undo my transformation!
Victory is mine!
The Oingo Boingo Brothers win!
We win!
Oh fuck!
Huh, what was that?
Don't worry about it. Probably construction or something.
B-Big bro Oingo...
Hang in there!
We've lost, Boingo.
No...
N-No! My Divine Thoth hasn't lost yet. I-I'll k-kill them myself!
Boingo...
Don't, Boingo.
Those guys aren't normal. It's impossible.
I've made up my mind! I'll do it on my own!
Just me!
You were always so shy... You've grown up, Boingo!
I'm gonna do it!
What's Thoth's next prediction?
Found you...
Th-They're the ones! They hit me and stole my wallet!
Fellas, if you beat the shit out of them,
I'll make it worth your while!
It's that guy!
Big bro! I'm so scared!
Although he had resolved to defeat them,
Boingo had no time for revenge.
But don't lose faith, Boingo!
That's just how life can be.
Huh?
Well, if it isn't Jotaro!
Yo, took long enough.
Long enough?
You sure take quick dumps!
You beat us here without a car...
...and your jacket is already back from the cleaners?
What the fuck are you two...
Oh, an ambulance.
Looks pretty bad.
That's unfortunate...
Oranges, huh? I was feeling thirsty.
I'll take one.
Oh?
That man's clothes...
You know him?
Nah, never seen him.
Now, let's go see how Abdul and Kakyoin are doing.
The brothers were taken out of the battle together.
The fight was over before Jotaro
and the others could even realize it had begun.
Ba-dum tsh.
Shinjiteruze
I believe in ya!
Shinjiteruyo
I believe in you!
Oingo Boingo Brothers
Oingo Boingo Brothers!
Ore wa Oingo henshin dekiru
The name is Oingo and I can transform!
Shinchou taijuu nioi made mo
My height, weight, and even smell...
Omoi no mama saa
...I can make them whatever I want!
Dare ni mo barenai satorarenai
Nobody will find out or even suspect a thing.
Souzou no kami Khnum
The God of Creation, Khnum!
Boku wa Boingo manga de yogen
I'm Boingo and I can predict the future with my comic.
Kanarazu ataruyo machigaenainda
The predictions it makes will always come true!
Totemo uchiki de itsumo hitoribochi sa
I'm really shy and always alone...
Shomotsu no kami Thoth
The God of Knowledge, Thoth!
Subete subete umaku iku
Everything, everything, will always go our way!
Sou yatte kita darou
That's how it's always been, hasn't it?
Insatsu ni deta yogen wa
The prophecy written in the book...
Mou keshite kaerukoto wa dekinai
...can never, ever, be changed.
Yogen no toori koto sureba
If we do everything according to what the prophecy says...
Subete umaku iku
Everything will always go our way!
Sou yatte kita darou
That's how it's always been, hasn't it?
Oingo Boingo Brothers
Oingo Boingo Brothers!
Shinjiteruze
I believe in ya!
Shinjiteruyo
I believe in you!
Oingo Boingo Brothers
Oingo Boingo Brothers!
Kujikecha damedayo shinsei to wa sou iu mono dakara
Just remember to never lose faith, because that's what it means to be divine!
Next Episode
Hey, look at that! It's a katana!
You have a katana.
I-It's stuck! It won't budge!
Now I feel like slicing you up, too.
Wield me, and kill!
Have at it! Show me that Divine Anubis Stand of yours.
Episode 28
Divine Anubis Part 1