Who's that?! Someone's coming!
I don't know who he is, but he's not normal!
Polnareff!
Either way, I'll kill him!
A playing card?
Welcome, Master Joestar.
We have been awaiting your arrival.
I am the butler of this mansion.
You may call me D'Arby.
D'Arby?
Yes. Terence T. D'Arby.
The man who you previously
defeated beyond recovery, Daniel J. D'Arby...
...is my older brother.
You're D'Arby the Gambler's younger brother?!
Are you here to avenge your brother?
Not at all. I wouldn't dream of it.
Didn't he tell you this already?
The fault lies with the loser for being deceived in battle.
I also believe this to be true.
My brother is at fault for failing.
I bear no ill will towards you.
My brother is my brother, and I am myself.
Do not think any differently.
He is ten years my senior.
I respect my brother to an extent,
but we come from different generations.
He's the type of man who has to
rely on deception and cheating to win.
He was only capable of defeating those
who were either old-fashioned or complete amateurs.
It would seem Lord Dio also recognized this,
which is why he chose me to be his butler.
What's the matter?
If you are so eager to fight me, please, step into the mansion.
Everyone, do not carelessly rush inside.
There's no time for this. Hurry and take us to Dio.
Jotaro! Be careful! He's trying something!
Terence T. D'Arby.
His Stand, Divine Atum, suggests the God, Atum!
H-Hey, he brought out his Stand!
Don't see that too often.
It has been quite some time since we
faced someone who openly used their Stand.
So who will it be?
Who shall my first opponent be?
What a pain in the ass! Jotaro, give him a good beating!
Let's make a bet.
The first attack Star Platinum will attempt to use against me...
...is a left-handed blow.
He will try to attack me with a punch using his left arm.
Let's make a bet.
It doesn't matter!
It's all the same if you hit him with everything you got!
Do it!
Hurry up and hit him, Jotaro!
Ora!
What? H-He dodged?
He's so fast!
Inconceivable!
Such a shame. I suppose I've lost this bet.
I enjoy gambling like my brother,
but I am not very good at it.
To reward you for besting me,
allow me to take you to a fantastical world.
What? A hole...
Curses! It really was a trap!
Jotaro!
Jotaro's being pulled into the hole!
Get him out!
Very well. You gentlemen may enter, as well.
Wha-
Mr. Joestar! Kakyoin!
Wait! It is too dangerous to follow them!
Abdul, can you hear me?
If you don't hear from us in ten minutes, set the mansion on fire!
Got it, Abdul?!
Mr. Joestar!
Episode 40: D'Arby the Gamer Part 1
This illusion... Are we above ground, or below?
The feeling of water at my feet... This reality...
It's too convincing...
What the hell is he up to?
Gramps, Kakyoin... Explain this mystery to me.
His Stand...
It definitely knew I would throw a right punch.
But how?
If we can't solve this mystery, he'll beat us for sure.
Would you care for a drink?
The drinks are real, of course,
and I assure you they are not poisoned.
Are we inside the mansion?
Indeed.
Where inside the mansion?
I cannot say.
Are we below ground?
Perhaps.
Was this illusion created by a Stand?
Indeed.
Is it your Stand's power?
It is not.
Is it Dio's?
Whose is it?
You needn't know.
According to the Speedwagon Foundation's intel,
there are at least two or three other Stand users here.
Is that true?
You needn't know.
I guess we're not getting any straight answers out of you.
I could lie to you if I wished.
But unlike my brother, I refuse to lie or play tricks.
So what's your point?
If we aren't able to defeat you, we can't proceed?
Exactly!
That's the right idea!
His needlessly polite attitude...
It's starting to get on my nerves.
Did you forget this is one against three?
We're in a hurry, and the three of us are prepared to fight you.
Please, no need to rush.
Before you do that, I have something to show you...
My collection.
Collection?
While not quite to the same extent as my brother,
I also enjoy collecting things.
Indeed, one likes to hear compliments about
their precious collection when showing it to others.
They can't be...
Dolls? A-Are those really dolls?
No, Kakyoin.
We're dealing with one of the D'Arby brothers.
They can't just be normal dolls!
D-D'Arby...
Will you please speak to me?
I'm begging you, speak to me!
Speak to me!
Oh my God!
They're alive... These dolls are alive!
You freak! They're souls!
My hobby is doll making.
However, I like to have real souls inhabit them.
Perhaps showing you this was ill-advised,
but such is the power of my Stand.
My brother found pleasure in lining up his little soul coins in a row,
but I found that rather simple and mundane.
I change their clothes and even speak to them on occasion.
For example...
This young woman's name is Sonia.
D'Arby! Oh, D'Arby!
I love when she tells me her beautiful love stories.
D'Arby...
Isn't her skin beautiful?
It makes me proud to show off a beauty like her.
D'Arby...
Dr. Elliott is a serial killer. He killed eight people.
I love when he tells me about the people he murdered.
I constructed his glasses and stethoscope myself.
Oh, that's right!
There's still something I haven't shown you!
A young lad from Japan; the video game master, Tatsuhiko!
His IQ of 190 makes him quite formidable.
Beating him and taking his soul was no simple task.
Mama... Mama! Mama!
You and your brother are lunatics.
Actually, you're probably even worse than him.
You're getting on my nerves!
You act like a gentleman, but you're nothing but scum.
You make me sick.
By the way, I'm sure you're aware of this from your run-in with my brother, but...
...aren't human souls truly a mystery?
Once a person has admitted defeat,
the energy in their soul instantly drops to almost nothing.
I prepare for that moment and take their soul!
This is how my brother's Stand and mine work!
We've heard enough! You're really getting on my nerves!
We'll make quick work of you, then move on!
You haven't heard quite enough yet!
You should know, Jotaro,
that you have no choice but to play at my pace.
Jotaro, it gave you quite a shock when
I correctly predicted which arm you would use, didn't it?
How exactly I did it must still be a mystery to you.
At that moment, I just barely grazed your soul.
What do you think happened when I did that?
W-What?!
What the hell is that?!
I left my Atum's hand attached to your soul.
If I were to crush your arm,
I'm sure it would greatly please Lord Dio.
However, if I did that, Kakyoin and Joestar
would instantly attack me, and I would be deftly defeated.
I would rather avoid that.
So how about this, gentlemen?
Why don't we play a little game and gamble our souls?
What?
If I admit absolute defeat, I will let go of his arm.
Gimme a break. No choice but to stay at your pace, huh?
True as it is, you're gonna regret ever tricking me, D'Arby.
I would be absolutely tickled if you said, "I will play a game and bet my soul."
However, the first to play will be...
...Kakyoin. You're up first.
Hey, what gives?
I should be the first to beat your ass.
You and Joestar are related by blood,
and as such, share no such relation to Kakyoin.
If I succeeded in taking your souls, and Kakyoin decided not to
attempt to win them back, he may choose to attack me with his Stand.
You're really full of yourself.
You talk like you won already.
Very well. I'll be your first opponent.
What?
Kakyoin!
It's fine. I feel confident.
I happen to have some experience playing video games.
I challenge you to a game of F★Mega.
★
I bet my soul!
Di
Divi
Divine
Divine At
Te
Divine Atum
Tere
Teren
Terenc
Terence
Terence T
Terence T.
Terence T. D'
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Terence T. D'A
Terence T. D'Ar
Terence T. D'Arby
I bet my soul!
Good!
Kakyoin!
You don't need to go first.
I have to.
Since you have that thing attached to your arm,
there's a chance you could make a mistake.
D'Arby, do we have your word that if you lose, your Stand will let go of Jotaro's arm?
There's nothing wrong with the TV, console, or game cartridge.
You could find this video game anywhere in the world.
Do not confuse me for my brother. I shall not cheat.
Now, let us begin.
Sure.
F★Mega!
★
Select your car.
Start by selecting your car.
Right.
So you decided on car #28, eh?
Mine is #15, since I was born on January 5th.
Are you ready?
Enough pleasantries, just go!
Race start in...
Five...
That technique he's using to quickly mash the acceleration button...
It's so he can get a boost start!
Three...
Damn! I won't be able to get a boost like this!
Two...
He's going to get ahead of me!
One...
Start!
He's blocking me!
My victory is assured if I can keep this up.
He'll never be able to get past me at this point!
And unfortunately for you,
I, D'Arby, never make a mistake during a race!
How terribly naïve of you, Kakyoin!
What?!
Kakyoin, just how much have you played this game before?
You needn't know.
All right!
This is your chance, Kakyoin!
Get your car back on course, and keep going!
That technique just now...
Pulling off something like that
goes beyond being experienced at F★Mega...
★
He has a bold personality despite his outward anxious appearance.
It's a tie! They're right next to each other!
No. Kakyoin ended up on the outside.
If they hit a corner together,
whoever's on the outside is shit out of luck.
355 kilometers per hour... 358... 360...
We'll hit the first corner in three seconds!
I can take the corner at this speed!
I'll go through it at full throttle!
Two... One!
They made it together!
They turned together at the same time and speed!
They're neck and neck!
I've taken a liking to you, Kakyoin!
You aren't phased in the slightest despite gambling your soul!
You've risen above fear for the sake of the game.
As someone who is capable of competing with me at this level,
I deem you worthy to be a part of my doll collection!
Kakyoin Noriaki thought to himself...
Me? Rise above fear?
Thanks. I've had training.
Six months ago, when I met your master, Dio...
...he planted a flesh bud in my brain,
showing me the true meaning of fear.
In that moment...
The moment I met Dio...
I realized what a terrifying monster he truly was.
I lost feeling in my legs,
every hair on my body stood on end, and I froze in place.
As I stared at Dio in a frozen panic,
the paralysis made my hair stand on end even more.
My stomach convulsed, and I became nauseous.
I nearly threw up.
Then Dio spoke these words as he gazed at me...
His voice was gentle, as if speaking to a child.
"Kakyoin...
...you have nothing to fear.
Let us be friends."
I despise what I thought next! After I heard that...
...I was relieved.
To be honest, I felt relief from the bottom of my heart.
It gave me relief to know I would keep on living!
But... it was humiliating. I can't forgive him!
I've never felt so humiliated.
I couldn't forgive myself.
I despised myself for giving in to him.
Jotaro saved me, and that's why I went on this journey.
I will never return to being that pathetic Kakyoin ever again!
D'Arby, that's why I decided to gamble my soul in this challenge!
Three... two... one!
They went together again!
The third corner!
That's why I, Kakyoin Noriaki, refuse to allow my nerves to make me mess up even once!
I'll show you!
All right! The fifth corner! Together again!
They keep going through them at the same time!
K-Kakyoin... you...
Next is the sixth corner!
A boost tunnel is visible once you pass the sixth corner.
Going through the tunnel allows you to reach speeds of up to 850 kilometers per hour!
I must enter the tunnel no matter what!
But the tunnel is only big enough to accommodate one car!
If they keep racing neck and neck,
one of them won't be able to enter the tunnel!
The sixth corner!
Again, they're going together!
It's the tunnel! I see the tunnel!
Kakyoin, don't let him push you out!
It seems you haven't realized yet, Kakyoin.
Do you think you can just push me out?
Take a look at your #28's remaining power.
K-Kakyoin has less!
At the race's start, you spun and were blown away by my blocking maneuver.
Didn't you realize you would have less energy after that?!
Two seconds until the tunnel.
You're gonna crash!
Let him have the lead!
Go into the tunnel after D'Arby!
I can't!
If I let him enter the tunnel first, I'll have no chance of winning!
One second until the tunnel!
Kakyoin!
Whoa! He tilted his car!
I never thought you would enter on the wall!
Y-You did it, Kakyoin!
Your mental game is stronger than his!
Keep going!
Silence! You're a distraction!
He's ramming him!
It matters not how little power I have remaining!
I'll take this next turn even if it's only
one hundredth of a second faster than Kakyoin!
I'll take the shortest path even if
it's only by one thousandth of a milimeter!
And I'll get through this tunnel even if it's but a moment faster!
No radar.
H-Hey, what's wrong? I can't see them anymore!
We have to make it through the tunnel in total darkness.
What?!
An absolute darkness where radar is completely useless!
There are eight curves, a mine, and a cannon.
The tunnel's exit lies at the end of the darkness.
One mistake and you'll hit the wall.
But I've memorized the timing needed to take each corner!
And so has D'Arby...
That sound means he's taking a corner.
What's going on? Where the hell are they?!
Who's going faster?
Three...
Two...
One!
Cannon!
For a second, I saw them in the light of the cannon blast!
Kakyoin is only a bit behind!
I can see the exit! They're exiting the tunnel!
D'Arby is definitely going faster!
He's ahead by a car length!
Victory is mine!
Next Episode
I never let my guard down regardless of the situation.
You have less power remaining!
In my hands, I now hold his soul.
Quit screwing around, Jotaro!
I know the rules of baseball.
You can't back out now!
I expected more encouraging words under these circumstances.
Episode 41
D'Arby the Gamer Part 2
It's pathetic!