W-What? What are you saying, Jotaro?!
You heard me.
Or are you already going deaf, Gramps?
I said I'm gonna declare my pitch.
I'll pitch straight, high to the outside.
Jotaro!
Do you believe me, or not?
Are you that foolish?
My Stand is able to see an opponent's soul much like how one sees with night vision.
There isn't a single human with a soul capable of lying.
Yes or no? Right or left?
I can discover the answers to these questions simply by asking.
Outside or inside? High or low? A changeup? A straight?
I will know the correct answer with one hundred percent accuracy.
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 42: The Desolate Void: Vanilla Ice Part 1
A straight, high to the outside?
Yes or no?
Jotaro isn't lying. A straight, high to the outside...
That is what he will pitch.
What is he up to?
Apparently he defeated my brother by bluffing,
but does he think that will actually work on me?
What a fool.
Here goes.
Don't forget that the game will end
once an eleven point difference is reached!
What?! It was a changeup?!
It went right through! Impossible! It turned!
It's a hit!
But the infielder throws to first, and he's out!
I-Impossible...
I was certain he chose a straight, high to the outside...
Even if he were a holy man like Buddha, or a genius con artist like my brother, he couldn't possibly possess that kind of control over his soul!
I'm going with a straight, high to the outside again.
H-He's not lying this time, either. He's serious!
Jotaro... You aren't cheating, are you?
I am! I am!
What?!
He really is cheating!
A forkball, low to the inside!
Pitcher catches pop fly!
Out!
He's cheating... Jotaro, you cheater!
Did you rig the game console?!
It isn't rigged?
I know for a fact you're cheating!
How are you doing this?
H-He isn't responding...
Shit! It has to be a yes or no question to work!
Looks like your mind-reading questions
can only be answered with yes or no.
It's just like your brother said...
"It isn't cheating unless you get caught."
"It isn't cheating unless you get caught," is it?
How dare you speak as if you know better than I do!
Who do you think you're speaking to?
Pitch, Jotaro!
I'll figure out your little trick, then wrench out your soul!
So, shall we continue?
My next pitch will be...
A straight, high to the outside.
Jotaro's soul isn't deceiving me...
He's positive he'll pitch straight, high to the outside.
I'll figure it out! I'll figure it out!
I'll figure out how you're cheating, no matter what!
The will of his soul still hasn't changed...
It keeps repeating "Yes!" He's seriously going to do it!
Here it comes!
It's still saying "Yes!" He threw a straight!
But now it's dropping! It's a forkball!
What?! It changed course!
Out! Three outs! Change!
Bottom of the 1st
I don't understand! I just don't understand how he's cheating!
Up until the very last second,
Jotaro's soul showed the will to pitch straight!
Yet somehow the pitch changed!
Why? Why is this happening?!
You're finished, D'Arby.
Shut up!
T-Taking your hat off was suspicious!
The cheating began the moment you took it off!
Stand up! I'm going to inspect your seat and controller!
Sh-Shit! I don't understand!
I don't understand, but I'm sure you're using your hat to cheat!
Am I right?
You're using something here to cheat, right?
Are you using Star Platinum to cheat?
And yet somehow you're still cheating, Jotaro?!
Shit! I... I know I can read people's souls!
And I know I'm reading Jotaro's soul accurately!
So why are all of his pitches different from my readings?!
It looks like... he's starting to get older.
He doesn't look like a twenty-something kid anymore.
D'Arby, it's your turn to pitch.
Hurry up and do it.
Four-three...
I can score another run in no time...
I'm an expert gamer...
I can never lose...
I'm an expert gamer! I can never lose!
My mind, too, is invincible from countless battles!
A master of games is a master of life itself!
I won't let this damage my reputation!
Fair! Home run!
That's the fifth run for the Jaguars!
Five-three!
C-Curses! I accidentally released his soul!
Kakyoin's soul is back! He's coming to!
N-No! No! I haven't admitted defeat!
It was an accident! I let go of his soul by accident!
Deep in your heart, you admitted defeat,
and that's why his soul went free.
Th-The controller... Joseph's Stand is holding it...
O-Oh, whoops.
To think something so idiotic...
That means the person... using the controller... Shit...
...wasn't actually Jotaro, but you, Joseph Joestar!
That's right, D'Arby.
I bet your brother would have easily caught us cheating.
Anyway, Gramps...
I'm glad you got the idea without me signaling you.
You can bet I'll always know what you're thinking!
You're my grandson, after all.
Get it together, Kakyoin.
Shit... How underhanded...
Now where were we...
Our last order of business is getting rid of him.
P-Please forgive me! I gave you back Kakyoin's soul!
Everything is as it should be!
Forgive me, please? Please? Please?!
If you wanna know if we'll forgive you,
how about reading our souls?
Here's a question for you;
Am I gonna hit you with my right fist, or my left?
Take a guess.
P-Please, will you just lightly hit me with your right?
Y-Your left?
B-Both of them?!
Are you really gonna "Ora Ora" me?!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Oh my God!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Terence T. D'Arby retires!
Terence T. D'Arby
Unable to Recover (Retires)
Ora!
It looks like we broke through some kind of wall!
Let's get the hell out of here! Jotaro! Kakyoin!
Gimme a break.
Forgive me for disturbing your rest.
I believe you are already aware, but about ten minutes ago...
...Joestar's group infiltrated the mansion.
In addition, I must report that D'Arby has fallen.
D'Arby was a true genius.
Why do you think D'Arby lost,
even though he easily could have won?
You may enter, Vanilla Ice.
Pardon my intrusion.
The Joestars are still trying to save that woman, and have shown they are willing to cast their lives aside to achieve this.
This still leaves Kakyoin and the other two.
Let's see...
Oh, yes. Abdul and Polnareff, in a vain attempt to defeat the mighty Dio,
have shown complete disregard for their own well-being.
They've deluded themselves into believing that
giving up on defeating the mighty Dio is akin to giving up on life itself.
Such a foolish notion.
Regardless, this foolish notion is important to them.
And D'Arby, despite swearing to me his undying loyalty,
has proven he was unwilling to lay down his life for the mighty Dio.
Ultimately, that is why he failed.
D'Arby will never understand why he lost.
Ice...
Look at the wound on my neck.
It is likely that once I have consumed the blood of just one more
person, this body of Jonathan Joestar's that has thus far resisted me...
...will completely fall under my control,
and with it my wound will heal.
Ice...
Will you offer me your blood?
Yes. With pleasure.
Please accept it!
You decapitated yourself...
This pleases me.
However, Vanilla Ice...
I refuse to accept blood from someone of your worth.
I shall heal my wound with the blood of another.
You needn't die for this.
Return to life with my blood.
With your resolve, I am certain you will triumph.
Lord... Dio...
Returning to life in your own body is ideal.
It is instantly familiar.
I shall leave them to you, Vanilla Ice.
Lord Dio...
I shall meet your expectations.
I shall eliminate them, without fail.
Would it kill you to use the door?
Such is to be expected of a Stand that can vanish from this world.
V
Va
Van
Vanil
Vanilla
Vanilla I
Vanilla Ic
Vanilla Ice
The ten minutes we promised them have passed.
Mr. Joestar instructed us to set this place aflame, but... I believe we must enter the mansion!
Yeah.
Polnareff, I must tell you something before we enter.
Even if you become lost or sustain a serious injury
within the mansion, I will not come to your aid.
Iggy, this goes for you, too.
It may be harsh, but the goal of our journey is to defeat Dio.
Promise me that even if I am defeated, or otherwise become separated from you, that you will not stop to help me.
Your own safety comes first.
We must not be defeated trying to save one another.
Yeah, you're right, Abdul.
If we make it out alive, you better treat me to some gourmet eats.
I will treat you and Iggy both.
All right, let's do it!
Silver Chariot!
Hey, Abdul... What now?
It looks like it never ends.
Mr. Joestar instructed us to set the mansion aflame,
but... burning this labyrinth would only put us in harm's way.
Regardless...
Magician's Red!
These flames are capable of detecting all living things.
Humans, animals who breathe
through their skin, and any moving objects.
It is also capable of detecting Stand energy.
We must watch it closely.
Why are the flames linked together?
They are linked so that each flame will point in a different direction.
As long as the entity is within fifteen meters,
it will detect its size and location.
Mr. Joestar and the others were dragged underground.
We must descend.
The flames have already detected something!
It is to our left!
What?!
The Fool!
Hold up! Who the hell is this?
Look around you, Polnareff!
The labyrinth is disappearing!
It seems the illusion was the work of a Stand user.
It is most fortunate Iggy defeated him so quickly.
This man is named Kenny G.! He retires without a fight!
Name: Kenny G.
Stand Power: Illusions
Retires Without A Fight
Now the mansion appears as it should.
The flames are no longer detecting signs of life.
The moment you turn around...
...you will die.
The flames have not changed...
Iggy's nose has not picked up a scent...
Wh-Who is this?!
Inconceivable! Neither Iggy's nose nor the flames detected it!
It came from nowhere!
Polnareff! Iggy! Look out!
H-Hey, Abdul! Where'd he go?
W-What the hell was that?
W-Where did those arms come from?
H-Hey, Abdul!
Where are you?!
Abdul!
Hey, where are you?!
Wh-What the fuck is that?
Where did it come from?
Why didn't Abdul's flames detect it?
Hey, Iggy!
Why didn't you smell it earlier?
Tell me!
Where are you, Abdul?!
Where did you go?!
Abdul...
...has been disintegrated to death.
I do not know exactly where the void in my mouth leads...
...but I do know it is a dimension of darkness.
I sent him there.
The two of you are next.
I will obliterate any foolish notions you have of defeating Lord Dio!
Bit by bit... One after another...
I, Vanilla Ice, will scatter you throughout my dimension of darkness.
You're lying...
Abdul...
...isn't really dead!
Don't fucking lie to me!
Next Episode
Is this fate telling me to live?
It felt like a wall just collapsed somewhere in the mansion.
It sounds like a battle!
He's really determined!
I will kill you at all costs!
I won't let his determination get the best of me!
I cannot die now.
Eat my sword and go to hell!
Episode 43
The Desolate Void: Vanilla Ice Part 2