Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
The World is clearly much more powerful and precise!
You have shown me enough.
Prepare to meet your end!
The time has come for me to finally eradicate what little remains of the Joestar bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
I shall finish you here and now
with the mighty power of The World!
The World! Time Stop!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
The World!
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Ora!
Episode 47: Dio's World Part 3
At last, the Joestar bloodline will finally cease to exist.
To my greatest of enemies
who dared to interfere with my destiny...
...I bid you farewell!
What?
He moved!
He... Impossible!
Somehow his fingers moved!
I-It can't be...
It can't be!
It can't be... they're the same?
So it's the same kind of Stand as Star Platinum.
The World and Star Platinum are the same kind of Stand?
This brat... Can he see me?
Or is it possible his hand moved subconsciously?
No more time.
Ora Ora!
Were you able to see me just now?
I asked if you could see me, Jotaro!
Who's to say?
I have no idea what the fuck you're talking about, Dio.
Very well! It matters not!
It makes no difference whether you can see me or not while time is stopped!
If you possess the power to move while time is stopped
as I can with The World, then show me!
Indeed, I recall the moment six months ago
when I first learned I could stop time.
To test the speed and power of my Stand,
I ordered my servant to fire a shotgun at me.
But as I prepared to catch the pellets...
...in an instant, it appeared as though
everything had stopped moving.
My first thought was that it was an illusion.
Whether you're a trained boxer during a fight,
or someone faced with a harrowing situation...
...you will experience each moment
during that time as if it were several seconds...
...as I assumed was the case here.
However, The World was still able to move,
allowing it to easily avoid the suspended pellets.
What's more...
...it was even able to grab them!
This isn't an illusion!
Lord Dio!
I am certain you will master this ability to control time!
You must truly believe in your ability to stop time!
It must come as naturally as breathing!
Or as simply as snapping a pencil in half with your fingers!
You must reach the point where it becomes completely natural.
Recognizing this fact is important!
This power must become completely natural to you!
You are the true emperor of this world, after all!
Controlling time must become completely natural to you!
Eventually, I felt the cogs of time
and The World engage one another.
It felt as though a beautiful light had finally pierced the darkness.
Never had I experienced such a magnificent feeling!
I, the mighty Dio, had finally surpassed
every Stand and life form that ever existed!
Although right now I can only stop time for five seconds, my power will continue to grow stronger!
Jotaro! Show me how powerful you really are!
The World! Stop Time!
So you put magnets on me...
Did you do this while I was testing your power earlier?
They must have come from a wallet or pocket planner.
You managed to deceive me.
I mustn't take my eyes off you.
However!
Having to rely on such a simple trick proves to me that
you really are incapable of moving while time is stopped!
All you have done is add mere seconds to what is left of your short existence!
This ends now!
Die, Jotaro!
What?!
H-He... really... can move!
If only for an instant, but he can!
The magnets weren't to trick me into thinking he could move!
They were to trick me into thinking he couldn't,
thus luring me closer!
Controlling time must become completely natural to you!
Of all things... This Joestar descendant...
...had the gall to invade my world of stopped time!
I could only move for an instant... Not long at all...
But gimme a break...
I only got one punch in.
You. Woman.
Fetch me my leg.
Do as I command!
Act as though you are a flight attendant, bringing it to me
as you would caviar and drink to a first-class passenger!
Guess if I don't go for your head, my attacks won't do shit to you.
You already regained your strength.
That hole in your gut completely closed up.
Your eyes followed me, which means you can see
every single move I, the mighty Dio, attempt to make, Jotaro.
Thanks for that.
Kakyoin gave you quite an advantage.
Because he figured out the secret of The World's power...
...it allowed you to figure out that you could move
while time is stopped, and thus invade my world.
But now I'm intrigued...
How long are you capable of moving
within my world of stopped time?
Two seconds? Three seconds?
Or perhaps you can move for five seconds
and are pretending you cannot.
Won't you tell me?
This is bad.
I could move longer if I practiced, but...
...for now, I can only move for an instant.
If I were to guess... I would say you can only move for an instant.
However, since you managed to invade my world of stopped time,
I will no longer underestimate you by coming closer.
In spite of this, the advantage is still mine!
Jotaro, your defeat will come regardless of how long you are capable of moving while time is stopped!
You look pale.
The sight of these knives alone must have made you realize
a fate far worse than Joseph's awaits you!
Asshole!
Where the fuck does he get these ideas?
He's out of his mind.
Escape is futile!
The World!
Five seconds!
Once time resumes, do you think your Star Platinum
will be able to deflect all of my knives at once?
Four seconds!
Bearing witness to your own demise
must be truly terrifying, Jotaro!
Three seconds left...
Ora!
Only two more seconds! Is that the best you can do?
This proves beyond a doubt
you can move for no more than a instant.
One more second...
Zero.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
This is the end.
But have another for good measure.
Honestly, I am quite relieved to be rid of you so swiftly, Jotaro.
I never foresaw you entering my world of stopped time.
To put it in perspective, despite how useful the automobile can be,
it is rendered useless when the streets become overcrowded with them.
Which is why only I, the mighty Dio, should be able to stop time!
Gimme a break...
Throwing all those knives at me...
I paid good money for this uniform...
I stuffed my clothes with magazines
just in case he tried anything, but...
...I didn't expect him to hit me with a barrage of knives...
If I have any hope of getting out of this alive, I need to wait for my chance to strike...
If I don't find a way to smash his head in, he'll kill me.
I must be careful now.
The Joestar bloodline has proven itself rather fortuitous.
He may be acting dead to deceive me.
I must know that he is truly dead!
So to be sure...
...I shall chop off his head!
This will finally put an end to you...
...Jotaro!
Burn in hell, Dio!
Th
The
The W
The Wo
The Worl
The World
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
Burn in hell!
Polnareff!
The World! Time has stopped.
So, it was Polnareff?
Resume time!
What a shame, Polnareff.
With a bit more accuracy, and a little more force behind your blow,
you could have severed my brain stem with your rapier!
B-Bastard! That's impossible...
The mighty Dio never succumbs to sneak attacks!
And as for your little Joestar Egyptian tour group...
Once I am done with you, it shall be completely wiped out!
How'd it come to this? Now he's gonna kill Polnareff.
It would have been best to play dead until
I got my chance to smash his head in, but...
...I need to act now if I want to keep Polnareff alive.
Still, there's no way Dio will enter Star Platinum's range.
It will end just like last time.
I need to make sure he doesn't realize I'm alive.
As long as he's unsure, my chance to strike will come.
But talk about ironic...
I tried as hard as I could to move while he stopped time,
and now I'm struggling to stay still while time is moving...
Farewell, Polnareff!
Jotaro, I heard that!
You're alive... Or at least, you're regaining consciousness...
Don't move! Police!
We have guns!
Put your hands up!
Excellent, perfect timing.
I would like you to shoot someone with that gun of yours.
Use it on the man lying down over there.
Shoot his leg, torso, or wherever you want.
Careful now. We can't have you miss.
Perhaps I only imagined Jotaro made a sound.
You twisted motherfucker...
At least now he's focused on me instead of Polnareff.
He doesn't know what's going on.
He needs to know for sure that I'm dead.
This is really fucked up...
The sound of his breathing...
I cannot hear it. He stopped breathing.
But what about his heartbeat?
This is insane...
If I black out, I'm dead...
This is no laughing matter...
Dying while using my Stand to stop my heart...
He has no heartbeat. Surely he's dead.
Perhaps it really was my imagination.
But just to be sure, I shall chop his head off.
Is this agreeable, Jotaro?
What?!
Ora!
Time Stop!
The World!
I almost blacked out...
Even if you stop time...
...I'll still smash your fucking head in, Dio!
W-What? Impossible...
Ora!
Finally...
I finally smashed his head in...
But that Dio motherfucker survived for
one hundred years at the bottom of the ocean...
He could still be alive.
I can't relax just yet...
I shall kill you!
W-What is this? Impossible! M-My legs...
My legs refuse to move...
I cannot stand up!
This pain in my head... And this nauseous feeling...
How could this happen?
The mighty Dio, afflicted with sickness?
Is the damage he did to my head preventing me from standing up?
Curses! I must act quickly!
You'll be easier to track if I can smell the gasoline on you.
I feel kinda bad kicking a guy while he's down, but...
Nah, actually, I really don't.
My friends and a lot of innocent people died because of you.
The World!
That place...
I must reach that place...
Time... Resume time...
He put his head to the ground to listen for passing cars...
...but...
He's not getting away!
That place! That place!
As long as I reach it...
Your hiding spot is taken. There's no escape.
Give up already, Dio.
The World!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
You fell for it, Jotaro!
This is my escape plan!
You've lost this battle of wits against the mighty Dio!
Does this street look familiar to you?!
This street... I-It can't be!
Exactly.
My escape plan was to take the blood of Joseph Joestar!
Damn you, Dio!
Next Episode
Jotaro...
This was a pretty great trip, huh?
The blood of a Joestar is just what I needed!
This is an amazing high!
Just one simple reason.
Episode 48
A Long Journey's End, and a Farewell to Friends
You pissed me the fuck off.