Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
This building, huh?
I've been repairing roofs in Cairo for forty years,
but I can't say I've seen this place.
My daughter's condition has gotten worse.
She'll only last three or four more days...
I can feel it...
Dio is nearby.
Let us make haste.
If we continue to ask around, we will find him.
It's so freaking hot today...
And I haven't bathed since yesterday...
I'm losing my handsome edge.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
What do you want from me?!
How stupid are you?!
Just buzz off already!
You're a foreigner, so you can't just sit here like a beggar!
Just who do you think you are?!
Oh, are you in need of assistance, traveler?
It isn't much, but take it.
Hey, this is...
Y-You scum! How dare you!
This is my turf, dammit!
Turf?
Hey, Polnareff!
Do not rest there!
And hand the money over to that man!
Is he a beggar?
My apologies. My friend here is still learning the ways of the city.
You could've told me that earlier!
My profession as a beggar doesn't allow me to speak in public!
This city is home to a Beggars' association.
Each beggar is allotted turf
where they may exclusively conduct business.
It is a bit bizarre, but this rule prevents chaos from erupting.
And worse yet, you hurt my pride.
I wonder if I'd earn more dressed as a destitute foreigner...
I should try that out.
Oh yeah, I thought you looked familiar.
Aren't you Abdul the Fortune Teller?
I heard a guy tried to kill you, so you fled to Japan.
I have heard you are quite familiar with this city, which is why I am here to ask a favor of you.
It will be worth your while.
We are looking for the building pictured here,
and we must make haste.
Guess I'm off early today.
I'll find the place in that picture in three hours tops.
You can wait for me here.
Hey... Come to think of it, where did Iggy go?
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 38: Pet Shop: The Gatekeeper of Hell Part 1
No doubt about it...
That's the mansion.
Only took me two hours.
There's nothing in this city I can't find!
Suddenly Iggy thought to himself...
That bird's a Stand user just like me...
Must be some kind of ice Stand.
And it looks like he's protecting that mansion.
He's taking out anyone who tries to enter.
W-Which means, that bird...
...will come for me next!
During ancient times, falcons would freely soar through the Nile Valley,
making them perfect hunters for the ancient Egyptians.
The god of these falcons is known as Horus,
the esteemed guardian deity of the Royal Family.
Falcons are capable of spotting small animals from several kilometers away, which is why they are said to possess the Eye of Horus.
The design of the Eye of Horus symbolizes fortune and glory.
This bird is known as Pet Shop.
His Stand represents a god of the heavens, Horus.
Iggy again thought to himself...
L-Looks like I found the mansion
Joestar and the others are looking for, where that Dio guy lives...
Also...
It was definitely his Stand's power that made that hunk of ice.
Guess that makes him a guard bird acting like a guard dog.
But ya gotta be kidding me...
I've got nothing to do with this Dio guy!
I was dragged to Egypt against my will to travel with Joestar's pack!
No way in hell I'll fight!
All I want is a cushy life, to chase some tail,
and to live out the rest of my days in peace.
There's no way I'll do something as stupid as fighting
a violent asshole like him, especially if I get nothing out of it!
I'll just act like a dumb dog so he won't pay attention to me.
Those eyes...
I can't get a good read on him from the way he's looking at me...
I'm pretty sure I could beat him with my Stand,
but I'll keep up the dumb dog act, anyway.
This doesn't concern me!
Hurry and go back to the mansion, you birdbrain!
Oh, there's a bird.
What's with this bird? It's not getting out of the way!
I-I can't stop!
I-I'm gonna run it over!
W-What was with that bird?
H-How did it fit under my car?
What kind of bird charges towards a car
without even trying to get out of the way?
C-Crazy bastard...
Either way, looks like he lost interest in me.
He's only attacking when someone tries to enter the mansion.
Because of him, even if Joestar's pack somehow finds this place,
they'll have a hell of a time trying to break in.
Well, it ain't my problem.
Chibi! Buchi!
Chibi! Buchi! Where'd you go?
Hey, have you seen my dogs?
Their names are Chibi and Buchi.
Quit yer yappin'! What're ya asking a dog for?
It's not like I'll start talking or somethin'! Are you stupid or what?
Th-That collar...
It's Chibi's collar!
How did Chibi's collar get under the gate?
It's covered in blood!
Chibi and Buchi...
Is he talking about those two big guys from earlier?
Chibi! Buchi!
Hey, you can't...
You're not trying to slip under that gate, are ya?
He'll kill you!
Chibi! Buchi! Are you there?
Chibi! Buchi!
This ain't my problem.
Doesn't matter to me if some human kid dies.
Survival of the fittest is the law of nature.
Idiots die. So do the careless.
I don't need any more trouble.
Later.
Chibi! Buchi! Where are you?
Come back!
He's eating them! No!
Ya gotta be kidding me.
Turning my back on some kid who likes dogs...
...ain't my style!
Div
Divine
Divine Hor
P
Divine Horus
Pe
Pet
Pet S
Pet Sh
Pet Sho
Pet Shop
Chibi! Buchi!
Dammit, since I'm here...
...I guess I'll fight!
It would appear Pet Shop has finally realized Iggy is a Stand user like himself.
You birdbrain! Come at me! I'll kill ya!
The average speed of a falcon's descent is over three hundred kilometers per hour.
No other organism is capable of reaching such speeds.
A falcon will rip out the vital organs of its prey
with its razor-sharp black talons while hunting.
Even while traveling at three hundred kilometers per hour,
it is still able to pinpoint the vital organs of its prey.
What? Is he smiling at me?
It looked like the side of his beak edged up a little!
A smiling bird?
W-What the hell?
Something's not right...
The air's gone cold...
Th-There's ice on the ground!
Crap!
My feet got stuck to the ground while I wasn't paying attention!
My Stand's feet, too...
Damn!
Icicles!
But seriously, Abdul...
Do you really think that sunglasses guy can find Dio's mansion?
If he is unable to, then nobody will.
He knows the complex layout of Cairo better than anyone else.
Believe in him and wait.
You say that, Abdul...
...but we searched for three whole days and found nothing!
It's hard to believe he'll find it in just three hours.
You keep saying this, Polnareff!
Honestly, will you calm down for just a moment?
I know it's hard not to feel anxious,
but we have no choice but to rely on the locals for help.
Jeez. Iggy's been gone for a while, too.
Where the hell did that dumb dog run off to?
Iggy isn't exactly thrilled to be part of our group.
He couldn't have gone far, so we just need to wait for him.
Aren't normal dogs supposed to like humans?
What a snooty fucking dog.
I barely got away...
That thing's ice took the skin right off my paw pads...
Dammit! I should've just let that human kid die.
That bird's Stand is no joke.
The ice it makes isn't normal.
There's gotta be more to it.
I just need to get the hell out of here.
Talk about holding a grudge!
Iggy suddenly disappeared!
Where could he have gone?
Shit...
That ruthless asshole really doesn't hold back...
But he's just a stupid birdbrain.
It reeks down here, but I'll deal with it.
I just gotta lay low for a while.
W-What the hell is with this bird?!
Hey!
Too gullible!
All you did was break apart The Fool's shapeshifting sand!
I got ya! Only a birdbrain like you would fall for that!
You're losing blood.
I wouldn't suggest moving like that.
I'll be honest, I never had any interest
in you or that Master Dio of yours.
Let's call it a draw.
You got me with those ice missiles earlier, anyway.
W-What's your deal?
You think you're Bruce Lee or somethin'?
Hey! I said we would call it a draw!
Let's stop already. Okay?
So that's your Stand's design...
He used that thing to freeze his wound shut!
This is bad!
He blocked the exit while I was distracted!
And now the ice is coming for me!
Shit!
His ice is covering the whole tunnel!
I-I gotta get out of here!
He blocked it here, too!
He's tryin' to finish me off for good!
Talk about excessive!
He's taking this way too far!
He's a killing machine!
And worst of all, if he catches me, he'll eat me alive!
What?!
M-My foot!
M-My foot's stuck!
Next Episode
It can't get much worse than this!
That dumbass dog!
Goddamn that birdbrain!
There may be a Stand user preventing
anyone from coming close to the mansion.
This is my only option.
If I don't try it, he'll kill me!
Episode 39
Pet Shop: The Gatekeeper of Hell Part 2