Everyone, hold on!
C-Crap!
The water receded... Everyone, stay still!
Do not make a sound!
The time to be quiet has passed.
I know right where each of you fell.
Four steps... Five steps...
I hear someone tip-toeing...
I hear you, I hear you.
There, that should have sounded like walking.
You accursed water Stand, attack that spot!
The moment you reveal yourself,
my Magician's Red will burn you asunder!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 26: Iggy's The Fool and N'Doul's Divine Geb Part 2
There!
Hold on. Why did he only take five steps?
Why hasn't he moved any further?
Now!
Magician's Red!
What?!
Abdul!
Who are you?
What strength...
Abdul!
That was a sneaky little plan...
I must listen more carefully.
Those weren't footsteps.
It would seem he threw some ring-shaped objects.
And based on this burn...
...that was Abdul just now.
He's done for.
Let's end this...
It's back!
...Abdul!
Now I hear someone running...
You fool! Jotaro, what are you doing?!
Judging by the distance between footsteps, this person is 190...
...no, 195 centimeters tall.
It's not Joestar. These are the footsteps of a young man.
It must be Jotaro.
Jotaro, where are you going?
It dived!
Now the water is chasing after Jotaro!
So that's what he's doing!
It won't attack Abdul again, but...
Jotaro! It's going to catch up with you!
Word has it that the most punishing
Stand in their group is Jotaro's Star Platinum.
If I can dispose of him, I'm sure Lord Dio will be very pleased.
For Lord Dio, I'll give my all to defeat Jotaro!
Just now, I heard Jotaro pick up an object off the sand...
What was it that landed there?
What was that thing?
No, not a thing!
It's that mutt! Jotaro grabbed the dog!
He finally caught on.
Gimme a break, you twerp.
You ditched the buggy before it was attacked, right?
You can sense the enemy's location by scent, can't you?
Don't stop, Jotaro!
Now, then. You're gonna help me out, Iggy.
Where will he attack? Answer me, Iggy!
Otherwise, you're dead.
Don't expect any gum from me.
Iggy!
So now he can float?
Hold it!
I may be heavy, but don't you dare try escaping by yourself.
My Star Platinum is extremely quick.
Try to shake me off, and it'll snap your neck.
What? His footsteps disappeared after they jumped...
They still haven't landed.
Impossible....
This is good!
Jotaro's going to travel through the air with Iggy to find the enemy!
If we can find the user, our chances of
defeating this powerful Stand are good.
He's gone?
The sound of Jotaro's footsteps is gone.
Where is he? Where did he go?
Why have his footsteps stopped?
He's starting to lose altitude...
I guess The Fool can't fly very far.
So it can only glide like a paper airplane?
My shoes are about to scrape the ground...
Hey, quit straining yourself...
It's making you gassy.
Don't let us hit the ground.
There's no choice...
I'll have to help him gain altitude by kicking off the ground.
Ora!
We made it pretty far,
but that sound puts us at a disadvantage.
He'll know we've been traveling through the air.
I see. That mutt's Stand...
It's capable of flight.
And it's approaching quickly...
...in my direction!
Jotaro, I'll defeat you before you get close!
His Stand started chasing after Jotaro!
That jump must have given him away!
We have no choice but to leave this fight...
...to Jotaro.
Here it comes.
The helicopter's noise gave it away,
unlike Iggy's Stand which only makes sound when the wind hits it.
He won't know exactly where we are.
If I can reach the Stand user before losing altitude, I win.
There he is.
Only about four hundred meters away.
Looks like my enemy is blind.
S-Sand! There's sand falling on us!
The fucker is flinging sand up into the air...
Shit!
He'll hear the sound bouncing off us, like a submarine sonar!
I can hear it... The reflected sound.
I can even tell how high up you are...
...Jotaro!
Di
Divine
Divine Geb
N'
N'D
N'Do
Power: C
Speed: B
Range: A
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
N'Dou
N'Doul
Shoot him!
Star Platinum!
Ora!
No matter how fast your Star Platinum is, if you can't tell where I'm coming from, I'll be one step ahead of you!
One more shot!
This mutt...
That mutt is trying to save itself!
He revealed Jotaro's location to my Stand!
He's trying to abandon him!
Motherfucker...
You fucking mutt...
That ally of yours is quite unsympathetic, Jotaro.
This is it.
I will bring this to a merciful end...
Ora!
Wha-
What? I heard him throw something this way!
It's slicing through the wind...
What is it?
That's Iggy.
Now listen up...
If you and Iggy don't use your Stands
to defend yourselves, you're gonna collide.
This immense power...
Curses! He'll crash right into me!
What kind of person is he? Throwing a dog...
Curses! I was one shot away from finishing Jotaro...
Damn!
I couldn't keep track of Jotaro's location because of that mutt!
Where? Where are you?
He isn't moving...
He's staying absolutely still somewhere...
That must be his plan!
Where are you, Jotaro?
Where? Where the hell are you, Jotaro?!
Right here.
I see...
I didn't think you had made it this far.
If I hadn't recalled my water Stand to defend myself,
you would have already knocked me out from behind.
I suppose I won't be needing this staff to listen anymore.
However, I still need it to return home...
Ora!
Even the ocean couldn't manage to knock my hat off.
But don't sweat it, I held back.
You aren't badly injured.
No way! You used your own Stand to...
What the hell were you thinking?
Jotaro, I'm sure you were thinking about interrogating me
for information about my eight allies you have yet to encounter...
Joseph Joestar's Stand, Hermit Purple, is capable of spying on us.
I refuse to speak of anything that could leave
my Lord at a disadvantage.
Dio...
Why are you all so loyal to Dio?
Enough even to die for him...
Jotaro, I no longer fear death...
Because of my Stand's power,
I haven't felt the fear of death since I was a child.
I was able to murder anyone I pleased,
and commit any crime I wanted...
Even the police didn't scare me.
That dog surely understands how I felt.
That man was the only person to make me wish
from the bottom of my heart that I wouldn't die at his hands.
He was so powerful, deep, imposing, and beautiful.
And he was the first person to acknowledge my worth in this world.
It felt like I had waited my entire life to meet him...
I do not fear death, however...
I did fear that he may cast me aside to die!
The wicked need a wicked savior.
But there is one thing I can tell you...
My name is N'Doul.
My Stand represents what could be called the Tarot's origin.
It represents the god Geb, one of nine Egyptian gods.
He is god of the earth.
Nine Egyptian gods?
What is that?
My Stand is the only one I will speak of...
...since it is my Stand you defeated.
This is all I can tell you...
A man capable of making a fanatic out of anyone, Dio...
Just who is he?
And who are the people that represent the nine Egyptian gods?
I don't completely get it yet,
but all we can do is keep moving ahead.
Hey, hey, calm down. I'm not mad or anything.
From your perspective, Gramps dragged you
out to the desert against your will to fight for him.
That must have been a real pain in the ass.
Here, Iggy. Want some gum?
Knock it off. I'm apologizing, aren't I?
Here.
Gimme a break. What an annoying mutt.
We're in the middle of the desert, so do what you want.
Well, I'll be damned. You picked up my hat for me?
Maybe you're not so bad.
Thanks.
G-Gum? You fucking mutt...
You're no ordinary dog.
Hey!
Jotaro!
Jotaro! Are you okay?
Gimme a break.
Oh? Could that be a comic book by any chance?
Quite unusual!
So you Egyptians read comics as well?
You want a snack?
Say, I might be pushing it, but...
could I take a peek at that comic of yours?
I'm a cartoonist out on a research trip,
and I'm quite fascinated with unusual comic books!
In return, I'll let you use my binoculars.
Let's see... The title is Oingo Boingo Brothers Adventure...
There's no author credit...
The art is pretty unique!
It's nicely printed, and in full color!
Once upon a time, there lived two close brothers.
The name's Oingo.
I'm Boingo.
The little bro, Boingo, was kinda shy,
so he couldn't do anything without his big bro, Oingo.
He was a loner.
While big bro Oingo was gone,
Boingo met a traveler who was really nice to him.
The traveler gave him snacks and let him look through his binoculars.
Boingo had so much fun.
Oh, it's 10:30!
However, after the kind traveler left...
...he impaled himself on an electrical pole, and died.
What a strange comic...
Is stuff like this popular in Egypt?
And the book itself is pretty weird...
All the pages after this are blank...
There's nothing printed on them...
They must be missing.
What a bizarre and oddly realistic comic...
I know it's asking a lot, but will you please sell me this book?
Not happening!
My little bro's book isn't for sale!
Get the hell out of here.
Little bro?
Didn't you hear me?!
Little bro, I told you not to talk to strangers.
There's a lot of bad people out there.
Attention, everyone! The bus for Aswan is about to depart!
Let's go. They should be heading to
a hospital in Aswan to treat their wounded.
I see...
There's nothing we can do.
We'll just wait for the next one.
Next Episode
We're invincible together!
Who's there?
Polnareff, it's just me.
Jotaro, what happened to your school jacket?
You're acting really weird today.
You aren't...
No way...
Big bro Oingo! The prediction is absolute!
Episode 27
Oingo's Divine Khnum and Boingo's Divine Thoth
You can do it!