Have your wounds healed yet, Abdul?
Yes. But Kakyoin, I am far more relieved that you will be well.
That I will.
He didn't get my pupils,
so the doctors have been telling me I'll be fine.
When I was in junior high, while we were playing a baseball game...
...a fellow classmate got hit in the eye by a stray baseball,
but he was fine the next day.
There was some fluid that leaked out, though.
For real?
No...
I can take my bandage off in a few days.
I'll catch up with you then.
We're less than eight hundred kilometers
from Dio's location in Cairo.
Guys, be careful moving forward.
Man, the numbers on this receipt...
Are they Arabic numbers?
It's confusing as hell.
The zero's a five, right?
So this dot is actually zero, and this seven is a six?
And this wormy-looking one is...
A four. So the total amount is-
46,350 Egyptian pounds?!
That's expensive!
So cute!
Just look at him!
He's so unique!
What in the world? He's chewing gum.
Is he waiting for someone?
He's so well-behaved, too!
It appears waiting outside was not enough for him.
Gimme a break.
You think you're so cool?
Why is the little guy chewing gum?
What a strange dog.
Uh, hello?
Let me give you a piece of advice:
Stay far away from that dog.
He might seem cute and charming, but in general, he hates people.
If you let your guard down, you'll regre-
Y-You fucking mutt! G-Get off of m-
Oh, goodness! He passed gas!
What a darling!
You two look like best friends!
W-We don't even get along!
Dammit, Iggy! Get off of me!
We're heading in, lovebirds.
M-Mr. Joestar?!
Hey, hang on!
Y-Y-You...
You fucking dog!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 28: Divine Anubis Part 1
The ancient Egyptians were known to bury their dead on the side of the Nile where the sun sets.
That's why all of their cities were built on the east side.
The structures on the west side are reserved for the dead.
But our enemies won't care about east or west.
They'll attack from all directions.
Boy, that cow of yours... She's one lazy bovine.
Pretty strong though...
Hey, Chaka! Quit dragging your feet!
You're wasting time!
For the love of god!
What a slacker! Just who do you take after?
Your cow and your son look just like you!
A katana?
What's this doing here?
Hey, look at that! It's a katana!
Hand it over!
Huh? Did somebody lose it?
Who would drop a katana?
It's incredible! Bet it's worth something nice.
Hey, what if the owner is around here somewhere?
I'd be really worried if I dropped this.
Maybe it's just a long lost antique?
Should we take it to the police?
Fool! We'll line our pockets from selling this!
But I'm the one who found it...
It's worthless if it's just a replica.
Hurry and take it out!
What's wrong?
I-It's stuck! It won't budge!
Here, let me try.
Hold that end.
N-No good! The blade isn't even showing!
Let me try...
Shut it! If I can't do it, there's no way an idiot like you could!
M-My hand!
My hand!
M-My hand! My hand is cut!
But what cut it?!
The blade never even came out!
I didn't touch anything but the hilt!
What an ominous sword...
Hey! Let me try getting the sword out!
Shut it! Go ahead and try if you want!
I-It came out so easily...
I barely had to pull...
But... What is this?
I can hear the blade ringing...
I-I'm not a sword expert or anything,
but even I can tell just how beautiful that blade is...
It looks like an actual Japanese katana!
It's as if the blade were wet...
What an amazing find!
Hey, give it here! You shouldn't be holding it!
Give it to me!
H-Hey, wha-
What... What did you do?!
I-I don't know!
F-F-Father, you were standing right behind me!
I-It's not my fault...
What the hell are you doing? Hurry!
Hurry and get him a doctor!
There's something weird about this katana!
It's like it has a mind of its own!
Be calm.
Be calm, Chaka.
Nothing is wrong.
Nothing at all, Chaka...
W-Who are you?
That voice... I can hear it from somewhere...
I am known as Divine Anubis.
I am the Stand whose card represents
the God of the Dead and the guardian of the graveyard.
You have unsheathed me.
You shall become my user.
You are my user!
You have become an expert...
You are an expert in swordsmanship.
You are stronger than anyone.
Wield me, and kill!
My father and that man deserved to die.
Now I feel like slicing you up, too.
W-What? H-Hey, Chaka, don't!
Please stop!
N-No way! He didn't even hurt the cow!
Murder Joestar!
Chop up Polnareff!
Slice Jotaro in half!
You are an expert! An expert swordsman!
You are stronger than anyone and can cut through anything!
Kom Ombo?
Do we really have time to make a stop here?
Quit griping.
So long as they allow us to take the ferry, we cannot complain.
Man, I'm starving! Let's get some grub.
You're such a loudmouth.
Here, this gum will have to tide you over.
Isn't that crap for Iggy?
Well, it can't hurt to try some.
By the way, where's the toilet?
Let us search for one.
Hey, mister, listen here!
Want some papyrus?
Paper is made of papyrus.
Would you like it as a memento?
Look, see? It's the real thing!
Papyrus?
I'm selling it cheap!
You're sure this is the real thing?
You betcha.
This piece was made by a famous Egyptian craftsman.
It's a fake.
If it were real, I wouldn't be able to rip it in half like that.
I'm not stupid, you know.
Huh?
Where did Mr. Joestar and the others go?
Iggy?! Why, you little... Hold it!
Y-You still owe me!
That dumb dog totally gave me the slip...
Hey...
You have some guts...
...attacking with this many people around.
It's funny...
You guys usually won't let us see you, or try to attack directly.
That's how a true man does it.
I didn't expect to see that from you guys.
Identify yourself.
I am Chaka.
I am the user of the Stand which
represents the God of Death, Anubis.
Jean Pierre Polnareff, I will take your life.
"I will take your life"? Now that's a straightforward line.
You're a bigger man than I would have expected.
Have at it! Show me that Divine Anubis Stand of yours.
Chariot!
He has a sword, but...
...is he really gonna fight me with it instead of his Stand?
Something's wrong...
The way he moves, and how he's wielding his sword...
He's a complete amateur! But there's something else...
This is bad!
I need to keep my distance.
Di
Divi
Divine
Divine Anu
Divine Anubis
Ch
Cha
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Chaka
W-What the hell?
The sword phased through the pillar!
And it didn't cut my shirt!
Somehow he cut me, but not my shirt!
If I hadn't kept my distance, that would have killed me!
You son of a bitch! Chariot!
Quit hiding like a coward! Show yourself!
C-Crap...
What the hell? I lost him.
I-I can't tell which pillar he's hiding behind...
That Stand can phase through stuff to cut its target!
My Chariot is only able to strike within a meter at best...
Shit, he has me at a disadvantage.
You've got some nerve to strike me with your sword...
But this will be the end of you and your confidence!
Well, Chaky, how about this?
Bring it on!
All I've gotta do is stay away from those pillars!
You wanna try hitting me from underground?
What?!
The pillar!
I can do more than pass through them!
I can cut them in half if I want to!
Die, Polnareff!
Th-That was close...
Even Jotaro doesn't know Chariot has that secret technique.
The ability to launch the blade...
If my opponent can dodge the blade,
I become completely defenseless.
I can only use that attack if I'm in deep trouble.
Well, I don't think he's dead yet...
...but he won't be fighting again anytime soon.
That's strange...
His sword is still in the sheath...
Did it slip back in?
This katana...
Now that I'm seeing it up close...
...it really is beautiful...
I want to see the entire thing...
Hey, Polnareff. Finally found you.
You worried us after you wandered off alone.
What if you got attacked by an enemy?
Polnareff?
Huh? O-Oh, Mr. Joestar...
I'm not sure if it's because I turned around too quickly
or because of my wounds, but I feel completely out of it...
Polnareff, why are you crouching?
You step on something nasty?
What is this? You have a katana.
Has something happened?
Yeah... I got attacked by an enemy.
What? An enemy?!
It's over now.
His Stand was called Divine Anubis.
He was a Stand user and expert swordsman who could phase his sword through objects to cut behind them.
It was a tough fight.
"Of course, he wasn't nearly as strong as I am!"
Polnareff thought to himself.
He attacked me with this swor-
Huh?
Where'd it...
Mice! Those mice are trying to steal the sword!
Hey!
Talk about creepy...
So there are thieving mice here, eh?
You guys like stealing cheese, so stick to that!
That's weird...
It's so tight, I can't remove it anymore.
Polnareff!
I'm glad you're safe,
but don't forget we should always travel in pairs.
Don't be careless!
Our enemies will not hesitate if they find us alone.
Damn! That whistle is from our ship!
Let's hurry back. We're heading to Edfu today.
Hey, wait!
Polnareff...
What're you gonna do with that sword?
I'm gonna hand it over to the police,
since it's a dangerous weapon and all.
Yeah, it's for the best.
If you had left it in those ruins,
anyone could have found it.
It appears to be quite valuable.
Hey, Iggy! Be silent!
What if we get thrown out?
What the hell is wrong with you today?
Now the fucking dog won't shut up.
I guess I'll go take care of this now.
Polnareff! Did we not just finish telling you to never go alone?
I just told you!
Jotaro, go with him.
Sure.
Hey, shouldn't we head to the police station?
Oh, come on!
A man's got to look his best, right, sir?
Yeah, definitely.
Pops, could you set my katana down over there?
Sure.
It's a dangerous weapon no matter how you look at it.
I was rolling around so much yesterday that my handsome face got all dirty.
Make me shine, Pops.
Sure.
Ow! Ow!
Hey, wise guy! Your razor is dull!
Make it sharper! Sharper!
This is supposed to be the most relaxing part of a hair cut!
Gimme a break. He's such a pain.
Is that so? My apologies.
Nice!
Now it's cutting nice and close. Feels good.
That's... good to hear.
It's très bien! Très bi-e-n!
Could you also get under my chin?
Sure.
Right here... underneath your chin, correct?
Right under your chin, Polnareff?
What?!
It's me, you fool. The user of the Anubis Stand!
Next Episode
The katana is actually a Stand!
I've never lost to anyone I fought before!
This thing is strong.
The more we fight it, the faster it gets...
Polnareff's eyes...
Your head is mine!
Episode 29
Divine Anubis Part 2