Tokyo
Tokyo, Hong Kong, Singapore...
Hong Kong
Singapore
And now...
Calcutta
...we're about to cross India.
And... Well, I'm a bit worried.
I picture India as a place where people only eat curry
and can become sick at any moment.
As for me, I'm worried I won't handle the culture gap well.
That is a rather inaccurate assessment.
Worry not. It is a nice country of simple folk.
I can assure you.
Well, this is Calcutta. Let us be off.
Hey, gimme a tip!
I'll hold that for you!
Want a tattoo? They're real spiffy!
Need some antivenom? It won't give you a stomach ache.
Let me show you a hotel!
Calcutta, India.
During the 20th century, its population was 11 million.
An immense energy swirls about the city!
Gross! I stepped in cow shit! Dammit!
I'm fine, I don't need anything.
Someone already stole my wallet!
Seriously, no thank you.
Tip! Tip! Tip!
If I don't get a tip, you ain't going to heaven, mister.
Hey! Get your snotty nose off it, nosy!
Abdul! Is all of India like this?!
Indeed! Is this not a great country?
This is exactly what makes this country so wonderful!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 10: Emperor and Hanged Man Part 1
Here, have this.
This is chai.
It is very delicious.
Chai.
One of India's most popular drinks.
A sweet drink made by boiling black tea, sugar, and ginger with milk.
Finally, some peace!
Give it some time.
You will see just how wonderful it is here once you are acclimated.
I like it here. I could get used to this.
Really, Jotaro? Do you really mean it?
Talk about culture shock.
I'll like it once I'm acclimated, huh?
Well, they do say people adapt to their surroundings.
Where's the toilet?
Over there, sir.
Polnareff.
Yeah?
What about your order?
Order for me.
Better make it something good.
As a Frenchman, I require only the finest of delicacies.
Well, I guess we can pick whatever.
What's something he would like...?
Excuse me.
Oh, sir, one moment.
Please use this.
What's this for?
Hey!
This toilet's got a weird shape, but it's pretty damn clean.
A nice guy like myself can't stand to use a dirty toilet.
Is something the matter?
"I-I-I-Is something the matter," my ass!
Th-Th-Th-The toilet...
Inside the toilet...
...there's a pig sticking its head out!
Even for India, this is an unusual toilet.
They accidentally made the pig pen down below a little too high.
So when the pig gets hungry, it sticks its head out.
Th-That's not what I wanted to kn-
T- uh, what?! That means this pig's food is...
That's why it's there?!
That's why you're supposed to use this.
Here...
See? Now you can do your business
while the pig's recoiling from the blow to the head.
Our manager is always talking about how great it is
when the pig licks his butt, because he gets it so clean.
Ain't that something?!
Please, take your time.
W-Wait! Don't leave me alone!
Gulp...
I don't think I'll ever be acclimated...
I'll wait until we get to the hotel.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Crap!
I-It's gone?
I could have sworn I saw something weird there...
I'm just seeing things...
It can't be helped.
I mean, there was a pig in the toilet.
I guess it isn't too much of a stretch that
I'd see the illusion of a monster in the window.
So this is what they mean by culture shock in India.
Wha-
What?!
W-Who is that?!
I can only see it in the mirror!
So this is the mirror Stand Jotaro heard about!
This is bad!
This is really bad!
Silver Chariot!
W-What the hell was that?!
Goddammit!
A Stand!
Where's the user? Who is it?!
The man with two right hands...
There are so many people...
Damn!
What's wrong, Polnareff?
What is it?
If that...
If that was a Stand, that means...
That means he's finally here!
Jotaro, the Stand user you heard about that uses mirrors is here!
The motherfucker that killed my sister!
That bastard stamped out my sister's life, soul, and pride!
Finally... I finally found him!
The man you want vengeance on is here?
Mr. Joestar, I'll be traveling on my own from here on out.
Wh-
Now that I know the guy who killed my sister is near,
I won't wait until he comes after me.
I'll be at a disadvantage if he gets to me first, and that's not my style.
I'll find and kill him first!
Even though you have no idea
what he looks like or what his Stand is?
Knowing he has two right hands is enough!
And he knows I'm after him, as well.
He should be worried that I'll come for his head in his sleep.
Later.
You will go for wool, and return home shorn.
The hell does that mean?
It is as you heard it.
Are you implying I'll lose?
Indeed!
Are you so foolish that you cannot see
the enemy struck so you would follow it?
I refuse to let you travel alone, Polnareff!
Listen here, let me break it down for you!
I don't give a fuck about Dio!
I told you guys in Hong Kong
I was only tagging along to get my revenge!
Mr. Joestar and Jotaro already know this!
I've been a loner from the start!
I've always fought alone!
You insolent man!
Did you already forget you were brainwashed by Dio?
And did you also happen to forget how this all leads back to Dio?!
I wouldn't expect you to know
what it feels like to have your sister killed!
I heard the last time you saw Dio, you got scared and ran.
A coward like you would never understand how I feel!
What was that?
Hands off!
You're lucky you even beat me in Hong Kong.
Don't lecture me.
You...
Oh, are you angry now?
If you think you're mad, you should imagine what I feel like right now!
Keep acting like you're the mature one as always, Abdul.
Why, you-
Mr. Joestar!
That's enough. Let him go.
No one can stop him while he's like this.
No, my intent was not to stop him.
I never took him to be this kind of man.
Indeed it was cowardice that made me flee that day.
But that is why I now think we can win...
...and can say with certainty that you will lose.
Huh?
Then I'll say this with certainty, too.
Your little prediction is wrong.
Hop off.
I'm here fer an ol' pal.
Yer gonna hafta head back yerself from here.
Please make me your wife!
I'll dedicate my life to you. I'll do anything for you.
So please, let me stand by your side forever!
Don't be a fool. Yer only sixteen.
I'm of age to be wed.
I love you.
Listen, I'm just a lonely drifter...
I live every day like it's my last one, an' one day maybe it will be.
A royal like yerself shouldn't even be thinkin' 'bout marryin' me.
Don't matter how much we love each other.
Really?
You really love me?
Yeah. Yer all I got in this big world.
But that's the thing...
'Cause I love ya so much, we just can't get married.
Ya understand?
Even right now, I feel like my chest'll just about explode.
But once'n a while, I'll git back here an' hold ya just like this.
That alone'll make me happy.
Okay...
Later. Love ya, babe.
It ain't very kind to be eavesdroppin'.
I bet yer just itchin' to say how I'm just bein' indirect as usual, an' how there's a million gals like 'er...
But she's easy an' convenient.
She'd do right about anythin' fer me, even kill 'erself.
Ya know that's my style, right?
My boss, J. Geil.
Anyways, 'bout Silver Chariot an' Polnareff...
Seems like he's gone lookin' fer ya.
What's the plan?
He totally fell fer that trap of yers.
Should we kill 'im first?
Let's go.
With y'all an' yer Hanged Man...
An' me, Hol Horse, with my Emperor...
...we'll kill 'em all.
Ha
Han
Hange
Hanged
Hanged Ma
J
Hanged Man
J.
J. G
J. Gei
J. Geil
I guess he really isn't coming back...
What?
You saw him?!
You're sure you saw a man with two right hands?
Where?
Huh? That's weird...
I lost him. I swear he was right over there.
What?
He was with that man right there.
The gun's mightier'n the sword.
Man, ain't that one fer the books?
Just who are you?
Hol Horse, ya might say.
I'm the user of the Stand representin' the Emperor card.
Lord Dio paid me to take care of ya varmints.
Hey, cowboy. I don't need the long-winded intro.
Do you know the man with two right hands?
Well aren't y'all a rude one! Yer the one who asked.
Whatever...
I came here with 'im.
He's close by.
What?
Where is he?!
Well ain't that a pointless question.
I'm the one who'll be takin' care of y'all.
It's always trash like you that give me that line...
Yet it always ends up the other way around.
Oh? Was that funny?
Lord Dio was tellin' me... "Since that Polnareff's always
makin' light of his foes, beatin' 'im'll be a piece of cake."
He was right, an' it gave me a chuckle.
If I can't see him until I defeat you, then that's just what I'll do.
Bring it on.
Ya know 'bout Stratego, right?
The tank's stronger'n the soldier, an' tanks're weak to mines.
Ya see, it's the basics of battle.
Me an' my Emperor're stronger'n y'all,
so I'll just let ya in on a lil' secret 'bout what my Stand can do.
The gun's mightier'n the sword.
Fer real, someone's gotta write that down!
What are you getting at?
My Stand's a shooter.
No sword's beatin' a Stand that shoots.
What, you mean like in marbles?
I'll kill you!
Ya din't take me seriously, Polnareff!
Now ya really lost!
If I shed its armor...
Dodging a bullet will be nothing!
W-What?!
I-Impossible! It changed its trajectory!
D-Dammit!
The bullet's part of my Stand, too!
Not takin' me seriously just cost ya yer life!
Polnareff!
Wha- Abdul!
I was worried about you, and look what has happened!
You are too arrogant, Polnareff!
W-Worried?
Damn you! Are you going to lecture me again?
The enemy knows everything about you!
You said you were a loner,
but from here on, you cannot win by yourself!
Well ain't that rotten timin' fer a distraction.
Move, Polnareff! The bullet is coming back!
Magician's Red!
I will burn it asunder!
Damn that Abdul! He went after Polnareff himself!
Where are you, Mr. Abdul? Polnareff?
I have a bad feeling...
Hey, there's a weird fight going on over there!
The puddle...
What?!
Mr. Abdul!
Man, it's my lucky day!
My gun an' J. Geil's mirror don't play well with Abdul's flames.
We were thinkin' he'd be the toughest one. Lucky!
The scariest piece in this here game of Stratego's out.
Mr. Abdul!
H-He's just injured...
It's just a minor wound... He'll start speaking again...
He'll open his eyes at any moment...
Mr. Abdul, won't you?
You're going to wake up, right?
Mr. Abdul, wake up!
Please! Mr. Abdul!
Impossible. He went out far too easily...
It's too sudden!
That's what he gets for lecturing people.
Just look where it got him.
W...
What did you say, Polnareff?
Mr. Abdul was worried about y-
Who asked him for help?!
He likes to meddle in other people's business, but he's slow as hell, so they got him.
Guys like him just get in the way...
That's why I said I'd do this myself!
Why, you...
He saved your life. How could you?
It just pisses me off...
Having people up and die on me...
Polnareff...
It really pisses me off!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
I'da expected a fella with such a rough mug to go down a bit harder!
Come to think of it, your sister...
...was really good at sobbing!
So you really do want me to hold it in, huh?
Don't let him get to you!
Mr. Abdul told you not to fight by yourself!
Episode 11
Emperor and Hanged Man Part 2