Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
This is bad!
He blocked the exit while I was distracted!
And now the ice is coming for me!
Shit!
His ice is covering the whole tunnel!
I-I gotta get out of here!
What?!
M-My foot!
M-My foot's stuck!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 39: Pet Shop: The Gatekeeper of Hell Part 2
Hey, the sun's about to set.
It's been over three hours, and even though that beggar guy was sure he'd find Dio's Mansion, I guess he was wrong.
Yo, Abdul?
I have been thinking,
and perhaps it would be best if he not find it at all.
Suppose he has already found it, yet is unable to return.
H-Hey...
There may be a Stand user preventing
anyone from coming close to the mansion.
Asking the beggar to find the mansion for us
may have been more dangerous than I anticipated.
Hey, now...
M-My leg...
My... leg...
That icicle chopped it off!
I'd be done for if I hadn't left it behind!
I-I'll just hide here for a while...
I need to lay low until he's off my scent.
The Speedwagon Foundation'll
make me a prosthetic leg anyway, but...
Goddamn that birdbrain!
You'll pay for this!
I swear I'll get my revenge!
Goddammit!
Th-That noise...
It sounded like something dove into the water!
I-It couldn't be...
Contrary to popular belief,
some birds are capable of diving underwater.
Indeed, like humans and dogs,
birds use their lungs to breathe, however...
...they also possess air sacs for storing oxygen,
located in five to six places in the chest and abdomen.
Air Sac
Lungs
Because of these air sacs, birds are capable of flying at altitudes of
six to seven thousand meters; higher than any human could withstand.
Even if it were being strangled, a bird could survive for
several minutes due to the vast quantity of oxygen in its body.
In short, birds are able to stay underwater
much longer than a dog can!
T-There's something coming in the water...
I-It can't be!
I can't believe it, but the sound heading this way's gotta be...
It can't be!
It couldn't be!
That damn bird!
He found me here underwater!
That bastard... Where'd he go?
Th-They're coming! There's more coming!
His ice! One... two... three...
Th-Three shots in total!
Take 'em back!
I-I did it... Serves ya right!
Th-The water stopped leaking in...
And now ice is starting to form at the root of the icicle!
W-What the hell?
Th-That's it!
Since I'm surrounded by water...
...he's trying to freeze me inside!
He cut off my airway!
B-But he's not trying to suffocate me!
He's trying to crush me!
It's no use! It's collapsing!
He's too powerful! I can't hold out!
I'm completely surrounded by freezable water!
Goddammit!
I thought I'd be safe underwater,
but somehow he's got me cornered!
I-I'll just have to dig my way out!
This is just my luck! It can't get much worse than this!
My leg got chopped off,
and I still have to deal with this stupidly powerful bird!
I'm at my limit... I'm gonna be crushed...
I have to dig faster if I wanna escape!
What's this? Why is there an empty space here?!
It's birdbrain!
He's aiming an ice missile right at me!
Crap! The Fool is still behind me!
There's no time to defend!
I can't back out either!
I know! Th-This is my only option.
If I don't try it, he'll kill me!
I'll let him crush the sand on purpose,
and use the air pressure to shoot myself forward!
I-I did it... I won...
Damn birdbrain. Serves ya right...
B-But I'm done for...
I lost too much blood,
and I'm not strong enough to swim... to... shore...
I-I'm gonna drown...
And here I thought I'd get to live a life free of trouble...
Dammit...
I messed up...
How did this happen?
I was just passing by, and saw you drifting in the river!
That bird got you, didn't he? Just like he got my dogs...
You'll be all right...
I think he's gone now.
Don't die on me! Hang in there!
I'll fix you right up!
The despicable bird, Pet Shop,
and his Stand, Divine Horus: Obliterated!
The Despicable Bird
Pet Shop -Stand: Divine Horus-
Obliterated
Div
Divine
Divine Hor
P
Divine Horus
Pe
Pet
Pet S
Pet Sh
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: C
Pet Sho
Pet Shop
Damn that Iggy! Where the hell did he go?
He needs to quit being such a pain.
I'm concerned with how long it's been since we last saw him.
That dumbass dog!
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Is there someone following us?
No... I thought I heard a voice calling for us.
A voice?
I-Iggy?!
Iggy!
What has happened to you?
He looks seriously injured!
Hey... He's missing a front leg!
W-Was he hit by a car?
He is not the kind of dog to let himself get in an accident.
Were you attacked by the enemy, Iggy?
It looks like someone already treated his wounds.
And with perfect medical technique.
It wasn't Iggy's voice.
I heard a human's voice calling.
It looks like Iggy had a run-in with the enemy.
I saw a boy holding him in his arms...
...as a doctor from the Speedwagon Foundation cared for him.
Just like the one...
...who treated my eyes.
Th-That's...
Kakyoin!
If it isn't Kakyoin! Hey!
Kakyoin, have your eyes finally healed?
Guys, I'm glad you're well!
It's great to see you!
Have your wounds healed?
Yes. I'm fine now.
I have a few scars, but my vision has completely returned.
I'm happy to hear it!
Jotaro...
Hey, Iggy, where are you going?
Despite Iggy never showing an interest in humans or Stands,
it looks like he wants to lead us somewhere.
I don't know what happened while he was fighting the enemy Stand...
...but he seems angry about how much pain he's endured.
Where exactly is he trying to take us?
Hey, Iggy! Wait up!
Th-That car...
That's the luxury car the beggar was driving!
B-But it being wrecked means...
What happened?
It looks like something enormous made a huge hole in it.
It is just as I feared!
I never should have contracted him...
Could this be the work of the Stand user Iggy fought?
There is little doubt in my mind.
Iggy!
Hey, what's going on?
Suddenly I'm having cold sweats!
This overwhelming oppressive feeling...
Where's Iggy t-trying to take us?
I think I know!
This atmosphere...
This dark aura...
Th-This is the mansion...
...from the picture.
Iggy, I can't believe you actually found it for us!
The mansion stood ominously before Jotaro and company, projecting an abnormally sinister energy.
It held the source of all the adversity they had encountered,
as well as their destiny; the embodiment of evil.
They had journeyed long and far to reach this place.
Traveling through many lands,
and encountering Dio's countless Stand-wielding assassins.
It was, indeed, a series of life-or-death battles
that proved difficult to survive.
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Tears, laughter, sadness, rage, and joy.
Their journey was fraught with these emotions.
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
In order to save the life of Jotaro's mother, Holly, they departed from Japan a mere fifty days ago.
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Their goal was to defeat Dio,
finally concluding a one-hundred-year destiny in the making.
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Joseph thought to himself...
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
He was determined to reach his goal
and save his beloved daughter, no matter what!
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Kakyoin thought to himself...
In order to save Holly, and to conquer
the weakness in his heart, he would defeat Dio at any cost!
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
Abdul thought to himself...
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
He knew there was evil in this world that could not
be allowed to flourish, and so, it must be destroyed!
Polnareff thought to himself...
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
He would make Dio pay for manipulating him with his flesh bud,
as well as making him go against his morals!
Seinaru Vision Stand...
This sacred vision will Stand...
Iggy thought to himself...
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up tachihadakaru
Stand up, stand up, stand up, to those that stand in your way
The only reason he had endured all of this absurdity was because of that despicable Dio!
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now teki wo taoshi
All right now, all right now, all right now, show them no mercy
And no matter what, he would make him pay!
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down michi wo hiraku
Break you down, break you down, break you down, carve out your own path
And finally...
In other words, if we beat the shit out of Dio
here and now, it'll all be over.
Tamashi no Vision Stand Proud!
May your spirit's vision Stand Proud!
He's here. There's no doubt we're feeling his presence!
He's inside the mansion right now!
Which means that we...
...have finally reached the last stop on our journey.
Are you guys ready?
The gate's open.
We could just stroll on in.
But yesterday it was closed...
Since I sensed his presence,
chances are he sensed ours as well.
If we're not careful about entering the mansion,
it could be more dangerous than entering a starving lion's den.
Now...
...what should we do?
The door opened! Watch out!
Hey, look at this corridor...
I can't see where it ends...
It can't be real, can it?
Could it be some kind of trick or illusion?
Polnareff, don't go through the door.
We'll probably encounter at least one or two Stand users before Dio.
What's that?! Something's coming!
Who the hell is that? Is he a Stand user?
Welcome.
Master Joestar, we have been awaiting your arrival.
I am the butler of this mansion.
Next Episode
Let's make a bet.
The first attack Star Platinum will attempt to use against me...
Jotaro, give him a good beating!
I'll go through it at full throttle!
If we aren't able to defeat you, we can't proceed?
Exactly!
That's the right idea!
Episode 40
D'Arby the Gamer Part 1