They're exiting the tunnel!
D'Arby is definitely going faster!
He's ahead by a car length!
Now my speed will be doubled!
Victory is mine!
No!
You have less power remaining, D'Arby!
Which means...
Kakyoin's #28!
It spun and knocked D'Arby's car off the track!
It was going 850 kilometers per hour!
He's off the track!
Kakyoin's #28 landed safely!
Yes!
Whoever has less power goes flying.
You were wrong to think losing power didn't matter.
I lagged behind by a car length so I could
knock you off of the track, and you didn't even notice.
Is that so?
I'm afraid it's you who has failed to take notice.
My plan all along was to lose power.
I did it on purpose.
You took the bait and sent my car flying off the track as intended.
This battle isn't over!
Behold! Watch where my machine will land!
What?!
I-It flew right over the gap to a later part of the track!
I-Impossible!
Indeed. It normally isn't possible.
Normally, you would expect to crash right into the ground after driving off the course at 850 kilometers per hour.
Reaching the next part of the track this way is usually impossible.
However, Kakyoin, you made it possible by slamming into me.
I wanted you to send me flying!
I purposely reduced my power so you would attempt to hit me.
Now, then...
Shall we continue the race, Kakyoin?
Don't admit defeat, Kakyoin!
Kakyoin!
In my hands, I now hold his soul.
He finally admitted defeat.
He admitted within his heart that
continuing the race was a pointless endeavor.
Still, Kakyoin, no one has ever
been able to make me sweat like you have.
This doll is now an especially valuable piece of my collection.
He is the first opponent I've faced who overcame their fears,
and refrained from making mistakes due to their lack of mental fortitude.
K-Kakyoin!
I will treasure it for the rest of my days.
Whoa, there!
I would advise against attacking me in retaliation.
But not just that.
If I were to slip on a banana peel and hit my head...
...or choke on a piece of chewing gum...
...or die of a heart attack from the bang
of an inflated bag of popcorn being popped...
...Kakyoin's soul would pass on into the next realm.
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 41: D'Arby the Gamer Part 2
J-Jotaro?
Hey, Jotaro! Why are you sitting down?
Let me defeat him! I'm next!
Gramps, have you played any of these games more than Kakyoin did?
Stay out of it, Gramps.
This isn't like poker or hanafuda.
Next is baseball.
I challenge you to a game of baseball.
I bet my soul.
Good.
And I shall bet Kakyoin's.
I removed Atum's hand from your arm.
Now that I possess Kakyoin's soul,
I have no need to hold onto your arm.
It would be disadvantageous
for my Stand to fight you with one hand.
Your Star Platinum is capable of
extremely quick and precise movements.
I didn't expect you to choose the baseball game.
This just so happens to be the game I'm best at.
D'Arby! If you lose to Jotaro, I'll defeat you in an actual battle!
Don't forget that!
Oh! That's a Baseball!!
There's nothing wrong with the game.
I've confirmed it.
To start, please select your team.
The Jaguars.
Jaguars!
Interesting.
So you've chosen a team with a strong offense.
You have two players with a batting average higher than .400.
In that case, I'll select the Red Dragons.
Red Dragons!
Will you bat first or second? Take your pick.
First.
Very well. The Jaguars are up first.
There's an option to create a character that will portray your players in-game.
This is Star... Platinum.
Input. Now, let us play ball!
Jaguars vs. Red Dragons!
Play ball!
Top of the 1st
I chose #15 as my pitcher, since I was born on January 5th.
Now then, let's begin.
The pitcher is winding up.
The first pitch!
What?!
Strike!
H-Hey, Jotaro... What the hell was that about?
You swung before the ball left the pitcher's hand!
H-Hey, Jotaro... Why do you keep taking practice swings?
It can't be... You've never played...
...this baseball game...
No, you've never played any video game before?
Answer me, Jotaro!
So what? I know the rules of baseball.
I'll figure out the controls as I go.
W-What?!
That ridiculous, terribly-timed swing...
And the way you're holding the controller...
This is your first time playing this game, isn't it?!
Strike two!
You swung way after the ball hit the glove!
You're a complete amateur!
Goddammit, Jotaro!
You've never played a video game before, have you?!
Strike! Batter out!
Quit screwing around, Jotaro!
I've had enough of your attitude!
You gambled your soul! You can't back out now!
Gimme a break.
I expected more encouraging words under these circumstances.
"It's just the first inning. You only just started.
You can do it, Jotaro," and such.
What the hell are you thinking?
Even with your Star Platinum's extremely precise movements,
did you think you could beat him without any knowledge of video games?
What were you thinking, Jotaro?
What in the hell were you thinking?!
Jotaro...
If this is some vain effort to trick me into
thinking you're an amateur, it isn't going to work.
I never let my guard down regardless of the situation.
Even if it were an infant betting their soul,
I would still give my all to defeat them.
Gramps...
I wasn't thinking about anything...
...except...
...that he's sitting there, so sure nobody can beat him at this game, oblivious to the fact I want to smash his fucking face in.
The only thought on my mind right now is getting back Kakyoin's soul.
Say what you will, but it's only the top of the first inning, and with one out.
Let us continue the game.
Don't forget that if one of us takes
an eleven point lead, the game will end.
Second batter, #3.
Strike!
W-Why is this happening?!
This time the ball was at least forty centimeters away from where he was swinging!
Strike two!
Not even close!
Strike! Batter out!
It's no use...
Their difference in skill is far too vast...
It's like a tea ceremony club filled with members who had never
held a bat in their life decided to challenge a championship team!
It's pathetic!
Strike!
Strike two!
It appears as though he truly is an amateur. He's weak!
Now I understand how a judo master feels when he gauges the strength of his opponent by how they put on their gi.
When it comes to video games, Jotaro is truly an amateur.
However, I refuse to lower my guard.
I've memorized the weakness of every batter.
My next pitch will be low to the outside.
I'll pitch my best screwball and get three strikes before he manages to get a single run.
Top of the first, two outs, two strikes, and no balls.
Here comes my next pitch.
Bring it.
I've pretty much mastered how to swing.
What? What did he just say?
"How to swing"? What?
Did he really just say he mastered how to swing?
What the hell is he talking about? What is he talking about?!
What?!
Jotaro!
Good. This game is interesting.
H-Hey, don't tell me...
It's still going! The ball's still in the air!
Did he seriously just say that?!
"I've pretty much mastered how to swing."
Mastered? Did he really say "mastered"?!
I-It's fair!
No way! No way!
Home run!
Home run! A home run!
Jotaro! Damn you!
Di
Divi
Divine
Divine At
Te
Divine Atum
Tere
Teren
Terenc
Terence
Terence T
Terence T.
Terence T. D'
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Terence T. D'A
Terence T. D'Ar
Terence T. D'Arby
Jotaro!
What did you just say?
Mastered?
Did you really say "I've pretty much mastered how to swing"?!
Don't make me repeat myself.
There's no doubt he was only a beginner before!
Is he saying he managed to master the controls in eight swings?
Kujo Jotaro's Star Platinum is capable
of extremely precise movement...
Now I know exactly why he's such a nuisance to Lord Dio, as well as how my brother lost to him!
Interesting. I like seeing this in an opponent.
In spite of how boldly you boasted about your
formidable ability at the top of the first inning...
...I will make you regret ever speaking a word.
Let us continue the game, Jotaro.
You did it!
It's fair! It's fair!
You got another home run!
Now it's four-zip at the top of the first inning!
You really got the hang of this game, Jotaro!
You've got this! Keep it up!
Hey, D'Arby...
I bet you don't want to hear this, but I'm feeling generous.
If you return Kakyoin's soul right now and take us to Dio...
...we'll consider sparing your life.
My brother was both a talented gambler, and a talented cheater.
Yet at no point did he ever approach me and say,
"Hey, brother, would you like to play a game of poker?"
Not even once.
Do you know why that is?
When I was fifteen,
my brother decided to make a move on my girlfriend.
I beat him senseless for it
despite the fact that he was ten years older.
I broke his ribs and kicked him until he was vomiting blood.
And after all that, the only words he could muster were "I'm sorry."
Do you know why?
What the hell are you getting at?
Since we were children, my brother has known he couldn't beat me.
He knew there must have been a reason for it.
Right now, Jotaro's confidence is growing as he becomes better and better at this game.
However, he is still just as uncertain as my brother was as a child.
He is uncertain of my abilities.
"It couldn't be, or maybe it is..." is what he's been thinking.
Am I wrong, Jotaro?
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm changing pitchers! Switch #15 for #77!
#
Name
Strt
Ptch
Rlf
Clsr
Ptch
Strt
Number
Position
Games
Wins
Losses
Hits All.
Saves
ERA
Starting
Pitcher
Control
Breaking Ball
Pitch Speed
Versatility
Luck
Stamina
Relief
Pitcher
Closer
#77 is a fastball pitcher whose fastest pitch clocks in at 165 kilometers per hour.
R. Handed
Pitch Speed
Traits
Throws fastballs,
but can only
throw straights
and forkballs.
Power Level
ERA
Number
Now I shall declare the pitch I'm about to throw!
#77 will pitch...
...a forkball straight down the middle!
What? Did he just reveal his pitch?!
I'm pitching a forkball right down the middle!
Do you believe me, or not?
Jotaro, he's trying to play mind games with you!
Don't let his tactics get to you!
Pitch, D'Arby.
Do you believe me, or not?
Here it comes! Straight down the middle!
It's a straight!
But will it stay straight?!
Will it fall, or won't it?
He swung! Jotaro bet on the forkball!
But it's not falling! It's staying straight!
He hit the bottom of the ball!
Out!
Top of the first, three outs! Change!
Top of the 1st
How could you be so stupid?!
You actually believed him and swung for a forkball!
No.
He was sure I'd swing for a forkball,
so he changed it to a straight fastball.
Like he said, I've been uncertain since we entered the mansion.
Somehow he knew Star Platinum would throw a right punch.
I-Impossible! So are you telling me...
...that he can somehow read your mind?
Next is the bottom of the first. It is my turn on offense.
I declare I will hit a home run!
I will hit the ball you pitch into the leftmost stands.
Gramps...
You're sure the game and console weren't messed with, right?
There's no way.
I've been keeping an eye out for any signs of cheating from him.
That means his Stand holds the secret.
It doesn't just take souls...
It has some kind of hidden power.
Let's try this...
I should learn something from this.
What?! He's gonna try hitting the batter on purpose?
Where will you decide to aim your pitch? Inside?
Perhaps high?
Or maybe low?
Do you have some kind of trick up your sleeve?
What?! He dodged just as the pitch was thrown!
H-He read it! He read it perfectly!
There's no way he could have known that
without reading Jotaro's mind!
Home run!
That's one run.
N-No way...
We've seen so many different Stands before,
but never one that could read minds!
If it can read minds, will any amount of intelligence or power be enough to defeat it?
W-What will you do, Jotaro?
Bottom of the 1st
Dammit! H-He's declaring another home run!
Will the next one be outside?
And will it be low?
Or perhaps it will be straight?
Home run!
Four-two.
If you can deduce information about your opponent and surroundings, you can figure out how they tick!
Somehow his Stand knows the exact course the ball will take with perfect accuracy!
And it's not because he's cheating!
Another home run! It's four-three!
How can we stop him from reading our minds?
How?
This will be turned around shortly.
Now, will the next one be inside?
Down the middle? High? A changeup?
Wherever could it go?
Your hat...
You fool.
Do you really think I would resort to
underhanded methods like my brother?
Jotaro, it's not that!
Hiding behind your hat is pointless.
He isn't watching the reflection of the screen in your eyes!
And he's not listening to the sound of your fingers to figure out which buttons you're pressing, either!
I've been watching him the entire time.
There has to be another reason!
I haven't sweat like this in a while.
That's why I took it off.
Hurry up and throw the next pitch already.
But I don't think I need to worry about sweating anymore.
I'm gonna declare my pitch.
It's gonna be a straight, high to the outside.
What's that?
W-What? What are you saying, Jotaro?!
You heard me.
Or are you already going deaf, Gramps?
I said I'm gonna declare my pitch.
I'll pitch straight, high to the outside.
Jotaro!
Do you believe me, or not?
Are you that foolish?
Next Episode
What are you saying, Jotaro?!
I said I'm gonna declare my pitch.
Jotaro isn't lying.
Yes.
Did you rig the game console?!
No.
I'm sure you're using your hat to cheat!
"It isn't cheating unless you get caught."
Episode 42
The Desolate Void: Vanilla Ice Part 1