Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 15: Justice Part 2
Polnareff... I want you dead!
I'm going to avenge my son by ripping out your innards!
But right now, I can't let him find Hol Horse's corpse.
Hey, ma'am!
She's not behind the counter, either.
Things will only get worse if the other three show up!
I need to kill them one by one, dammit.
Just stay away!
Ma'am, you there?
I think I just heard something crash.
Is everything okay?
Ma'am, I'm coming in.
Ouch...
What happened, ma'am?!
Don't mind me, it's nothing.
I simply fell and banged my hip!
You fell?
That's really dangerous, especially after burning your hand.
You sure are absent-minded.
Thank you.
Please excuse me... I'll be fine.
Your concern is appreciated.
Get the hell out!
Who the hell let you in here, goddammit?!
I'll spare you my wrath for now...
But soon, I'll kill you just like I did Hol Horse!
All it takes is a tiny wound...
...and I can turn you into a puppet for my Justice to control!
Here we go... your staff.
What's wrong? You're dripping with sweat.
N-No, really, pay me no mind...
Please just rest in your room.
You sure?
But aren't you running this hotel all by yourself?
Don't you have any family?
Maybe a son?
Huh? What was that?
N-Nothing, I was just going to say I've grown fond of living alone.
Oh? I see...
But aren't you lonely?
Like, say your son had a wife...
Your grandkids would be happily running around the lobby right now.
They might be noisy, but...
...aren't families great?
If you had kids, you think they'd be older than me?
What's wrong?
Did they move to the big city or something?
N-No... They've passed away.
Oh, I-I'm so sorry. I've been so rude!
You're the cretin that killed him, goddammit!
I'm going to murder you! Murder you!
Here, have a seat.
Want a shoulder rub?
I'm all alone, too.
I lost my mother when I was really young.
All of this makes me remember her...
Just for tonight...
...you can call me your son...
...and ask me whatever!
You stinking brat!
Maybe I really should just kill you right now!
Whoa, you're really tense!
I guess you've had it rough.
Wh-Who is that?
H-Hol Horse? You're still alive?
He must have made his Stand disappear
before he shot himself in the mouth!
Th-That face!
P-Polnareff! Behind ya...
It's Hol Horse!
Wha—
The hell?!
Silence! I know you're the one who
murdered J. Geil, because I'm his mother!
Chariot!
You're a Stand user?
Those responsible for murdering my son shall die!
M-Mr. Joestar!
Too late.
I've already ensured you can't contact the other three.
Because...
I've summoned some friends!
Who the hell are they?!
I-It's you...
That Indian traveler we found dead when we first got here!
How are they moving?!
This is my Stand Justice's ability!
A person can have no more than one Stand,
but my Justice bypasses this by controlling corpses!
It can control hundreds, even thousands!
Aren't you taking this needless grudge a bit far?
To think that such a twisted Stand user was after us...
This here town... wants y'all dead...
And if ya get so much as a scratch, this'll happen!
All I need is one tiny wound.
Just a little one.
Then my Stand, Justice, will kill you!
Get him!
Gotta run!
Polnareff! Ya can't just leave me here!
Fuck off! Did you already forget about Abdul?
I have no reason to help you!
You can die for all I care!
You can't escape, Polnareff!
I'll rip your brain out!
I'll snap your spine in half!
I'll crush your balls!
I shall avenge my son!
How terrifying!
How can an old woman run this fast?!
Take this!
Shit! He ran into the back room!
After him! Break down the door!
W-What the hell?
This hallway leads down into the basement...
Even if I tried to yell for Mr. Joestar and the others,
I'm too far away for them to hear me!
I think I'd be fine fighting on my own,
but I'll be in big trouble if I get so much as a scratch.
She'll do anything to take control of me!
D-Damn... Isn't there a way outside?
I can't get out the window with those bars.
Shit...
I'll hide in here!
The door just broke...
I might end up having to fight them...
But I can't let them land even a single scratch on me.
I can hear them in the hallway.
They must be checking the other doors...
Crap, they're getting closer by the second!
And what the hell?
Am I in a bathroom?
Why am I always getting attacked in the bathroom...?
Shit, the toilet is so dirty...
All right, come at me!
But the second you walk in,
my Chariot will chop you all up in a single breath.
W-What?
Now I can't hear anything.
Those things... and that hag...
What the hell are they doing?
Aren't they going to break down the door?
What are they up to?
Just do something already!
They saw me from the other side!
The fuck?!
Sh-Shit...
He stabbed my tongue!
Well done!
He's finally fallen under my Justice's control!
You fucking little brat!
I'm going to crush your stupid face
if you don't open that door right this instant!
Now laugh!
How pitiful, Polnareff!
Very pitiful, indeed!
Because of your act of cowardice, my son, J. Geil,
died feeling even more pitiful and upset than you do this very moment!
Now then... Why don't we have you
make this bathroom spotless, Polnareff?
Lick the toilet until it shines!
Lick it all up!
Lick... it... all... up...
Like that!
A-Anything but that...
Anything but that!
Save me...
W-What is it? There's no reason to barge in without knocking.
What do you need?
I'm looking for Polnareff.
And I did knock.
Maybe you didn't hear me since you were doing something else...
...old lady.
J
Ju
Jus
Justi
Justic
Justice
E
En
Eny
Power: D
Speed: E
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Enya
I'm looking for Polnareff. You seen him?
What should I do?
Jotaro is clever, unlike Polnareff,
and will know the right questions to ask.
He'll think I'm suspicious if I play dumb.
What a pain!
I'll tell him the truth, and as soon as he
turns his back to me, I'll stab him with my scissors!
After that, my Stand will kill him.
Yes, of course.
I know exactly where Mr. Polnareff is, Mr. Jotaro.
Crap... Jotaro doesn't know even
the smallest scratch will defeat him.
S-Stay away! Go tell Mr. Joestar and Kakyoin!
That old hag is the Stand user!
He was just here. Right now he's using the toilet, Mr. Jotaro.
Really, the toilet? Behind this door?
Yes, that's right.
Just go through that door,
and it's the last door at the end of the hall.
You fool! You really are just a stupid brat!
Killing Polnareff will make my son in heaven happy!
If I kill Jotaro, Lord Dio in Egypt will be happy!
Oh, that's right.
I forgot to ask, old lady...
Oh my, what's the matter, old lady? Looks like you fell.
Did you trip?
T-Too close...
Oh, that could have been really bad.
Running while holding scissors...
What a relief nothing bad happened.
Such a relief...
Sorry to ask while you're down, but I have another question.
Why did you just call me Jotaro?
I didn't tell you my name, and nobody said it in front of you.
I'd like to know.
Come on, tell me.
Maybe it's because I liked Columbo as a kid,
but when something bothers me, I become restless.
W-Why do you suspect me?
The hotel register!
You wrote your name on the hotel register earlier, did you not?
It's so dry in here...
You wrote "Kujo Jotaro."
Oh?
When you say "hotel register," you mean this?
Yes, exactly that!
Kujo Qtaro?
"Jotaro" isn't written anywhere.
I suspected you from the moment
you said "Joestar" when we first met.
I told the others not to use my name.
And yet, somehow you knew...
So quit playing dumb.
I already know you're one of the Stand users that's after us, hag.
Well, what's wrong?
Aren't you gonna show me your Stand?
I've already shown you!
Ora! Ora! Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
My Stand, Justice, has triumphed!
I just need one spot! One little spot!
You've fallen into my trap, Jotaro!
Polnareff!
Jotaro, it's me, Hol Horse!
Enya's got herself a fog Stand.
Yer wound'll turn into a hole like mine, then she'll control ya!
She can even control corpses!
Shut your mouth, Hol Horse!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Can you punch fog with your fist?
Can you cut fog with your sword?
Can you shoot fog with your gun?
Useless! Absolutely useless!
You pests can't do anything!
She's got the strongest Stand!
Them puny Stands of ours're useless!
Nothing'll beat that Stand!
Yes, yes, keep it coming.
Keep pouring on the compliments.
Now, Jotaro, I'll control you too!
R-Run, Jotaro! She'll put a hole in your leg!
Gimme a break.
No need to run.
Before this fucking hag takes another breath,
my Stand will defeat her.
Oh? What now?
Before I do what one more time?
You stupid little brat!
Before I take another breath?
I'll do that right—
Just one...
What...?
Jotaro's Star Platinum is inhaling Justice's face!
P-Please stop...
And he's holding it in!
Soon she won't be able to breathe!
Now then...
Looks like her head is full...
...of the fog she liked to play around with.
I'm so mad...
Why the hell do you even care what I've been licking?
Quit asking stupid questions.
Cough, cough, the toilet, cough...
Eh? You were licking what now?
I didn't quite catch that.
Who even cares?
I want to disinfect my tongue!
Just get me some medicine!
I'm pretty sure I heard someone say "toilet."
Actually, I already know.
But I can't resist messing with him!
Hey! Did Jotaro already tell you?!
You fucking old geezer!
He's messing with me!
Forget about the medicine!
All right, all right. My bad.
I'll fix you right up, Polnareff.
It'll get infected if we don't take care of it.
Toilet.
Toilet licker...
Goddammit! Let's get back to our journey! Jotaro! Kakyoin!
Everyone, get outside.
What on earth?
One step outside, and now this place is...
It's a graveyard.
She was using her Stand's fog to make this graveyard look like a town with a hotel?
So we were talking to the corpses that were buried in these graves...
S
Sta
Star
Star Pl
Star Plat
Star Platin
Ku
Star Platinum
Kujo
Kujo Jo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: A
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
T-Take her with us? The old lady?
Yeah.
We need to know how many more Stand users there are,
what their powers are, and where in Egypt Dio is hiding.
Not to mention what Dio's Stand's power is.
If we can get the old lady to tell us that alone...
...we'll have a major advantage.
I highly doubt she'll tell us, though...
We just need to use my Hermit Purple
to project what she's thinking onto a TV.
Now I see!
Since there's no TV here, we'll just do it in the next town!
Hol Horse!
That bastard!
Our car!
I'll be payin' Dio a vist!
See ya later!
So long as ya ain't killed first!
But lemme warn ya!
Kill the old lady soon as ya can.
She'll show ya just how scary Dio really is if ya don't!
Later!
What the hell is he talking about?
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Why have you come for me?
Lord Dio truly trusts no one.
They should have no problem shrinking.
When I say I'll do something...
They both flew back at the same time!
Oh God!
You don't need strength to kill a man!
Episode 16
Lovers Part 1