It's about time...
...Dio!
Congratulations, Polnareff!
Not only did you manage to avenge your sister,
you even made it all the way here from the Far East.
Can I take your head as a prize for getting this far?
You have one more chance.
Descend two steps, and you may join me as an ally.
But if you would prefer death, ascend the remaining steps.
When I first met you...
...I was completely at the mercy of your malevolent charm.
After that day, I was led down a path of utter failure.
It was a fate worse than death!
I lived for nothing more than to do your bidding!
But now, I've quelled my fear.
All that's left is my will to fight!
Even though two people in our group have died since our journey with Mr. Joestar first began...
...their deaths have only strengthened my resolve!
Is that so?
In that case, ascend.
I see, I see, Polnareff...
By descending the stairs, you have chosen to ally yourself with me, the mighty Dio!
W-What?!
I'm sure I just tried going up a step!
What's wrong?
Have I weakened your unwavering resolve, Polnareff?
Could it be that you truly do fear me?
Or did your subconscious fear
cause your body to act against your will?
That's impossible! I'm sure I tried going up the stairs!
W-What did he do?! Was it his Stand?
I-It can't be...
It was Dio's Stand...
...The World?
J-Just what can it do?
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 45: Dio's World Part 1
Polnareff, for what purpose do humans live?
They live to attain peace of mind
by conquering their fears and anxieties.
Seeking fame...
...controlling others...
...and acquiring wealth are methods
by which they attain peace of mind.
Some even choose to attain
peace of mind through friendships or marriage.
When humans express a willingness to help others,
or proclaim their actions to be in the name of love or peace...
...their true motive is really to attain peace of mind.
Attaining peace of mind is the true goal of all mankind.
So tell me, now that I have enlightened you,
why do you still feel anxiety in serving me?
This is the simplest path to attaining peace of mind.
Doesn't the thought of challenging me,
knowing it may bring about your demise...
...give you anxiety?
No way... Am I really subconsciously submitting to him?
You're a very powerful Stand user.
I would hate to kill you.
Will you sever your ties with Joestar and your friends, and come serve me for all of eternity?
I promise it will bring you eternal peace of mind.
I'm at my limit...
Abdul, Iggy... give me courage!
Th-That's enough, Dio!
I already submitted to you once!
I refuse to submit again before I've even seen your Stand!
Then you leave me no choice...
Prepare to meet your end, Polnareff!
Is that The World? Bring it on!
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
TN: Muda is a taunt/battle cry used to express futility.
M-Mr. Joestar!
You don't need to worry anymore, Polnareff!
Dio!
Was that Dio?!
After him!
I need to tell you guys something first!
I experienced The World's power just a moment ago...
W-Well, I say experienced, but I didn't understand it at all.
I-I'll tell you exactly what happened!
I thought I was climbing up the stairs toward him,
but I kept going down instead!
I-I'm not sure I'm making any sense right now...
...but I just can't explain what he did.
It felt like I was going insane.
He wasn't using a simple trick like hypnosis or super speed...
It was something strange and terrifying...
What about Abdul and Iggy?
Th-They didn't make it...
They died to save me...
I see...
Mr. Joestar, the sun is setting.
We need to hurry.
Right...
Hey, Nimrod... What's above this floor?
A-A tower...
It's a single room at the very top!
Lord Dio rests there during the day...
Is there any other way to the top?
N-No... That's the only way.
All right. Lead us up.
Ora!
It's him...
Even though I've never met him,
I've known about this man for as long as I can remember.
This has been a long time coming...
I feel like I've known him since the day I was born.
So does Jotaro...
He brings back nothing but bad memories.
The Joestar blood coursing through our veins has destined us to do battle with him.
I have no regrets.
Be it our journey thus far, or whatever will happen next...
I regret none of it.
I've got a feeling in my gut,
and it's telling me I'm on the side of light.
Dio is darkness.
Mr. Joestar and the others are on the side of light, too.
Even though I'm injured, my courage still grows stronger.
I'm on the side of light; the side of righteousness!
Attack as soon as the coffin opens.
But be careful.
There's no telling if he's in there or not.
Nimrod, open it up!
L-Lord Dio! I swear I haven't betrayed you!
I only led them here because I believed you could defeat them!
As surely as I believe pissing into the wind will wet your pants!
Please understand!
Shut your mouth and open it up already!
Please make sure these idiots die!
Lord Dio!
He's coming out!
Me?
I-I'm inside the coffin?!
But I just opened the lid!
W-What? How?!
I had my eyes glued on him!
Did any of you see Nimrod go inside-
No, get put inside the coffin?!
N-No... I was watching him the entire time,
but he appeared inside before I could tell what happened!
Polnareff is right! This wasn't some kind of trick or super speed!
We're in trouble...
We're in big trouble!
Run!
D-Dammit!
What are you doing, Polnareff?!
Goddammit!
What in the world was that?
I couldn't see a thing, but I felt something much more powerful than any Stand we've ever seen before!
It was like knowing a bulldozer is coming for you
by the sound of the engine alone!
I felt it, too! That cold, murderous intent!
It felt like someone put an icicle up my ass!
It would have taken us out one-by-one if we had tried to fight it!
This is bad! Really bad!
It's almost sunset!
His time has finally come.
Don't tell me we're gonna sit on our asses until sunrise!
I'll make myself clear, Mr. Joestar!
There's no way I'm running away from this now!
I agree with Polnareff.
So do I, but the situation has changed.
We've encountered his Stand, The World, yet we still have no idea what it does.
If you climb a mountain without knowing which route you'll take,
or where the summit is, you'll inevitably get lost!
Inevitably!
In fact, it's as inevitable as
a good belch after drinking a refreshing cola!
Dio is definitely gonna come after us.
He'll want to finish us off before sunrise!
We need to use this chance to discover his Stand's ability!
It's the only chance we have!
No! I'm not running away!
Abdul and Iggy died for me!
I'll use underhanded tactics,
and burn in hell for it if I have to, but I refuse to run away!
Wait, Polnareff!
Gramps, we can't stop him.
Jotaro, tell us your thoughts.
Polnareff will fight him in pursuit.
We'll fight him in retreat.
Basically...
...it's a pincer attack.
Hey, mister.
I wanna buy your truck. Name your price.
You kiddin' me?! I need it for work!
What're you-
Let's go, Kakyoin!
There you are, Dio!
Run away until sunrise? That ain't happening!
I'll defeat you by myself!
Even without knowing what your Stand is capable of,
I have my ways of defeating you!
You're dead!
Hold up, Polnareff.
Normally I'd leave a stubborn guy like you alone...
...but Gramps and Kakyoin wanted me to stay...
...so here I am.
Jotaro!
Gimme a break.
Th
The
The W
The Wo
The Worl
The World
An automobile...
Such impressive power and speed.
We only had horse-drawn carriages in my time.
Hey, pal! What's the big idea?
This is Senator Wilson Phillips' car!
Do I gotta make you spew blood from your eye sockets?!
My, my... Young folks are so hot-blooded these days.
Ow!
Silence yourself and get in the front seat.
You will be driving me.
Wh-Who the heck are you?!
Do you think you can get away with this?!
No, of course he won't!
Nobody can get away with doing this to me!
I graduated from high school and college with top marks!
I was captain of the college wrestling team!
I became a politician since my peers admired and respected me!
I own a one-thousand acre villa in Hawaii!
I married a gorgeous model twenty-five years my younger!
I pay fifty times more in taxes than regular people!
I've crushed every enemy on my path to become the president!
I'm Senator Wilson Phillips!
Listen up, whippersnapper!
I'll have you locked up for this!
Locked up for-
I won't repeat myself.
Drive.
Wh-Who the heck is this guy? He'll kill me!
I'll die if I don't run!
I'm dead meat if I can't escape!
Help... me?
W-What?!
I just jumped outside, so h-how did I end up inside?!
How could this happen?!
Make haste until we reach the truck.
If you fail to reach it, I will kill you.
C-Certainly!
How am I inside?! How?!
I know! It's because I'm a senator!
There's nothing a senator can't do!
I can feel his dark aura coming closer.
It's after us.
He's coming right for us!
Can Dio tell exactly where you are?
No. Our shared connection is through the body of my grandfather, Jonathan Joestar.
We can sense each other
through an inexplicably shared wavelength...
...but it's only good for knowing when the other is nearby.
It's why I couldn't tell where the mansion was,
even though we were so close.
The only thing he knows is that a Joestar is close.
He can't tell the difference between Jotaro and I.
I don't think he noticed that we split up.
That's weird...
In the movies, the engine always starts right up...
W-We're stuck in traffic...
Rush hour traffic at this time is bumper-to-bumper.
Go.
I would if I could, but I can't move an inch.
The sidewalk is wide enough. Go.
The sidewalk?!
It's packed with people heading home from work!
It matters not. Go.
C-Certainly!
Quickly now.
Certainly!
It started. Hurry and get on, Polnareff.
O-Okay...
I've gone to great lengths for you!
My life... You'll spare my life because I'm a senator, right?!
I will not.
That's it! I'm dreaming!
A senator like me could never die like this!
I'm dreaming! I'm dreaming! Yippee!
There they are. Approach them. As close as you can.
The World is ineffective unless I am close.
He's getting closer! In that car! That's Dio!
Kakyoin!
Kakyoin...
Dio, take this!
Emerald Splash!
W-What is he?!
He didn't move from his seat,
and he deflected my attack with one finger!
How about this?!
He even deflected a concentrated splash! Damn!
When did he call out his Stand?
Impossible! How didn't I notice?!
Just a bit too far away.
He flew out of The World's range.
W-What's happening?!
What do I stand to gain from telling you?
Keep your eyes forward and drive.
Be careful, Kakyoin! You got too close to him!
I-I'm sorry... I-I couldn't help it...
Several months ago, he said to me
"There's no need to vomit with fright...
Be at peace. Be at peace, Kakyoin..."
Dammit! Never again! I will never lose again!
Kakyoin, are you okay?
Did you see The World?
Yeah... I attacked it from about ten meters away.
Any closer, and he would have got me.
Now we know his Stand holds a secret
far more frightening than anything we could have imagined.
But I did discover two things.
First, it can't travel a far distance
like Hierophant Green or Hermit Purple.
It's short-ranged and powerful like Star Platinum, with an effective range of ten meters.
Second, it attacked with its fist,
which means it probably doesn't use projectiles like bullets.
If we can get within ten meters of Dio undetected,
I think we may stand a chance of defeating him.
We need to investigate carefully.
We can't be too cautious when dealing with an enemy like him.
That's strange... His car stopped...
Watch out! Something's coming for us!
What?!
Mr. Joestar!
What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I figured it out!
I know how to reveal the secret of Dio's Stand!
Next Episode
When I remember that Abdul and Iggy are gone,
it gives me goosebumps.
I wonder if it's because they were
the first friends I shared a common goal with.
This journey to defeat Dio.
Show me your Stand, Dio!
Episode 46
Dio's World Part 2