Your sword is quite fast.
It is very impressive, but do you truly believe you can
defeat me before the flame on the table strikes twelve?
Does this not strike you as conceited... Um...
...Polnareff.
But allow me to introduce myself fully...
Jean Pierre Polnareff!
Merci beaucoup.
I appreciate your formality.
However...
Monsieur Polnareff, do not be foolish and think my flames will burn as they would in nature.
My Stand is named Magician's Red
for its ability to freely control flame.
They say the world was once completely engulfed in flames.
Your Magician's Red is the master of these flames, signifying the beginning of everything.
However, you dare call me conceited?
Do you think my swordsmanship is nothing more than mere conceit?!
He pierced all five of them in a single stab!
No. Look closer.
That's...
I-I see... The flame is connected between each coin.
I'm glad you understand what this means for you.
I'm not conceited at all.
My Stand is capable of severing fire!
It can cut air in half, creating a gap of nothingness between it.
Simply put, your Magician's Red is no match for my Silver Chariot!
When did he...?
My Stand, represented by the Chariot card,
suggests conquest and victory.
I could end things right here in this cramped room, but...
...Abdul, your flame is much stronger out in the open, is it not?
It's only right that my Stand defeats you
under the fairest of circumstances; a true victory!
Now everyone out!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 5: Silver Chariot
W-What the hell is this?!
This is Tiger Balm Garden.
Huh?
Tiger Balm Garden!
A garden found along the hillside of Hong Kong's Tai Hang Road.
Its unique appearance and flavor make it
number one among Hong Kong's bizarre sights!
I've got a prediction for you.
First off, Abdul, you...
...you will be destroyed by the power of your Stand.
Abdul...
Jotaro, you need not interfere.
With all of this open space, I can freely control my Stand.
Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
What's wrong?
Is your precious flame too good for me?
In that case, it's my turn!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
That bastard! H-He's mocking us!
He carved the statue to look just like Magician's Red!
You know...
...you make for a nice decoration in this garden, Magician's Red.
It's coming.
Will you finally show me your true power?
Fantastic!
Show me what you got!
Hey, we need to hide!
Abdul is using that move!
What's that?
Crossfire Hurricane!
Is that all you got?!
My sword can create a gap of nothingness where I slice the air,
which I'll use to cut your flame in half!
Abdul!
His flame is so strong, he's burning himself!
As I predicted!
You're dying by your own flame!
Ah, my oh my, oh my, oh my!
You still have the gall to come after me?! How unsightly!
What was that?
What?!
Impossible!
Why are there flames coming from where I severed him?
That wasn't his Stand!
It was the statue!
Your eyes were obscured by the flames.
Your Silver Chariot only succeeded in slicing through the statue it carved earlier!
I told you I was capable of freely controlling flame.
The flames you sent back at it melted the joints and allowed it to move.
Meaning you were the one to be defeated by the power of your Stand!
And now, we shall finish this!
Crossfire Hurricane!
If you wanted to fight a fortune teller with predictions, you were ten years too early.
What terrifying power!
His Stand must have melted after taking that attack. It's over!
Those are nasty burns.
He's dead, or close to it if he's lucky.
Well, maybe not lucky.
Either way, he isn't going anywhere fast.
His Stand is defeated; it's done fighting.
Now, Mr. Joestar...
Let us continue on our journey to Egypt.
W-What?
His Stand just exploded into pieces!
He flew up in the air while lying down!
Bravo! Oh, bravo!
H-He's...
Inconceivable!
He's uninjured!
But how is he floating there?
Take a good look with your inner eye.
That's...
Yeah, you got it.
My Stand, Silver Chariot, with its armor shed!
You look surprised.
It would be dishonorable of me to defeat you
before I explained my previous move.
It's only fair, after all.
Will you allow me the honor of explaining it?
Very well.
Let us hear your explanation.
My Stand didn't break apart and disappear.
Silver Chariot was wearing armor. All it did was take it off.
Only some of its armor was burned off by your flames.
That's why I'm mostly unharmed.
And with its armor gone, it's much faster.
Did you see my Stand lift me up?
Indeed. That's just how fast it is now!
I see.
Because of its heavy armor, it was forced to take the brunt of my Crossfire Hurricane.
However, that means it is now vulnerable!
Now that it lacks proper protection...
...if I were to attack it again, it would not survive!
Oui, precisely.
But that's impossible!
Impossible? We shall see about that.
I'm gonna show you something that will blow your socks off.
Oh? Please do.
W-What?!
His Stand just created six... No, seven duplicates!
I-Impossible...
Stand users can only have one Stand!
It appears I've succeeded.
These are afterimages.
These afterimages of my Stand will confuse not just your sight, but all of your senses.
You don't stand a chance of keeping up with it.
How do you like my swordsmanship now?!
S
Sil
Silve
Silver
Silver Ch
Silver Cha
Silver Char
Silver Chari
J
Silver Chario
Je
Silver Chariot
Jea
Jean
Jean Pi
Jean Pie
Jean Pier
Jean Pierr
Jean Pierre
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Jean Pierre P
Jean Pierre Pol
Jean Pierre Polna
Jean Pierre Polnare
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Red Bind!
And just as I finished saying you won't stand a chance of keeping up with it...
Your flames will only hit the afterimages.
Striking at random now?
You're getting a bit desperate, Abdul.
The only thing he's accomplishing is wasting his energy.
Crossfire Hurricane!
Non, non, non, non, non, non!
That was an afterimage!
That attack will never work against my Stand!
Come on, come on, come on!
Abdul!
Such precision... H-He has...
...an impressively well-trained Stand ability!
I trained ten years for personal reasons.
Now, give it your best shot.
My next move will finish you.
In the name of chivalry, you insist on explaining your attacks.
That is quite honorable.
Therefore, I shall also reveal a secret before beginning my next attack.
I have several variations to my Crossfire Hurricane.
It is an Ankh-shaped flame, yet it need not stay whole.
I am capable of separating it to let the pieces fly independently.
Crossfire Hurricane Special!
Try to dodge this!
It's no use, Abdul!
They formed a circle!
There's no opening!
Naïve! Naïve, naïve, naïve, naïve!
Naïve!
I'll use your power against you again!
Sever it! Send it back to him!
What?!
That's...
...the hole in the ground he made earlier!
That's it!
He used the first flame to create a tunnel!
Then he sent the Crossfire Hurricane through it!
I told you...
My flames can be separated to fly independently!
Burning to death is a rather painful way to die.
Use this dagger to end your life.
I was conceited...
I didn't think his flames were a match for my swordsmanship...
I'll die honorably by burning to death...
Since he was able to defeat me, I'll accept my fate out of respect...
Ending my own life would be dishonorable...
I see now you truly are a chivalrous man.
Even now, you have chosen not to attack me with the dagger while my back was turned.
You have remained honorable despite your orders from Dio.
You do not deserve to die.
Something must be behind this...
Jojo!
Got it.
Those tentacles are nasty!
Jotaro, hurry and pull it out!
Hurry! Hurry!
Put a sock in it, Gramps.
Good! Now that the flesh bud is gone,
we can be bud-dies! Ba dum tsh!
Kakyoin, doesn't it piss you off when idiots make shitty puns?
The boat we chartered from the Speedwagon Foundation yesterday should be at the harbor by now.
What is it? Do you need something more...
...Polnareff?
I didn't thank you for freeing me from Dio's grasp yet.
For that, you must thank Jojo.
Don't bother.
It appears no one will accept your thanks.
That's fine. I'm not the forceful type.
But one more thing...
Monsieur Joestar, I have a bizarre question to ask you.
A bizarre question?
Pardon my curiosity, but I noticed you refused to remove your gloves while eating earlier.
Your left hand wouldn't happen to be the same as your right, would it?
Huh? My left hand, a right hand?
That really is a bizarre question.
What are you getting at?
I'm searching for the man who murdered my younger sister.
I've never seen his face...
...but, I know he has two right hands.
My hand was lost in battle fifty years ago.
Pardon my rudeness. I'm sorry.
Do you mind telling us what happened?
It was three years ago...
My younger sister and her classmate were
coming home from school on that rainy day...
...walking on a country road in France.
On the side of the road, a man stood with his back to them.
Strangely, despite the heavy downpour, the rain was falling around him
in a dome-like shape, as if he were surrounded by an invisible shield.
Suddenly, her classmate's chest was
sliced open like a blade had cut her.
And then...
...my sister was raped, and then killed.
That was all the man wanted from her.
Miraculously, her friend somehow survived.
She hadn't seen his face, but she saw he had two right hands.
Nobody believed what she said, except for me!
I believed her since the man possessed a secret power similar to mine!
That man must have been a Stand user.
I swore!
I swore he would atone for my sister's death so she could finally rest in peace!
I'll use my Stand to get revenge!
And then a year ago, I met Dio!
I see something!
It's...
A vision. It is not mine.
What lies within your heart is being projected through my power.
How about it?
Would you like to be my friend?
I can sense you're distressed. You're in pain.
Stay by my side, and it will disappear from your heart.
The vision in the crystal is what pains you, correct?
I'll lend you my power.
I, too, suffer in pain...
My body is unable to be out in the sunlight.
Please help me so I can help you.
I will find this man for you!
Then, he ordered me to kill you guys.
I really believed it's what I needed to do.
Although the flesh buds are partially to blame, Dio's power of manipulation is truly terrifying.
Yeah. But based on what you just said...
...it sounds like Dio found the man with
two right hands, and they've now joined forces.
I've decided to go to Egypt with you guys!
If I find Dio, I'll find the man who took my sister's life!
Is that okay?
I have no objections.
You're just gonna follow us either way.
Jean Pierre Polnareff!
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Stand name: Silver Chariot.
Silver Chariot
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Power: Fast and precise swordsmanship!
Silver Chariot
Jean Pierre Polnareff
You can count on me!
Gimme a b-
Excuse me!
Can you snap a quick picture of us?
So dreamy!
This is totally my chance!
Pretty please!
We want it facing the ocean!
Shut the hell up! And fuck off!
Now, now, now, now...
I'll take your picture for you!
Come, come.
With your banging legs, we need a full body shot!
That's good!
Just one more now!
Très bien!
Just like this button, I want to
push, push, push my way into your hearts!
Something about him alludes me...
Talk about a mood swing.
He's the kind of guy who keeps his brain in his pants.
Gimme a break.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Can't you do something about those school uniforms?
And students should dress as students.
Face me, one-on-one, you cowards!
Could she be that Stand's user?
If a Stand user inhales even a little bit of cigarette smoke...
Episode 6
Dark Blue Moon
By the way...