I'da expected a fella with such a rough mug to go down a bit harder!
Then again, I suppose some folks gotta have a sad endin'.
It ain't exactly uncommon fer someone
to bite the dust before sayin' goodbye.
I bet it sounds like I've dealt with this firsthand, but...
Polnareff! Don't let him get to you!
Don't you get it?!
Mr. Abdul told you not to fight by yourself!
But you ignored him...
You wanted revenge, even if it meant dying alongside your enemy!
Mr. Abdul followed you because
he was worried, and look what happened!
Just what do you expect me to do now?
We have to retreat.
Abdul was mercilessly stabbed in the back...
My sister was killed without hesitation...
Yet you still expect me to hold these regrets inside and run away?
We won't stand a chance if we don't know how their Stands work!
Don't fight a losing battle!
That's what Mr. Abdul wanted to tell you!
Hey! Come on, lil' Pol Pol!
Why, you...!
Polnareff! Slowly walk back towards me!
We'll escape in that truck!
So you really do want me to hold it in, huh?
F-Fi-
Hey, Polnareff.
Episode 11: Emperor and Hanged Man Part 2
Abdul died to keep you alive.
I bet you really feel like you owe him something, huh?
He would still be among us, if not for you.
W-Why, you...
Where's your user?!
Polnareff, calm down!
Really though, there's no need to be sad.
You should be thrilled!
You'll be reunited shortly.
I'll kill you, and then you can join
those fools you hold dear in the next world!
Your little sister was an absolute darling, Polnareff!
Once you and your sister are reunited, you should ask her...
...how exactly I killed her!
Polnareff, don't let him get to you!
Don't retaliate!
Why, you...!
Do you know why your Chariot cannot cut down my Hanged Man?
I exist only within a mirror.
And your Stand is incapable of entering a mirror.
That's why!
Does that make you mad?
I bet you're really mad!
Hey, Hol Horse! Fire away. Let's put an end to this idiot.
Aye aye, sir!
Die!
Emerald Splash!
What?!
What? Polnareff...
...got hit in the crossfire!
Kakyoin, huh? Not bad!
My Stand ain't gonna hit from here.
Even if I got 'im, the bullet'd be mighty weak.
So boss J. Geil went after 'em, eh?
Seems he's itchin' to finish off Polnareff 'imself!
I-I'm sorry, Kakyoin.
I-I...
I didn't care if I died, so long as I could avenge my sister.
But... I get it now...
I understand how Abdul felt.
I refuse to let his feelings go to waste.
I'll fight to keep living!
Do you really understand?
Yeah.
Take this instead of a handshake as proof we've made up, Polnareff.
Right. Th-Thank you, Kakyoin...
Once they come after us, we'll defeat them together!
Abdul, you...
Back there, I'm sure I stabbed it with my sword.
But my strike didn't land...
There wasn't any resistance.
Even after breaking the mirror, his Stand,
Hanged Man, still attacked from the shards.
It tried to attack my reflection from inside the mirror!
But my Stand can't go inside a mirror...
How am I supposed to attack it
while it's in some kind of mirror world?
Damn!
Polnareff, you keep mentioning something about "the mirror world" and "inside the mirror..."
...but a world within mirrors doesn't exist.
This isn't some kind of fantasy or fairy tale.
Are you shitting me? You saw it too, didn't you?!
You can only see it in a mirror,
but when you turn around, it's not there!
Yes.
But the image in a mirror is just a reflection of light... nothing more.
You don't have to tell me that!
Listen! I can only speak for what's happening right now!
If Stands exist, so could a mirror world!
Impossible.
Look, you...
I believe there could be a clue that will help us
solve the mystery of Hanged Man.
If Stands can defeat other Stands...
That means there's still something we don't know about his-
Polnareff! It's inside the steering wheel plate!
What?!
It caught up to us!
Look out!
A-Are you okay, Kakyoin?
I-I hit my chest, but I'm fine.
What?
Chariot!
Kakyoin! Get away from anything reflective!
Dammit... I get it now. I just saw it.
It's going from mirror to mirror!
It moves by jumping from one reflective surface to the other!
It traveled all this way...
...by continuously reflecting!
Reflecting?
That means it acts like light!
Is acting like light the true nature of his Stand?
Kakyoin, it was just in the car's bumper!
It'll reflect off the car's bumper and into something else.
Stay away reflective material!
And take anything off your body that reflects!
Rip the buttons off your uniform!
Misters, are you okay?
Do you fellas need some help?
Hey, kid! It's dangerous, get out of here!
Boy, your car's totally messed up...
Hey, you're bleeding.
You sure you're okay?
W-Why, you...!
It's in that kid's eye!
Hey, kid. Don't look at us!
Huh?
I said don't look at us!
Quit following me with your eyes!
Huh? But you're hurt.
I'm fine! See? Couldn't be better!
Now go look over there!
But you're bleeding...
Look over there, you little shit!
Damn you, J. Geil!
What will you do?
You wouldn't stab this cute little kid's eye out
with that sword of yours, would you, Polnareff?
Polnareff!
I finally have you!
There's nowhere left to run!
Not unless you stab out that kid's eye!
What a coward! This is unforgivable!
Hey, Kakyoin.
You can't say lame shit like that in this kind of situation.
Listen up! In these situations...
...you gotta say something like this before you get revenge!
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff!
For my sister's honor,
and so that my friend Abdul can rest in peace...
I'm going to hurl you...
...into the depths of despair, J. Geil!
Sorry, kid! I'll buy you a caramel later!
There's sand in my eye!
P-Polnareff, it's in your eye!
I don't really understand how its power works,
but it's essentially moving at the speed of light.
That's faster than any normal person can see.
But I knew that if I got the kid to close his eyes,
the next place it would jump to is my eye.
I see...
Hanged Man can only exist within the world of reflections.
When one world is about to be destroyed,
it has to move to something else that is reflective!
Which means...
If I have my sword ready and know its trajectory, I can cut it!
The user is over there!
You bastard. Finally...
Finally!
Finally we meet...
J. Geil!
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff!
I've learned the secret of your Stand.
It's a Stand of light that moves at incredible speeds.
There's no way I could keep up.
However, if I know where it's going...
...and I slash its trajectory in that moment...
I can slash you, too!
If Kakyoin and Abdul hadn't shown up, I probably
wouldn't have figured it out, and you would have killed me.
Polnareff! He's not the man with two right hands!
That's not J. Geil!
W-What?!
Polnareff!
E
Em
Empe
Empero
Emperor
H
Ho
Hol
Hol Ho
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Hol Hor
Hol Horse
Polnareff!
Over here!
You dumbass!
I'm J. Geil!
You...
That poor sap is just a drifter who happened to be in town.
I just cut him up a little bit
so he would have the same wound as me!
You totally fell for it!
Approaching him without even knowing what I looked like was a huge mistake!
You bastard...
Take this! My Emerald—
Hey, hold up!
Take a good look around you!
Hey, gather 'round!
These nice fellas tell me they're giving out money!
What?!
They'll give us money for nothing!
Thanks a bunch!
You have such big hearts!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
Please give us money!
Do you finally see what's going on?
You think you saw through my Stand?
You fools.
I've known about my Stand's weakness for quite some time.
If there are so many reflective surfaces that you can't figure out its trajectory, it has no weakness!
Don't look! Quit staring!
Stop staring at us!
No more running.
Is it worth it to blow them all up?
You did sacrifice your youth hunting me, after all...
But now you'll just accept defeat before you succeed?!
What a lonely, pathetic life.
Meanwhile I, J. Geil, will continue to have cute girls
like your sister surround me, as I live a fun, happy life!
Come to think of it, your sister...
...was really good at sobbing!
Time to die.
W-Why, you...!
Polnareff, that's not what you should say in this situation.
While exacting revenge,
you shouldn't say something lame like, "Why, you."
You should say this...
My name is Kakyoin Noriaki!
To avenge my friend, Abdul...
...and so that the soul of my friend
Polnareff's sister may rest in peace...
...I will have you pay with your life.
This gold coin will go to whoever picks it up first!
It's shiny enough to see your own face in!
Now I see, Kakyoin.
It looks like all of their eyes are focused at one point now.
Yeah.
So now we know the trajectory Hanged Man will have to take!
Merci, Kakyoin!
Now!
Wait!
Open... Open...
Looks like you're the one who's really good at sobbing, J. Geil!
I'll send you to Hell, sobbing the entire way.
But I have something to do that I can't
rely on the guardians of Hell to do for me...
And that's...
To turn you into a pincushion!
I've been waiting years for this moment!
I'll leave the rest to Yama.
So that was Hanged Man...
He was rotten to the core.
I finally got my revenge!
Ha
Han
Hange
Hanged
Hanged Ma
J
Hanged Man
J.
J. G
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: A
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
J. Gei
J. Geil
Hold it!
I finally found ya!
What's the holdup?
If yer gonna leg it, run like yer lives depend on it!
Right, boss J. Geil?
Say yer prayers. This here's the end of the line!
Act like it's over and come at us!
Show us whatcha got, darnit!
Right, boss J. Geil?
Ya hear what I'm sayin', boss J. Geil?!
I don't think he's listening anymore.
He's a bit held up right now...
Seeing as he's burning in Hell!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Don't gimme that bull! Yer bluff ain't gonna work on me!
There's no way y'all beat 'im!
Even I ain't got a chance in hell
of beatin' the invincible Hanged Man!
Polnareff, that just ain't funny!
That son-of-a-bitch's body is about two or three hundred meters that way. Wanna go see it?
Sure, will do!
Hey! Are you running away?!
I don't stand a chance against them fellas!
No way I can win alone!
I'll leg it fer now, then get 'em when I can!
A fella like me's only good when I'm one half of a duo!
I'll take Number two over one!
That's the Hol Horse way of life!
That a problem?
What?!
Mr. Joestar! Jotaro!
We already know about Abdul.
Though it was a simple funeral, his body's been buried.
The one who stabbed Mr. Abdul in the back was the man with
two right hands, but the cause of death was Hol Horse's bullet.
What should we do with him?
I'll give him his sentence.
Death!
Wha-?!
Please run, Sir Hol Horse!
Sir Hol Horse!
What's with you, woman?!
I don't know what's going on, but I'm always thinking of you!
It's my only reason to live!
Please run! Hurry!
You bitch! Let go!
What's wrong with you?!
Jotaro! Kakyoin! Don't let Hol Horse get away!
Too late.
Huh? Oh...
Well said, baby!
I'll accept yer feelings an' keep on livin'!
I'm just high-tailin' it since I love ya, baby!
Always will!
Why, you...!
Come back here!
Don't "ah" me, you bitch!
Polnareff, that woman is one of many people he probably took advantage of.
Besides, he lost his will to fight.
We don't have time to deal with him.
Abdul is gone...
But we still have to move forward.
It's already been fifteen days since we left Japan.
Jesus...
Well, it can't be helped.
All right! Let's resume our trip to Egypt!
Listen here! To defeat Dio, our hearts have to be as one.
We can't just go off on our own!
That's when they'll come after us.
Got it?
Let's get a move on!
Gimme a break.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
It's coming into view, the city of Varanasi.
Murderer!
I am responsible!
I am Joseph Joestar! An American!
What?!
I love you.
You know, doesn't that kind of look like a face?
Episode 12
Empress