What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I figured it out!
I know how to reveal the secret of Dio's Stand!
What?!
As Kakyoin Noriaki gazed at Hierophant Green,
he began to recall memories of his youth.
Your son, Noriaki, doesn't seem to be making any friends.
Nobody dislikes him, but he refuses to open up.
I'm worried about him.
I'm his mother, and even I don't understand him.
When I was younger, I thought...
"If you live in a city where you're bound to meet a lot of people...
...and you spend your entire life there, will you ever truly get to know those people, and will they know you just as well in return?
The address books of my classmates
are filled with the names of their friends.
They must have at least fifty friends each.
Maybe even a hundred.
My mother has my father, and my father has my mother...
...but I have nobody...
The rock stars on TV must have tens of thousands of friends...
I'll probably never meet anyone who sees me for who I really am.
All because not a single friend of mine can see my Hierophant Green.
Anyone who can't see it will never truly understand me."
Mr. Joestar, Jotaro, Polnareff, and Abdul
made me realize what true friends are like.
When I remember that Abdul and Iggy are gone,
it gives me goosebumps.
I wonder if it's because they were
the first friends I shared a common goal with.
This journey to defeat Dio.
In these short few weeks, we've become close friends.
Kakyoin Noriaki gazed at Hierophant Green and thought to himself...
"I'll make it invisible to everyone, just like it was before.
Yes, to reveal Dio's true identity and finally defeat him,
I'll make its presence completely disappear!"
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 46: Dio's World Part 2
Hey, Jotaro!
That car got totaled!
Up there.
Gramps and Dio are on the roof.
Only Kakyoin and Joseph are here.
I see. They're attempting a pincer attack.
Jotaro and Polnareff must be preparing to attack from behind.
A useless effort.
This is...
...Kakyoin's Hierophant!
Hierophant's barrier!
This is...
Correct!
Using the barrier my Hierophant created,
I can hit you within twenty meters from any direction!
I can also sense every move you or The World make!
Take this, Dio! Twenty-meter radius Emerald Splash!
You fool! Prepare yourself!
The World's true power, as its name suggests, is to reign supreme over the entire world!
Show me your Stand, Dio!
The World!
Kakyoin!
He went flying away instantly!
Impossible!
Kakyoin!
W-What... just happened?
Is this it?
It's over... I won't survive this...
I can't speak... or even lift a finger...
It's 5:15...
That means it's about midnight in Japan...
I wonder what my parents are doing right now...
Maybe they went to sleep...
I hope they aren't worried about me...
Kakyoin Noriaki's final thoughts were not of his parents in Japan.
Though he cared deeply for his parents, when his mind drifted to the final unsolved puzzle, his thoughts of them were put aside.
I can sense every movement made in my Hierophant's barrier...
But somehow Dio ripped the barrier apart all at once...
Why didn't it rip strand-by-strand?
They broke simultaneously; not a millisecond between them...
How did he destroy a twenty-meter large barrier all at once?
How?
Without even a moment passing...
How... All at once...?
How?
Kakyoin!
I-I can't stand around and do nothing!
Hermit-
Joseph, you're next.
Isn't it fitting that Joestar blood is the only way for
Jonathan's perfect body to become completely mine?
Dio!
How could he destroy them all at once without any time passing?
Time passing...
Time...
The clock!
I-I get it now...
H-How is that possible? There's no other explanation...
I-I need to tell them!
Somehow I need to tell them this terrifying truth...
Somehow I have to tell Mr. Joestar...
If I don't, all of them...
...will die!
How dare you hurt Kakyoin!
I'm taking that body back for my Granny Erina!
Erina? Ah, you mean that simpleton country girl.
Such foolishness.
I will drink your blood to commemorate your death!
Joseph Joestar...
...prepare to die!
M-My final Emerald... Splash...
What's this? He completely missed me.
He must have seen it fit to go out with a bang using what little strength he had left.
No way!
Kakyoin wouldn't do something pointless at a time like this!
Why did he shoot there?
What could it mean?
Was he trying to tell me something?
It's... a message...
It's all I could do...
Mr. Joestar...
Please get it...
Please... figure it out...
Kakyoin!
Kakyoin Noriaki...
Kakyoin Noriaki has died.
Kakyoin Noriaki... has died
Hermit Purple!
And take this!
The energy of the sun, the Ripple!
You senile old fool! Your Stand is too weak!
You cannot escape!
Kakyoin, why did you shoot the clock tower?
What were you trying to tell me by shooting it?
It must have been important!
I-It's Mr. Joestar!
Dio is chasing him!
But where's Kakyoin?
Kakyoin, you couldn't have!
Did you actually discover the secret of Dio's Stand from that brief encounter?
He destroyed the clock with an Emerald Splash...
...which destroyed the clock hands...
...and stopped the clock...
N-No way! Could it be...
The secret of Dio's The World...
...is that it can stop time!
Take this, Dio! Twenty-meter radius Emerald Splash!
The World!
Behold, The World!
While time is stopped,
you will neither see nor feel anything that befalls you.
Die, Kakyoin!
You don't even realize I have killed you.
You will never know what truly transpired.
I-I get it, Kakyoin!
You sent me your dying message...
...and I read it loud and clear!
H
He
Her
Herm
Hermit
Hermit P
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purpl
J
Hermit Purple
Jo
Jose
Josep
Joseph
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Joseph Joes
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Joseph Joest
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
It stops time?
His Stand lets him move while time is stopped?
He's dangerous! Really dangerous!
Calm down! Calm down and think!
The word "panic" isn't in my vocabulary!
I need to think of something...
I need to find a way to overcome and defeat him!
H-He disappeared!
W-What's the matter?
Can't hit me, Dio?
Didn't you want to drink my blood?
You've guarded yourself by channeling the Ripple around your body.
When your Hermit Purple is imbued with the Ripple,
it acts as a high-voltage wire wrapped around your body, correct?
You're quite the schemer, you cunning old man.
I could say the same of you.
You realized I was using the Ripple
and made sure not to touch me, you shrewd bastard.
But I think I finally figured out how your Stand works.
Dio, even though you can stop time,
it doesn't work for very long!
Only about three or four seconds.
Any longer, and you would have just killed us back at the mansion,
saving yourself the trouble of chasing us down!
So you already know how The World works?
Very impressive.
Kakyoin was the one who figured it out.
I refuse to let his death go in vain!
So what?
How will you use this information against me?
Just what can your pathetic Ripple do against me?
Hermit Purple and the Ripple!
Enough!
I needn't touch your Ripple to attack you!
Hey, look at that!
Some old fart fell outta the sky!
He's just like Santa Claus!
The fuck were ya doin' on the roof?
Prowlin' fer some nice ass?
Gramps!
J-Jotaro!
Stay back!
Don't come any closer!
Jotaro! What perfect timing!
But he's still not quite within my range.
Joseph must be taken care of first.
Jotaro! The secret of his Stand, The World, is time!
His Stand can stop ti-
The World!
At first, I could only stop time for a mere blink of an eye.
However, as the wound on my neck began to heal,
I could stop time for two seconds, then eventually three.
Now I am at five seconds.
Although it is strange to consider it five seconds
since time has stopped, it is indeed five seconds.
Eventually I will reach a minute, then ten minutes, and then an hour.
Then as long as I wish!
It's quite thrilling.
Soon I will be able to stop time for even longer!
Careful now, Joseph.
I see you're still guarding yourself with the Ripple.
Your troublesome Ripple may have been a nuisance to me
one hundred years ago, but now it is powerless before The World.
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Muda!
Joseph, grandson of Jonathan...
...this is the end for you!
One more second...
Zero.
Th
The
The W
The Wo
The Worl
The World
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: B
Growth Potential: B
Gramps!
S-Stay back!
R-Run away... J-Jotaro...
D-Don't... get near him...
K-Keep your...
...d-distance...
Stay away... Stay away from him...
Y-You're no... match...
Kakyoin has also been dealt with.
And I suppose Polnareff is hiding nearby.
But it matters not...
Now, Jotaro...
It's your turn!
You asshole...
...Dio!
Oh? You've decided to approach me?
You wish to face the mighty Dio?
Despite your grandfather, Joseph,
discovering the secret of The World...
...he was nothing more than a desperate, pathetic old man; no better than a student rushing to complete their exam before time has run out!
The thing is, I gotta get closer to beat the living shit out of you.
Then come as close as you'd like!
Ora!
Much too slow! The World is the ultimate Stand.
Even if you wish to ignore its ability to stop time, its speed and power far exceed Star Platinum's!
So it's the same kind of Stand as Star Platinum.
Powerful and precise, but short-ranged.
I wanted to find out how powerful The World is compared to your inferior Stand...
...however, that no longer appears necessary.
Find out what? You barely grazed my leg. Didn't feel a thing.
Though I guess you hurt my wallet by ruining my pants.
Why can't you Joestars ever concede defeat?
I suppose I shall humor you to see what more you are capable of.
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Shall we see whose attack rush is faster?
Muda Muda Muda Muda!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Next Episode
I recall the moment six months ago
when I first learned I could stop time.
...in an instant, it appeared as though
everything had stopped moving.
I shall finish you here and now
with the mighty power of The World!
The World! Time Stop!
Episode 47
Dio's World Part 3