After capturing Enya, Jotaro and company acquired a carriage.
Near the Indus River Delta, they arrived in a prosperous Pakistani city,
the leader in both trade and commerce, Karachi!
India
Pakistan
Calcutta
Varnasi
Delhi
Karachi
Indus River
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 16: Lovers Part 1
A doner kebab stand!
Why don't we stop and grab something to eat?
Doner kebabs, the hamburgers of the Middle East!
A slab of meat is placed on a spit,
allowing the surface to be roasted as it turns.
The cooked meat is shaved off, then served on bread.
It's as delicious as it looks!
Excuse me. I'll take five.
That'll be one thousand yen.
A thousand yen?
In the Middle East, the customs of
Japan and the West are thrown out the window.
Namely, the prices are never set in stone.
Foreigners will arrive here for the first time,
completely oblivious to the art of haggling.
They are easily exploited.
But in this world, such exploitation isn't frowned upon.
The person tricked into paying an exorbitant price is seen as a fool.
Now allow me to explain how it works!
A thousand yen?
Like here, for example,
act as though you see through their clever ruse...
Don't be ridiculous! That's far too much.
...laugh out loud, and then...
How much can you give me?
...they will ask the customer how much they're willing to pay.
Make it 250 yen for five!
In return, the customer names a price so low,
you would feel guilty to even suggest it. And then...
"Seriously? Have you no sense?"
they'll say as though you're mocking them.
If I sold 'em at that price, my family would starve!
Then they will gesture as if their head were being cut off.
But you mustn't give up yet!
Well, maybe I'll just go somewhere else...
Act as if you're leaving!
Okay, friend! I'll cut you a deal since you're a foreigner!
It'll be 700 yen.
He'll say this to stop you.
Make it 300.
Commence haggling!
600!
350!
550!
400!
450!
425!
Deal!
All right, I got them at half off!
Take that! I made out like a bandit!
But just as you're thinking that...
I usually sell five for 150 yen!
Bye-bye, thank you kindly!
Hey, guys! The old lady woke up!
I-I... I haven't said anything!
W-Why have you come for me?
Do you think that I, Enya, would actually
tell them the secret of Lord Dio's Stand?
W-What the hell is with these tentacles?!
Why...?
Why have you come to kill me?!
Because it's clear that Lord Dio truly trusts no one.
It's my job to make sure you never speak again.
And as for the four of you...
...I will be taking your lives.
Ma'am!
What?!
My name is Dan...
Steely Dan.
My Stand represents the Lovers card.
I will see to it that you all meet the same fate as Enya.
How could you?!
She was one of you, right?
Ma'am!
L-L-Lies... Lies...
All lies...
Lord Dio would never do this... to me....
Those things coming out of her body aren't a Stand!
They're corporeal! Actual, moving tentacles!
My Lord would never do something like this to me...
He would never plant a flesh bud...
Flesh bud?
I live to serve Lord Dio... I believe in him...
Ma'am!
T-Those rays...
The sunlight caused the tentacles to wither!
It's a flesh bud! It's made of Dio's cells!
Precisely! I'm impressed you figured it out.
That is what a flesh bud from
Dio's cells looks like when it's fully grown.
I simply helped it sprout a bit faster.
Enya, apparently you were the one who told Lord Dio of the existence of Stands...
...but there is no way Lord Dio would trust
a decrepit old woman such as you.
It would appear this never occurred to you.
Old lady!
Tell us the true identity of Dio's Stand!
Tell me!
You placed your hope and trust in Dio!
But now you know he's not the man you thought he was!
I have to defeat Dio! Please, tell me!
Tell me! You need to tell me about Dio's Stand!
Lord... Dio...
He still believes in me...
I will not speak...
Oh God!
How pitiful...
What a truly pitiful old woman she was.
But the fact that her trust ran so deeply
further proves the power of Lord Dio's sinister charm.
Because Enya was connected to my sister's death,
part of me is glad, but...
...I'm still gonna kill you.
We won't hesitate even if it's four against one.
Prepare yourself.
Get up.
Hey, jackass!
Quit acting like you're hot shit.
We'll kick your ass if that's what it takes.
Go ahead.
But none of you will be able to lay
even a single finger on me, the great Steely Dan.
Ora!
What?!
W-What's wrong, Mr. Joestar?
They both flew back at the same time!
You idiot! I was still talking!
You could have just killed your grandfather!
Listen carefully!
Did you really think I appeared before you just to kill Enya?
Y-You bastard...
You have the Stand that represents the Lovers card, right?
W-What is it?
The only thing you must know is that this battle has already begun, Mr. Joestar.
You fools...
You will never find my Stand no matter how hard you look.
Hey, kid.
Here's a tip. Hit me in the leg with your broom.
I-It can't be!
Hit me!
What happened, Mr. Joestar?!
I-It hurts!
I don't know what's happening, but the pain is unbearable!
You haven't figured it out, Joseph Joestar?
My Stand enters the bodies of others!
The moment Enya died, it entered your brain through your ear!
What?
My Stand and I are one and the same.
If my Stand is hurt, I will be as well, and vice versa.
So if you so much as scratch me...
...my Stand will react to my pain and suffering in that exact same moment by going berserk.
It will inflict pain several times greater
to the same part of your body.
I'll say it once more...
You will not be able to lay even a single finger on me!
I should also mention that Lovers has taken Lord Dio's flesh bud into your body.
It's growing inside your brain.
Just like Enya, it will eat you from the inside and kill you!
Ow!
Did I say you could hit me twice?
You fucking brat!
Well, if I'll be honest, my Stand, Lovers, is very weak.
It isn't capable of moving even a single strand of hair, making it the physically weakest Stand in the world.
But even so...
...you don't need strength to kill a man!
Do you understand, gentlemen?
L
Lo
Love
Lovers
St
Ste
Stee
Steely
Power: E
Speed: D
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Steely Da
Steely Dan
If I get hurt in a car accident, hit by a baseball, or even just trip and fall, Mr. Joestar...
...your body will suffer much greater damage than mine.
I-I can even feel pain in my prosthetic hand...
And in ten minutes,
your brain will be devoured, killing you just like Enya.
Jotaro, calm down! Don't do anything stupid!
No. I'll kill him so fast, he won't feel a thing.
Won't feel a thing, huh?
That's a great idea.
Let's see you try it, Jotaro.
It sounds fascinating.
What were you planning to destroy?
Come on! My face? My throat?
Come on, what's wrong? Just try it!
Let's see what will happen!
How about busting a hole through my chest?
Or perhaps you should forego using your Stand altogether and just bash my head open with a rock?
Here, I'll even give you the rock to use.
Is this one big enough?
Don't underestimate me.
When I say I'll do something, I fucking do it.
Don't do anything rash, Jotaro!
You've already seen his power!
Are you trying to kill your own grandfather?!
H-He's the kind of guy that would do it!
You're not taking me seriously!
You...
Jotaro!
Don't underestimate me, asshole!
After grandpappy Joeseph dies, next on my agenda...
Look out!
...is sending Lovers into your brain to kill you!
W-What the hell is your problem?!
H-How can this be?
My own grandson is getting beat up just to save me...
We're completely at his mercy.
His Stand is inside my brain...
When I was younger, I had to deal with poison being placed inside my heart, but...
I have to do something... I need to do something!
H-Hey!
Jotaro! Keep him away from Mr. Joestar!
We're gonna get as far away from him as possible!
Oh, I get it...
You think that getting far away
is enough to weaken my Stand's power?
Even the weak can possess a different kind of strength.
My Stand, Lovers, may be weak...
...but while it's inside someone's body,
I can still control it from much farther away than any other Stand.
Even from hundreds of kilometers away.
Hey, Jotaro! I'm talking to you!
What are you looking away so calmly for?
Look at me!
Sounds like you're losing your cool.
Do you plan on following me until Joseph dies?
Dan, was it?
I'll make sure you pay for this.
If that's why you're following me,
maybe I should take out a loan first.
Is this all you have?
I see you're vain enough to wear a TAG Heuer...
I'll just borrow it.
There!
It's an electronics store!
Mr. Joestar, they have TVs!
H-Hey! What are you guys doing?
Polnareff, did you seriously think we were running away?
I'm taking this fight to the Stand inside my head.
F-Fight?!
We only have a few minutes. You'll be assisting us.
Huh?!
Hermit Purple!
There!
Oh no!
How did we end up needing to look inside my own brain?
S-So that super tiny Stand... it really is inside of Mr. Joestar...
But how are we gonna defeat it?
Our Stands will enter Mr. Joestar's body, and we'll defeat it there!
W-What?!
Stands are images created from energy.
They should have no problem shrinking.
Kakyoin!
Hey, take it easy on me.
We have no time to lose. We're going in, Polnareff!
A-All right!
Hierophant Green!
Silver Chariot!
Smaller!
Become smaller!
We'll be entering through a blood vessel.
R-Right...
A drainage ditch...
This ditch... I could try jumping across,
but I would risk tripping and twisting my ankle.
And walking all the way to that bridge would be a pain.
Hey, Jotaro...
Lie down across the ditch and pretend to be a bridge.
I'll use you to walk over.
What's that? You won't be my bridge?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I said pretend to be a bridge, you spineless bastard!
W-What's wrong?!
Mr. Joestar!
M-My leg...
It's going numb...
What the hell is Jotaro doing?!
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Come on, hurry up.
Good.
You make for a rather sturdy bridge, don't you?
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
Come on...
Mr. Joestar, the enemy's Stand, Lovers,
is in the brainstem, the point where the nervous system begins.
Polnareff and I will enter the vein from inside your ear,
then swim through the blood vessels toward the brainstem.
Polnareff, open a hole in the wall of the blood vessel.
H-Hey, hold on a second!
You're using your Stands, right?
Can't you just slip through it?
At this size, it's not possible.
The wall of the blood vessel is too thick.
The hole will be microscopic, so there's no need to worry.
Cutting through a blood vessel or nerve could take several minutes.
Otherwise, we already would have cut down the enemy's Stand.
And this is only the beginning...
Keeping our Stands this small is really exhausting...
It uses so much Stand power...
Here we go!
Oh my God!
I-I don't feel so good...
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
My back itches...
I'm in such a great mood right now!
Maybe you should just lick them clean?
The one who knows himself best is the victor!
However, your strengths only really start to show once you acknowledge your weaknesses!
Episode 17
Lovers Part 2