My, how dashing!
In all my years working here,
I've never received such a strange clothing request!
I'm in a hurry. What's the total?
See ya.
C-Come again...
Let go! Let go of me!
Don't touch me anywhere funny!
Quiet! Don't say that!
Here's the ticket.
No! I don't wanna!
I wanna stay with you guys!
Little Miss...
My daughter, who is Jotaro's mother, is in grave danger right now.
We're on this journey to save her life.
Quit running away and go home.
I'm sure your parents are worried about you.
There.
Pfft, fine... I'll let you off easy this time, grandpa.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
See ya! I guess life really is just a bunch of goodbyes!
Though I wish I could have seen him one last time...
Bye-bye, Jojo! You better save your mom, no matter what!
I'm rooting for you!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
India
Calcutta
Varanasi
Delhi
Pakistan
Karachi
Indus River
Pakistan, a young country established
in 1947 following its separation from India.
While primitive people were first settling in Japan,
it had already become a thriving civilization.
Because it belonged to India for five thousand years,
the people here in Pakistan continue to carry on their history.
Episode 14: Justice Part 1
But Jotaro, I'm surprised you found someone who could make you a Japanese school uniform in Pakistan.
It's even the right size!
It's one hundred percent wool.
Polnareff, is it safe to drive right now?
It appears the fog in this area is getting quite thick.
Yeah, it just might be a bit dangerous.
There's a huge drop on one side, and no guard rail.
The fog is getting thick up ahead.
It's not even three o'clock yet, but we have no choice.
Let's find a place to stay in that town for the night.
I wonder if they'll have a nice hotel...
A nice hotel?
It has to have a decent toilet, of course!
I'll never get used to the toilets in India and West Asia
where you clean yourself with your hands.
Did I just see a dog's corpse?
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Never mind, it's nothing.
This is a nice little town.
I'd guess there are a few thousand people living here.
Let's ask about a hotel at this restaurant.
This town sure is quiet, huh?
Every other place has been super crowded and noisy.
It's probably because of the fog.
Listen up, everyone.
In Pakistan and further west in the Islamic world,
this is how you greet people.
Just smile and say...
Assalamu alaikum!
E-Er... You didn't need to close up because of that...
We just need some information. Is there a hotel near here?
Anyone home?
I dunno.
Hey, wait a minute!
What do you mean you don't know?
W-What's with that guy?
I must be seeing things.
I bet he couldn't understand you since your pronunciation stinks!
Let's ask the guy sitting over there.
Hey, pal! Sorry to bother you, but we're looking for a hotel.
Preferably a hotel with nice, clean toilets.
Do you know-
Hey, buddy! You okay?!
What?!
He's dead! He died with pure horror in his eyes!
W-What the hell is this?
Why's he lying there dead in the road?
What killed him?
A heart attack? A stroke?
Could be... but this doesn't look like normal heart failure.
A-A gun! He's got a gun!
You just noticed?
I see smoke. He fired it.
And just recently from the looks of it.
Maybe two to five minutes ago.
Either way, it happened just before we got here.
Suicide? With a pistol?
No, it's not that. There doesn't appear to be any
wounds on the body, and there's no sign of blood.
Then how did he die? Look at him!
His face is contorted like he was screaming in terror!
I don't know...
What did this guy try to shoot?
What in the world is going on?
No one in town noticed anything?
Ma'am, excuse me!
Someone just died here. Please call the police!
Pardon me. My acne has been festering.
Anyway, is there something you need?
I said I'd like you to call the police.
The police?
For what?
Look! There's a dead body over there!
Oh, my. There's a dead body?
What on earth could I do about that?
You could call the police for starters!
Right, right. Call the police...
I understand.
My acne has been so itchy since it festered. Terribly itchy...
What is with these people?
Someone died, and not a single person
cares enough to look, let alone an entire crowd.
Did they even hear the gun go off?
Even people from New York or Tokyo aren't this apathetic.
That dog...
It feels like the fog is getting thicker and thicker.
The entire town feels engulfed by it.
It's really creepy.
Doesn't it sort of look like a skull right there?
What's the plan, Gramps?
You don't think this is another Stand user, do you?
Unlikely. There's no motive.
Would someone looking for us kill an innocent bystander?
If so, then why?
Don't rule it out just yet.
His death was pretty extraordinary.
Before the police get here, let's thoroughly investigate the body.
It looks like he was a traveler, just like us.
He has bus and train tickets.
And it looks like he's Indian.
He has Indian money on him.
He's not from this town.
Oh?!
A wound!
There's a wound shaped like a ten yen coin below his throat!
Is this what killed him?
But why isn't any blood coming from it?
With a hole that size, blood should be gushing out.
Normally, at least.
Looks like this is no ordinary murder.
We need to get to the bottom of this. Don't hold back.
Take off his clothes.
W-What's with this corpse?!
It's full of holes!
He looks like the Swiss cheese you'd see in Tom & Jerry!
And there's no blood coming from any of them!
How in the world was he killed?
What does it all mean?
Careful...
The odds of a Stand user being nearby just increased.
Everyone!
We're leaving this town right now!
What?!
Impossible!
This isn't the car!
Hermit Purple!
Hey Gramps, what the hell are you doing? Are you an idiot?
Oh no!
What do you mean, "What am I doing"?!
The car was right here just a minute ago!
Huh, the car?
We parked over there.
B-But, just now...
You look like travelers.
With fog like this, leaving town is a perilous affair.
There are many cliffs, you know.
I run a little bed and breakfast.
If it suits you, why not rest there for the night?
I'll give you a good price.
Oh, we finally met a normal person!
H
He
Her
Herm
Hermit
Hermit P
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purpl
J
Hermit Purple
Jo
Jose
Josep
Joseph
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Joseph Joes
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Joseph Joest
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
There's a strong possibility a Stand user
is hiding somewhere in this town...
The thick fog gives them the upper hand.
We'll need to stay on guard tonight.
But... even without anyone attacking us,
this town gives me the creeps.
Come now, Master Joestar. This is my hotel...
I'll lead the way. Please follow me.
Just twenty years ago,
one of those 007 films was shot at this small hotel.
John Lennon from The Beatles also stayed here once.
What? For real?!
No, not at all.
Wha-
But I like to think I run a nice hotel.
We currently have no other guests staying with us.
Will meat for dinner be fine with you?
Or would you prefer fish?
Hold it, old lady.
Just now, I heard you say "Joestar."
Where did you hear that name?
Come now, sir! That person there
said "Mr. Joestar" just moments ago!
What? Me?
Well, I could have...
You certainly did!
When you've been in customer service for many years,
you pick up on people's names quickly.
I'm certain of it!
Ma'am, may I ask what happened to your left hand?
Oh, this? I just burned it a little...
It's probably because of my old age,
but I accidentally spilled boiling water on it.
Old age? What are you talking about?
You don't look a day over forty!
I might even ask you on a date!
Please don't tease me so, sir!
What the hell are you spewing, imbecile?
I despise you most of all, Polnareff!
I'll make sure you suffer a thousand times what my son did
when I kill you by cutting off your dick and ripping out your guts!
Oh, this place isn't half bad!
Here, Kakyoin.
Right.
My autograph's worth as much as Lennon's.
It starts with Paul, after all!
Make sure you're careful with it.
My, my...
I'll be sure to take care of it...
...to commemorate your death!
It's done.
Oh! Well then... I'll show you to your rooms.
Man, talk about a weird town...
All right, let's go to the toilet.
Looks like there's no signal.
Then I can't use Hermit Purple to get information on the enemy...
Hey, Mr. Joestar...
What is it?
Is there a toilet here?
My room doesn't have one.
Maybe the hotel has a communal bathroom?
Ah, makes sense!
Man oh man, he's so carefree.
Even when an unknown Stand user could attack at any moment...
So Joestar an' his gang're on the third floor?
Hol Horse... you're finally here.
Yeah, I tracked them varmints way out here.
But ya really surprised me there, Enya...
I din't think ya'd come here by yer lonesome.
W-What's the matter, Enya?
What's all the fuss about?
I-I am so happy, Hol Horse!
I'm so glad you came!
I'm so glad you came here to see lil' ol' me!
It warms my heart!
Hol Horse, you were friends with my son, were you not?
Friends?
We sure was!
Sob, sob...
Were you close?
Close?
Yeah, inseparable!
We made a good team.
Ya okay? This ain't like ya.
Have you really come all this way to avenge my son for me?
Yeah! Sure did!
I gotta avenge my best bud!
That really warms my heart!
Now I don't feel so bad killing you!
E-Enya?! W-What'n the hell're ya doin'?!
How could you, Hol Horse?
You had a lot of nerve to desert my son to save yourself.
I was determined to kill you the moment I saw you again!
My son's best friend? How dare you?!
W-Wait! Ya got it wrong!
When I got there, J. Geil was already dead!
Unforgivable!
You're just as despicable as that Polnareff!
You will die at the hands of my Stand, Justice!
J-Justice?
I'm certain you have heard about it...
...but now you shall see for yourself, Hol Horse!
Th-The blood where she stabbed me...
The fog's suckin' it out!
A perfect hole has appeared!
That's right!
My Stand, Justice, is a Stand made of fog!
Any wound touched by the fog becomes a perfect hole like that, and then...
...they dance with Justice!
The fog has entered the hole in your arm, like a string!
And now, you are my puppet!
Die by your own hand, Hol Horse!
Dammit! Don't act like ya won!
Emperor!
Die, ya old hag!
Justice has triumphed!
What was that noise?
There's a lot of noise coming from
the room at the back of the lobby...
Polnareff, what's wrong?
I heard a strange noise just now.
It's probably nothing, but I'm taking a look anyway.
I'll be in the lobby, so yell if you need me.
Curse you, Polnareff!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
He was just here. Right now he's using the toilet.
Really, the toilet?
Just go through that door.
I'm pretty sure I heard someone say "toilet."
Why am I always getting attacked in the bathroom...?
Episode 15
Justice Part 2