Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 17: Lovers Part 2
You made for a nice bridge, Jotaro.
Hey, Jotaro. My back itches.
Scratch it.
A bit lower.
Lower...
Ah, that's the spot.
Don't dig in so hard with your nails.
Mr. Joestar?
Hey, what's wrong?
I-It's feels like someone's tickling my back!
I can't concentrate and use my Stand like this!
Mr. Joestar!
W-When did all of these people show up?
Mr. Joestar, keep it down!
Everyone's staring!
They'll think you're insane!
I-It's not like I'm yelling because I want to!
Oh no!
Poor man...
We should give him our change.
What did she say?
What a scene... Having older relatives ain't easy.
No kidding.
Kakyoin, just buy the TV.
We need to scram.
R-Right.
You're the owner?
Uh... yeah...
We'll take the TV.
Kakyoin's Hierophant and Polnareff's Chariot
have somehow shrunk themselves and entered Joestar's body...
Are they trying to fight me?
I see!
That's where they'll exit the artery wall leading to the brainstem, and my Lovers.
Over here!
We only have a few minutes left
before the flesh bud eats through Mr. Joestar's brain!
Come on, you two!
There we go.
Nice!
Now, Mr. Joestar!
Hermit Purple!
Th-These are...
These tentacles are part of the flesh bud!
We're finally at the brainstem,
but the flesh bud has already grown a ton.
Shit!
That's it!
L-Look!
It's using its scissor-like hands to knead Mr. Joestar's brain cells
into a gooey mash so it can feed them to the flesh bud!
If we can't beat it and sever the flesh bud's roots quickly, it will grow big enough to eat through his brain!
Fine then! I'll slice it up!
Well, not slice... I'll grate it...
...like a daikon radish!
You bastard!
My chance!
We did it!
N-No, we're not done!
That bastard is pretty fast, Kakyoin.
But I already know all its tricks.
If that's the best it can do, it's no match for...
Polnareff!
Who are you talking to?
Polnareff, that isn't me!
And the thing you cut wasn't his Stand! It's starting to melt!
W-What?!
I'm Lovers!
Polnareff!
It was disguised!
Brain cells! It used Mr. Joestar's brain cells!
It was using the mash of kneaded brain cells to disguise itself as my Hierophant!
The thing you defeated earlier was just a dummy made of brain cells!
Man, I totally had you fooled, you fucking idiots!
Come on!
What's the matter?
Shine those shoes right, Jotaro!
I'm in such a great mood right now!
I want you to shine my shoes until they're as bright as I am happy!
I want to see the sunlight reflect off them.
You can use your uniform to shine them if you want.
Actually, maybe you should just lick them clean?
Hey, bastard!
The hell are you writing?!
Punched in the gut
Hit with a rock
Wallet stolen
Watch stolen
Walked across like a bridge over a dirty river
Forced to scratch back
Forced to shine shoes
Kicked in the face
Just what you owe me.
I'll make sure you pay it.
I tend to forget things, so I'm making a memo.
Jotaro, you asshole...
Well, whatever. It won't matter in the end.
Whoa! Kakyoin, look!
Look at the dummy's head I just cut open!
W-What the hell is it?
It's splitting into two!
Listen up...
In this world, the one who knows himself best is the victor!
In Aesop's fable, the tortoise beats the hare, because the tortoise knew his own strengths and weaknesses better than anyone!
Same with me!
I'm well aware that I lack the power or speed necessary to mortally wound either of you.
However, your strengths only really start to show once you acknowledge your weaknesses!
Emerald Splash!
Did it work?
M-More dummies made out of brain cells...
They're multiplying!
But a person can only have one Stand,
which means only one is real!
Where's the real one?!
Right here!
Emerald Splash!
Close one! You almost had me.
They keep multiplying as we hit the wrong ones!
No, no...
It's me...
It's me! It's me! It's me! It's me!
It's me, bitches!
Polnareff, that's enough!
Withdraw your Stand.
I can't stand to watch you get hurt for my sake!
Fuck!
I just can't stand the thought of leaving you like this!
Withdraw your Stand! It'll kill you!
Not to mention...
Time's up...
Don't give up until the very end, Mr. Joestar!
It's no use...
I can't tell the difference!
Which is the real one?
Which one is the Stand?!
Which one?!
The weakest of all is also...
The most, most, most, most...
...most, most, most, most...
...most, most terrifying of all!
Say, Jotaro, look here. It's a gold bracelet.
Imagine how happy it would make a girl, receiving a present like this.
Jotaro, see that space in the glass?
Use your Stand to sneak through and steal it!
I told you to steal it, dumbass!
Hurry it up!
Or, ya know...
I don't mind breaking the glass and taking it myself.
Will you be okay if I get caught
and let them beat the shit out of me?
Joseph would definitely die from the pain.
Hurry the fuck up!
The clerk's looking the other way!
This man is shoplifting!
Motherfucker...
Lo
Lov
Love
St
Lovers
Ste
Stee
Steely
Power: E
Speed: D
Range: A
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Steely Da
Steely Dan
This man is shoplifting!
Hey, salesman!
Young man, don't let him get away!
Sure!
Motherfucker...
What? A thief?
Which one?
That guy?
The Asian kid?
Back where I'm from, we'd chop your fingers off for thieving!
Hey, Jotaro.
You better not use your Stand against civilians.
Bastard!
Take this!
Despicable!
You thief!
Get out of our country, mouth breather!
We're done with you. And you can keep your fucking fingers!
That was great! Well done!
I got something even better from all that commotion you caused!
Jotaro!
What the hell are you laughing for?
What's so funny?
Nothing. I'm just happy.
It makes me really happy that
you're about to get what's coming to you.
I'm looking forward to making you eat your own shit.
You fucker!
That's where you're wrong!
Grandpappy Joestar will be dead in seconds.
Just face facts.
Nah. I think you're underestimating us.
You clearly don't know Kakyoin.
What?!
"Your strengths only really start to show
once you acknowledge your weaknesses," eh?
I see...
I'm inclined to agree.
To know yourself is an important lesson...
Though clearly you don't know your enemies very well.
You haven't done your research.
Didn't you realize?
My Hierophant...
...can spread its roots along the ground...
...and inspect every single one of you!
What the hell is touching me?
You're the Stand!
Emerald Splash!
We did it!
Well, well, well, well...
Looks like Kakyoin finally did some damage.
Here's hoping I have time for some
personal payback once he's through with you.
It knows it's done for, and it's trying to escape through the artery!
It's getting away!
It's trying to get out of Mr. Joestar's brain!
Huh? It's leaving?
All right! That's great!
Mr. Joestar, hurry! The flesh bud!
Right!
Overdrive!
The flesh bud is disappearing!
I-I'm saved...
At least now we can all stay best buds with Mr. Joestar.
Polnareff, you know...
Oh! B-But wait...
If it's leaving my brain...
It means Steely Dan...
...is calling back his Stand!
Not good! Jotaro doesn't know it's coming!
What's wrong? Why are you stepping back?
Why don't you tell me what happened to my grandfather?
Hey, hey, hey...
What's got you worked up?
You need to be somewhere?
You wouldn't be trying to run away, would you?
And at a time like this...
Please forgive me, Master Jotaro!
I admit defeat!
I can change! I'll lie on the ground and lick your boots!
What I did was awful!
You can hit me as much as you want! Punch me! Kick me!
But please, spare my life!
Soon...
Lovers will soon be back!
That dumbass Jotaro is fucking clueless!
I'll get to his brain through his ear!
Kakyoin's several hundred meters away. Just you wait!
You'll be in so much pain you'll wish you were dead!
I-It's here!
It's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
Now! Go in!
Ora!
I figured you were planning something like this.
Didn't you know that my Stand, Star Platinum,
has perfect eyesight and precise reflexes?
Are you sure you did your research on us?
I-I-I wasn't planning anything!
Your Stand's power...
"Your" Stand? Just "your?"
N-No! I-I meant your excellency's Stand
is more powerful and just than any other!
I didn't stand a chance, so it came back!
P-Please look!
That attack broke my arm and leg!
I can't fight anymore! I can't move!
Well...
As for what you owe me...
I guess I'll take your arm and leg as payment.
Do you swear you'll never show your ugly face to us again?
I-I do! I swear!
I'll go to some deserted island!
I'll go to the ends of the earth and never come back!
Are you lying to me?
I'll punch the shit out of you if I see you again.
I'm not lying! I'd never lie!
Fuck off.
Let's play soccer over there!
But then I can't play!
Jotaro!
You fool!
Take a look at that girl over there!
My Stand, Lovers, just went into her ear!
It's heading for her brain.
Don't you dare move, Jotaro!
I just gotta stab you in the back!
I'll make sure you never move again!
Don't even think of attacking me with your Star Platinum!
That girl will surely die!
You would never kill an innocent child, would you?
Gimme a break...
Fine, go ahead.
Hey! Don't you get it?! I told you not to-
...move? Move...
What's wrong?
Weren't you gonna stab me?
Like this?
I can't move! Why?!
W-What the hell is wrapped around me?!
You didn't notice?
Kakyoin tied Hierophant's tentacle to your Stand as it escaped.
You must be pretty fucking stupid
if you didn't realize it was leaving a trail all the way here.
Please forgive me!
You should have asked Enya if you wanted forgiveness.
Forgiving you never even crossed my mind.
D-Dio paid me in advance... Y-You can have it all...
Gimme a break...
You really are fucking scum.
The debt you owe...
...can't be repaid with money!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Here's the receipt.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
I still can't shake the feeling we're being watched.
Don't you think you're getting worried over nothing?
It's like we're being watched.
I just can't shake the feeling that somebody's watching us
Something's weird. Something...
Episode 18
Sun