Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
Ka...
...kyo...
...in...
...Beware...
...of...
...him...
Di...
...o's...
...ser...
...va...
...nt...
Dio!
Where's Kakyoin now?
He is with Jotaro!
Can I have some ice cream?
Welcome!
Little girl...
Ice cream's good and all, but so's this!
It's chilled coconut juice!
Want some?
I guess we'll try it.
We'll take three.
Yes, thanks! That's twelve dollars.
Hey, that should only be six dollars!
Well, this should cover it.
Okay.
Come again!
Thanks, pal!
You shithead... Did you think you could
get away with stealing my wallet, you fucking bitch?!
Spill your guts!
Kakyoin!
You scumbag...
You're worth even less than a cockroach's dick.
My precious wallet...
How dare you steal it from me with
the same fingers that wipe your filthy ass?!
What you've done is unforgivable.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Hey! What's wrong with you, Kakyoin?
You'll kill him!
Th-That back-breaker!
What a vicious move!
And he's using such foul language...
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Kakyoin!
I said back off! Got it?
Dammit, Kakyoin.
What's gotten into you?
Are you insane?
That hurt...
You didn't have to push me like that.
Only a horrible person would try stealing my wallet.
It goes without saying I'd retaliate.
Is that so wrong, Jotaro?
He's...
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 9: Yellow Temperance
What are you glaring at?
That's an awfully steely gaze you're giving me, Jotaro.
Don't tell me... You couldn't be looking to fight me...
...just because I taught that thief a lesson, right?
Look, a rhinoceros beetle!
A rhinoceros beetle? Where?
Awesome!
There's four of them up there!
I see them!
Awesome!
Jojo!
There's no need to strain yourself over this!
I'm just a bit agitated today.
The trip here was exhausting, and it put me in a bad mood.
A bad mood?
You seemed fine earlier.
Gramps and Abdul think we should get to India by train.
We're leaving tomorrow.
We'll take a cable car to Singapore Station to reserve tickets.
Mr. Kakyoin...
Jojo's getting ahead of us.
R-Right... I'll be right there.
Mr. Kakyoin, you must really like that coconut juice, huh?
W-Was that a rhinoceros beet-
N-No, I'm just seeing things...
It must've been a fiber from the coconut or something.
Yes, I love... coconuts.
What's the matter?
N-Nothing.
Yo, Jotaro.
You gonna eat that cherry?
I'll have it if you won't.
I'm famished.
Whoa, there! Look out, Jotaro!
Jojo!
Just kidding!
I was only kidding, Jotaro.
TN: Rero is an onomatopoeia for rolling the tongue.
I-It's like Mr. Kakyoin is a completely different person!
That look again!
Why do you keep staring at me
with that dumbass look on your face...
...Jotaro, my man?
Get on, Kakyoin.
The cable car's here.
Now get the fuck on.
I've got your ticket right here.
I can tell you're being possessed by something...
...so allow my fist to send you on your way.
What?!
You're wrong.
It would be wrong to say I'm possessed.
You're not Kakyoin!
Didn't you notice my body growing bigger and bigger recently?
What the fuck are you?
A Stand?
No, I just touched it...
Is it possible there are Stands that can be touched?
Jojo!
I have the power to combine with the flesh my Stand consumes...
...allowing it to be seen and touched by normal people.
It represents the Temperance card, Yellow Temperance.
This is my real, handsome face!
Come on, Jotaro, my man!
Take a look at your hand.
There's a bit of slime on it from when you hit me.
So I'll say this only once!
It will spread to your fingers if you touch it.
You should really try picking your nose with that hand!
My Stand is a slow eater.
It gets bigger the more it eats.
It will never come off!
Y-You asshole!
Ora!
Whaddya mean, "Ora?!"
I'm gonna take your shit and shove it
down your throat while my Stand digests you!
I-I'm burning!
Y-You...
J-Jojo's grandpa? We're in trouble!
Anne? What's wrong?
M-Mr. Kakyoin is...
Kakyoin?!
Could he truly have betrayed us?
Mr. Kakyoin's face split apart!
But Mr. Kakyoin isn't really Mr. Kakyoin!
And...
Jojo's in the cable car, and there's this weird slime eating his finger, and we're in big trouble!
Calm down! Where are you?
The cable car station near the trade center!
He's being attacked!
Mr. Kakyoin is attacking Jojo!
Get back to the hotel as soon as possible!
Did someone say my name?
Where have you been?
Jojo left me behind, so I went sunbathing by the poolside.
In your school uniform?
So?
That's a relief. This is the real one.
Which means, Anne, your Kakyoin is...
...an imposter!
I know that already!
Jojo!
Jojo just jumped out of the cable car!
St
Sta
Star
Star Pl
Star Plat
Star Platin
Ku
Star Platinum
Kujo
Kujo Jo
Power: A
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: A
Growth Potential: A
Kujo Jota
Kujo Jotaro
G-Gimme a break...
A Stand that absorbs flesh?
It keeps eating my finger...
Anyway, before we fight,
I gotta do something about this Stand.
I'll chop my finger off if that's what it takes.
You think you've escaped me?
Well, have I got some news for you.
Find a straw to suck all of that crap
out of your ear holes and listen up.
My Stand, Yellow Temperance, has no weakness!
It's not that I let you escape...
I just don't need to chase after you!
You fucking bitch!
This is gonna burn, but at least this thing will die.
What the...
That only made it spread!
Burning it won't work...
What should I do?
Hold it.
Oh, my. Talk about a strange entrance.
Don't mind me.
Hey, kid. Give me that ice pop for a second.
Hey, you! Why are you bothering that kid?
Is he yours?
Of course not!
Then shut the fuck up and enjoy the view.
Sorry about this.
I'll buy you a new one once we're on the ground.
If burning it won't work...
Motherfucker!
I-It formed needles to dig into my hand!
Hey, you! Fire and ice aren't going to work.
I told you earlier! It has no weakness!
You fucking bitch!
You're...
Papa! The doggy! The doggy!
You asshole! You were already in this cable car?
M-My Pocky!
That's dangerous! Don't pull!
Let go!
I'm here to finish you off...
...Jotaro, my man!
Ora!
You're fast! However...
I told you I have no weakness!
Are you even paying attention?
You fucking rube!
My Stand is like armor that consumes energy!
A barrier that fights back!
No matter how fast you are, and no matter how strong...
...you're totally helpless before Yellow Temperance!
I can't be bested!
You can't even run unless you're okay with losing that hand!
Do you understand?!
It's impossible for you to win!
You're trapped!
Until you're digested, anyway! I'm gonna eat you!
Gimme a break.
This thing really does have no weakness.
It may be the strongest thing I've faced.
What a scary guy.
But you know, the Kujo family...
...No, the Joestar family...
has its own philosophy when it comes to fighting.
There's just one thing...
...left to do.
What?
That's...
...run away!
What?!
I'm still gonna eat you, shithead!
Do you seriously think you can run from
the inescapable grasp of my Stand?
I'm running...
...into the water!
I-I can't...
You had to let your Stand's guard down to breathe.
No matter how invincible a Stand is, if the user is defeated,
the Stand is defeated along with them.
Do you understand?
You were talking a lot of shit back there, huh?
I'm the kind of guy who takes that personally.
Ora!
P-Please stop!
I'll never recover from this!
You broke my nose!
And I'll probably need to have my jaw wired shut, too...
Dio paid me to do this.
I didn't plan to risk my life going after you people!
There! See?
So spill...
Tell me about the Stand users that are planning to attack us.
Th-That's the only thing I can't tell you!
I still have some pride!
I can't sell out my own side... I just can't...
I see. How honorable.
I remember now!
Death, Empress, Hanged Man, and Emperor are going to come after you!
So, what are their powers?
I-I don't know...
N-No, really! I really don't know!
Stand users never reveal their powers;
their weaknesses would be exposed...
B-But, there's an old hag who told Dio about Stands...
...and her son is one of them.
His name is J. Geil.
A man with two right hands!
His card is Hanged Man.
He's the one who killed Polnareff's sister, right?
I've heard rumors about his power...
A mirror. Supposedly he uses a mirror.
I haven't actually seen it, but Polnareff will never beat him.
He'll die.
I just realized, Jotaro...
The goddess of fortune is still on my side!
See that drain?
There's a bunch of crayfish inside it.
Give that a good look.
A manhole!
That tiny drain...
...is connected to this manhole!
I'll pull you in and hold you there!
You can't attack me now!
I guess the info I gave you about the man
with two right hands will follow you to the grave.
Kujo Jotaro!
It's almost too perfect that I was in just the right place to trap you!
Man, this is my lucky day!
I even powered up from those crayfish!
I'll fucking crush you... into a delicious jam!
After I kill you, Dio will give me a hundred million dollars!
To think I'm making that much money from a few minutes of fighting!
Isn't that just lucky?
You castrated dog!
Gimme a break...
You oughta take a good look at yourself.
You haven't realized it yet,
but your stroke of luck... is about to to run out.
A broken nose is the worst injury you've had so far.
That was when you were really lucky!
A water pressure punch... f-from inside the drain?!
I-I was just kidding, Mr. Jotaro!
I was just messing around! I didn't mean anything by it!
Come on, you can't be serious?
Y-You're not thinking of hitting me again, are you?
I'm badly injured...
You broke my nose and I still need to have my jaw wired shut...
I have nothing left to say to you.
It's a waste of time...
...for me to say anything else.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Y
Yel
Yello
Yellow
Yellow Te
Yellow Tem
Yellow Tempe
Yellow Tempera
Yellow Temperan
Ru
Yellow Temperance
Rubb
Rubber
Rubber So
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: D
Rubber Sou
Rubber Soul
Oh man...
We're finally headed to India, huh?
Now I know the man with two right hands is called J. Geil...
By the way, where's Anne?
She was at Singapore Station until the train left, but...
I presume the time came to meet with her father,
and she is now with him.
That kid... Knowing her, she was probably
lying about seeing her dad in the first place.
Still, it's a bit lonely without her.
Right, Jojo?
But talk about creepy...
A Stand that perfectly disguised itself as me...
Apparently it transformed just before we left the hotel.
Jojo, are you eating that cherry?
I'm not trying to be greedy, but they're my favorite.
Can I have it?
Sure.
Thank you.
Oh, Jojo, look. A flock of flamingos.
Gimme a break...
Jojo...
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Someone already stole my wallet!
No thank you!
Tip! Tip! Tip!
If I don't get a tip, you ain't going to heaven, mister.
Hey! Get your snotty nose off it, nosy!
Abdul! Is all of India like this?!
Indeed! Is this not a great country?
Episode 10
Emperor and Hanged Man Part 1