Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Let's rewind to a bit earlier!
Episode 32: Alessi's Divine Set Part 1
While Joseph's group was fighting Mariah, Jotaro's was...
Here you are, ma'am.
Your bourbon whiskey and soda on the rocks.
Enjoy.
Oh, yummy!
Glug, glug, glug.
My, you sure drank that quickly for this time of morning, ma'am.
Don't worry about it.
My husband's on an important business trip
and won't be back for a week.
Now, try some of this cake!
Why, don't mind if I do, ma'am!
What I'd give to be a kid again...
It's almost nine o'clock...
Gramps and Abdul are late.
They could've encountered an enemy.
You think we should go look for them?
Yeah. But gimme a break...
Come on, Iggy.
I know, I know. You're hungry, right?
So am I.
Hey, where are you going?
Jesus, you dumb dog...
Let's go.
Hey!
Let me play, too!
You're too fussy; no way!
Don't be like tha-
Little boy, I'm glad you didn't cry.
Very good. Are you okay?
Little boy, how old are you?
Four, eh? Hmm...
Very good. What's your papa doing right now?
Working.
So papa's away at work? Very good!
And what about mama?
She's doing laundry at home...
Very good!
So you're playing here all by yourself?
Then as punishment for getting mud on my pants,
I'm gonna beat the hell out of you!
How will you pay for this?
How many years are you gonna force me to wait
before you're old enough to pay me back?
You spoiled brat!
Mama!
While Joestar and Abdul are busy fighting Mariah...
...I, the great Alessi, will kill Jotaro and Polnareff.
Those guys are tough.
But I'll do what I must to beat them.
Very good, me.
This man's name is Alessi.
His Stand represents Set, the god of storms and violence.
He has a habit of repeating the phrase "Very good."
Polnareff, stay alert.
Just who do you think you're talking to?
Mr. Joestar and Abdul aren't here...
...and it doesn't look like anything is too strange up here...
Gramps, Abdul, you here?
Jotaro...
I think something happened.
Yeah.
That looks good!
Let me try some!
Okay, sure.
My kebab sandwich! W-Wait! G-Give it back!
You thieving dog!
A pincer attack?
You're both so clueless.
You think you have me cornered,
but it's really me who has you cornered!
You'll burn to a crisp!
Magician's Red!
Hermit Purple!
Abdul is able to defend himself with his flames, but...
Joestar, you don't stand a chance.
The difference in power between
my Divine Bastet and your Hermit Purple...
U-Um... I... uh... dropped some change...
Jeez, where could it be?
Hey... Why do you keep following us and staring at our backs?
I can feel your murderous intent.
W-Were you speaking to me?
W-What are you going on about?
My parents provided me with these eyes!
They can't be murderous...
I even found the coin I dropped!
Well then, I guess I'll just have to
find out for myself if you're a Stand user...
...or not!
Th-That was close...
So you really are a Stand user!
He's running away?!
Hey, Jotaro! It's the enemy!
An enemy showed up!
Polnareff?
Where'd you go, Polnareff?
Jotaro, over here!
Come back here, you!
Wait!
What the heck?! He's fast!
Why the heck is he so fast?!
He's already so far ahead...
Huh? What the... my voice!
Ow!
W-What happened to my shoes? They're huge!
Hey, that's not safe.
You'll get hit by a car if you run in the road like that.
You're lucky you hit me instead.
Shut up, you retard!
Watch who you're talking to, bigmouth!
Move, you moron! I'm chasing someone!
What the heck are you doing?! W-Wait, what?!
What?! I'm so high up!
He's lifting me with one hand!
Just how tall is he?!
His hands and face are huge!
Hey, watch your mouth, brat!
I'll show you what happens when you disrespect an adult!
Get rid of those baggy clothes!
And quit pretending to be an adult!
You snot-nosed brat...
Y-You jerk...
What the heck?!
Move it, kid! You're in the way!
Wh-What's going on?
It's like everybody got huge!
What?!
W-W-What?
I'm a kid?!
Th-This really is me!
I turned into a kid!
Div
Divine
Divine Set
A
Al
Ale
Ales
Alessi
C-Could it be... this kid...
Could this kid really be...
...me?! I-I-I'm a kid!
I turned into a kid!
No way! No way! No way!
I-It was that guy's Stand...
That creepy guy's shadow-like Stand...
When our shadows touched, he used his power on me!
H-How could this happen?
Darn it, this is bad! This is really bad!
Jo-
Jo...
Jo... N-No...
Jay... Jackie... J...
W-What was it? I can't remember his name!
He could really help me out here too! S-So why...?
Why can't I remember?!
Hey, kid. Have you seen a French guy around here?
He's about this tall, and his hair looks like yours.
Th-That's me! Me! Me!
Gimme a break... That's the last time I ask a kid for help.
W-Wait!
Now that you have the body of a child,
your mind is reverting to that of a child's, as well.
Your memories are regressing to those you had at this age.
I'll forget things I knew as an adult?
He's right... I can already feel it...
Has the time come?
Preying on the weak... I love it!
Very good, me!
Whoa, there! You're not going anywhere, brat.
I have to tell you this quietly,
but preying on the weak makes me feel really good.
I won't deny that I'm pretty messed up...
But you know what they say...
If you think you're weird, you're not really that weird.
So I'm not weird, right?
One thing I know for sure is that
I'm not gonna lose to some stinkin' kid.
Guy over there whose name I can't remember, help-
So you see, my mission is to dispose of you.
I'm stuck! It can't get it out!
It's a shame...
...but I have no time to mess with you.
That's Silver Chariot, huh?
Well, I suppose that means
you've had your Stand since you were a child.
However...
M-My Chariot! Even Chariot is a kid!
I-It's super weak! And it bent its sword!
Since my Divine Set turned you into a child,
your mental strength has also regressed into that of a child's.
So in effect, your Stand is a child now, too.
The same as it was when you were this age.
You get it now?
It would appear so...
Very good.
However, despite its lack of strength, you can still use your Stand.
My Stand will have to take care of you.
Die, Polnareff!
You're mine!
Oh no!
It snapped!
S-Serves you right! I meant to do that!
Ow! Ow! It hurts!
Little boy, are you okay?
H-He's gone!
It figures an adult showing up would make him run away.
I'm safe for now, but I can't get over how scary he is...
Little boy, hold on!
You're hurt! What happened?
Huh? Uh... Um, uh...
What are you mumbling about?
Those wounds don't look good.
I'll fix you up at my place. Come on.
I-I guess I'll go...
I have to find that guy and beat him,
or I'll never be an adult again!
He won't attack with an adult around,
so now's my chance to figure out how to beat him!
Come along now.
Whoa...
Oh, right.
You're hurt. Here, grab on.
She smells nice...
It hurts!
Shit!
I won't keep quiet after that brat made a fool of me!
To protect my pride as an adult, I'll beat him to death!
Th-That guy... It looks like he gave up on me.
Okay, little boy.
Come to the bathroom and we'll take your clothes off.
You're so filthy. I'll wash and treat your wounds for you.
What are you standing there for?
Oh, all right.
I'll take them off for you. Here, raise your leg.
This isn't... This isn't...
What's wrong?
I-It's nothing...
No, this is something!
This is definitely something!
I don't know why,
but this feels like it should be really embarrassing...
And, and, and...
It's so small!
This makes me really sad for some reason! Boo-hoo!
Now, hold onto me.
We have to get all of that dirt off you.
Lift up your leg.
I-I-I-I'm so happy! Is this really, really okay?!
Is it okay? Of course it is, you'll get infected if we don't.
Oh, your wee-wee has dirt on it, too.
I... I feel like something really fun is happening,
but I can't tell what because I'm a kid!
All right, be a good boy, okay?
Okay!
You little shit...
I'll cut you in half, then tear you to pieces!
What are you smirking for?
Okay, let's wash your hair.
Huh? No! No, no, no, no...
I hate shampoo!
It burns my eyes! I hate it!
Rock, paper...
Scissors.
Monkey, monkey, monkey...
Monkey do, monkey do...
I lost!
Now, sit down.
Does it sting?
Yeah, it really stings.
Will you wash it by yourself then?
Sure, I can do it.
Oh? Very good.
I'll say it once more!
Very good!
N-No way!
Next Episode
Pretty strange that you fell out the window
already covered in blood.
The bars are too close together!
This is what true despair feels like!
I touched the shadow again!
She's gone... Where'd she go?
What do you think I did?
Episode 33
Alessi's Divine Set Part 2