Damn, it's dark. My eyes're strugglin' to see.
Where the hell'd he go?
It's the middle of the day,
but I can't seem to find 'im in this big ol' mansion...
I think it's over here... Dio's room...
W-What's this? Dio's leftovers?
These ladies just gave 'im their blood without puttin' up a fight.
Beats me how they'd be okay with that.
I guess he's got the devil's charm.
An' come to think of it, where'd he get all this loot from?
Seems there's nothin' he ain't capable of.
Do you...
...need something?
L-Lord... Dio!
D-Dammit!
Just standin' in front of 'im is makin' me quiver!
Cool it, Hol Horse.
Ya gotta stay calm.
He ain't nothin'! Maybe just a tad stronger'n me...
I just asked you a question, Hol Horse.
Ah, uh, w-well... I got a report fer ya...
I hear the fifth an' sixth gods, Mariah an' Alessi, got beaten.
And?
A-An' that's my report!
Joestar's gang're gonna be in Cairo tomorrow.
Three of the nine gods're left.
When I said, "And?"...
...I was asking to hear about you, Hol Horse.
When will you defeat them for me, Hol Horse?
You swore me your loyalty,
yet you have hardly raised a hand in battle.
Any fool can report to me.
You have failed me twice,
both times running back with your tail between your legs.
The body you see before you once belonged to a man named Jonathan Joestar.
He was the grandfather of Joseph Joestar.
Look, my two fingers here...
See how the left takes longer to heal?
The left side of this body is still weak.
It is undeniable evidence that I am not
fully accustomed to this body.
I am still vulnerable.
It is for this reason that I cannot yet face them.
I expect you to kill Joestar and the others this time.
Otherwise, I will kill you myself.
W-What a crock of shit!
Is he tryin' to corner me like a rat?
"Defeat them for me"?
That's rich!
I'll side with whoever's toughest!
I din't swear loyalty to ya from the bottom of my heart!
I ain't gonna sell my soul!
Dammit! Are ya really that strong?
Yer back's wide open!
His body probably ain't movin' like it should be yet...
C-Come to think of it, that Joestar's got four pals with 'im...
...but this guy's all alone.
If I was feelin' like blowin' his brains out...
...it'd be a cinch.
Then all that loot'd be mine.
He's wide open!
I got Emperor pointed right at 'im, an' he ain't none the wiser.
Now's the time to finish 'im...
Just gotta pull the trigger...
It'll be over real quick...
My Emperor was made fer killin' at point blank!
I can do it! I'm gonna do it!
What are you doing? Hurry and get going.
I'll kill ya!
I'll splatter yer brains all over the floor, Mister Dio!
Do you really intend to shoot me?
H-He vanished...
Very good.
In the moment you tried to kill me,
you weren't sweating, and your breathing was stable.
You remained so calm. This is what I expect of you.
I din't see 'im move...
An' it ain't just that...
He din't even break them cobwebs...
No way he coulda gotten behind me!
That ain't just speed...
How? How'd he get behind me?!
I just don't know...
Was it Dio's Stand, The World?
Yer too weak to fight 'em yerself? Bullshit!
I-I finally get ya, Lord Dio. I'll be there fer ya to the end.
I-I concede...
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 36: Hol Horse and Boingo Part 1
Ladies and gentlemen, we hope your flight
from Aswan has been pleasant.
The plane will land on schedule at the
Cairo International Airport momentarily.
Whoops! Sorry 'bout that.
Looks like this taxi's here for us!
Later!
What? Got a problem, bitch?
H-How could you?!
I'm goin' to the Mena House Hotel in Giza.
I'm openin' the trunk, so cover them eyes of yers.
Got it?
Huh? Did you just say something, sir?
I ain't talkin' to ya!
Now pipe down an' keep yer eyes on the road!
C-Certainly...
Boingo, I'm sorry I had to force ya on that plane against yer will.
But ya gotta grow up sometime, Boingo!
'Cause that brother of yers got blown up,
he's gonna be in the hospital 'bout another month.
Which means it's time to team up with good ol' Hol Horse!
With that book of yers that sees the future,
an' my sharpshooting gun, we're gonna kill Joestar's whole gang!
Got it, Boingo?
I know yer shy an' don't trust anyone
but that brother of yers, Oingo...
But wouldn't ya like to avenge 'im?
Ya wanna grow up bein'
a damned coward yer whole life, Boingo?
I'm tryin' my best, too!
We've gotta fight!
Yer gonna get yer revenge, Boingo!
I'll untie ya now.
Can ya promise me ya ain't gonna make a fuss?
Yeah, that's good!
Don't get too excited. It'll make ya sick.
I'm on yer side, so ya ain't gotta worry!
Just relax!
Sir! Wha- Is he throwing up?!
Can it!
So, ya ain't good with flyin'?
Anyways, l-let's be pals, Boingo.
"I'm Boingo! This is Hol Horse!
He's a big meanie and a total jerk!"
While Boingo slept, the meanie tied him with rope and
stuffed him in a tiny trunk, taking him away from his big bro.
How sad!
Even though Boingo was scared, in order to avenge his big bro, he had to gather the courage to team up with Hol Horse!
Even though yer too spooked to get close,
I guess yer still tryin' to be brave how ya can.
Is it true them predictions yer Stand makes always come true?
I trusted them rumors an' decided to team up with ya,
but yer brother failin's got me a tad worried.
Tell me! They always come true, right?!
There's new pages appearin' in the comic!
While Boingo and Hol Horse strolled along
the outskirts of Cairo, they met a very pretty lady.
Then all of a sudden, she got jump kicked in the neck!
After the lady got kicked,
she became so happy that she gave Hol Horse some jewels.
Hooray! We're rich!
The hell is this?!
Ya gotta be kiddin' me!
Ya call this a prediction, Boingo?!
That's crazy! No way this'll happen!
M-M-M-My... My Divine Th-Thoth's
predictions made through the book...
...a-a-a-are absolute!
One hundred percent, indeed.
A hundred percent?! Quit messin' with me!
What kinda lady'd be so dang happy 'bout me
kickin' her in the neck that she'd gimme jewels?!
Listen here, Boingo.
I take pride in bein' nice to all the ladies.
I got girlfriends from all over!
I may lie to a lady, but I'd never hit her!
I give 'em respect no matter if they're beautiful or butt ugly!
Yer prediction ain't ever gonna come true!
'Cause I swear to ya, I ain't ever gonna hit her!
Even if ya offered me a truckload of loot, I'd still say no!
I-It's one hundred percent certain, indeed.
See? Ya goofed up!
Who the hell are you?!
That's... There was a scorpion inside my lady's collar!
And it's one of the most venomous kinds!
You saw the scorpion before it could crawl into my clothing!
If you hadn't crushed it, she would have been stung...
You saved my life! Please, allow me to thank you.
Would you like my necklace?
Please take it.
We're invincible!
Boingo an' Hol Horse, the invincible duo!
Div
Divine
Divine Thoth
Bo
Boi
Boin
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: E
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Boingo
The building in this picture, eh?
I've been repairing roofs in Cairo for forty years,
but I can't say I've seen this place.
But considering how it looks,
I'd say it was built about a hundred years ago.
You should find it eventually if you go south from here.
The buildings get older as you head further south in Cairo.
Sorry I couldn't be more help.
No, thanks a lot. Sorry to bother you.
Okay. I got it. Thanks.
I just made a call to Japan...
My daughter's condition has gotten worse.
She has no energy left.
She'll only last three or four more days...
I can feel it...
Dio is nearby.
I just know he's hiding around here somewhere.
He must be close.
Let us make haste.
If we continue to ask around, we will find him.
Then let's go. We have to keep trying.
We meet again, ya familiar mugs...
...or somethin' like that...
Can't believe them fellas're so close to Dio's mansion.
They damn near made it.
Oh yeah, Boingo!
'Bout that prediction of yers... it's got me dumbfounded.
No way somethin' that stupid's gonna happen!
M-M-M-My... My-
"My predictions're a hundred percent true", right?
Th-They are, indeed.
Dammit! Yer tellin' me I gotta believe this malarkey?
Ya can't be serious...
"I finally found ya... Joestar, Jotaro, Polnareff, an' Abdul!
Dammit! Them varmints keep gettin' closer an' closer to Dio's mansion!
I'll just shoot y'all square in the face!"
...Hol Horse resentfully thought.
"I'll avenge my big bro!"
...Boingo angrily thought.
But Hol Horse, don't even think about
using Emperor in the marketplace.
Now Hol Horse, you need to stick
your fingers up Polnareff's nose, and then...
Hooray! Everyone is bleeding and out cold!
Lucky you, Hol Horse! Now's your chance to kill them all!
Ya expect me to believe this?!
Ya call this a prediction?!
Stickin' my fingers up Polnareff's nose?!
What the hell? Well, Boingo?!
I get that it'll gimme a chance to kill 'em all, but it's total malarkey!
Listen here. Even if I got close 'nuff to a tough fella like Polnareff,
I ain't ever gonna get my fingers up his nose!
Don'tcha think it'd be much faster
to just blast 'im with my Emperor?
Y-You won't be able to g-get a shot off, indeed.
E-Even if you try to shoot, fate will not allow it, indeed.
Y-You must believe, indeed.
I-If you try to go against what's written
in my comic book, you'll just make things worse for yourself.
I-It is fate, indeed! It's one hundred percent accurate, indeed!
But yer brother failed before!
M-My big bro was trying to save himself
and transformed into Jotaro without thinking, indeed.
If he had trusted my comic and not transformed,
then the real Jotaro would have blown up instead, indeed.
The predictions are never wrong, indeed.
What to do...
P-Polnareff's gone!
Hey, where's Polnareff?!
He just up an' vanished!
Shit! It can't be...
Don't move!
I'll cut you up.
P-Polnareff...
Idiot! Don't try anything funny with me!
Keep your hands where I can see them.
I noticed someone stalking us like a hyena,
and imagine my surprise to see it was my good ol' friend, Hol Horse.
Still haven't learned your lesson and want to kill us, huh?
You took real good care of us in India.
You're lucky Abdul's alive, or I would have
slaughtered you the instant I saw your face.
Are you alone, Hol Horse?
Nah, you'd never come alone.
I bet you've got a friend nearby.
Well? Am I right?
Dammit!
Least he hasn't noticed Boingo yet...
I still got a chance...
Yer hand's showing! He'll see yer damn fingers!
You're not that scary by yourself,
but you have a knack for bringing out the talents of others.
Once you're teamed up with someone talented,
you become terrifyingly strong.
So where's the Stand user you partnered up with?
Yer fingers...
Tuck them fingers away, Boingo!
We're finished if he finds ya!
B-Believe!
You only got hit because you tried using your gun!
Believe in destiny.
Th-Then our victory will be assured, indeed!
Hey, what's under that box? Someone's in there!
Hey, Polnareff, did you find the man following us?
That's Abdul's voice! H-He's comin'!
Believe, indeed!
Believe, and find a way to stick
your fingers up Polnareff's nose, indeed!
F-Fer real?! Dammit...
I'll do it! I just gotta do it, right?!
Whoever's under there, get out!
My chance! He's lookin' away!
I know you're hiding under there!
What the-?!
Yes!
Hooray! Everyone is bleeding and out cold!
Lucky you, Hol Horse! Now's your chance to kill them all!
So, when the hell's my chance comin'?
The hell do I do now?!
What the hell are you doing, Hol Horse?
Wouldn't I like to know?!
What in tarnation am I supposed to do now?!
How do I follow this up?!
Is something wrong, Polnareff?
He is not responding...
Strange.
Sh-Shit! The other three're comin'!
Dammit!
How am I supposed to make the prediction come true now?!
What the hell do I do?!
Shinjite iinoka?
Can I believe in ya?!
Shinjiteoyo!
You can believe in me!
Hol Horse Boingo konbi!
Hol Horse Boingo Duo!
Ore wa Hol Horse hajiki no tsukaite da
The name's Hol Horse an' I wield a pistol.
Card no anji wa Emperor
My card represents Emperor.
Tachi ichi niban tete
I'm always second in a pair.
Dareka to kunde kagayakunosa!
I'm a shinin' star with a partner by my side!
Dagayo koitsu de daijoubuka?
But am I really gonna be okay with this kid?
Boku wa Boingo manga de yogen
I'm Boingo and I can predict the future with my comic.
Totemo uchiki nandakedo yuuki wo dasuyo!
Even though I'm still really shy, I'm gonna be courageous now!
Oniichan no kataki wo utsunda
I gotta avenge my big bro!
Boku no manga no yochi wa
The predictions in my comic...
Zettai hyaku percento desu!
...are one hundred percent true!
Koride koride umaku iku(noka)
That's to say, that's to say, everything'll go our way!(?)
Toppyoshi monakute shinjirarenuze
It's so crazy I can hardly believe it!
Insatsu ni deta yogen wa
The prophecy written in the book...
Zettai nandesu, unmei nandesu
...is absolute and is always up to fate!
Yogen no toori koto sureba
If we do everythin' as that prophecy says...
Subete umaku iku
...everything'll go our way!
Shinjiru karanaa
I really believe in ya!
Hol Horse Boingo konbi!
Hol Horse Boingo Duo!
Shinjirundesu hai!
Just believe in me, indeed!
Okay Shinjiruze!
Okay, I believe in ya!
Hol Horse Boingo konbi!
Hol Horse Boingo Duo!
Unmei to iuu no wa
This thing known as fate...
Seikaku ni wa yometokenai mono sa
...is something you can never, ever really know for sure!
Next Episode
Dammit! I'm cornered!
I'm trying to tell you to look behind me!
Sounds like someone got in a car accident over there.
I have some tea for you...
And 'cause I stuck my fingers up his nose,
the prediction came true!
My predictions are absolute.
Episode 37
Hol Horse and Boingo Part 2
It was fate, indeed.