Be quiet...
Where am I?
Is this an amusement park?
I've never been here before.
W-What am I doing lounging around on a ferris wheel?
Something's wrong.
I'm positive we were traveling through
the Saudi Arabian desert by camel...
Where is everyone?
Am I alone?
This is strange...
I don't see any children in this amusement part,
yet I can hear a baby crying.
I wonder where it is...
Th-This is...
Death 13!
It's moving!
Kakyoin! Kakyoin!
Hey, do me a favor...
Quit freaking out and shaking the bed like this is The Exorcist.
You're freaking me out.
Where are we?
Where do you think?
Come on, get up already.
We're leaving after we eat.
Looks like it'll be a hot one today.
I had an awful dream.
It was really bad...
What'd you dream about?
Tell me!
I don't remember. I'm drawing a blank.
What?
Still, it was bad...
Being woken up by you saved me.
Man, don't start saying weird shit like that.
Let's go. Hurry up and get ready.
My hand is bleeding.
When did that happen?
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 19: Death 13 Part 1
Jotaro and Mr. Joestar are already on their way to the plane.
We have to fly for five hundred kilometers.
My dog!
M-My dog... is dead!
Who would do this?!
A dog?
A dog...
I could have sworn I saw a dead dog recently...
I feel bad for him, but it has nothing to do with us.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Hold on a sec, Mister.
Whaddya mean you can't sell us the plane now?
Why'd you take our money and tell us we could last night?
I'll give you a refund.
You see, we have a sick baby. It's running a fever.
There's no doctor in this town,
so we have to take the baby somewhere else.
Th-Then how about the plane over there?
That one's broken.
The others are out and won't be back anytime soon.
What's up? Some kind of argument?
Yeah.
A baby...
A baby... A baby...
I distinctly remember hearing a baby cry...
...but I'm drawing a blank...
The plane should be back by tomorrow night.
I can sell it to you after that.
Tomorrow night?
That baby isn't the only one in a life-or-death situation!
We can't afford to spend two days sitting on our asses!
Are you suggesting we let the baby die?
Uh... Well...
Um, how about this?
We'll leave the baby with these gentlemen,
and they can visit a doctor on their way.
Uh... Well...
The Cessna only carries four.
But there's room enough for a baby.
Did... it just smile?
And... were those fangs?
You sure, lady? You feel safe leaving the baby with these guys?
H-Hold it. That doesn't work either!
It's too dangerous for a baby to travel with us!
I told them it would be dangerous...
What's there to worry about, Mr. Joestar?
No one would send their Stand after us while we're in the air.
We even checked to make sure the plane itself isn't a Stand.
It definitely is not.
I'm more concerned with Gramps' flying than an enemy Stand.
Oh, thank goodness. That's a relief.
But I wonder... Whose baby was that?
You're not its mother?
I only found it by the well this morning.
For some reason that baby's voice made me dizzy...
and I suddenly felt as if I needed to get it on that plane.
For some reason flying makes me really drowsy...
Mr. Joestar, I'll be taking a nap if you don't mind.
Sure.
The hell is this?!
K-Kakyoin, what is this place?!
Where's Mr. Joestar and Jotaro?!
The dream I had this morning is continuing...
We're inside the dream!
What? A dream?
Yes.
Oh! So, it's just a dream, eh?
That's a relief. A dead dog isn't nearly as scary in a dream.
Polnareff, what are you saying?
Dreams are only as scary as you make them out to be.
Come on, relax.
You're wrong!
Don't you think it's weird that we're sharing the same dream?
Good point...
It is kinda weird, but maybe that can happen in dreams.
Whoa! How did this happen?
This is both lucky and convenient, huh?
See? If you want to have fun dreams, then they'll be fun.
Listen! You remember that dog's corpse this morning, don't you?
I must have been sharing a dream with it earlier.
It was killed in the dream!
That's also when my hand was cut...
By who?
The enemy's Stand, Death 13!
The enemy's Stand?
Yes.
What, so you had a dream about Stands?
Relax buddy, relax.
No! It wasn't a dream about Stands.
A Stand was in my dream!
Right. So this is a dream, yeah?
You're so dense!
Rally-ho! You really are a numbskull!
Come on...
I'm just saying you're pretty dumb, Polnareff!
I-It's coming from the dog's wound...
Rally-ho! You've entered the dream of a Death God, Polnareff!
A megaphone?
W-What the hell is that?
Polnareff, get ready to battle! That's Death 13!
W-Wor-
Let's go, Hierophant Green!
Hierophant, come on!
Chario-
Hierophant isn't coming out! It won't work!
Chariot isn't coming out!
Is it because we're inside a dream?
Rally-ho! Isn't it romantic, dying while having a dream?
Rally-ho!
D
De
Dea
Deat
Death
Death 1
Death 13
J-Jotaro, do you feel that?
Yeah. I feel it.
Are you stupid?
You know only Stands can defeat Stands, don't you?
It's time for your eternal slumber, Polnareff.
Rally-ho...
Polnareff!
Die!
Polnareff...
Wake up, Polnareff.
Polnareff, the baby wet itself.
Change the diaper.
Drat! Someone must have woke him up...
Lucky him.
Rally-ho. Oh well...
The moment he woke up, these memories vanished.
I'll just have to get him the next time he falls asleep.
So, Kakyoin, I guess you're next.
Rally-ho!
Hey, Polnareff, you still awake?
The diaper! Change the diaper!
Yeah, got it...
It feels like I had a really bad dream...
But... I don't even remember having a dream.
I forgot...
Once you've changed his diaper, you can go finish that dream.
I won't wake you up again.
H-Hold on a second!
He took a dump!
Look! Just look at this!
He's a baby. Why do you think he wears diapers?
Seriously?! For real?
I never knew! You gross creature!
It's all over the place...
Quit complaining and change it already.
It reeks!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Grow up and become an adult already...
Does this work?
Well, good enough for me.
Jotaro, hold onto the edge there.
I'm gonna pin it.
Right. Like this?
Hey, keep a grip on the baby.
Rally-ho!
Stop! Stop it!
What's wrong, Kakyoin?
Hey!
What is it?
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
Dammit!
It's out of control!
H-Hey, are we gonna crash?
Stop!
Kakyoin, what the hell is wrong?
This is how he was acting this morning!
It doesn't matter, just calm him down!
Gramps, hurry up and get back in control!
We're gonna crash!
Hey, Kakyoin, calm down!
We're about to crash because of you.
Rally-ho.
Talk about a rough sleeper.
You're gonna kill my user if you keep this up.
Y-Your user is that baby?
I-I can't believe it...
He can't be more than six months old...
Not even close! Eleven months!
I'm a genius. A genius!
Even though I'm not potty trained, I'm way smarter than you guys.
Rally-ho!
That should stop you from screaming.
A Stand within a dream...
I have to let Mr. Joestar and Jotaro know of this somehow...
What are you doing?!
Level the fucking plane!
Listen up! The word "panic" isn't in my vocabulary!
I can fix this!
I'm not waking up...
Rally-ho. I guess nobody can see you cutting your arm,
since that knife is smaller than my pee-pee.
You can hurt yourself all you want in a dream,
but it won't wake you up.
As long as you're asleep, I control your mental energy.
Death 13 is a Stand that enters
the unguarded mental state of sleep.
Damn. Stop!
Gramps, what the hell?
We're gonna crash!
Hermit Purple can control it!
I did it!
I got control back just in time!
Close one...
It looks like we didn't crash...
You guys are reckless.
Now where were we...
How do you feel about dying from a crushed heart?
Joestar and the others will think you died of a heart attack.
Die, Kakyoin!
You guys see that?! How do you like my flying now, huh?!
Hey...
W-Why is there a palm tree out here?!
Gimme a break...
Seriously...
Is this for real?
Abu Dhabi
Cairo
Crash
Abu Dhabi
Cairo
Crash
Abu Dhabi
Cairo
Is this enough?
Yeah, thanks.
We survived, but...
Kakyoin, what's going on?
This is all your fault!
I don't know...
I feel like I had a bad dream again...
When I woke up, I was dead tired.
Is there something wrong with me?
Cheer up. You're just feeling fatigued.
We left Japan about a month ago, and it's been nothing but nonstop encounters with enemies since then.
Hey. The baby's fever is down.
Oh, thank goodness you're safe!
I don't know what we'd have done if we lost you.
Peek-a-boo!
So cute! What a smile!
What's so funny about that? It's not even a joke or anything.
You dummy.
Just shut up. I'm not exactly thrilled to be humoring this guy.
Hey, Gramps. The radio's still good.
What's the plan? Send an SOS?
Although Dio might find us...
It can't be helped. Let's call for help.
For the sake of the baby.
I thought something hurt. There's blood again.
Was I cut when we crashed?
What's this? These cuts look like letters...
Baby... Stand?
That's what it says...
W-What does that mean? It's my handwriting...
I can't remember...
Did I do this to myself?
There isn't any blood on my knife,
but these cuts were done by this blade.
Am I forgetting something important?
Darn. I heard they were clever...
...but I never expected he would try carving letters into his arm.
What was with the look in that baby's eyes?
As soon as our eyes met, he consciously looked away.
Baby...
Stand?
Baby... Stand...
Did something really happen to my mind?
I'm starting to think...
...this baby really is a Stand user!
Hey, Kakyoin! What are you doing?
Hey, hey, that's too rough.
You'll strangle him like that. What's wrong with you?
I-I'm sorry...
There, there, it's all right.
Let's get something to eat.
I'm sure you'll calm down once you eat something.
Hey, Jotaro. It looks like Kakyoin's really losing it.
There, there, everything's okay.
I'm not sure he's gonna make it through this trip...
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
What's the deal with Kakyoin?
Did you see that?
Kakyoin! That's enough! Stop!
You big idiot!
He has to be a Stand user!
Did you do that to yourself?
Did I just make things even worse?
Rally-ho!
Episode 20
Death 13 Part 2