Hey, you!
Yeah, you there!
You left this trash on the ground, didn't you?
That'll be five hundred Singapore dollars!
Huh? Five hundred?
Here in Singapore, littering is prohibited by law!
Five hundred Singapore dollars...
That's roughly 40,000 Japanese yen...
Trash?
You hear me?
What are you talking about?
I don't see anything except my luggage sitting right beside me!
Would you be so kind as to point out this trash you're speaking of?
Where's the trash, buddy?
That's your luggage?
That's right!
E-Excuse me!
Well, I'll be going, then...
What's with the kid? She's still following us.
Hey, weren't you going to see your father?
Why don't you stop following us and get going?
He'll be here in five days.
I can go wherever I want!
I don't have to take orders from you guys.
She will be at risk if she stays with us.
Maybe she doesn't have any money?
All right...
I guess we can pay for her hotel room.
Polnareff, we don't want to hurt her pride, so use some tact.
Gotcha.
Hey!
You're poor, right?
We'll pay for your room, so come on.
Let us just check in...
Y-Yeah...
I'm terribly sorry, but we're rather full at this time of year.
The rooms won't be next to each other. Is that all right?
Well, not like we have a choice.
Then for the rooms... Uh...
Abdul and I will share a room...
Jotaro and I will share a room, since we're both students.
That means the last room is for Polnareff and...
You're kidding! Like I'd room with him!
No way!
Well, she may be a child, but she's also a young lady...
Could you make that four rooms?
Certainly.
I'll be able to relax better in my own room anyway!
I'll be right as rain!
Come on!
We've been through hell since we left Hong Kong.
Let's hurry up and take a shower where it's safe.
Later!
Man, you people just won't let us catch a break, huh?
Show yourself.
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 8: Devil
That's some serious bloodlust you got there.
How about you tell me your name before I, Polnareff, kill you.
They call me... Devo the Cursed.
My Stand is that of the Devil card.
It suggests a curse's dark manipulations, deteriorating mental health,
and an unfavorable path of ruin and downfall.
How did you know I was in the fridge?
Seriously, are you that dense?
You took everything out of the fridge and didn't bother hiding it!
Ebony Devil!
Silver Chariot!
Man, you suck.
That ape we met the other day
was way more terrifying and powerful than you.
N-Now you've done it, Polnareff!
How dare you do this to me?!
It hurts!
It really fucking hurts!
What's with him?
It hurts!
Damn you...
How dare you? How dare you do that?!
Now I'll really hold a grudge against you!
Such... Such painful agony must be avenged!
I let you find and attack me on purpose!
H-He's gone...
He disappeared?
W-What's going on?
I-I can't believe it! When did he cut me?
I-I don't think I felt an attack...
No, I'm sure I didn't!
Mr. Joestar! A Stand user was hiding in my room!
Huh, is this Abdul?!
Anyway, listen! He's really confusing...
He could be weak or strong...
I-It was creepy!
He ran away... Shit, what the hell?
Keep your guard up! My leg was suddenly cut open!
Devo the Cursed, of the Devil card?!
Are you certain this is what he said?
Yeah. But I still can't make heads or tails of it.
I know for a fact I caught a glimpse of his Stand.
And even though I didn't see an attack, my leg's been cut.
Anyway...
I'll be there in five minutes.
Room 1212, on the twelfth floor, right?
Make sure to also contact Kakyoin and Jotaro for me. Bye!
Front desk.
Hello? Hotel room service?
I accidentally hurt my leg...
Can you bring some kind of medicine and bandages for it?
This is Polnareff in room 912.
Understood. We will bring them to you immediately.
Aww, how could this happen...?
Just when I thought things couldn't get worse, I wrapped my leg in dirty underwear...
Fuck...
Tell me, Abdul. Do you know who it was that attacked Polnareff?
I do.
Devo the Cursed.
An assassin who claims to be a Native American shaman.
He is a terrifying Stand user.
Mafia, militaries and politicians from around the world use his services.
I once met Devo myself long ago...
He was covered in wounds, and those wounds were all obtained by provoking his enemy to attack.
He controls his Stand through the power
he obtains from holding a grudge.
This is why it appears to normal people like a curse killed them.
And Polnareff fell for that trap?
It appears so.
What kind of Stand is it?
No one knows.
Everyone who has seen his Stand is dead.
Right now, it is dangerous for Polnareff to be alone.
Or any of us for that matter.
So we have a situation where he'll
attempt to pick us off one at a time...
He'll be here in five minutes.
Everyone meet up in this room.
Got it. We'll all meet up in room 1212, gramps.
What's going on, Jojo?
Let's go. Seems we're in danger.
Huh, that's weird. I can't find my room key...
I could have sworn I set it here...
Damn, where is it?
I can't get back in here without my key...
Should I just tell the front desk?
Will they charge me for it?
There it is! Must've fallen during all the commotion earlier...
Wha-
What?!
W-What's...
I-Is this shampoo?! Shit! My eyes!
Who's there?!
Th-This is bad!
Being trapped under this bed is bad, too!
Mr. Polnareff, room service.
I've brought your medicine.
Get away! You'll be killed!
Huh? W-What happened here?!
Get out of here! I told you, you'll be killed!
How dare you?!
How dare you stab one of my eyes out, Polnareff?!
A-A doll?! That's the...
Silver Chariot!
Are you fucking dense?
It's impossible for your Stand to fight where it can't see, ain't it?!
E
Ebo
Ebon
Ebony
Ebony De
Ebony Devi
De
Ebony Devil
Devo
Devo the
Devo the Cu
Power: D
Speed: D
Range: A
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: B
Devo the Curs
Devo the Cursed
Oh, Jojo!
Is something wrong?
Good, you're here.
Listen up. Don't leave your room.
We'll be back later.
Don't open the door for any strangers, okay?
O-Okay...
Shit! How heavy is this bed anyway?
Must be at least 120 kilograms...
I have to use Silver Chariot to cut this cord...
Y-You bastard!
Just as I stop attacking, he does this!
Even if I can't see, I'll just have to keep stabbing!
You suck!
Looks like your puny knight can't do much when it's blind!
You're too fucking dense!
Bastard...
Give it a rest already, small fry!
It's just you two?
How is the girl?
Well, we went to check on her...
But she's not a Stand user, so we thought we'd be
putting her in unnecessary danger by bringing her here.
Good point. So that just leaves Polnareff.
But he's really late...
It's been well over five minutes.
Le' go ob me!
Now I got ya!
I'm gonna snap your spear in half!
Yes!
Dammit... But at least I finally managed to cut the cord...
I need to call Chariot back under
the bed and get the hell out of here...
W-What's he doing?
Hey, Polnareff!
I'm gonna chomp your nuts off now, man!
He's a nasty little fucker...
Chariot!
Whoa, there.
I'm gonna go play a quick game of hide-and-no-seek!
Ya numbskull!
Why don't you give the floor you're stuck to a nice feel?
Th-This is...
It's completely soaked with beer, juice, and booze!
I spilled them on purpose!
If I could, I'd piss everywhere just to make it even wetter!
And now... what do you think I'm gonna do with this
malfunctioning hair dryer and that wet spot, Polnareff?
Let's just say I won't be drying you off!
Die!
This should take care of my grudge...
Polnareff!
You're not the only one who's been scattering stuff around!
H-How did you know where I was above the bed?!
How did you know my exact position?!
I broke that mirror!
It let me see the top of the bed really well from any angle!
At last, we meet.
Hold on.
Hey, Devo.
I've got a question for ya.
I'm looking for a man with two right hands.
Why don't you tell me about this guy's Stand.
You moron! No assassin reveals their Stand's identity!
That only happens if they or their opponent is dying!
Cocky bastards like you make their Stand's weaknesses so obvious!
If not for that mirror, you'd be fucking dead right now!
All right, let's do this once more!
What's the matter?
Didn't you say you were going to bite off my nuts or something?
Just try it, you vulgar little dick!
I'm gonna...
...slice up everything except your balls!
Sir?
You've been on the toilet for quite some time...
Is anything the matter?
De
Devo
Devo the
Devo the Cur
Devo the Cursed
Devo the Cursed's
Devo the Cursed's.
Devo the Cursed's..
Devo the Cursed's...
Devo the Cursed's... Last
Devo the Cursed's... Last Mom
Devo the Cursed's... Last Moments
Oh, Polnareff, you finally arrived.
Man, you took forever.
All right everyone, have a seat.
We need to figure out a way to defeat Devo the Cursed.
I-I'm beat...
Si
Silv
Silve
Silver
Silver C
Silver Ch
Silver Cha
Silver Chari
J
Silver Chario
Je
Silver Chariot
Jea
Jean
Jean Pi
Jean Pie
Jean Pier
Jean Pierr
Jean Pierre
Jean Pierre Po
Power: C
Speed: A
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: B
Growth Potential: C
Jean Pierre Poln
Jean Pierre Polnar
Jean Pierre Polnaref
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Answer me!
Why was there a dead boy's body in your hotel room?
Not to mention the dead body in the bathroom...
They're connected, aren't they?!
Answer me!
I have the right to remain silent.
You're finally here! You really kept me waiting!
I had the Speedwagon Foundation take appropriate measures.
Polnareff will be released soon enough.
However, that was too close.
To think the enemy's pursuit would happen again so quickly...
As long as Dio has Jonathan Joestar's body,
he'll know every move Jotaro and I make.
That's why he keeps relentlessly coming after us.
But on the other hand, we can read Dio's next moves as well.
I shall procure another Polaroid camera.
There's no need.
I can create a spirit photo even without a camera.
Huh?
Michael's not here yet? Where's Michael?
This week's number three jumps up five points from last week...
The price of gold today is...
You look delicious, meow!
What?!
The channels appear to be changing chaotically.
It's trying to connect words from the TV into a sentence.
It's more spirit audio than spirit photo.
There...
...is...
...a...
There! It said, "There is a!"
...trai...
...tor...
...among...
...us...
What was that? Did it just say...
I believe I heard it say, "There is a traitor among us..."
Ka...
...kyo...
...in...
...Beware...
...of...
...him...
Di...
...o's...
...ser...
...va...
...nt.
Kakyoin?! W-What?!
Inconceivable! Kakyoin is Dio's servant?
It's...
Joseph Joestar...
You're watching me, aren't you?!
Dio!
He found us! Look out!
B-But what does this mean?
It's just like you heard.
It clearly said Kakyoin is Dio's servant and that he'll betray us!
Impossible!
I'd trust Kakyoin with my life.
There must be more to it...
But if he really is working for Dio...
He could kill us in our sleep at any time!
It would make him Dio's Trojan Horse!
Where is Kakyoin now?
He is with Jotaro.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Yo, Jotaro. You gonna eat that cherry?
Hey! What's wrong with you, Kakyoin? You'll kill him!
Could he truly have betrayed us?
That back-breaker! What a vicious move!
What you've done is unforgivable.
Episode 9
Yellow Temperance