Enya, I have a question for you.
What is the purpose of living?
To obtain one's desires.
Simply put, this is the purest reason there is to live.
People want money, they want fame,
they want food, they want to be loved, they want to make love...
But when a person attempts to obtain
what they desire, mustn't they fight for it, Enya?
Certainly.
If that fight proves fruitless and they fail to obtain what they desire,
a feeling of frustration and failure will overcome them.
It is painful.
And they will fear for the coming battles as a result.
I believe that conquering fear is what it means to live.
The one who will stand at the top of the world
is the one who feels no fear.
Do you understand, Enya?
I taught you well about your Stand and how to harness its power.
What's more, you also possess an immortal body.
Is there something you fear?
Possibly.
What concerns you?
The Joestar bloodline.
Joestar? Those two? They are mere filth.
Those fools are no match for your Stand!
But when the lives of that filth are so deeply entangled
with my own, I cannot help but believe it is destiny.
To be more specific...
It is not that I fear the Joestars.
It is that I cannot take their bloodline lightly.
I must remove the Joestars from the cogs of my destiny.
You've decided to eliminate them yourself
simply because you feel that they cannot be underestimated?
Indeed.
Foolishness!
You should never engage in such foolishness!
You have Empress, Hanged Man, Strength,
Wheel of Fortune, Temperance, Emperor, Devil...
...and the Stand users who wield them to carry out your will!
You needn't worry about taking action yourself, Lord Dio.
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 7: Strength
A-A freighter!
That wasn't there before...
Jotaro, what's on your mind?
Do you think there could be another Stand user on this freighter?
No, I'm just wondering why nobody's shown themselves,
even though the ramp is down.
They came all this way to rescue us!
There has to be someone aboard!
Even if they're all Stand users, I'm getting on this ship!
Grab on. I'll help you up.
Gimme a break.
W-What's with this ship?
The captain's not in the pilothouse!
And the operator's not in the radio room!
There's no one anywhere!
And yet, look here!
All the meters and machines are still functioning!
Maybe they're locked in the bathroom with a bad case of the shits?
Hey! Where the hell is everyone?!
Guys, over here, look!
It's a monkey!
There's a monkey inside the cage!
It's an orangutan.
Who cares about some damn monkey?!
Let's split up and find the guy feeding it.
How is it?
Doesn't look like it's busted, but...
Abdul! That man is in danger!
Gimme a break.
That's one way to welcome a little girl on your ship.
B-But no one was touching it...
That crane moved, even though there was nobody operating it! I saw it!
Th-That crane impaled him on its own!
Be careful! There's someone here!
Hey! Don't touch any of the machinery!
If it moves or runs on electricity, don't lay a finger on it!
If you want to live, follow my orders!
Don't leave the cabin down below until we say it's okay!
Did anyone catch a glimpse of a Stand just now?
No...
I am afraid not...
I was closest to the crane, yet I felt nothing.
All right, I'll have Hierophant Green take a look.
I-I don't know what's going on,
but it feels like danger is following these guys...
Are they cursed?
I've been told about people who leave disaster in their wake, and that I should avoid them.
Could it be true?
There's one thing I can tell you with absolute certainty.
We're on your side!
So please, stay close to the others.
You want me to open the cage?
I can't...
I don't know where the key is, and you're so big.
You're giving me an apple?
That's weird...
This apple was cut with a knife, but the color hasn't changed yet...
Someone cut it recently.
So, that means there really is someone else on this ship, right?
Do you know where the person who feeds you is?
Y-You're a pretty smart monkey, aren't you?
You're a monkey, and you find human pinup girls...
...attractive?
Hey, be careful!
They say orangutans have five times the strength of a human,
so it could rip your arm off with ease.
Come on. Stay with us in the room on the other side.
And no more wandering.
O-Okay...
I can't believe it...
I had Hierophant Green search the entire ship,
but there are no signs of life anywhere!
We've searched every pipe and crevice, but there's nothing!
Well?
I-It's no use. There's no connection.
Try it again!
I'm all sticky from the salt water...
Hey!
Jojo!
Here's your fucking lock!
This ape... is no ordinary ape.
Is it possible he's...
Ora!
D-Did he just make that fan hit me?
So this ape is a Stand user...
But where is his Stand?
Why can't I see it?
What?
Is the propeller bending on its own?
Jojo!
What the fuck is this?
Again, I don't see a Stand, but somehow the window broke...
Star Platinum!
Ora!
What's with this thing?
The ape sank into the wall and disappeared!
Hey, did you see that?
Stay close.
Something bad's going down.
The ape vanished into the wall...
But that orangutan has to be the Stand user...
When I touched him earlier, I could sense energy from a Stand.
But why can't I see it?
No... way...
If I could see it this whole time, that means...
W-What?!
W-What is this?!
S-Shit!
Th-This... is...
This freighter...
Is it possible this ship is...
...a massive Stand!
D-Dammit!
It is! This ship is one gigantic Stand!
The ship?!
There are Stands that regular people,
like that girl and the crew members, can see?
The only explanation for them seeing it
is the enormous energy it is giving off!
I cannot even fathom the tremendous power
it would take to control such an enormous Stand!
Kakyoin! Use Hierophant Green and contact Jotaro!
I-I can't! It has a firm hold on my Stand!
So this is what it's like to stare death in the face!
We're already hopelessly stuck...
The pressure is getting worse...
If this keeps up, our bodies will be crushed!
E-Everyone will be...
W-We were careless...
The word that the orangutan was pointing to was "strength."
It means force, energy, power, or aid.
And... it is the eighth card of the Tarot!
The eighth card of the Tarot.
It suggests challenge, powerful will, and hidden instinct.
It suggests challenge, powerful will, and hidden instinct!
Ora!
This dirty fucking ape thinks he's already won...
"This ship, the entire thing, is my Stand!"
"You already lost!"
"You can't do a thing!"
That...
...is what the ape was thinking!
That button's not part of your Stand.
You angry?
I bet that hurt your pride since you thought you won.
No, it's not hurt...
...because apes don't have any pride!
That's exactly what makes you a fucking ape.
Now allow me to show you what being hurt really feels like!
Gimme a break.
I've heard that, when frightened,
animals show their stomachs to signal they've given up.
You want my forgiveness?
Problem is, you already crossed a line no animal should.
You're done for.
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
It's distorting... The whole ship is twisting up!
Hey, there's time to be surprised later.
This ship's going down.
We'll get out of here on the boats we came on.
I-I can't believe it...
The ship is transforming...
It's turning into a puny little boat...
Inconceivable...
That monkey used its own Stand to get this far into the ocean.
What terrifying power.
This is the first time I have encountered such energy.
We were completely overwhelmed.
If Jotaro hadn't figured it out, we'd be done for.
Do you think we'll encounter Stands that are even more twisted and powerful than his?
Want some gum?
I suppose we shall be drifting again...
Gimme a break. My cigarettes are soaked.
There'll be plenty of time for them to dry in the sun, Jojo.
We'll just have to pray we get rescued and reach Singapore safely.
It's been four days since we left Japan...
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
There are 46 days left on their time limit!
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Tokyo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Plane Crash
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
Hong Kong
Ghost Ship
Singapore
Cairo
St
Str
Stre
Stren
Streng
Fo
Strength
For
Fore
Forev
Power: B
Speed: D
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Foreve
Forever
It appears Strength has been defeated.
But fear not, the remaining six Stand users are all very powerful.
And one of them happens to be my son!
He will take care of them with his two right hands!
You are a strange old woman.
What is it that you desire?
I have told you many times...
My wish is to stay by your side.
Your guardian spirit has an unbelievable amount of power.
Your ability to escape trouble,
as well as your unique life, can be attributed to it.
I want to witness your life!
That is all...
Once upon a time, a prince from the land of
Sumatra went out to sea, seeking new lands.
He then found an island where there were white-maned lions called Singas, and so he named the island Singapura.
It is a country of straits that ships and tankers from around the world pass through!
A country whose people share both Western
and Eastern heritage thanks to free trade: Singapore!
About time. We're finally here.
We'll stay at a hotel tonight and figure out the best route to Egypt.
All right, let's stay at that one.
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Man, you people just won't let us catch a break, huh?
She will be at risk if she stays with us.
And Polnareff fell for that trap?
Trai...
...tor...
...among...
...us...
Joestar, you're...
Episode 8
Devil