Pardon us.
Mr. Kakyoin, how are you feeling today?
I've never been without my vision before...
It's a bit unsettling.
Does it hurt?
Not very much; I can feel the painkillers working.
I see. That's good.
Hello, Mr. Kakyoin.
Doctor, when do you think I can take off these bandages?
I have no time to waste.
Mr. Kakyoin, while your eye injuries are not life-threatening,
they aren't exactly minor, either.
I'm afraid I won't be discharging you anytime soon.
To be honest, I can't even give you an estimate.
Just kidding!
It's true you still require time to heal...
...but just moments ago, we were inexplicably
contacted by doctors from the Speedwagon Foundation.
They requested that we put you in their care.
With their advanced medical techniques,
I'm sure you'll have a much speedier recovery.
So, just who are you?
The Speedwagon Foundation is world-renowned.
I wouldn't have thought they'd get involved with some high school kid.
I'm lucky enough to have friends in high places.
Thank you, Mr. Joestar.
I might be able to join you sooner than I expected.
Jotaro, Polnareff, Abdul, Iggy...
Please wait for me.
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 30: Mariah's Divine Bastet Part 1
Here, about halfway up the Nile, is the city of Luxor.
In ancient times, it was known as Thebes.
Far to the west of the Nile, there lies a valley where the pharaohs of old were lain to rest.
This is the Valley of the Kings.
Over there lies the tomb of the famous King Tutankhamun,
located in the Valley of the Kings.
Wow, this place is pretty historical.
It is said that people illegally dig beneath
their homes in hopes of finding gold and treasure.
I wonder if there's any undiscovered tombs or treasures left...
Quite possibly.
Anyway, where's Gramps?
The toilet.
Between he and Iggy, they will notice anything unusual.
Toilet?
You as well?
Only if it's a real toilet...
Oh my God!
The air is so dry, the poop crumbles into dust and flies away...
So instead of water, this toilet uses wind?
There's no paper here, either.
Is this...
Is this a sand washlet?
You clean your ass... with sand?!
Desert sand is completely sterile.
Oh my God!
I'm no Polnareff, but maybe I'll just wait for the hotel.
With a toilet like that, I might as well do it behind a rock.
What a weird thing to see in Egypt...
This doesn't make sense...
Why does this rock have an electrical outlet?
What is it for?
It's not like it could be wired to anything...
I got electrocuted...
Mr. Joestar, what is the matter?
We are heading out.
R-Right...
Got it. I'm coming.
That was quite the surprise...
Since there's power here...
does that mean they're running wires underground?
What a strange place.
Talk about surreal...
The Divine Bastet Card
Its user's name: Mariah
The Divine Bastet Card.
Its user's name: Mariah.
The Divine Bastet Card
Its user's name: Mariah
Men seem to enjoy touching things,
even when they really shouldn't.
We could possibly make it to Cairo in two days,
but all of us have suffered injuries.
How about we spend tonight and tomorrow in Luxor to recuperate?
I agree.
Ever since we reached Egypt,
the enemy Stands have gotten a lot tougher.
We're winning by the skins of our teeth.
Hey, Mr. Joestar, what's wrong?
My prosthetic hand's been acting up.
The joints probably just need oiling.
Hey, mister! Is your radio busted?
How strange... It's a Japanese model, and I just got it...
It's annoying, just switch it off!
Mr. Joestar?
Yeah, I agree. We should probably rest up before we enter Cairo.
But we have to keep our guard up.
So, let's find a hotel.
How strange...
Mister, thanks.
Come again!
Ah, the radio finally started working again!
Huh? What the hell? My hammer feels... heavy...
W-What?!
Th-The nails... The nails! It hurts...
Hey, hey! Did you hit your fingers? Pay attention!
You have to be careful, slamming that hammer around willy-nilly!
For crying out loud...
Mr. Joestar...
Please wake up, Mr. Joestar...
Hey, hurry up in there!
Polnareff is complaining because we have not left for breakfast yet.
Just hurry and wake him up, Abdul!
Tell him he's got five minutes!
Old people are supposed to be early risers!
Jeez, what a loudmouth...
Tell him I'll be right down...
Right.
Did my watch stop?
But you know, Mr. Joestar...
You have surprising sleeping habits for a man of your age.
You turned all the way around.
You fell asleep facing south, yet somehow awoke facing north...
Could it be your age betrays your youthfulness?
Meet us downstairs.
Something strange has been going on since last night...
And my prosthetic hand's still acting up...
W-What's going on with this chair?!
It's moving on its own!
Is this entire floor tilted?
We paid a premium for this hotel, but clearly they cut a few corners...
Where should we go today?
The Karnak Temple was amazing,
so something like that would be fun!
It's a bit far, but how about the Valley of the Queens?
What the hell are you doing, you dirty old man?!
Pervert!
W-What the hell is going on...?
Oh, my. That's quite a boldly aggressive approach.
Y-o-u are just my t-y-p-e.
Smooch!
Oh my God!
Something strange is going on! Something really strange!
I knew something seemed off since last night!
What?!
Th-They're...
...sticking to me...
All of this metal is sticking to me...
Everything made of steel is flying at me!
Could it be that my body...
My body...
...has turned into a giant magnet?!
Ow!
C-Could this magnetism be a new Stand?
But why? Why can't I see the Stand?
Why are the knives and forks flying at me without a Stand around?
Could it be...
Did being electrocuted by that rock turn my body into a magnet?
I'm stuck...
O-Oh no! The escalator is made of steel!
And this magnetism is getting stronger by the minute!
What?!
H-Hey! Lady in the miniskirt!
I-I'm in trouble!
Your chains got tangled around my body,
and it's dragging me into the conveyor!
Please push the emergency stop button
at the bottom of the escalator!
At this rate, your chains will drag me in
and chop off my hands and feet!
H-Hey! Can you hear me?!
Enjoy the afterlife, Joseph Joestar.
W-What?! D-Don't tell me you're...
You're the Stand user?!
Di
Divi
Divine
Divine Ba
Divine Bast
Divine Bastet
M
Ma
Mari
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Mariah
D-Don't tell me you're...
You're the Stand user?!
Once my Stand, Divine Bastet,
has you ensnared with its magnetic energy...
...there is no way to escape its grasp.
S-Someone! Stop the escalator!
I-I know!
I'll push the emergency stop button...
...with my Hermit Purple!
N-No way! It's missing?!
Th-The emergency stop button isn't there?!
I-Impossible! The escalator...
...doesn't have a stop button?!
I'm being pulled in...!
My neck! My neck!
It's gonna rip my head off!
This is it!
This is it! I'm dead!
Mr. Joestar. Ahem! Paging Mr. Joestar!
It's gonna be ripped... all the way off!
The escalator has stopped.
I pushed the emergency stop button.
It was on the side.
N-No problems!
My escalator inspection has found no problems!
The stop button is in working order!
Oh, are you the hotel manager?
Could you please sign off my inspection here?
What has happened, Mr. Joestar?
It's an enemy. I've been affected by an enemy Stand.
My body is like a magnet now...
She turned me into a magnet.
Steel objects keep sticking to me.
Pull this thing off me!
And the magnetic force... keeps getting stronger...
It's her! That woman is the user!
Catch her!
We have to stop her magnetism right away,
otherwise it will be strong enough to keep me from moving!
Let us regroup with Jotaro and the others outside!
What?!
This statue... is heavy...
Abdul?!
We can't wait on Jotaro and the others!
She's getting away from us!
Mr. Joestar, leave me! Go after her!
R-Right!
I'll see her face at the very least!
Th-This is...
She went into the ladies' room...
What now?
I'm going in.
My life depends on it!
I'll catch that woman, no matter what!
M-Mr. Joestar?!
Gramps hasn't showed?
Yeah. Abdul went to get him, and he's not back either...
Could it be...
...they're secretly...
...eating delicious food without us?!
He's just taking his time in the toilet.
We'll look for them if they're not here in five minutes.
Oh, the toilet... Yeah, I guess so...
Come to think of it, this hotel sure had some pristine toilets...
Mr. Joestar, I commend you for entering here, but...
...as I expected, all of the stalls are in use.
Pardon me, but... I-I do not know... which stall is she in?
You'll know by her amazing legs.
H-Her legs?
Yes! Look for those legs!
You'll know right when you see them.
W-We have to peek inside?
No...
Also no...
M-Mr. Joestar, right here!
Over here! Are these her legs?
Oh, my. You're that wonderful man I bumped into earlier.
You came all the way here for me?
Such a bold approach...
Smooch!
Holy shit!
It's that old hag! But she's supposed to be upstairs!
C-Curses!
We found the wrong person! This is exceedingly bad...
How the hell did you mess this up?!
Abdul, run away!
Wai-
Perverts!
This does not bode well with my image!
Toilet disasters are Polnareff's thing!
Look at those peeping old men!
How awful!
You perverts!
No, you're love-l-y!
She went in that direction!
Shit! When did she get over there?
After her!
Abdul, I forgot to tell you earlier,
but don't touch anything that looks like an electrical outlet!
Don't touch it, no matter where you find it!
It's the enemy's Stand!
You'll feel a shock, then the magnetism will start!
I am afraid I already touched it, Mr. Joestar.
What?! W-Where?!
When I pushed the emergency stop button at the escalator...
...I saw an outlet nearby, and it electrocuted me.
Th-That woman...
M-Mr. Joestar, please try to keep your distance.
Moving with you stuck to me is difficult...
Y-You're the one getting closer, Abdul!
What are you talking about? It is you who is getting closer!
That's because magnets attract when they get close!
To think that I would end up a human magnet...
Mr. Joestar, this situation...
Yeah, it's not good!
Th-This enemy...
This enemy...
...is strong!
Next Episode
To think that I would end up a human magnet...
There's no time to complain about her power!
How dare she?
What shall we do? She told us...
...but not once have I truly abandoned a fight!
I'll keep fighting with everything I've got!
Episode 31
Mariah's Divine Bastet Part 2