Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
It's her! That woman is the user!
Oh, my. That's quite a boldly aggressive approach.
Smooch!
Oh my God!
Abdul, I forgot to tell you earlier,
but don't touch anything that looks like an electrical outlet!
I am afraid I already touched it, Mr. Joestar.
What?!
That's because magnets attract when they get close!
Mr. Joestar, this situation...
Yeah, it's not good!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 31: Mariah's Divine Bastet Part 2
Wait!
Shit!
She went around the corner!
After her!
How can this be?!
To think that I would end up a human magnet...
Calm down, Abdul!
There's no time to complain about her power!
We need to focus on defeating her Stand!
Where the hell did she go? Dammit!
I cannot see her!
Besides, we can't stay stuck like this forever!
Get up slowly, Abdul!
Understood!
We're up!
N-Now let's try to separate...
Since we're stuck together,
it means we're being affected by twice as much magnetic force!
Let's grab onto that fence, then pull ourselves apart!
Here we go, Abdul! Use your core muscles!
Create a rhythm!
Yes, Mr. Joestar!
One, two!
M-Mr. Joestar... Th-This is exceedingly unflattering...
Hey! What are you looking at?
We're just practicing a dance. A dance!
D-Dancing outside is truly splendid!
Get lost, dammit!
Okay, just a little more, Abdul!
One, two, and...
We did it! We made it without tripping!
I-Indeed we have...
Abdul, do you think you can slowly slide off of me?
Yes, I believe so.
All right...
I'll hold onto the fence...
...you try to slide down my body,
moving your head toward my toes.
Since our heads are sticking together, you should be able to
separate at my feet, since the polarity will be the same.
Positive
Negative
I-I see...
J-Just like that...
W-What's wrong, Abdul?
Th-This position...
Does it not appear very compromising?
Those watching may interpret this differently...
N-No one's looking! Hurry up and slide free!
They brought even more of their friends!
H-Hey, kids! Go away! Quit gawking at us!
Hey! I said go away, you damn brats!
Abdul, hurry! Hurry up and slide off!
That is easier said than done...
I refuse to be reduced to such a role! I swear!
Fine, then I'll move!
M-Mr. Joestar, slow down!
Mr. Joestar, if you move like that...
I-It's the old hag from the hotel!
I thought you were a wonderful gentleman,
yet here you are taking part in such debauchery!
You have some nerve to toy with a woman's heart!
You cheating scum!
Hurry! Hurry it up! Abdul, I'm gonna cry!
You wretched man!
Help me! Oh my God!
No, you are mistaken...
We did it!
We have to stay apart, Abdul!
Your magnetism will only get stronger!
Damn you, you ignorant fool! Go to hell!
There she is. That woman!
She's got guts to just sit there and smoke!
Abdul, approach her from over there.
Don't let her get away this time.
She's a devious woman.
She may have set a trap for us.
N-No, Mr. Joestar...
We have already fallen into her trap!
Railroad tracks!
M-My foot is stuck!
We're...
...stuck together...
...again!
Son of a bi-
Mr. Joestar, what is it?
That sound... O-Oh no! We gotta move!
Abdul, use Magician's Red's flames to melt the rails!
We have to move, pronto!
B-But, Mr. Joestar...
It's coming! The train's coming! Hurry and melt the rails!
I-I cannot! If I were to melt these rails...
...the train would derail, causing a terrible accident!
That woman... How dare she?
Even if I wanted to grab her, my Stand can't reach that far!
But there's a chance I can use this pole to pull us free...
I-It's no use! The magnetism is stronger than before!
Mr. Joestar! Keep pulling! Harder! You can do it!
I-It approaches! Pull harder!
What?!
I win.
Di
Divi
Divine
Divine Ba
Divine Bast
Divine Bastet
M
Ma
Mari
Power: E
Speed: E
Range: B
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Mariah
I've won, Lord Dio!
My next move will be to kill Jotaro and Polnareff!
Hey, Abdul!
Burning through the railroad ties and digging a hole was a great idea!
Now this is more like it!
This bodes well with the image of Mohammed Abdul!
I was born to play this kind of character!
That clever bastard...
You...
...fucking bitches!
Magician's Red!
Hermit Purple!
I got you!
Now, young lady...
I hate to do this, but I need to strangle you hard enough to put you in the hospital.
Your magnetism has been a real problem.
Must your mind wander to such dirty places?
My chest hasn't grown larger...
It's your magnetism that is growing stronger!
I was keeping these in my pockets.
My special pocket weapons!
Mr. Joestar, duck!
Magician's Red!
The magnetic force will only grow stronger...
...until it finally crushes your bodies into a bloody pulp.
She is escaping!
No, you're wrong. She won't escape.
She's controlling the distance between us.
I'm pretty sure her battle tactic is to stay a certain distance away.
If she comes too close, she'll get caught...
...but too far, and the magnetism will disappear.
The magnetism is coming from her Stand...
...and by the rules that govern Stands,
once the user is far away, their power will weaken!
What shall we do?
She told us the magnetism would continue to grow stronger.
Should we flee until the magnetic force expires?
No. Even if we escape the magnetism,
we won't have defeated her Stand.
I, Joseph Joestar,
have strategically retreated from fights in the past...
...but not once have I truly abandoned a fight!
I'll keep fighting with everything I've got!
This is a map of the city.
Right now, we're here.
She's over here.
If she continues down this road,
she'll loop around and head back this way.
We'll split up...
...then catch her here!
I can't see her as some weak woman!
I'll defeat her, no matter what!
After her!
Hey, look.
Gosh, someone cut the rail...
People from the city are here!
I presume they will report the damage
before the next train passes through.
Let's go!
Looks like something's up.
Someone cut the rail line!
Will the trains be okay?
They've stopped running for now.
Someone cut the rail line?
That's a pretty rude thing to do.
Why would anyone do that? Are they stupid?
Jotaro, I gotta say...
People like that always end up getting their just desserts.
I spent three months' pay on this...
Let's get married!
Wow!
They're coming up fast...
B-But they'll never catch up...
Stay calm. I gotta stay calm...
You look like you're having a tough time.
Our game of cat and mouse is over.
You think so?
I know these roads a hell of a lot better than you do.
Look behind you!
This is a pincer attack!
We have you cornered.
Here, at the last moment, the tables have turned!
A pincer attack?
You're both so clueless.
You think you have me cornered,
but it's really me who has you cornered!
Look above you!
High voltage power lines!
Curses! Power lines are...
Yes! The power lines are magnetic!
You'll burn to a crisp!
Magician's Red!
Hermit Purple!
Abdul is able to defend himself with his flames, but...
Joestar, you don't stand a chance.
The difference in power between
my Divine Bastet and your Hermit Purple...
...is greater than you can comprehend!
Woman, I will burn you asunder!
Something is pulling me!
My entire body is being pulled!
W-What is this?!
Although my flames are capable of melting steel,
I cannot defend myself from this...
I am being crushed!
I can't keep this up!
Joseph Joestar, since this is almost over...
...I must admit, you're an amazing man.
Although I've only known you for a short time,
you've enamored me with your wit, intelligence...
...and above all, your experience that younger men lack.
You're a very charming man.
Despite our age difference, I could see the two of us as lovers.
I-I'm glad you feel that way...
So why don't you save me?
You have much more power than my Hermit Purple!
I can't keep this up... P-Please, stop your magnetism!
You have a point...
But I don't think so.
You aren't nearly as charming as Lord Dio.
W-Will nothing convince you to stop the magnetism?!
I'm afraid not.
You'll just have to die.
Even though I'm begging you?
You're far too persistent, fool.
Then you've lost, young lady.
What?!
Oh... Oh shi-
We told you earlier, this was a pincer attack!
Magnets attract one another!
Your luck ran out the second you got between us!
She cannot hear you, Mr. Joestar. She has fainted.
The combined weight and magnetic force has crushed her.
I am afraid she likely broke many bones.
So... Does breakfast sound good?
Yes. I must say, that running around has made me famished.
It's already nine o'clock...
Fucking bitches...
Ma
Mar
Mari
Mariah
Di
Div
Divin
Divine
Divine B
Divine Ba
Divine Bast
Divine Bastet:
Rushed
Rushed To
Rushed To The
Rushed To The Hos
Rushed To The Hospital
With
With Bro
With Broken
With Broken Bones
Unable To Recover (Retired)
He
Her
Herm
Hermi
Hermit
Hermit Pu
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purp
J
Hermit Purple
Jo
Jose
Josep
Joseph
Joseph J
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Power: D
Speed: C
Range: D
Durability: A
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Joseph Joes
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
They're taking forever...
What the hell are they doing?
Even a woman wouldn't take this long to get dressed...
It's almost nine o'clock...
They could've encountered an enemy.
You think we should go look for them?
Yeah. But gimme a break...
Come on, Iggy.
I know, I know. You're hungry, right?
So am I.
While Joestar and Abdul are busy fighting Mariah...
...I, the great Alessi, will kill Jotaro and Polnareff.
Next Episode
Okay, little boy.
Come to the bathroom and we'll take your clothes off.
Very good.
I'll take them off for you.
I'll treat your wounds for you.
Very good.
Is this really, really okay?!
Episode 32
Alessi's Divine Set Part 1