Must be a big shock, being eaten by your dead sister!
People expose their greatest weaknesses
when they wish from the heart!
It never even occurred to you how unnatural it is to bring someone back to life.
You wanted to believe your loved ones were still alive somewhere on this earth.
You hoped they would suddenly
appear before you and say "Good morning!"
By the way...
You mentioned a third wish,
but you've already made it, haven't you?
You can't mean...
"Bring Abdul back to life."
Hail 2 U!
No... That's...
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Abdul!
Episode 22: Judgement Part 2
Ab... dul...
My fingers... are falling off...
Polnareff!
This is your fault!
Because of you, I... I...
...ended up like this!
Abdul... I... I made you...
I...
You will pay dearly for this, Polnareff!
With...
...your body!
I'll get better if I eat, right?
Isn't that right?
Big brother!
What's the matter, big brother?
S-Stay away! Stay away from me!
Both of you... go back to the ground already!
Why? You're the one who brought us back.
It is you who shall return to the ground!
I... I was so freaked out that I forgot to summon Chariot...
I was so distracted by my wish, I forgot to use my Stand...
Stay away, I'm begging you!
Please!
What?!
"I'm begging you"? Nuh-uh! You're all out of wishes!
You've had your three wishes!
You have none left!
Stop!
Hail 2 U!
Scream and cry as much as you like before it's over!
We're deep in this island's wilderness.
Nobody on the shore will hear you!
No one will come to save you!
I-It's no use... I'm done for...
I'm dead. He beat me.
Cherie...
Abdul...
Even though you're just dolls made of dirt,
being killed by you isn't so bad.
Abdul, just like you said, you died because of me...
I won't complain about whatever fate has in store for me...
What?
Are my eyes so blurry that I'm seeing double?
I thought I saw two Abduls.
But of course there's only the dirt doll.
If I'm hallucinating, I guess that means death is finally coming.
I've lost a lot of blood...
I'm definitely seeing things.
Well... I guess this is it...
I'm tapping out early...
Goodbye, Mr. Joestar... Kakyoin... Jotaro...
I pray for your victory...
Abdul, for you...
...I'll atone in the next world...
What?! Impossible!
I knew it! There is another Abdul!
My eyes weren't playing tricks on me!
First the dirt doll Abdul, and now this one!
Magician's Red!
Impossible! He should be dead!
He was stabbed by Hanged Man's user, J. Geil!
He should be dead!
Mohammed Abdul!
Yes, I am!
I-Is it really you?
I-Is this the real you?
Polnareff, you are still lacking in maturity.
You continue going on and on about
your sister with no regard for consequences.
Impossible!
You shouldn't be alive right now!
I was told you were stabbed in the back,
had your brains blown out by Hol Horse, then died on the spot!
Yes, I was shot. Right here on my forehead.
However, for a moment after I was stabbed in the back,
my head was facing upwards.
The bullet simply grazed me!
I suppose you would call that a blessing in disguise.
Hol Horse's bullet only managed to graze my skin and skull.
Thus my brain was unharmed.
Although I was still rendered unconcious.
You are Cameo of the Judgement card, are you not?
I will personally send you to Hell!
Hell 2 U!
The third wish, and the third wish alone...
He's real...
It came true!
Ju
Jud
Judg
Judge
Judgem
Judgeme
Judgement
Ca
Came
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Cameo
Mohammed Abdul lives once more.
This bad news...
Perhaps it would be wise for you to share it
with Dio and the other Stand users?
Right, Cameo?
I have to tell them! I really have to tell them!
Mr. Joestar, Kakyoin, and Jotaro!
This truly is surprising news.
However! I can still make this news in my favor!
"Cameo's Judgement has killed not only that idiot Polnareff,
but also Abdul, who turned out to be alive!"
That will be my good news!
Magician's Red!
Whoa, there!
Abdul!
He has quite a powerful Stand...
Be careful! He's not just powerful, but fast too!
Abdul, is this the extent of your strength?
It looks like I'll get to share my good news after all!
May fortune...
...be with you both!
What?!
Hail 2 U!
Big brother...
No. My Cherie...
...Cherie... is dead.
You're...
...just...
...a dirt doll!
Big brother...
Polnareff!
I apologize. I was wrong to say you had not matured.
No, you were right.
I should be apologizing to you.
This battle has been decided!
Abdul! Tell me your three wishes! I will grant them for you...
This time before you die for real!
Now, go ahead and try!
You have three wishes.
Asshole! He's fucking with us!
Abdul, ignore him!
You don't need to make any wishes!
Abdul, are you listening to me?
No...
Make it four.
Huh?!
What?
I mean wishes! Wishes!
I wish to have four wishes instead of three.
You can't be serious...
Will you deny me my wish, Cameo?! This was your offer!
I will make you keep your promise!
You still insist upon this futile contest of power?
What a weak kick!
What?!
He did it! Amazing!
My first wish was to have you holler in pain.
It came true.
I-Impossible! You're strong! You're way stronger than earlier!
The stab wound I received from
Hanged Man has not completely healed yet.
I was guarding it earlier, and thus could not fight at full strength.
Wha-
It was three days ago in India that I was finally able to stand up.
My trip here by plane was quite comfortable.
Now that's what I'm talking about, Abdul!
Now, my second wish...!
...is to have you scream in terror!
And my third wish...
...is for you to sob with regret!
Th-That asshole! He's running away!
Wait! Fuck!
Quiet yourself, Polnareff.
To have such power and speed...
It must mean this Stand's user is
somewhere close due to the rules governing Stands.
Is he here?
He must be hiding very close.
Could it be...
He was hiding under the ground?!
The coward! What should I do to him?
He had the nerve to use my sister, so I'll give him hell!
Hell 2 U!
Motherfucker!
I'll just drop a few things in there for him.
Dirt... sand...
...a spider...
...ants...
...and a match.
Bastard! I'm not done yet! Not yet! Not yet!
Hey, Polnareff.
I can feel nature calling!
So, shall we engage in the timeless ritual of male bonding by urinating together?
Somehow I'm alive...
Come now! Laugh, Polnareff!
Laugh, laugh, Polnareff!
Abdul... you've really changed, haven't you?
You never would have done this before...
This isn't because you were shot in the head, is it?
Come now, aim!
Right!
Please forgive me!
My fourth wish will be...
...that your wishes will never come true.
Magician's Red does not forgive.
Never.
Ba-dum tsh!
Ma
Magi
Magic
Magici
Magician
Magician's
Magician's R
Magician's Re
Mo
Magician's Red
Moha
Mohamm
Mohamme
Mohammed
Mohammed A
Mohammed Ab
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: D
Durability: B
Precision: D
Growth Potential: E
Mohammed Abd
Mohammed Abdu
Mohammed Abdul
Hey! Guys, you won't believe it!
Guess who I just found!
Polnareff, you had us worried!
When did you get those wounds?
You got attacked?
Who the hell cares about my wounds?
Listen! Don't let this shock you, Jotaro!
And don't pass out once you hear this, Kakyoin!
Who do you think I found, Mr. Joestar?
Behold and rejoice!
Here he is!
The man himself, Abdul, is alive!
Well, time to go.
Everyone, I shall help carry the luggage.
Yo, Abdul.
It's been a while. Doing well?
Abdul, is the wound on your back doing okay?
Yes, I am well. Perhaps a bit stiff.
Hey...
Has it really been two weeks?
Good thing we're all still okay.
Hey...
Jotaro, do you still not swelter wearing that jacket?
W-Wait a minute, you guys!
Dammit! I said wait, assholes!
Hey, what's the meaning of this?!
A dead man came back to life!
What the hell?! What's with the casual conversation?!
Oh, Polnareff, I'm sorry.
When I said I buried Abdul in India...
...that was a lie.
W-W-What?!
After my head and back were injured in India,
Mr. Joestar and Jotaro tended to my wounds.
Y-You assholes knew Abdul was still alive back in India, and you didn't tell me?!
And you too, Kakyoin?!
I was only told the day after.
However, I couldn't let the enemy know.
And since you're such a loudmouth...
...I mean, since you can't lie,
I suggested we not tell you until now.
If you had fucked up and spilled the beans, Abdul wouldn't have recovered in peace.
We were planning to tell you as soon as
we knew he was safe, but you ran into him first.
Oh yeah, Abdul!
Your dad's on this island!
Tell him you're here!
That was simply me in disguise.
W-What?!
Th-Then you guys... That was all...
Get lost!
Nobody tells me good news no more!
I ain't hearin' it!
Abdul's death wasn't your fault.
Was that really necessary?!
I thought we were friends, and you left me out like that?!
Hey, hey. No need to bawl your eyes out.
I'm sorry. I didn't think you would be this hurt...
My apologies, Polnareff.
I had good reason to come to this island in disguise.
Good reason?
Although part of it was to avoid the enemy figuring things out,
I also had Abdul do some shopping for me.
Some shopping?
It was a very conspicuous purchase.
I disguised myself as a wealthy Arab to purchase it.
All right, everyone! It's time to go!
Polnareff, cheer up already. Come on!
It's almost here!
Wait, what's almost here?
I don't see any-
What?!
A submarine?!
That's right! We're heading to Egypt in this bad boy!
N-No way! You seriously bought this?!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They've got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
I really like the design of the sparkly one...
A submarine, huh?
Perhaps something in a refreshing white would be better...
Hurry up with the coffee!
Oh, I don't know...
Hey, Kakyoin... Why six cups?
Yes, hello? Oh, Joseph! It's you!
Episode 23
High Priestess Part 1