Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
What the-?!
Yes!
Now Hol Horse, you need to stick
your fingers up Polnareff's nose, and then...
Hooray! Everyone is bleeding and out cold!
Lucky you, Hol Horse! Now's your chance to kill them all!
So, when the hell's my chance comin'?
The hell do I do now?!
What the hell are you doing, Hol Horse?
Wouldn't I like to know?!
Is something wrong, Polnareff?
Sh-Shit! The other three're comin'!
Dammit!
How am I supposed to make the prediction come true now?!
Polnareff, did you find the guy following us?
Answer us.
Abdul and the others are c-coming...
This ain't good... Not at all!
Chario-
Whoa, there!
Crap...
Y-Yes! I'm faster!
Hold still! I'll shoot!
Hey, can you hear me, Polnareff?
Hey, Polnareff!
Oh, there you are.
What is the matter?
Was there someone following us?
Dammit! I'm cornered!
Was he blowin' hot air when he said I'd get my
lucky break by stickin' my fingers up Polnareff's nose?!
Well this's as unlucky as ya can get!
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 37: Hol Horse and Boingo Part 2
Polnareff, is something wrong?
No...
If Abdul saw me right now, I'd be dead meat!
I'm gonna cry!
I'da used my gun in the first place if I'd known this'd happen!
Boingo, ya varmint!
At the very least, my gun's faster'n Polnareff's sword...
Dammit!
Polnareff?
Hurry'n make 'em leave!
If they find me, at least I'll still get to kill ya, Polnareff!
Th-There was nobody following us.
I was just imagining it...
I see...
By the way, why are you standing there in the corner?
Tell 'em ya were takin' a leak. A leak!
W-Well, you know... I had to pee.
Seriously?
Really, you had to pee?
That's an embarrassing thing to do right in the middle of the city.
Fuck, he's jamming that thing right into my head!
I know! I'll signal to them!
Guys, you gotta figure it out!
Look where my tongue is pointing!
I'm trying to tell you to look behind me! Behind me!
Behind me, goddammit! Behind me!
Why're them fellas bein' so quiet?
A-Anyway, that's all I have to say.
You guys should go on ahead.
Sure.
I'm lying!
Lying! Don't go!
Look where I'm licking!
Behind me! Behind me! Figure it out!
Are you okay? What's with the face?
Did you bite your tongue?
No, I believe he is saying something is behind...
Stupid, don't say it!
You don't mean...
P-Polnareff!
Did ya give 'em...
...some kinda signal?!
Dammit! Now I'm fumin'!
I... I'll kill ya!
Die!
What?!
Oh! Is that-
W-What? No way! He sneezed?!
It's Hol Horse! Be careful!
There's also someone hiding under the box!
No way! There just ain't no way!
Stickin' my fingers up his nose made 'im sneeze!
Dammit! If Polnareff din't sneeze, I coulda killed 'im at the very least!
Boingo, teamin' up with ya was a big mistake!
I'm gonna die!
I failed thanks to yer prediction, dammit!
I'm done fer!
B-Bro, look! That asshole from earlier is over there!
That's him all right!
That bitch blew my ear off outta nowhere at the airport!
Let's ram him!
What?!
Th-This is...
That truck was going so dang fast,
they din't have time to get outta the way usin' their Stands...
And 'cause I stuck my fingers up his nose,
the prediction came true!
I can hardly believe it! All four of 'em...
It was fate, indeed.
My predictions are absolute.
But we can't beat them for good yet!
We must see what the next prediction has in store for us, indeed.
Okay!
E
Em
Empe
Empero
Emperor
H
Ho
Hol
Hol Ho
Power: B
Speed: B
Range: B
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Hol Hor
Hol Horse
"Hooray! The chance to kill them has arrived!
But watch out!
Let's hide and see what happens first."
"It's too soon to get close to 'em!
Three of 'em already passed out, but that Jotaro's still awake!
He's standin' up!"
Only Jotaro dodged the truck in time!
That was a close one...
If I'd walked out there just now, he'da killed me!
Now he's lookin' fer me...
He must be wonderin' why I left before finishin' 'em off.
Don'tcha wanna beat 'em, Boingo?
After all this, we gotta win, no matter what!
Ain't that right, Boingo?
Yeah...
We're just a hop from victory!
Boingo, now how're we supposed to finish 'em off?
Them predictions in yer comic book are a hundred percent accurate!
I believe ya now.
I'll do anythin' it says!
If I gotta stick my fingers into somethin', I'll do it!
If I gotta eat shit, I'll do that too!
I just wanna win!
Th-Th-Th-There it is!
I-It finally appeared, indeed!
Th-The final prediction!
What?
At last, Hol Horse's next attack will be the climax!
Hol Horse saw two guys working on some sewage pipes.
He decided to pay them
to open up a section of the pipe for him.
If Hol Horse is able to fire
all of his bullets into the pipe at high noon...
Hey, sounds like someone got in a car accident over there.
Don't worry about it. Let's just hurry up and finish this.
Hold this pipe for a second.
Okay.
What'll happen if I fire my gun into the pipe?!
Hurry up'n turn the page!
...they'll all come flying out the other side!
Bam! Hol Horse's bullets shot right through his brain!
Right smack in the middle of his forehead!
Y-Yes!
It finally appeared, indeed!
I've been waiting for this, indeed!
I've waited so long for this prediction, indeed!
Yer amazin'!
I-It's amazin', but hang on a sec!
This ain't gonna go well if we din't read yer comic right.
Just lookit this page from before!
It's the prediction ya made before
yer brother got blown to smithereens!
Lookit what happened to 'im!
Th-That's just because my brother transformed without considering the consequences, indeed.
But y-you and I cannot transform, indeed.
That's... That's right! I can't transform!
I ain't gonna act like Jotaro even a little!
Wh-Which means...
You got it, indeed!
I'll get to avenge my big bro, indeed!
There's nothing that could go wrong with my prediction, indeed!
If you shoot your bullets into the pipe, Jotaro will die, indeed!
Hold on a sec...
It said a certain time...
At high noon?
Wait, high noon?!
Ain't that in just two minutes?!
D-Don't panic! Y-You just have to shoot into the pipe, indeed!
You have lots of time, indeed.
It's fate! It will happen for sure!
I-I know, a hundred percent!
I believe ya... I believe ya, but...
Since I gotta do it at just the right time...
...I'm startin' to panic!
H-Hey, fellas! Pipe down an' listen to me!
Pull out that there section of the pipe!
Get on with it!
Hey, just who do you think you're talking to?
Who the hell do you think you are?
I'll shoot ya both! Hurry'n open it!
M-Mr. Hol Horse, ordinary people can't see your Stand, indeed.
And the comic says you need to pay them, indeed.
Huh? Pay them?
I only got a minute an' ten seconds left!
I-I'll pay ya! I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I'll pay ya, so just open it!
Please! I'm beggin' ya!
Pay us? You weirdo.
You're gonna pay us just to open it?
Fine, then. Hurry up and pay us.
S-Sure...
Hey, what's your deal?
I ain't got no money!
Th-That's right! It's at the hotel!
Are you serious?
B-Boingo...
I gave ya my coin purse in case ya got lost, right?
Hurry an' hand it over!
O-Okay.
I only got forty seconds! Hurry!
I-It's mostly change, but... here's your coin purse.
Hey, I think I just saw one roll off into the shadows over there.
Even though it's mostly change, he had a lot of it.
How much do you think?
At least twenty pounds! Hey, you're sitting on one.
Pick it up later! Y'all can take everything!
Gentlemen, it's almost noon.
I have some tea for you
if you would like to take a short lunch break.
Oh, sounds nice!
Ya dumb bitch! You ain't first here!
Thanks, ma'am.
Ya pissants! I told ya to hurry up an' open it!
Don't make me split yer heads open!
I-It's open!
Now scram!
Die, Jotaro!
I did it! I shot into it at high noon, like the prediction said!
Go!
Gramps, hang in there.
I think I'm okay...
I, too, was just merely scratched...
But more importantly, Polnareff is...
A little help over here? This fucking block is crushing me...
We won!
Jotaro's got his face right at the pipe!
What?!
Seriously...
Sorry, Jotaro.
I don't know what the hell he was thinking,
but for some reason Hol Horse stuck his fingers right up my nose.
It was disgusting!
And it's still itchy. Sorry.
M-My bullets...
They missed!
Boingo! W-W-What's the meanin' of this?!
What the hell?!
I don't know, indeed!
M-My predictions are absolute! It's fate!
I can't believe it either!
My predictions have never, ever been wrong before, indeed!
Ya see?! Jotaro an' his pals are still kickin'!
My bullets missed 'im!
Yer prediction din't get even close!
Ya little...
And with that, please tune in tomorrow.
Now for the twelve o'clock news...
What?! Now it's noon?
M-My watch... My watch...
It's fast!
Th-That means I shot 'em all off before noon...
An' now it's really noon!
What the hell is gonna happen...?
Just tell me what'll happen next!
I-It can't be...
If yer prediction was right, I shoulda hit Jotaro dead-on!
That direction...
Just what the hell is gonna happen next?!
Hey, I just heard someone screaming around the corner.
I don't know what's going on, but it can't be good.
Since we were around when the truck crashed, we'll get in trouble if the police show up.
Let's go!
But what the hell happened to Hol Horse?
Dunno.
He already left for some reason.
Hey, standing in front of that pipe is dangerous, Jotaro.
That water is filthy.
Is he dead?
Nah, but he's in critical condition.
I still have no idea what happened.
It's almost like the bullet went
into his forehead and exited from the top.
A centimeter lower and he'd be a goner.
He sure is a lucky guy.
My prediction wasn't wrong.
This is what fate had in store for Hol Horse all along.
But that Jotaro...
How is he so lucky?
Big bro and Hol Horse lost against fate.
Only Lord Dio is a match for someone as lucky as him.
Big bro Oingo... After seeing what happened to Hol Horse,
I'm starting to think revenge is pretty dumb.
Let's just forget about Jotaro and his friends.
If my Stand's predictions were used to help make others happy,
instead of hurting people like they have been...
...everyone would love us, and I bet good luck would come our way.
I'm sick of spending my life
cowering under a box, afraid of everyone.
This fight has forced me to grow as a person.
I'm coming back, big bro!
Back to you, in Aswan!
S-Sorry! I wasn't thinking when I kicked it!
I didn't mean to hit you.
I'm sorry.
Wait, th-this dog...
I've seen him before, but where?
Th-This dog! It couldn't be!
No!
Hey, by the way, where'd that fucking dog run off to?
Iggy?
He's probably just eating something off the street.
I told you he would serve no use to us.
If it were that easy to change your personality
and grow as a person, no one would ever suffer.
Boingo became even more withdrawn than before,
and was admitted to the hospital with Hol Horse!
Hol Horse and Boingo
Retire
Ba-dum tsh!
Shinjite iinoka?
Can I believe in ya?!
Shinjiteoyo!
You can believe in me!
Hol Horse Boingo konbi!
Hol Horse Boingo Duo!
Ore wa Hol Horse hajiki no tsukaite da
The name's Hol Horse an' I wield a pistol.
Card no anji wa Emperor
My card represents Emperor.
Tachi ichi niban tete
I'm always second in a pair.
Dareka to kunde kagayakunosa!
I'm a shinin' star with a partner by my side!
Dagayo koitsu de daijoubuka?
But am I really gonna be okay with this kid?
Boku wa Boingo manga de yogen
I'm Boingo and I can predict the future with my comic.
Totemo uchiki nandakedo yuuki wo dasuyo!
Even though I'm still really shy, I'm gonna be courageous now!
Oniichan no kataki wo utsunda
I gotta avenge my big bro!
Boku no manga no yochi wa
The predictions in my comic...
Zettai hyaku percento desu!
...are one hundred percent true!
Koride koride umaku iku(noka)
That's to say, that's to say, everything'll go our way!(?)
Toppyoshi monakute shinjirarenuze
It's so crazy I can hardly believe it!
Insatsu ni deta yogen wa
The prophecy written in the book...
Zettai nandesu, unmei nandesu
...is absolute and is always up to fate!
Yogen no toori koto sureba
If we do everythin' as that prophecy says...
Subete umaku iku
...everything'll go our way!
Shinjiru karanaa
I really believe in ya!
Hol Horse Boingo konbi!
Hol Horse Boingo Duo!
Shinjirundesu hai!
Just believe in me, indeed!
Okay Shinjiruze!
Okay, I believe in ya!
Hol Horse Boingo konbi!
Hol Horse Boingo Duo!
Unmei to iuu no wa
This thing known as fate...
Seikaku ni wa yometokenai mono sa
...is something you can never, ever really know for sure!
Next Episode
Iggy isn't exactly thrilled to be part of our group.
I am here to ask a favor of you.
No doubt about it, that's the mansion.
Come to think of it, where did Iggy go?
Ya gotta be kidding me.
Turning my back on some kid who likes dogs...
Episode 38
Pet Shop: The Gatekeeper of Hell Part 1