"What is that which in the morning goeth upon four feet;
upon two feet in the afternoon; and in the evening upon three?"
The guardian of the pyramids, the Sphinx,
would offer this riddle to travelers.
The answer is "Man."
Legend has it that those who were
unable to answer were devoured by the Sphinx.
Thirty thousand kilometers from Japan,
Jotaro and company have finally reached Cairo.
Cairo is immense.
Rather than searching aimlessly,
we should work our way from the outskirts towards the center.
We're finally here!
Jotaro and company finally made it to Cairo.
However, before they can reach the pyramid that is Dio,
a few more Sphinxes stand in their way.
Welcome, travelers. What would you like?
I have a question for you.
We're looking for the building in this picture.
Do you know where it is?
Joseph and company were exhausted.
Since their arrival, they had been locked
in a constant search for the building in the picture.
The picture was a spirit photo
Joseph managed to take of Dio's mansion.
Since Dio had relocated to a new hideout,
the Speedwagon Foundation lost track of his whereabouts.
Where could Dio have gone?
If they're unable to find him within the next several days,
Holly's life will come to an end.
Sirs, this is a café.
You must order something if you wish to stay.
We'll take four iced teas.
Never seen it.
Cairo has a population of six million...
...and there must be at least two or three million buildings.
Will we ever find him?
There must be someone...
Someone must know its whereabouts.
This building, huh?
I can't tell from this tiny picture.
Sorry, can't say I recognize it.
I see. Sorry to bother you.
Come on. Let's keep investigating.
That building... I know of it.
There's no mistaking it. It's that building.
Shiritai yo (nemutta monogatari ga)
Seeking out...
...the slumbering legend
Shakunetsu no (suna wo namidatete)
Scorching below us...
...the shifting sands
Shukumei wo (mata yobisamasu)
Our destiny...
...is awoken once again
Shuchaku no chi wo kogasu kamoku na honou
The tenacious blood that burns the silent flame
Obikiyoserareta kamigami no keshin
The manifestations of the Gods that have been called forth...
Osore wo shiranu ken ga tsuranuku
...we will fearlessly pierce with our swords!
Mezasu basho towa mada minu sadame
As we march towards an uncertain destiny...
Chikazuitekuru kessen no toki
...the final battle draws nearer!
Utsubeki period wa Star Platinum
And the one to end it all will be Star Platinum!
Hajimattashimatta monogatari ni ubawareta mama no toki ni
Our tale has begun and our time runs short
Ima owari wo tsugeru tame arukitsuzukeru Crusaders
To end it all the Crusaders must continue onwards!
Kuuhaku no last page ni sono kobushi wo tatakikome
Let loose your fists on this blank last page!
End of the world
End of the world...
Sono chi no kioku
...and the memories of your bloodline!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
Ora!
Episode 34: D'Arby the Gambler Part 1
D-Did you just say what I think you said?
It sounded like you said you knew about it!
Yes.
I'm absolutely certain I know of the building which you seek.
Come again? Really?!
This is excellent!
Yeah! It's pretty lucky that we found someone who recognized it from the picture!
Where is it? Please tell us!
Are you attempting to solicit the answer for free?
Y-You're right... I'm sorry.
I'll pay you ten pounds.
So, where is it?
I'm quite fond of gambling.
It's a cheap thrill.
I can never get enough.
That's why I've chosen to make my living from it.
Are you also fond of gambling?
I'm not sure what you're getting at...
If you don't like to gamble, simply say so.
I just want to know what you're talking about.
In that case... would you care to make a bet with me?
If you win, I'll reveal the location of that place for free.
A bet? I'm a pretty confident gambler,
but I don't have time for poker right now.
I'll throw in another twenty pounds if you tell us.
The wonderful thing about gambling is
you can bet on just about anything.
It will take just a moment of your time.
For example...
Look over there. See that cat?
Here's my bet; which piece of smoked fish will the cat go after first?
The right, or the left?
How is that? It's silly, but thrilling.
Hey! You're really pissing me off!
Just take the thirty pounds and tell us!
Polnareff, that's no way to bargain for information!
Okay, then I'll just have to gamble for it!
I choose the right one!
Good! Now we're having fun.
Then I shall bet on the left.
Hey, now...
Well, Jotaro? Do you not find him suspicious?
Yeah, he could be an enemy Stand user.
Though he might just be a compulsive gambler.
At the first sign of anything unusual,
defeat him with Star Platinum.
Gotcha.
By the way, if I lose, what do I gotta pay you?
Like, a hundred pounds?
I have no need for money.
How about your soul? I will have your soul.
Is he fucking with me? Cocky bastard...
The sooner I can get away from him, the better...
Your answer?
Yeah, okay, sure. That's fine.
Oh? The cat has taken notice of the smoked fish.
The right!
The kitty's going for the right one!
If I were a cat, I'd go for the bigger one!
The one on the right is definitely bigger!
You saw it.
It snatched the left piece before the right, then ran away.
I win.
Hey, you lost, Polnareff! What's your plan now?
I'm getting sick of asking people about that building!
Now, as we agreed upon, you must pay me.
Pay? With what?
Your soul.
That is what you gambled.
Your soul!
I am a Stand user who appropriates souls!
Gambling opens the way for the soul to leave its vessel.
My Stand's power is to steal it in that moment!
What?! What the hell?!
Polnareff!
Whoa, there! Don't kill me! It's too late!
If I were to die, Polnareff's soul
would be destroyed along with my Stand!
Polnareff!
H-Hey!
H-He has no pulse!
He is dead! Polnareff is dead!
Polnareff!
This is Polnareff's soul.
It is proof for Lord Dio that I have
rid him of one of his many nuisances.
Even though he was nothing more than a simple fool.
Allow me to finally introduce myself...
My name is D'Arby.
D-A-R-B-Y.
With an apostrophe after the D.
A Stand that steals the soul of anyone who loses a bet to its user!
Its name is Divine Osiris!
By the way, this is my cat.
Y-You cheater!
You have deceived us!
You call this gambling? More like cheating!
Cheating?
Listen here. The only reason you feel cheated is because you failed to see through my ruse.
I have a belief; gambling is much like a relationship
in which you must deceive your partner.
The one who sheds tears in the end is the loser.
Do you intend to kill me with your bare hands?
Very well. Go ahead.
But doing so will also destroy his soul!
Listen to me! You will not leave this place in one piece!
Do you remember what you were doing
on the night of September 22nd, 1984 at 11:15 PM?
What are you speaking of?
Because I certainly do.
Around that time in California, I was gambling with an American man
named Stephen Moor, and he said the exact words you just did.
This is him.
Surrounding him are his father and wife.
If you wish to win back Polnareff's soul,
your only option is to continue gambling with me.
Th-This man is a demon...
He's trying to take our souls one-by-one.
So what will you do?
Go home if you're too afraid...
...and leave Polnareff behind.
Well, have a drink and give it some thought.
Would you like some chocolate?
M-Mr. Joestar, what do you think you are doing?
You know what surface tension is, Barbie?
It's D'Arby. My name is D'Arby.
It's the force preventing that whiskey
from spilling out of the glass, correct?
What are you getting at?
The rules are simple.
We'll take turns dropping coins in the glass.
The one to make it overflow loses.
Hey, Gramps...
You cannot, Mr. Joestar!
I'll bet my soul!
Div
Divine
Divine Os
Divine Osir
D
Divine Osiris
Da
Dani
Danie
Daniel
Daniel J
Daniel J.
Daniel J. D'
Power: E
Speed: D
Range: D
Durability: C
Precision: D
Growth Potential: D
Daniel J. D'A
Daniel J. D'Ar
Daniel J. D'Arby
I'll bet my soul!
Good!
What?!
Inconceivable! You cannot! He is a cheater!
Then I won't let him cheat!
I'm the one who chose our bet!
Jotaro, make sure he doesn't try cheating.
Okay! This is fine. I accept your bet.
But first...
...will you allow me to inspect the coins and glass?
Of course you can.
You have the right to make sure I'm not cheating.
First things first, I want you to promise me that you'll return Polnareff's soul if you lose.
I pride myself as a professional gambler.
I will pay you in the event I lose. But I won't.
Fine, then you start. Drop a coin in.
Mr. Joestar!
Leave this to me.
I'm a master of the glass and coin game.
It's more difficult than it looks becase of the surface tension.
It should fit about eight or nine coins in total...
...so long as I remain calm and don't let my fingers shake.
May I put in more than one coin at a time?
If you can do it all at once.
Well, then...
F-Five coins?!
Hey, I think I just saw a ripple!
Quiet!
Keep your hands off the table!
Your turn.
You've got guts, dropping in five at once.
I'll start with one.
More than that is too risky.
Seriously, Gramps...
There's a piece of cotton between his finger and the coin...
...and liquid is dripping from it.
He's squeezing it into the whiskey.
And yet you told me to watch him for cheating?
You fucking cheater...
Not bad.
It's completely full!
Even a single coin will make it spill over! I won!
He said himself that it's not cheating unless you get caught!
This is bad for my heart! I was sure it would spill over.
Now it's your turn, Obie.
It's D'Arby! Quit messing up my name!
My name is D'Arby!
It is neither Obie nor Barbie!
Sorry, pal.
He's messing up his name on purpose to piss him off.
That's Gramps for ya...
A true gambler at heart.
Let's keep going.
It's your turn to put in a coin, D'Arby.
It's difficult to see with my shadow in the way.
I'll drop it in from this side of the table.
You can do it from wherever you like.
Because I cheated, it's already at the limit!
He'll never get it in, no matter what he tries!
It'll overflow if he so much as touches the surface!
I can tell you think the surface tension is at its limit.
You think it's impossible, right?
But you couldn't be more wrong...
I-Impossible! There's no way!
It definitely should have overflowed!
And just what do you mean by
"It definitely should have overflowed"?
As you can see, it went in.
I didn't see him trying to cheat.
I was keeping watch with Star Platinum.
He dropped the coin in fair and square.
No doubt about it.
B-But I made sure!
When I added the liquid to the whiskey,
I made sure it would overflow!
Why? Another one couldn't possibly have gone in!
How did he do it?!
Go ahead, Mr. Joestar!
Make it quick.
Or do you intend to wait until it evaporates?
I-I can't believe it...
Mr. Joestar!
Joestar knew deep down he had lost the bet!
That is why his soul emerged!
I, D'Arby, have won this gamble!
Polnareff, I'm sorry...
Holly... I can't save you anymore...
Mr. Joestar!
Gramps!
That makes two.
With that out of the way, let us continue gambling.
That is, assuming the two of you don't
run away with your tails between your legs.
You monster!
Will you ever learn?
If I die, their souls will be lost!
Curses!
Quit it, Abdul!
Hey! You'll have to leave if you want to make a scene!
Fuck off! Stay out of it.
Absolutely!
You figured it out too late, Jotaro.
Did he tamper with the glass?
This is how he got another coin in.
He left some chocolate on the bottom of the glass.
Before the game began, he asked to inspect
the coins and glass, and that's when he stuck it on.
As you are no doubt aware,
because you didn't catch it in time, it was not cheating.
H-How did you do it?
How is it that the chocolate allowed another coin to enter?
Even though it's melted now,
he stuck the chocolate to the bottom of the glass when it was solid.
He used just enough of it to tilt the glass up without us noticing.
This side will spill
Glass is tilted
But once the chocolate melted, the glass became level.
Surface tension becomes equal
Chocolate melts
Even with the surface tension at its limit,
he set it up so at least one more coin would fit.
W-What?!
B-But...
How was he was able to manipulate
the chocolate to melt at the right time?
He used the heat of the sun.
I never suspected it.
He moved to the side of the table, which caused
the sun's rays to directly hit the glass, melting the chocolate.
But it's fine.
D'Arby, prepare your trump card.
We'll finish this with poker.
Jotaro!
How amusing!
I happen to be a bona fide poker champion!
Poker?! This man was able to outsmart Mr. Joestar!
I-It is too dangerous!
I know.
He isn't violent, but he's definitely the most dangerous Stand user we've encountered so far.
Still...
I can't afford not to try!
Next Episode
I'll exchange three cards.
I'll exchange two cards.
He made no suspicious moves!
A good cheater knows to take advantage
of psychological blind spots.
Only one joker.
Now then, Jotaro...
Fine, I'll bet my soul.
Episode 35
D'Arby the Gambler Part 2