Long ago, there existed an extraordinary man wished for even more power.
He could live like the birds, dwell with the fish,
breathe like the trees, and move like the water.
But he could not face the sun.
So he created a stone mask.
One day he would conquer the sun.
And the world would be his!
Episode 26: "The Man Who Became A God"
Cars...
Did Cars land in the magma?!
You bastards...
We got him!
I-I need armor.
Like a clam or a crab...
...I'll make armor.
I'll cover myself.
It's not working!
It's melted rock, idiot!
It's over a thousand degrees!
You're gonna burn to a crisp!
So hot!
T-That did it!
Finally!
We finally took down Cars!
Jojo, that shock triggered an eruption!
Let's get to safety before celebrating!
Good idea. Hang on tight!
What a wonderful sound.
It's music to my ears.
I've been longing to hear that sound from you, Jojo!
Cars...but how?!
A bit of his shell.
I see. Cars...
First, Cars covered himself in a shell like a crab.
But it was still organic.
It couldn't withstand the magma's heat and burned away instantly.
Cars 's secret was in a second layer of armor!
That second layer...
... was bubbles!
The bubbles created a layer of air between Cars' body and the magma.
Heat from magma
Air
Body
As the outer layer burned, more bubbles came up to replace it.
This allowed Cars to survive in magma for a few minutes.
The Earth gave birth to life.
But now! Alas! In the end...
... Cars had conquered the Earth!
Long, long ago, far earlier than man's first recorded history
a certain group of creatures evolved on our planet.
They could only live at night, as they died when exposed to the sun.
So they lived below ground.
Even without the sun, they led long lives feeding on other living things.
Early humans that appeared feared them as gods or demons.
They rarely died, so they did not have many children and their population was small.
They knew no strife and lived in peace.
But then...
... a genius was born among them.
There is strength hidden in this body, abilities undreamed of.
I will unlock greater power!
The genius created a stone mask.
The mask granted him undying power, but he required more life energy.
He had to consume more creatures to live.
If left unchecked, he would eventually consume all life.
His brethren began to fear the mask and its gifted creator!
His existence is a threat!
He has to be removed from this world!
We have to destroy him!
Fool! Don't you wish to conquer the sun?
Don't you wish to rule over all?
Don't you wish to purge your fears?!
...If not, then disappear.
The genius slaughtered all his brethren, including the parents who raised him.
He and one companion took the two surviving babies and left.
They set off on a journey in search of ultimate power.
And ten thousand years later, that power was in his hands!
He's a god. He's become a god.
Humans can't stand before a god!
Submission is our only option!
What was that? Did you just say something, Jojo?
Take this!
Overdrive!
Rip...ple?
Did you say "Ripple Overdrive"?
Jojo!
That shock!
I'm melting! That's impossible!
My leg is melting!
What? It's like he used...!
It can't be!
It is! That was the Ripple, you dimwit!
I conquered the sun, and you still thought the Ripple was beyond me?!
W-What?!
And it looks like my Ripple is hundreds of times more potent than yours.
Hundreds of times more potent?!
That's just like being burned by the sun itself!
His flesh is liquefying and then vaporizing!
So how do you like that taste of your own medicine?
An excellent response.
Well, let me ease your suffering.
Jojo!
This is it. I'm going to die.
It's over for me.
Jojo accepted this fact completely.
He felt no fear, no pain, no regret.
He thought, "I did all I could. "
Before the epitome of evil, all he could do was watch as the cold reality of death approached.
Stroheim was no different.
Unable to move, he understood how it felt to be a frog about to be swallowed by a snake.
This breathing technique...
To send a Ripple-user like you into the black pit of death...
...what better method to use than the Ripple itself?!
The Ripple...
... far greater than mine...
Sail into the infinite abyss of oblivion!
The Ripple?!
What?!
The Red Stone!
The Red Stone of Aja!
Why did Jojo hold the Red Stone toward Cars?
Even he didn't know!
It was merely instinctive. He felt the Red Stone being drawn toward the Ripple.
But Jojo's body understood.
His body was always moving unconsciously to keep him alive.
Jojo's will to live pushed his body into action!
T-The Red Stone is a Ripple amplifier.
That energy made the volcano's eruption reach a sudden peak!
T-The whole slab they were on was blasted into the sky!
S-Such tremendous force!
But do you think a little eruption will be enough to get rid of me, Jojo?!
I'll become a bird to escape!
Goodbye forever, Jojo!
That's the power of the Earth for you! It shot my arm all the way up here!
Now, Cars!
Your next line is, "Was this all part of your plan, Jojo?!"
Was this all part of your pl-
For an instant, Cars was distracted by Jojo's arm and taunt! This instant would seal Cars' fate!
Hot chunks of rock he could have dodged launched him higher!
Was this all part of your plan, Jojo?!
You're god damn right it was! I planned every little detail...
From the very beginning!
That's a total lie, but I'll say anything to piss off Cars, heh!
The material released in the eruption reached escape velocity!
If even the Earth's power couldn't kill Cars...
It would instead banish him to the depths of space!
Stars?! I-Impossible!
It 's over.
Granny...
Stroheim...
Uncle Speedwagon...
Smokey...
And Lisa Lisa...
Farewell... everyone.
Jo...
Jojo!
Eight hours later, Stroheim was recovered alive, and reported the following to Speedwagon:
Feb
February
February 28,
February 28, 1939
Jo
Jose
Josep
Joseph
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Joseph Joes
Joseph Joesta
Joseph Joestar
O
On
On I
On Iso
On Isola
On Isola di
On Isola di Vu
On Isola di Vul
On Isola di Vulca
On Isola di Vulcano
Has
Has Died
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
Has Died...
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
On Isola di Vulcano
February 28, 1939
Joseph Joestar
I'm in outer space?!
I'll use jets of air to change my trajectory and return to Earth!
I-It's not working!
I-I'm freezing!
The air is freezing around me!
It turns to ice the moment it comes out of me!
I-I can't change direction!
I can't go back!
Cars would never return to Earth.
He became something between animal and mineral, has he floated through space forever.
And though he wished for death, he was unable to die.
Eventually Cars simply stopped thinking.
Outside New York City, April 1939
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
on earth, as it is in heaven.
Goodbye, Jojo.
Now that I think of it, we only met six months ago.
But I'll always remember you.
Always.
Come, Erina, you mustn't catch cold.
Let's go home.
Just a bit longer.
Guess who?
Hey, everybody!
I finally got to New York and nobody was there to meet me!
So I heard you were all at a funeral. I looked high and low!
Hey, Master Lisa Lisa! Are you all healed up?
Messina, you're here too!
I wanted to ask Stroheim if he could beef up my hand with some cooler gadgets.
But it looks like the Germans were called to war.
Hey, now! What are you thinking?!
This is a funeral, you idiot!
Who's an idiot?!
Hey, did you just call me an idiot?!
Just calm down. Let's go have a talk.
You're causing trouble for these nice folks.
It's...
No way!
Hey! Don't start any trouble!
You aren't getting away with calling me an idiot!
Jojo!
Jojo's alive!
Alive?
H-Hang on, now! What's with all the surprise?
It's like you've seen a ghost!
What?! Why's my name on a headstone?!
D-Don't tell me this is...
Jojo!
You're still recovering, so you shouldn't stand in the rain!
Take this.
I-It's Suzi Q.
What's that ring on her finger?
Y-You don't know about my wife, either?!
Your wife?!
Your wife? Oh, my!
Being introduced as your wife...
It makes me blush!
Right?
Don't "right" me!
Hey... back when the volcano erupted...
... the rock I was on shielded me and fell into the sea.
A Venetian fishing boat picked me up.
Then you nursed me back to health in Venice for two weeks.
But no one knows any of that!
You sent that telegram, right?!
T-Telegram?
Yeah, you said you would!
Could you stop with the clickity clicks?
I'm sorry! I forgot!
Oh, no! Unbelievable!
What is that woman thinking?!
Get back here!
Jojo is alive!
I said I'm sorry!
Sorry doesn't cut it!
Jojo...
Elizabeth Joestar
Lisa Lisa, a.k.a. Elizabeth Joestar, later told Jojo that she was his mother...
While traveling back to America.
In 1948, she married a Hollywood screenwriter.
Erina Joestar
Erina Joestar continued her work as a teacher.
In 1950, at age 81, she died peacefully, surrounded by her loved ones.
Robert E. O. Speedwagon
Robert E. O. Speedwagon continued with his various enterprises
and helped to further American science and medicine.
In 1952, he died of a heart attack at age 89.
He was never married.
Smokey Brown worked his way through college, majoring in political science.
Smokey Brown
and became the first black mayor in Georgia, his home state.
Rudolf von Stroheim never saw Jojo again.
In 1943, he died as a proud German soldier, fighting in the Battle of Stalingrad.
Rudolf von Stroheim
...the best in the world!
And so, time marches forward...
JFK International Airport, New York, 1987
... towards a new generation.
And Jojo...
Oh, I bumped you. Are you okay?
Oh, dear. You should watch where you're going.
You're right. I'm fine though.
We all make mistakes.
Wait a minute. Are you Japanese?
Yeah, why?
Well that changes everything!
Alitalia flight 285 for Tokyo is now boarding.
I repeat. Alitalia flight 285 for Tokyo is now boarding.
My only daughter has been married to a Japanese man for over 20 years now.
Why did she get married on the other side of the world?
I bet my own grandson wouldn't even recognize my face!
Unforgivable! I hate the damn Japanese!
Although...
...these Walkman things are pretty cool.
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
Part 2: Battle Tendency
The End
Atlantic Ocean, near the Canary Islands, 1983
Y-Yahoo! We finally got it!
R-Relax! Just bring it up!
It's a hundred-year-old treasure chest!
L-Let's pop it open!
Some-Stuffs
Original Translation:
Timing:
Typesetting:
Editor:
Quality Check:
Encoding:
Raw Provider:
Mudasubs (Episode 1-14)
Retail (Episode 15-26)
Fadeout4
Tonitonichopchop
Mazrim
Fadeout4
Wrrry