Caesar Zeppeli was born in Naples,
son of the famous furniture maker, Mario.
His father was a proper Italian, dedicated to his family.
To Caesar, Mario was the ideal man.
When Caesar was ten years old, Mario left without a word.
They were motherless, and their distant relatives stole all they had.
Caesar became violent, and grew to hate his father.
I bet he's living carefree with some woman!
I'll find him and kill him!
Caesar threw away both his youth and his future.
He committed theft, arson, muggings, assault...
everything short of murder.
Even the Mafia feared him.
Hey kid, you're Caesar, right? What's your last name?
I don't have one!
Then you aren't Italian. Real Italians are proud of their families.
Never holding back, he started fights with his wrench.
With his foe stunned, he finished them off with a single blow!
Though he didn't know it, Caesar was already using the Ripple.
Then, at age sixteen in Rome...
No mistake, It's him!
Caesar resolved to murder his own father.
However!
W-What is that?!
A diamond! That's definitely a diamond!
Boy, don't touch that stone!
You!
W-What's the wall doing?
S-Stay back... It's a trap!
Caesar knew nothing of the truth.
He knew nothing of the tragic death of his late grandfather,
Will A. Zeppeli, at the hands of the Stone Mask fifty years ago.
Mario had taken on his legacy by training in the Ripple,
eventually leading him to discover these ruins.
He searched the globe looking for a way
to defeat the monsters in the wall.
But Caesar never knew any of this.
Young man... I beg of you...
Find a woman in Venice named Lisa Lisa.
She is the only one capable of stopping them.
Perhaps because Caesar had grown, Mario did not recognize his son.
Fa...
Caesar realized his father had left to keep his children safe from this dreadful affair.
Hurry... hurry, you must go!
Father!
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Timing:
Fadeout4
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 20: "Caesar's Lonely Youth"
I see...
Caesar's misunderstanding led to his hatred...
...which in turn became pride for his father and family.
So Caesar picked up where his father had left off.
So it was Cars who killed Caesar's father...
Forgive me, Caesar.
I didn't mean to speak ill of your family.
If you want to go in there to fight despite it being a trap...
...then you must have found a way to beat Cars.
I've changed my mind!
If you're going in, then I'm right behind you...
...Caesar Zeppeli!
One set of footprints went inside.
W-Who was that?
I swear I saw someone!
Am I seeing things?
No, that's not an illusion!
What the hell is that?!
Caesar?
He vanished!
But I know he's here somewhere!
He can only be a few steps away!
Does Cars have a new technique?
No, the sun is too strong.
He can't be outside!
The Cat Stance, an element of kenpo.
Caesar has never once heard of kenpo.
He relaxed his limbs,
ready to attack without losing his speed or rhythm!
He did all of this reflexively.
Caesar!
What are you doing? Going to this hotel alone is madness!
Stay back, instructor!
I can't move, let alone go inside.
Something is hiding in the entrance!
What's that?
I can't see a-
It's a footprint!
He jumped!
He's coming from above!
I-It's...
...Wham!
Instructor Messina!
What the hell? That was Wham!
Are he and Cars here together?
But how is Wham able to be outside during the day?
He almost looks like a ghost.
Where is that smart-mouthed trickster?
Jojo...
I hear he's learned much.
Where is the man who killed Master AC/DC?
Wind... I see, Wham can control the wind.
The wind is making him transparent.
Air is coming from those pipes in his chest.
It's only slightly visible because of water vapor.
I've got it!
He's cloaking himself in vapor from those pipes!
It's refracting the light off him.
It's like a suit that bends light, protecting him from the sun!
That's why he's transparent!
I see Jojo isn't here.
You're the bubble-user Caesar, correct?
Just by looking at you, I can see you've also learned much.
Very well. You are worthy of death
at the hands of the mighty Wham!
We'll just see who dies!
Right now, I feel the same way I did back in those slums!
Just like when you killed my father!
I'll use my rage to destroy you!
Don't think your wind will just blow my bubbles away!
I've got bubbles that can even slice through wind!
I updated my grandfather Zeppeli's Ripple Cutter!
Bubble Cutter!
High speed rotation turns the bubble cutters into disks!
My Ripple ensures they won't pop!
Wham, the wind protecting you is just air to them!
Instead of defending you, it will draw the bubbles in!
His skill with the Ripple is far greater than I expected.
Damn Ripple Warrior!
Hold it! I won't let you enter the hotel!
Bubble Cutter: Gliding!
Now, while you're off balance...
...I'll give you a Ripple kick!
But Caesar was in for a shock!
Normally, if your legs give out, you try not to fall.
Especially if you need to escape into the hotel from the sunlight.
However, Wham...
...fell backwards on purpose!
He's not just an immortal monster!
With senses like that, he's a genius fighter as well!
But my Bubble Cutter must have done some damage.
The advantage is mine!
I have a way to beat you inside the hotel!
My nerves are honed to a razor edge.
I can even feel subtle changes in the air.
I have the same intense feeling I had when I was in the slums.
My breathing is normal. I'm not sweating.
Perfect Ripple conditions!
Instructor Messina!
Taken off your coat, have you, Wham?
They're gone, both Caesar and Messina!
Are they already inside the hotel?
T-That's...
What happened?
Take this, Wham!
Bubble Launcher!
I said that won't work!
Bubble Cutter!
Running?!
I refuse to run or hide!
Bubble Cutter!
Take this, Wham!
Bubble Cutter: Gliding!
Wham!
No more games!
It's over!
Holy Sand-
Stop and look around you!
My Bubble Cutters are now Bubble Lenses floating in the air!
Lenses?
And that hole you knocked in the wall
is like the open shutter of a camera!
The lenses send sunlight...
...right into the hotel!
What?!
You can't move!
You're film! A frozen film!
You're completely exposed, Wham!
Trying your barrier again?
I won't let you!
I'll finish you off with a direct Ripple blast!
One point...
...at one moment.
A tiny miscalculation.
Caesar's body created a shadow at a single point!
Wham immediately took advantage of this mistake!
He showed Caesar once again that he was a fighting genius!
Wind Mode! Holy Sandstorm!
S-Such destruction!
I-It couldn't be!
It's Wham's Holy Sandstorm!
So that means Caesar is-!
You've grown so much.
I am satisfied.
I haven't had such a fight in ages...
...warrior of the Ripple.
And it was such a close fight...
If my wind hadn't the strength to blow away your lenses...
...I have no idea how I could have stopped the light.
And if Master Cars, who cannot use wind, had met you here first...
...and met your power...
Even if he had won...
...he would be in much worse shape than I am now.
Don't.
You will not fight again.
My Holy Sandstorm has shredded your body.
Stop. The battle is done.
You have no more Ripple.
See?
You've almost bled out.
Understand that this means you have no hope.
Stop.
Goodbye.
Your life has ended.
What?!
My piercing with the antidote. Why?
I-I'm... not afraid to die.
But I am a proud member of the Zeppeli family...
It's in my blood...
Something like this might mean nothing
to an inhuman monster like you...
My father didn't recognize me, but he sacrificed his life to save mine.
My grandfather gave his Ripple energy
to Jojo's grandfather, Jonathan, before he died.
It's tradition. I have to do something.
I can't let my life's flame sputter out...
This is the Zeppeli family spirit, from the past to the future!
It's the human spirit!
Jojo, this is the last of my Ripple!
Take it!
That's Caesar's voice!
Did you hear him?
Yes.
But Caesar can't be-!
Caesar!
He made a bubble from his blood...
It must have taken all of his Ripple to make it.
He saved it for this moment,
for his friends, rather than using it on me.
Let them have it.
It's not because I'm sentimental like humans.
His talent as a fighter was profound.
He has my respect as a fellow warrior.
I will hold you forever in my memory, Caesar.
A man as splendid and as fleeting as his bubbles.
T-This place is in ruins!
Wham's Holy Sandstorm must have done this!
And Caesar was caught in it.
A bubble...
C-Could it be...
It can't!
It's Caesar's bandana!
And...
A piercing! Wham's lip piercing!
The feeling of this Ripple energy...
It... It can't be!
I haven't called Caesar's name since we got here.
It was because I was afraid.
If I cried out his name and there was no response...
If the only response was silence... That's what scared me.
I couldn't accept it.
So I didn't call him...
But now I know.
The Ripple in that bubble told me everything.
Caesar, just moments ago...
...died right here.
Caesar, you bastard. You were a showoff 'till the end.
Leaving a gift like this...
Caesar, where are you?!
Where are you sleeping?!
I'll find you! I'll dig you up! Caesar!
Jojo!
We don't have time to waste searching or grieving for Caesar.
What?!
There are two of them and two of us. Two versus two.
And the only thing we know by that blood trail
is that Caesar badly injured Wham.
We're in enemy territory.
Let's go and finish it!
Jojo, come on.
Take the antidote, then we'll hunt them.
T-This woman...
Not even a single tear for Caesar?!
Master Lisa Lisa...
...your cigarette's backwards.
Lisa Lisa is our master, she has to keep a calm demeanor.
I know she wants to cry much more than I do...
He treated her like a goddess, and knew her much longer than I did.
I have to hold my feelings back.
Caesar, I know you thought I was self-centered...
But just now, I understood how someone else was feeling.
I guess I'm a little more mature.
However, I'll show no sympathy when I fight these beasts!
I've inherited your fighting spirit!
It... It's blood...
Caesar... right here...
Caesar...
Caesar!
This is enemy territory. Cars and Wham are nearby.
But neither of them could hold it in.
Jojo cried out Caesar's name.
Lisa Lisa shed tears of pain and sorrow.
But their cries were only answered by cold silence.
Caesar was gone.
For Jojo and Lisa Lisa, the silence only confirmed the truth.
Though his body had died, his soul lived on.
Rest in peace, Caesar Zeppeli.
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
They stand there
Twenty four before my love and I'll be there
Next Episode
I'm in a bad mood.
I'll hug you to death!
We fight tonight, under the full moon.
You have no tomorrow!
Fight alongside me, Caesar!
Episode 21:
"One-Hundred Versus Two"