This building was originally a 14th-century castle.
It was converted into a hotel in the early 1900s.
Ten years ago, it was closed after its owner suddenly died.
Now it's been turned into a shelter from the sun by Cars.
The enemy lurks within, but Jojo and Lisa Lisa know nothing of the hotel's layout!
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Timing:
Fadeout4
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 21: "One Hundred Versus Two"
Damn it!
What's with the creepy cobwebs?
This place needs cleaning!
It's already depressing enough without these decorations!
But just look at this trail of blood...
Wham took a heavy beating from the Ripple.
Caesar didn't go down without a fight.
We can't let him recover from this!
We're going in, Master Lisa Lisa!
What is it?
W-Well...
T-This doorknob feels really strange...
It felt like I was grabbing some guy's hand.
I'm not a door, man!
Huh?!
What are you looking for, man? I said I'm not a door, man!
A vampire!
Look out, Jojo!
Jojo!
If it weren't for that weapon, I'd have peeled your face right off!
The name's Wired Beck, man.
I killed my lover and escaped from prison.
But then Lord Cars made me part of his gang with a mask, man.
He has my loyalty, man.
I'm not gonna to let you waltz in and disturb Lord Cars' rest, man.
Those fiends! So they're already unleashing their hounds on people?!
Gimme a break.
You're just a pawn damned for Hell.
Here, let me give you a little push into the abyss!
Lisa Lisa?
Beautiful, man! Magnificent, man! Your skin's so smooth, man!
Come here! Let me drink your life through that skin, man!
I'm in a bad mood.
I don't want to hear or see a thing from a lowlife like you.
But if you want to grab me, just try.
It will be the last thing you ever do.
Spikes!
So that's what those are!
They're not fingers, they're spikes!
He's covered in wire-like body hair!
I don't like it when women joke at my expense, man.
Girls who laugh at me get punished, man!
I'll give you a little squeeze!
I'll hug you to death, man!
Yikes! He's faster than I thought!
Her scarf!
I see. Lisa Lisa's scarf becomes a Ripple-infused weapon!
What's with the scarf?
You wanna catch me?
Don't make me laugh, man!
And now I'm free, man!
Uh... What?
Where are you going, man?
Come, Jojo. Let's move.
Uh, okay.
Lisa Lisa's movements flow like silk...
She doesn't waste any effort!
Hey, quit ignoring me, man!
Hey, you!
A woman like that deserves to be punished, right?
Oh no, man. Your time is up, man.
You're the one who's getting punished, man.
You got a dose of the Ripple, man.
Don't be ridiculous, ma-
She really is as strong as I thought!
I thought she'd be weak in a fight, but she's better than me!
I'm impressed!
As expected from my Ripple master!
By the way, Jojo...
You still haven't taken the antidote Caesar won for you, have you?
This?
Why?
I'll drink it after I beat Wham.
This ring isn't just a promise between Wham and I anymore.
Now it represent a promise to Caesar to fight and keep living.
Lisa Lisa, will you hold onto it for me until I need it?
No.
You should keep it.
There's no telling what might happen to me.
As they went deeper, Wham's trail of blood grew even thinner.
Jojo and Lisa Lisa were fully aware what this meant...
Wham's wounds were healing!
They're here.
I've been waiting.
You've grown quite a lot.
Bastard, you killed Caesar!
Look at the floor, Jojo. You need to forget about Wham for now.
Don't worry. My head is cool.
I noticed it, too. The footprints, right?
There are two sets.
That means Cars is here! Where is he?!
Quit hiding and show your face!
Yes, two sets of footprints.
Even though I feel the breathing lungs
of dozens of people in this room!
It's her. I see...
You're quite composed and perceptive for a woman.
I can see how Jojo and Caesar learned so much in such a short time.
And you're even capable of feeling such slight breathing.
You're among the finest of the Ripple warriors.
W... What the-?!
Y-You guys, you're all vampires, aren't you? Dammit!
No response? How creepy!
Cars!
Lord Cars gave us, his chosen few, eternal life!
It's one-hundred against two!
When our master gives the order,
we'll tear you both to shreds, Jojo!
T-This is bad. One-hundred on two...
Lisa Lisa, we can't win this one!
Wait, Lord Cars!
Back in Rome, we promised to fight each other.
I want to avenge Master AC/DC.
Please allow me to fight.
I shall not.
Our goal is to obtain the Red Stone of Aja.
Never forget that, Wham.
Right...
That's right! There's no way! I don't even feel like it anymore.
I'm pretty sure I could beat you anyway.
But even if I did, I've still got all these vampires hanging out...
Win or lose, it's lights out for me, right?
With those odds, giving up is the only rational choice.
I'm throwing in the towel.
Shit! Did you all just see that?
And here I thought I could zap them all at once.
Right, kill the both of them!
If you kill us, you'll never have the Red Stone.
Hold it!
What was that, woman?
I'm not so naive that I would bring the Red Stone here with me.
If neither I nor Jojo are at a certain location at a specific time...
...the Red Stone will be destroyed by a time bomb!
Woman, don't try this with me.
Are you that confident that you'll be able to find it in time?
The bomb itself is tiny,
but more than enough to destroy the Red Stone.
Is there really a time bomb? She never mentioned this...
I'll just run with it!
Yeah, it's all true!
If we die, it goes boom! Kaboom!
Even so, we can't let you out of here alive.
I have a suggestion.
Jojo and Wham can fight one-on-one.
And myself and Cars will also fight one-on-one.
And to the winner... goes the Red Stone!
What?!
The victor will win the Stone and their future.
It will all be clear.
Who will hold the Red Stone, you or us?
Who will survive? The Pillar Men or humankind?
Damn woman!
Wham!
It's laughable, Lord Cars.
S-She's good!
Lisa Lisa... She's a far better gambler than I could ever dream to be.
Woman, you have gumption.
Very well! We will fight for the Red Stone.
Just don't delude yourselves!
You have no tomorrow!
She just turned our luck around to give us more-or-less even odds!
All right, then. Let's do it!
We need a proper time and place for our battle.
Wham, your thoughts?
We fight tonight, under the full moon!
The place will be at the foot of Mt. Piz Berlina,
fifteen kilometers southeast of here.
We shall meet at the ancient stone circle
named Skeleton Heel Stone.
Many warriors have found either death or glory in that place.
A stone circle?
Hey, you can't just pick a place that suits your fancy!
Wham, that's an interesting choice.
Now, about the Red Stone...
Jojo!
Bring the Red Stone to the stone circle at midnight tonight.
And be sure that bomb is removed.
The woman stays here as insurance!
Lisa Lisa!
They don't want us to run.
It's a reasonable request. Jojo, go and fetch the Red Stone.
Don't worry about me.
Right. I'll see you at the arena.
Trust me.
I do.
Caesar...
Until yesterday, I lived only thinking of myself.
But there's a new feeling burning inside me now...
Is this compassion?
Damn it! I just want to wreck those bastards!
I'll do it for Caesar, Messina, Lisa Lisa and for everyone else!
I'll fight for all of you!
As I thought, there's no bomb at all.
Lisa Lisa, you're deceptive, even under pressure!
Now, maybe I should bring you a change of panties, hmm?
Whyat are these photos?
It's Granny Erina!
Why would Lisa Lisa have this?
Who are these people?
May 1889?
It's fifty years old!
This young man is Speedwagon!
Granny Erina!
And Straits is holding a baby!
Lisa Lisa... That's right,
I really know nothing about her life or her past!
Why does she have these photos?
It's the real thing.
We accept your bargain.
We'll fight you one-on-one!
Now that you've seen these photos,
I guess I owe you an explanation.
Actually, I had planned to tell you before the fight.
Just who are you?
Fifty years ago...
Erina lost her husband, Jonathan Joestar, on a ship sailing the Pacific.
He was your grandfather.
That day, your grandmother Erina saved a baby girl's life.
That was me.
The baby in that picture is me.
H-Hang on now.
That was fifty years ago!
If you were a baby fifty years ago...
H-Hey! How old are you, anyway?!
Y-You're fifty?!
I... I... If you're fifty, that means you're a...
...g-g-gran-!
Right? Normally...
Y-You look like you're in your late 20s...
They say Ripple energy is full of life and keeps you young...
But I guess this is why you don't behave like a young woman at all.
Ah, I think I see a wrinkle behind those shades!
Just kidding!
Now, prepare the arena!
Light the fires!
There's no time to talk now.
It will wait until later.
You and I share common roots.
Roots?
The stone mask killed my parents.
Since Erina was pregnant when she rescued me...
...I was raised by Straits.
A-Are you serious? By Straits?
Straits taught me about the Ripple.
Straits gave me the Red Stone.
S-So... Straits is your foster father!
It's tragic that the fear of aging drove Straits to such madness.
Jojo, my feelings about you killing him are complicated...
...but it feels like it was destiny.
What can I say?
I-It really is complicated.
What a bizarre relationship!
Lisa Lisa carries a past full of sadness...
Jojo, we're out of time.
W-What's that rumbling?
They're here. Now the battle can begin.
T-They're-!
Outta the way! I could give a damn if I crush ya!
I-Is that a d-dinosaur?!
N-No, horse! It's a horse!
Lord Cars, Lord Wham, please move!
They've gone mad!
Lord Wham, please!
What fine steeds.
We used masks to turn these horses into vampires.
V-Vampire horses?!
In this arena, Jojo will face Wham in an ancient-style chariot duel!
A chariot duel?!
A true ancient Roman death match!
You'll ride through the arena while you fight!
Lord Wham or Jojo? Who will fall or be beaten down while riding?
Defeat means death!
That's the rules, Jojo!
These beasts have the power of 150 horses!
Even Lord Wham has difficulty controlling them.
Hey, wait a minute!
I'll fight you wherever the hell you want...
...but vampire horses are your minions, right?!
Worry not. The reins conduct the Ripple.
Wham will use his strength.
You can use the Ripple to control them.
S-Seriously? They look pretty vicious!
Watch out! Hey!
I see. Even a little Ripple does it.
Wham! Wham! Wham! Wham!
Wham chose an ancient form for this battle.
He must be serious about this.
He's not doing this for fun, or even trying to make a sport of it.
Beat him, Jojo. We have to win this.
There are no draws!
Wham!
I haven't taken this antidote yet!
I promised Caesar I'd drink it after I killed you!
That promise will give me power I've never seen before!
Fight alongside me, Caesar!
Lets start this chariot duel!
Along the drifting cloud, the eagle searching down on the land
Catching the swirling wind, the sailor sees the rim of the land
The eagle's dancing wings create, as weather spins out of hand
Go closer hold the land, feel partly no more than grains of sand
We stand to lose all time, a thousand answers by in our hand
Next to your deeper fears, we stand surrounded by million years
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out and out
Next Episode
Wham! Wham! Wham! Wham!
Start!
Episode 22:
"A True Warrior"