Using Caesar 's bandana, Jojo barely defeated Wham.
Next, Lisa Lisa faced off against Cars.
Stroheim and Speedwagon appeared suddenly with help.
However, in a cowardly turn, Cars used a double to fight.
He sprang out and stabbed Lisa Lisa in the back.
Jojo and Lisa Lisa are in the greatest peril of their lives!
Cars, you bastard! I hope you rot in hell forever!
Jojo doesn 't know.
He doesn 't know that that woman is his own mother!
Don't let go, Jojo.
It's a forest of crystal spikes below. She'd die instantly.
C-Cars!
Your soul is as rotten as a pumpkin left in a field that even flies won't visit!
Shout at me. Grumble at me. Insult me.
While you're holding that rope, that's all you can really do.
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Timing:
Fadeout4
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 24: "The Link to Jojo"
Jojo! Lisa Lisa!
Jojo doesn't realize his mother's life is in his hands!
Mr. Speedwagon, we should tell him!
No.
Why not?!
It's not the time.
Stroheim, are you done with the vampires?!
We have to help Jojo!
Give me a break!
You think we can get rid of them in just a minute or two?!
Get out of my sight!
It's no good. They need more time!
Jojo...
Careful, the rope will slip if you don't watch it.
While you're holding the rope, your hasty feet can only move so far.
He kicked Cars, but the Ripple didn't flow into him!
W-We're in a real fix!
Looks like your Ripple is running dry.
You might have just enough for one last, all-out attack.
I'll just stroll up to you and take your life like I'm plucking a flower.
Cars!
It's true I might have barely enough in me for one final attack.
I'm not exactly confident.
But even so, I've come up with a plan.
It's something to make you choke!
Do you want to know what it is?
I won't tell you!
Hey!
You're not tying any ropes together!
This is a match!
What do you think I'll do with it?
Wh-What is Jojo up to?
He set his scarf on fire!
Before this fire burns me, I'll use all I've got left to send you packing!
The fire is a gamble!
It's a risk to motivate me!
I seek life within death!
Jojo...
An act like that...
...reeks of desperation!
Don't toy with me.
You're just dodging around in order to catch your breath.
I'll say it again: I want to kill you at my leisure.
I won't swing around like Tarzan!
Come on, now! I need to breathe!
Who cares if I look silly?
Listen.
I can cut Lisa Lisa's rope whenever I please.
And if you dodge again, I will!
Is that all right?
Should I cut the rope?
You want me to do it?
You don't, do you?
Don't!
You ran before. Now come to me, slowly.
If you want me to cut the rope, stay where you are.
The coward!
What's your choice?
Is your life more precious than this woman's?
Here's my choice!
I don't know what you're planning, but if I cut this, you'll fall as well!
You fool!
Jojo!
Lisa Lisa!
Idiot. That's two birds with one cut.
What the...?!
He...!
This rope is connected to Jojo!
When did he do it?!
He didn't have the time!
When he first kicked, he let himself be cut along with the rope!
While he lit the match, he secretly tied his leg to her rope and made a loop.
He needed a distraction.
So he set his scarf on fire.
And then to tie the ropes together, he let Lisa Lisa be cut down on purpose!
That cunning devil!
Now you're holding me and Lisa Lisa up!
You deceived me, Jojo!
I never thought I'd hear that from you!
It seems you like tricking, but you hate to be tricked!
You may have lived for over 10,000 years.
But to compete with my skills, you need another decade!
Cars!
Your time is up!
Ripple Overdrive!
D-Did it work?
T- That was the last of my Ripple.
I'm burned out.
Idon 't have any Ripple left.
I-It got into him!
Yes!
He did it! He hit Cars with the Ripple!
Off you go!
You...
Look! Cars fell into the crystal spikes!
He's finished! See?
The Ripple will travel right up his arm!
You're weak! Your time is up!
Even we could finish you now!
He's trying to spook us.
All right! Let's eliminate him for good!
Bring out the UV amplifier!
Yes, sir!
Master Lisa Lisa...
Cars said he didn't quite kill you.
I don't think he hit anything vital.
If we act quickly, I'm sure you'll live through this.
It's finally over.
It is. I'm glad.
Hey, Mr. Speedwagon?
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why did Granny Erina tell Jojo his mother died when he was little?
Why does Lisa Lisa hide her past from him?
Smokey, that's...
Granny Erina told me not to ask you, but I have to know!
She's his mother. Keeping that from him is awful.
Smokey...
Jojo and Granny Erina are my friends.
They saved me from crooked cops, even though I was just a thief.
That's why I'm here! I'll do all I can to help.
All right, Smokey.
I'll tell you.
You did take good care of Erina while I was away from New York, after all.
But promise not to tell Jojo!
This is a Joestar family issue. It's not our place to talk about it.
The name "Lisa Lisa" is an alias.
Her real name is Elizabeth.
She was raised by a Ripple-user named Straits.
She and Erina 's son, George, fell in love and got married.
George and Elizabeth had a son. You know him as Jojo.
Jojo 's father George was a member of the Royal Flying Corps.
A viation developed rapidly during the First World War.
George was among the first brave pilots to fly into battle.
He stood out as a hero even among the Royal Flying Corps.
However...
... a gut-wrenching horror from the past came back to haunt the Joestars.
Fifty years before, a vampire named Dio had created a legion of blood-sucking zombies.
Straits, myself and the others thought we had exterminated them.
But one had escaped, hid within society, and lived for decades undiscovered!
This zombie was a cunning, intelligent creature.
He created no spawn.
He ate even the bones and hair of his victims, leaving no evidence.
And by some wicked twist of fate...
... he worked as a commander in the Royal Flying Corps!
T-The Royal Flying Corps? With Jojo's father?
That's right.
George uncovered his secret.
He had listened well to Straits and me.
But ultimately, George was just an ordinary man.
He had character and talent, but he hadn't trained with the Ripple.
Before he could unmask the commander, he was discovered and attacked!
His message to Straits wasn't in time.
George's death was covered up as a nighttime plane crash.
Straits and I found this suspicious, and eventually found the truth.
That night, I told Elizabeth as she held an infant Jojo.
Instead of showing grief...
... she flew out of the house!
She was a genius with the Ripple, but her emotions consumed her!
She was witnessed when she killed the commander.
The military didn't know about zombies or the Ripple.
They concluded that Elizabeth had attacked their beloved commander, killed him, and burned his body.
Soon she was known around the world as a murderer and national traitor.
We used all the Speedwagon Foundation's resources to cover her trail.
Elizabeth had to leave England behind...
without even a word to her son.
Erina knew what had happened, and she had a request.
When this child grows up and asks about his parents...
...please tell him they both died.
This child...
And so Elizabeth became Lisa Lisa.
Why?
Why is it that way?
At least tell him his mother is alive!
I know painfully well why.
Erina lost her husband and son in the battle between the Ripple and the masks.
But thinking of her grandson Joseph... of Jojo...
...she didn't want the Ripple in his life!
Lisa Lisa felt the same way!
Such a tragic family.
Such a miserable fortune.
But now...
Now Jojo...
Jojo used the Ripple to save his mother's life!
Mr. Speedwagon...
Now there's no reason for Lisa Lisa to hide.
Jojo knows about the Ripple, and he used it to save his mother!
True.
But it's not up to me.
We have to know how Erina and Lisa Lisa feel first.
But...
Colonel!
We're ready to fire!
Right! Aim it right at him!
We will have the honor of executing Cars!
Behold, Cars!
I can't tell you how good it feels to give this order myself!
Don't, Stroheim! The mask!
The Stone is in his mask! UV light will help him!
D-Damn it!
Stop! Don't fire the UV amplifier!
N-No!
I-I didn't see him holding the mask.
I didn't see him put the Red Stone in!
Dear God...
Cars...
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
We spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley... hey!
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
there with you
Next Episode
The ultimate life form...
He can manipulate life at will!
Is there no way to stop him?
Cars, the Ultimate Being, is born!
Episode 25:
"Birth of the Ultimate Being"