Rome
What the hell is this?!
Trying to feed me spaghetti somebody dropped their pen in, huh?!
N-No sir... This is pasta with Nero sauce,
which gets its color from fresh squid ink.
What?
It's quite good!
Tasty! It's so good!
It's just great!
Standards have sunk so low at this hotel.
They'll let in the most tasteless people.
Signorina, I have a gift for you.
How beautiful!
Every night, before you go to bed,
I'd like you to think of me when you take this off.
Oh no!
How can this lecher say all that with a straight face?!
The garbage he's spewing is making my nose burn!
Now, please take it...
I'll enchant this... and it will make you fall under the spell of my love.
I hate guys like this!
Now let's see if I can enchant those lovely lips...
That jerk!
I can't believe he's so desperate to score!
Enough!
All right...
A nasty use for the Ripple, eh?
I'll wrap these around his face to show him his place for a while!
I-Impossible!
The Ripple! That was a Ripple!
Pardon me...
You have a call from someone named Speedwagon, Mr. Caesar Zeppeli.
Mama Mia... Well then, let's go.
W-What?!
You mean that womanizing creep is the Zeppeli we're here to see?!
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Timing:
Fadeout4
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 14: "The Ultimate Warriors of an Ancient Age"
The Speedwagon Foundation.
An organization founded by Speedwagon with
the wealth he earned in the oil industry.
Speedwagon Foundation Headquarters, Washington DC
Their aim is to better mankind by furthering medical science in
pharmaceuticals, photochemistry, and several other disciplines.
However, the Foundation's true purpose...
...is to uncover the mysteries of the stone mask!
The sample is being bathed in ultraviolet light,
so please wear this protective mask.
All right, release the snake!
The snake was absorbed!
Santana isn't dead! He only turned to stone to protect himself!
He'd be moving again if it weren't for the light!
Unbelievable! So how do we kill him?
He not only devours humans, but vampires of the stone mask as well!
And if he's immortal...
But Mr. Speedwagon, don't worry.
As long as we continue to keep his remains
under ultraviolet light, Santana will be unable to move.
Precisely!
What a relief...
I suppose we'll have as much time as we need to deal with him.
This photograph of Santana was taken in Mexico
while he was inside of the ruins where we found him.
Look closely.
Each of their horns has a different shape!
And if the one at the bottom is Santana...
...then who are the others?!
Stroheim claimed the Germans discovered more
Pillar Men that are entombed somewhere in Europe.
What?!
Given that these four faces are arranged vertically,
It's likely this is the hierarchy of the Pillar Men!
As Stroheim pleaded with us using his dying words,
Jojo and I must fly to Rome to meet with a man...
And that man is...
...the grandson of Will A. Zeppeli...
...Caesar Zeppeli!
Miss, where are you from?
I see you're admiring the fountain.
Would you like me to snap your picture?
The birds in this country really seem to like me.
It's a shame the men are such creeps!
Enough, you two!
Now that you've met, you could at least talk a little!
Mr. Speedwagon, let me be totally honest with you.
After the tragedy that befell my grandfather fifty years ago...
...my father inherited his burden, and so he spent
his entire life chasing the shadow of the stone mask!
The blood bonds among Italian families are tight-knit,
more than any other people in the world!
We take pride in our heritage, following their example!
As I continue to do!
And what about him?
You told me he didn't know a thing about
his own grandfather until three months ago!
He's an irresponsible fool, and undignified!
What's that, asshole?
You better watch your mouth!
Caesar, wait!
Jojo didn't know anything because I never told him!
And apart from that...
I heard that he supposedly beat Straits and the man from the Pillar...
...so I waited in the hotel restaurant to see what kind of man he was.
But after testing his Ripple, I was utterly disappointed.
This child's Ripple is far too weak!
His victory over the man in the Pillar was nothing but a fluke.
I have no desire to fight alongside this ape!
Caesar, that's because Jojo's Ripple has never been properly trained...
Uncle, it's too late for that now.
You asshole, I'm gonna beat you to a pulp!
Can't let you do that.
You couldn't even beat this girl with that pathetic Ripple of yours.
Well, you couldn't even beat this pigeon!
Are you trying to mess with me?!
I like to make fun of people,
but that doesn't give you the right to mock me!
Y-You... used the Ripple on this girl when you kissed her!
I'll say it again, you couldn't even beat this girl.
S-Should I stop them?
No, it might be harsh, but maybe it's better
for Jojo to lose here and learn his lesson.
See what I mean?
My grandfather died that day because
your grandfather couldn't hold his own in a fight!
And I'm expected to shame myself by
allying with a descendant of his bloodline?!
Caesar, you've done enough!
Y-You prick...
Insulting me is one thing, yet you had to
bring my dead grandfather into this?
You'll pay for that!
I have the an ability to defeat the Pillar Men...
with a devastating coup de grâce!
My secret Ripple Bubble Launcher!
I've hidden a special mix of soap water in my gloves and clothing to create Ripple Bubbles!
Let this wash you away to where you came from, Joestar!
I applaud you for not losing consciousness...
...but your Ripple won't be able to break my bubble shield.
And look at that, you're already out of breath.
You should just take a short breather in there.
Now you're gonna say "Signorina, let me undo my Ripple's magic."
Now, Signorina, let me undo my Ripple's magic...
I used the Ripple to stuff a pigeon in her mouth when she had her hands around my throat!
I just knew that you'd kiss her again to undo
your Ripple, you shameless casanova!
I'll say it again... You couldn't even beat a pigeon!
What a bother...
Come on, what's with this guy?
What kind of guy strikes a pose just to sit in a freaking chair?
He's seriously making me mad!
He's only getting away with this because I don't have
a special move like that Bubble Launcher yet!
I gotta think of something, quick!
But all that work sure seems like a pain in the ass...
I'll just have to show him who's boss with my favorite card trick!
Hey Jojo, what are you doing? Shuffle those cards properly.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I said shuffle them properly!
No cheating!
Oh no, he figured me out!
Though I suppose there's no way
you could ever beat me without cheating.
So what did you plan on looking at
with the mirror attached to your shoe?!
Watch your mouth, hick!
Bring it on, casanova!
Caesar!
What is it that you've been waiting for since eight o'clock?
What am I waiting for?
I was waiting for that car!
What? A German officer?!
Looks like he got the okay.
This man is part of a German security detail.
He's going to be our guide.
What?!
Remember, Italy and Germany are allies!
The Germans want to study the power of my Ripple for science!
The only reason an Englishman like you will even be able to see the Pillar Men...
...is because I asked the Germans to do me a favor, Jojo!
Mr. Speedwagon, we'd like to hear any information you have.
If we work together, we can find a way to deal with them before they awaken!
Hey, Mark...
How is your girlfriend doing back at home?
Oh, well, about that...
We're getting married when I go back to Germany next week!
Really?!
Mama Mia, that's wonderful news!
I actually helped set him up with his girlfriend in Germany, you know!
H-Hey, eyes on the road!
And get your filthy hands off the driver!
By the way, Jojo...
Do you happen to have a girl?
Of course you don't!
What kind of woman would tolerate your abrasive personality?
Nessie would be easier to find than the right woman for you!
Damn this guy, he's so full of himself...
I'm gonna come up with an amazing special move,
and then I'll rub it in his face!
Look, something's wrong!
W-What is that?!
Settle down!
We have them surrounded by ultraviolet light, they can't move!
Now go and see what the hell's going on!
Yes, sir!
We discovered some important info when
Stroheim's unit was wiped out in Mexico.
We have to keep this excavation moving, that way we can
get this tomb into a secure shelter within German borders.
What the hell happened, though?
It's too dark to see a thing.
Look closely.
I think I heard something...
A horn?!
O-Oh no, it's...
It's awakening!
Increase the intensity of the ultraviolet lights!
Sir!
He's blocking out the lights with blood and gore!
I can tell how the world has changed during
my slumber from the screams of these weaklings.
I-It spoke!
You cannot hold back the wrath of Wham with false sunlight!
Our hands!
They're stuck together!
Wham!
Awaken, my masters!
The entrance to the Pillar Men's chamber is
the world-renowned "Mouth of Truth?"
How startling! The air feels very ominous...
Caesar, have you tried using the Ripple on the sleeping Pillar Men?
The Ripple is only intended for use on living things.
Technically, they're not alive when they're stone.
It won't work on them unless they've awoken.
Hey, isn't the army supposed to be watching this place?
Where are they?
I don't see anybody! It's too quiet in here!
Maybe you're just too loud.
I-It's strange...
The guards that should be stationed here are gone.
What?
Hey, I just stepped in something! And it's super disgusting!
What the hell is it?!
Th-This is-!
Human skin!
Th-They're all dead!
There's no way!
Hey, German guy! Don't go that way!
There's something over there!
W-What the-?!
Unbelievable! Th-They've...
They've awakened!
Run, Mark!
Mark!
Caesar... Caesar!
They're not even acknowledging our presence!
They're paying as much attention to the German boy they just killed...
...as a man would pay to an ant that he just stepped on!
It appears that night has fallen for now, Wham...
Yes, Master Cars.
What shall we do?
Is it not obvious?
We shall head out in search of the Red Stone of Aja,
hidden somewhere in this world.
We're nearly there!
We simply need to place the Red Stone of Aja
into this Stone Mask, and its power will be ours!
But Master AC/DC, the world of mankind
has changed so much during our slumber.
The Roman Empire once held the Red Stone...
...but that empire and their civilization have likely fallen.
Then we must first locate the Red Stone.
The Red Stone which the Roman Empire greatly desired.
Mankind would not lose track of something like that.
I swear to locate it for you.
There's plenty of time.
For the time being, let's head overseas to see
just how much the human world has changed.
Wham!
Fool, what is the meaning of this?!
Wait, AC/DC!
Forgive me, Master Cars!
Wham, I know how much you hate it when
someone stands within your shadow...
...but I forgot how you attack on instinct
when someone invades that space.
It has been two millennia, after all...
I have attacked the ones that I am meant to serve!
Please punish me however you see fit!
No, I couldn't imagine it.
I'm counting on that warrior's instinct of yours
as we move towards our goal.
It was my fault for entering your shadow.
Forgive me, Wham.
Master Cars...
Let's go, Wham.
Right!
Caesar!
Kill me! Hurry up and kill me!
Mark!
T-The pain is excruciating...
I'm terrified...
I was numb at first, but now it's beginning to hurt a lot!
Now hurry up and do it, Caesar!
Mark!
T-There's nothing we can do!
There's nothing left we can do to save him!
We're helpless!
I've never felt so useless!
C-Caesar...
You...
Thank you, Caesar...
Mark!
Mark was just an ordinary young man.
He was no different from anyone else.
He loved his family, his girl, and his country...
He worked hard at his job, just like anyone else his age.
He had his whole life ahead of him!
Caesar!
Jojo... stay out of this!
I'm putting an end to this!
I couldn't live with myself otherwise!
Along the drifting cloud, the eagle searching down on the land
Catching the swirling wind, the sailor sees the rim of the land
The eagle's dancing wings create, as weather spins out of hand
Go closer hold the land, feel partly no more than grains of sand
We stand to lose all time, a thousand answers by in our hand
Next to your deeper fears, we stand surrounded by million years
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out and out
Next Episode
Even I'm getting tired of talking!
I told you to continue!
He's rotten!
A clan of Ripple users...
My secret, the Holy Sandstorm!
Episode 15:
"A Hero's Worth"