Some-Stuffs Presents
This elderly gentleman is someone we're quite familiar with.
Or rather, we're familiar with that scar and those eyes.
It's been too long, Mr. Speedwagon.
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
I've caught wind of your success in
the oil industry since you moved to America.
Timing:
Fadeout4
No, it isn't much to speak of.
I see the passage of time has been very kind to you.
Typesetting:
Fadeout4
I can hardly believe we're the same age.
I must say, I'm envious of the benefits
that come along with mastering the Ripple.
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Times have changed in the 49 years since Jonathan's death,
and since then, a new era has arrived.
Quality Check:
Mazrim
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Straits has succeeded Master Tompetty,
and he brought along his associates.
Speedwagon has become an oil baron.
And together they're off to Mexico, searching for something.
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
It is an object of great interest, discovered by
an archaeological team funded by Speedwagon's company.
Distro:
ExWizzard
An object, once hidden from society,
that has been revealed to these men alone!
What I am about to show you may come as a surprise.
No, I am almost certain that it will send shivers down your spine!
It will fill you with a sense of dread far more terrifying than
anything we felt during our battle with Dio fifty years ago!
Why would a chamber like this exist so deep within these ruins?
This is why I've called upon you, my friend!
Th-That's...
...the stone mask?!
There are more than one?!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
1938 New York
It all started in the autumn of 1938.
As usual, I was out on the prowl.
Get outta here!
Buddy, don't tell me you've never heard of this drink before!
Pal, I'm just guessing from your English accent...
...but are you a tourist?
What? Just got here?
Either way, you wanna drink, you gotta pay!
That's just how it works here!
Hey! British fella, that kid just ran off with your wallet!
What a slowpoke, that was a piece of cake!
Yo, Smokey. Looks like we finally caught ya...
...red-handed!
You damned thieving negro!
I could have you rotting in prison for up to twenty years for this!
Come on, man! It was just a wallet!
You little shit! Do you have any idea how much I hate you people?!
But you see, I'm a pretty reasonable guy...
...so just bring me twenty bucks a week...
...along with half of everything you steal!
Hello?
Are you the dolt that got his wallet swiped?
I'll need to hold on to it for evidence!
Well, actually, I was just gonna say...
...I gave that wallet to him, officer.
And just like that, this 6'3" Englishman was covering for me!
Anyway, that said...
...I'd appreciate it if you let him go and gave me back my wallet.
What's that?!
I really did give it to him.
We're the best of pals, you see.
Now let him go.
Oh! A pal of yours?!
How 'bout you give us his name then?
Don't mess with me!
Unless you also want to go to prison for obstructing justice!
Huh, dumbass?!
I've got a question for you.
I really don't get it, but what's the point in acting like this?
What exactly are you trying to accomplish?
There is no point!
I do what I want because I feel like it, you punk!
I already wiped snot on your right cheek, so now let's do the-
Watch your fucking attitude! You dirty cop!
Are you trying to resist arrest?!
Give me your best shot!
But I'm warning you...
...the moment that hammer cocks,
I'm going to snap your finger in half like a matchstick!
At this range?! I'll blow your goddamned head off!
At that moment, his entire body looked like it was glowing!
I don't know what kind of magic he used,
but that bottle cap flew off so hard it
smashed that cop's finger into a bloody pulp!
I can't believe I let my temper get the best of me again!
Oh crap... Granny Erina's gonna let me have it!
This guy is nuts!
He just clobbered a pair of cops,
but he's worried he'll get in trouble with this Granny Erina?
Hey, pickpocket! Let's scram!
When I asked him how he shot the bottle cap like that,
he said he didn't know.
All he said was he could do stuff like that since he was a kid.
Apparently so could his grandfather, but he died real young.
His dad was a pilot who died in the war, and he couldn't do it at all.
I don't think his mom is alive either.
I really owe ya one...
The name's Smokey.
What's yours?
Joestar.
Joseph Joestar.
BATTLE TENDENCY
Episode 10: "New York's Jojo"
But you can call me Jojo.
This is... Who is the man depicted on this pillar?!
This is no ordinary sculpture.
It contains amino acids and has a cellular structure!
There's also a very faint trace of a pulse and body heat!
In other words, this thing is alive!
Mr. Straits, I don't care what sort of creature this is,
nor how many thousands of years it's been here.
Nor do I care why it created the stone masks,
or as to why it was entombed here!
It doesn't matter to me!
I called you here for one simple reason;
please use the Ripple to destroy this thing while it remains asleep!
For this, and this alone!
Joseph Joestar...
...How is Joseph Joestar?
I have heard he used the Ripple to aid you in the past.
Why are you bringing up Jojo right now?
As I seem to recall,
this story took place when Jojo was thirteen years old.
Yes. I believe the story goes that
your plane was hijacked and you were held hostage.
Hey, kid!
You can't be hanging out down here. Now beat it!
You're hijacking old man Speedwagon's plane, right?
What's that got to do with me?
I'll just keep reading my comic,
and you people can finish whatever it is you're doing.
Watch your mouth, you little snot!
Jojo!
This isn't good!
Jojo's not the type to lose his cool over getting hit,
but staining the clothes he got from Erina is a whole different story!
Keep calm, Jojo!
You idiots wouldn't hijack a plane unless
you were prepared that it might crash, right?
That was... the Ripple!
This kid's insane! He's gonna make us crash!
Somebody take the stick!
How do I do that?!
Pops, grab a seat and get ready to jump!
That was a foolish stunt to pull without thinking ahead!
I thought about it for a second...
At the very least, I thought about protecting you and Granny Erina.
You guys are my only family after all...
He may look like Jonathan,
but he's not what you would call a gentleman.
That was when I first learned Jojo could use the Ripple.
Perhaps Jonathan passed down some of that power to him...
...causing him to be born with
some degree of proficiency as a result.
Perhaps... But why bring this up now?
W-What are you doing?!
It looks to me like I just killed these men...
...and once I kill you, Jonathan's grandson will be filled with despair... and rage!
He will seek me with a vengeance.
S-Straits-
Straits...
H-Have you gone mad?!
No, I am actually quite composed, Speedwagon.
I took to the way of the Ripple as a means to preserve my body.
Though ironically, the more one trains,
the more one understands the limitations of their aging body.
I was ashamed when I realized that I was only barely superior to normal humans.
Even the Ripple is incapable of ebbing the flow of time!
During our battle fifty years ago, I realized I admired Dio!
His power! His beauty! His eternal youth!
I yearned to possess the power of the stone mask for myself...
..so I'll destroy anything that gets in the way of that goal!
Y-You've lost your mind, Straits!
Now allow me to use your blood and obtain my immortality.
That will leave Erina Joestar and Joseph as
the only people to know of the mask's existence!
After I've killed them, I'll unlock mysteries
within the stone mask Dio never even dreamed of!
D-Don't do it...
The stone mask holds terrifying secrets we may never understand!
Miss... Eri... na...
Jojo...
Hey! Watch where you're walkin', ya dumb brute!
Go get a dog if you want someone to kiss your ass!
Hurry up and get out of my way you-
Hello there! Huh, now what was that?!
Could you repeat that back to me, nice and slow?
Maybe in a language I can actually understand?
Watch what you say, or I'll beat you!
Jojo...
...what are you doing?
G-Granny Erina!
What are you doing to that man?
Uh, well...
I was just...
Taxi!
I was just hailing the taxi, Granny Erina!
Oh, Jojo, how very thoughtful of you.
Mr. Smokey, I'd like you to join us.
The Joestar family was just an old woman and her grandson...
...but slowly, I began to learn about their great legacy.
Say Granny...
...Speedwagon asks us to come on over to New York...
...but now he's off on some trip?!
That's pretty rude, don'tcha think?
I'm sure the life of an oil baron is a busy one.
So, Granny...
Honestly now, you only knew Speedwagon as Grandpa's friend?
And that's all? Really?
What are you getting at?
I mean, the old man is a bachelor.
And you've been a widow for a pretty long time.
I say this because I'm curious if there was
something "more" between the two of you.
You foul-minded-!
I get it! I won't mention it-
Granny, forgive me!
I know! Speedwagon's an honorable guy!
The Joestars never seemed to live for very long...
Granny Erina's husband died in some kind of ship accident when she was younger.
She was pregnant at the time, and her son would
grow up to marry the little girl she rescued that fateful night.
They were Jojo's parents.
Her son died in the war, while his wife later succumbed to disease.
Granny Erina was one of the nicest people I had ever known.
She was kind not just to me, but to everyone.
I think it might be because she had such a sad life herself.
Jojo was the same.
I think his kindness was what ended up causing the most trouble.
And it was all my fault...
Waiter! Waiter!
Yes, sir?
I didn't know this joint served filthy pigs like him!
He's stinking up the place and ruining my meal!
People like him should be kept out!
Sir, it is the policy of this establishment
to allow anyone who can pay to dine here.
Are you shitting me?!
You telling me this place lets the pigs dine on pork?!
I think I should be going now...
Jojo...
Granny, you aren't going to stop me, are you?
Hardly.
He may be free to have whatever prejudices he wants...
...but I refuse to forgive such disrespect towards a friend.
Deal with him quickly so as not to disturb the other customers.
Sounds good to me!
You wanna go, pal?
Hey, big guy!
If you're looking for those brass knuckles,
they aren't in your coat pocket!
They're in your back pants pocket!
How did he...
Now you're gonna say "How did you know about my brass knuckles, you punk?"
How did you know about my brass knuckles, you punk?!
I could tell from the indentations on your knuckles
that you used them pretty recently.
There's also blood on your shirt.
A splatter of blood!
You were just recently beating someone up, weren't you?
So the blood on your shirt can only mean one thing;
you took your coat off before beating them!
In short, doesn't it only make sense for you
to have put it in your back pocket and not your jacket?
Now you're gonna say "What does it matter, you little shit?"
What does it matter, you little shit?!
How does that feel?!
That's what you get for being such a smartass!
What are you going on about?
And what the hell were you hitting?
Because whatever you were just fist fighting with, it wasn't me.
Can't you see how easy it is for me to read idiots like you?
Got that? You damned idiot!
Please excuse the behavior of my associate.
Madam, you're Erina Joestar, correct?
Mr. Speedwagon has helped me out of a fix or two.
He told me all about you, back when we were in London.
I'm glad I've found you.
I have some underground information that
hasn't been revealed to the public just yet.
Mr. Speedwagon has been murdered.
What was that?
According to current rumors, the culprit was a monk from Tibet.
A monk? Was it Straits?!
Apparently the bodies of Speedwagon and
a few others were found on a river bank in Mexico.
Nobody knows for certain who did it, and we are
also unsure as to the current whereabouts of this monk.
I think I understand...
This... must be about the story Mr. Speedwagon told me,
about Dio and the stone mask.
Jojo, that guy's from the Mafia!
You can't trust him. He's probably up to no good!
Whatever suits you.
Fella, your lighter's in your breast pocket.
Smokey, I appreciate the warning,
but I'm almost positive this guy is telling the truth!
The only thing that motivates these guys is money!
This info coming from a group like the Mafia
without any way of exploiting it tells me it's true!
However!
True or not, I can't allow you to bring
such terrible news to Granny Erina out of nowhere like that!
And now she's both startled and sad, you dumbass!
The madness from fifty years ago... It still hasn't ended...
Are you afraid, Granny?
I'll be here to protect you.
That's not it, Joseph!
It's about you!
It's about the destiny you
may end up being caught in that frightens me!
Don't worry about me.
If this is my destiny... then so be it!
I wasn't sure what had happened,
but I knew these two definitely had a troubled past.
Hey, Smokey!
It's freezing today...
This magazine! Take a look!
What is it?
These things, do you think they make
girls' you-know-whats look bigger?!
Let's see... "Will make you go from AA cup to C."
Heh, now they're playing dirty! Better watch out!
Huh?
It says it's $1.25 for a pair...
E-Excuse me...
Ya know, I get the feeling I've seen you somewhere before... Possibly...
Perhaps we've already met?
Hey, how come I can't see
your breath in this freezing cold weather?
And is it just me, or did I catch a glimpse of
something nasty in your mouth? Fangs perhaps?
Don't play dumb with me, asshole.
I don't care where we do this, Jojo.
I'm going to end your life before you get
the chance to awaken your true potential!
Oh? Is that so?
I knew he was a little unhinged, but this is insane!
I don't know where he got it, but he's
going nuts with a Tommy Gun in the middle of the city!
Straits, I've been waiting for you to show up!
I doubt that was enough to kill you...
...but for old man Speedwagon...
...consider this my declaration of war!
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
Next Episode
This is a vampire?!
I'm gonna tear you to pieces, Straits!
German medical science is number one in the world!
Don't you understand anything?!
Repent for your sins in hell!
Episode 11:
"Game Master"