You bastards!
Don't turn your backs to me!
Take this! Deadly Ripple Bubble Launcher!
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
Timing:
Fadeout4
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 15: "A Hero's Worth"
I-It couldn't be!
Great! Caesar might be a pain, but at least his Ripple works!
You're surrounded by my bubbles. Now prepare to be bombarded!
H-He just popped... your Bubble Launcher!
It wasn't the wires on his head that popped the bubbles...
It was the gust of wind they created!
That means those wires are anti-Ripple weapons!
WHAM
These monsters already understand how the Ripple works...
...just from when they encountered it two thousand years ago!
AC/DC
CARS
W-What's going on with the air surrounding them?
No, Caesar! Get down!
What the-?
Close your eyes! That wasn't just wind, it was the aftermath of a vortex!
Caesar!
The Ripple Tribe...
I thought we eliminated them all two thousand years ago...
But here they are in Rome, waiting for us to awaken.
Damn... you...
You killed my friend...
You think losing an eye will stop me?!
W-What the hell's so funny?!
The Ripple Tribe always says the same thing.
It was much like when we crossed over from
the western continent those two thousand years ago.
"You think losing an arm or an eye will stop me?!"
"How dare you take my friend's life!"
This is why we laugh.
Y-You monsters!
Let's go. We must locate the Red Stone of Aja.
G-Get back here!
You're running away?!
Your throat and lungs are your weak points!
We know that if you are unable breathe, you cannot use the Ripple.
Now I'll tell you what I always say.
Brat, come and face the mighty Wham
again once you've grown stronger!
When we meet again, I want to admire your strength...
...before I utterly destroy you.
It appears there are no other Ripple users.
Let's move.
Look over here!
Don't go and ignore me now!
He only scratched your eyelid. It looks like your eyeball is fine.
Take your cute little Bubble Launcher and hold tight!
I can take care of this.
Jojo!
It's time to show off the brand new technique I've been working on!
What?!
Let me introduce myself.
The name's Joseph Joestar, and I'm the guy
who mopped the floor with your buddy.
I call this the Ripple Clacker Volley!
I start off by filling these American clackers with the Ripple...
Oh no!
Jojo, what are you doing?! Now isn't the time to mess around!
Why you... My friend was just killed! Yet you act so flippant!
Me? I'm dead serious.
Caesar, you're still mourning the loss of your friend.
I can feel your pain and anger.
But more than that, I can't stand egotistical jerks like these guys!
I'm not an expert yet, but let's see what you think of my Clacker Volley!
I hate to admit it, but my the Ripple is still weak.
But on the other hand, I can use my Clacker Volley
to cut into your skin and hit you with the Ripple.
That should even out my handicap.
Pretty good, right?
Take this!
Let's go.
How absurd.
Perhaps humans have regressed over the years.
Regressed?
Perhaps so.
Jojo, quit playing around!
All you did was throw metal spheres at them!
Jojo... Jojo really isn't taking this seriously!
He's acting like this is just some normal thug!
But... these beings surpass him in every way!
Seeing him so outmatched is devastating!
Crap! Nobody here is taking me seriously!
Hold it, big guy! You're gonna get hit!
Don't.
Human lives are short enough. Do not rush to die.
Shut it! Spaghetti nero looks bad too, but it's a real treat!
You need to have a taste of my Clacker Volley before you judge it!
The clackers vanished!
I've been working on the railroad, all the live-long day!
L-Look!
How's that? Are you still fooled?
If you don't get it...
...let me show you!
Take this, fella!
Those moves are impossible!
He's moving even faster than Santana!
The clackers didn't even touch him!
I admire your weapon, your courage, and you tactics.
Things are becoming interesting.
Thus...
I'll give you one minute.
I bestow upon you a single minute to fight the mighty Wham.
Jojo!
As you can see, I've slit your wrist right down to the artery.
In other words, you have one minute to tend to that wound
before you lose consciousness from blood loss.
Give me everything you've got!
This is what I have always said to members of the Ripple Tribe:
"Here is an hourglass measured in blood."
Wham, we'll be waiting outside.
Boy, go pick up your weapon!
Huh? What? What'd you just say?
"Go pick up your weapon?" Is that what you said?
That won't be necessary!
I have no need to go pick it up.
That was my Clacker Boomerang!
One minute is all I need to beat you!
Make fun of me, will you? I'll smash you to pieces!
Then I'll finish you with the Ripple!
Very well.
Hit me all you like.
You are the first person to scar my face.
And for that reason, I will bestow this honor upon you before you die...
You're telling me no one has ever hit your face before?
Big words!
You didn't even bat an eye when you killed Mark!
I'll make you regret holding your nose so high!
Look out! He's up to something!
I don't think you're hurting him anymore!
Th-This is gonna be bad!
You have good instincts to jump back.
I let you hit me to punish myself for getting caught off guard.
But that has ended.
Jojo, hurry and finish him!
Here is my technique.
Holy Sandstorm!
I-I'm in trouble!
He spins his left arm clockwise!
And his right arm counter-clockwise!
Jojo is caught unaware, and Wham's fists seem to grow before his eyes!
The space between his fists becomes a destructive vacuum!
The whirling creates a torrent of wind and sand!
He ripped through that marble pillar like a piece of old cloth!
I've never seen such power!
Jojo...
That was my Holy Sandstorm.
Jo... Jojo!
N-No, stay back!
Mr. Speedwagon, you have to get out of here!
I'll do something to hold him back!
The blood in my eye threw off my aim...
...but it was enough, even when you hid behind the pillar.
Dead already?
Ordinarily, I would ignore humans like yourselves.
But you witnessed my shame, so I must be rid of you as well.
Prepare yourselves!
I'm imagining things.
H-He couldn't be!
U-Unbelievable. He's trying to escape!
Playing dead like that... He has no shame!
I can understand leaving me, but Mr. Speedwagon? How spineless!
That guy is the biggest menace I've seen!
My breathing is out of control. I can't use the Ripple!
I only have my specialty left...
All I can do is run!
Look at our dismal hero!
Jojo is on the ground, forced to play dead.
He's about to leave Speedwagon to his fate!
Even so, Jojo will still remain the worthy hero of this tale!
Here's why!
Still alive, are you?!
You coward!
You thought you could trick me and escape?!
I only needed to fool you for a few dozen yards.
All I needed was to get to this mine cart.
So you only acted like a coward to
lure me over and let your friends escape, eh?
And you fell for another one of my tricks.
Old man, get out of here, now!
Caesar, you too!
Jojo...
That bastard... has some nerve!
I've sure painted myself into a corner...
I need to come up with something.
What a pain...
An unbending hero!
Only if Jojo lost his will to fight would he lose his status as a hero.
Jojo!
Dammit! He's far more injured than I am!
He may put on a foolish act, but he takes his fate seriously.
He knows he has to beat those monsters!
You speak quite brashly for one in such a terrible state.
You're a tough man.
Weak-spirited, but tough indeed.
How are you so tough?
Is your brain defective, or do you have another trick for me?
You want to know?
Don't tell me...
Is it something stupid like going into
the mine and using explosives on me?
Crap! He knows!
Or do you plan to pull the brake and send the mine cart flying?
Something like this?
H-He did it again!
The time on your wristwatch is almost up.
There is zero percent chance you'll survive this.
You are out of tricks.
But tell me this...
Why don't I see defeat in your eyes?
You want to know?
You really want to know?
No, it doesn't matter. I'll just kill you now.
If you give me a month, I'll become strong enough to beat you.
What was that?
Give me a month and I'll surpass you.
I'm the first person to scar your face.
If I put my mind to it, my potential is limitless.
No, never mind what I said.
Well, finish me off quickly.
It's an honor to be killed by a warrior like you.
Continue.
Oh, I'm tired of talking!
Make it painless, Wham.
I told you to continue!
Jojo is still okay!
You have a long life ahead of you.
You'll have to carry the shame of being scarred by a human.
The only way to fix that is by beating me
in a fair fight after I've trained.
What? Don't feed me your lies, Jojo!
I only need a bit more to get to him!
He called me a coward when I ran...
Using a word like that means he's the "proud warrior" type.
I can use that against him!
I'm a bit new to fighting.
But if I train with the Ripple for a month,
I know I have the talent to beat you!
I was the first human to hit your head,
and I was able to carve a chunk out of it!
But you still have a chance to kill me
before I grow into a real threat to you!
Why you-!
Wham.
Master AC/DC.
His minute is up. Why do you allow him to live?
Crap, it's his friend!
Master AC/DC, I've grown fond of this wielder of the Ripple.
I-I got him!
Jojo, is it?
I agree to your proposition!
You say you will be stronger in a month,
so I will give you a month to live.
You aren't gonna kill me?
Indeed.
We'll fight again?
Indeed!
This is a bad idea. You'll regret it.
Yes! I'm safe for now!
However...
I need to ensure that you will not simply run away.
Wham, will you be using that old thing again?
The Wedding Ring of Death.
I will put this ring around your aorta.
W-What are you doing?!
The ring will start to dissolve in thirty-three days.
Inside is a virulent poison.
The ring cannot be removed. Any attempt
will break it, releasing the poison!
You have only one way to avoid the poison...
Fight and defeat me within thirty-three days
and take the antidote from my lip piercing!
Jojo!
"Till death do us part," a true wedding ring.
Midnight in thirty-three days at the Colosseum
is where I will wait for you, Jojo.
You guessed wrong if you thought you could escape.
I don't imagine we'll fight, but here's a little present from AC/DC!
I'll put it around your windpipe!
My heart and throat!
Mine is a different poison from Wham's.
The antidote is in my nose piercing.
Cars, you want in?
Nonsense.
We are immortal.
A worthy opponent is a rare thing that gives our lives meaning.
I can understand why you're doing it...
...but our main goal is to obtain the power of the Red Stone of Aja.
Do not forget that, you two.
Let's go!
Jojo, grow strong and overcome my Holy Sandstorm!
W-What the hell?
A wedding ring? That's some black humor if I've ever heard it!
And now I've got two of them!
Do I look like a damn polygamist or something?!
Well, at least Speedwagon and Caesar are safe.
There's no sense in getting down about it.
Jojo.
You damned fool...
Despite the blood you lost, you pulled a first-rate bluff
that would impress even the best gambler!
How amazing!
Let's study the Ripple together.
We'll grow stronger...
You and me both.
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
They stand there
Twenty four before my love and I'll be there
Next Episode
I only said one month as a bluff!
Step through those doors and you'll see!
Master, you can't!
I won't hold back because you're a girl!
Welcome to Venice!
Episode 16:
"Lisa Lisa, Master of the Ripple"